<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 22:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bybit Announces World Series of Trading with $8 Million in Prize Pool</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-announces-world-series-of-trading-with-8-million-in-prize-pool/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bybit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260323</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bybit_dubai_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bybit_dubai_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The event is expected to be a showdown for elite crypto traders.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bybit unveiled the &#8216;2023 World Series of Trading (WSOT),&#8217; the registration of which will commence on July 13.</p>
<p>The event is in its fourth edition and will feature a prize pool of up to $8 million worth of USDT. It also includes a live stream giveaway on August 24, offering traders the chance to win Rolex Explorers and Huracan Evo Spyder Lamborghinis.</p>
<h2>Bybit&#8217;s All-Star Showdown for Elite Crypto Traders</h2>
<p>According to the official press release, the window for general registration is from July 24 to August 17, which will offer traders a chance to secure their spot among &#8220;elite&#8221; contenders across the world. Bybit further added the real action begins on August 7 when traders clash in a furnace of strategies and lightning-fast decisions.</p>
<p>Commenting on the development, Bybit&#8217;s CEO and co-founder Ben Zhou stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Brace yourselves for the ultimate showcase of trading talent, strategy, and sheer determination. This is the moment where dreams are forged, boundaries are shattered, and champions are crowned. So, we call on all traders to enter or witness the World Series of Trading, where the best of the best meet and the crypto world comes alive.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Bybit will make demo trading available to participants for the first time ever to ensure that the competitions become more accessible to beginners.</p>
<p>Influential traders and megastars such as The Moon, CryptoBanter, GINAREA, and Cornix are set to participate in this year&#8217;s WSOT.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bybit claimed that that event attracted <span style="font-weight: 400;">approximately 117,000 traders from all over the world between 2020 and 2022, which generated a trading volume of over $177 billion.</span></p>
<h2>Bybit Expansion</h2>
<p>Over the past year, Bybit has been working on an aggressive expansion of its global footprint across different parts of the world.</p>
<p>More recently, Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-scores-preparatory-license-by-dubais-virtual-assets-regulatory-authority/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">granted</a> the Minimum Viable Product (MVP) Preparatory License to the crypto exchange&#8217;s subsidiary, Bybit FinTech FZE.</p>
<p>Bybit had previously stated that it is closely monitoring the United Kingdom, Hong Kong and the European Union jurisdictions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-announces-world-series-of-trading-with-8-million-in-prize-pool/" rel="nofollow">Bybit Announces World Series of Trading with $8 Million in Prize Pool</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC&#8217;s Gensler Skeptic of Crypto Wash Trading Amid a Plethora of Bitcoin ETF Filings</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/secs-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-wash-trading-amid-a-plethora-of-bitcoin-etf-filings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260520</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/GaryGensler2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase may have some issues to resolve if its going to be accepted by the SEC as an adequate surveillance partner for BlackRock.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recent comments regarding Bitcoin exchanges from Gary Gensler – Chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – suggest that his agency may not be so eager to approve the recent wave of Bitcoin spot ETF applications in its mailbox.</p>
<p>The chairman claimed that crypto trading platforms like Coinbase are structured in such a way that makes them open to wash trading and market manipulation.</p>
<h2>Problems With Coinbase, According to the SEC</h2>
<p>Gensler commented on the exchange during a media availability on Wednesday, shortly after an SEC meeting related to broker-dealers and money market funds, according to The Block.</p>
<p>In its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuit</a> against Coinbase last month, the SEC alleged that Coinbase was illegally operating as an unregistered broker, national securities exchange, or clearing agency – services the agency argues should be kept separate.</p>
<p>Gensler echoed this general concern to reporters, saying that crypto exchanges often operate “a bunch of conflicted services.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“What that means is they could be trading directly against you and market making against you which you would not see, or hope to see on the New York Stock Exchange or NASDAQ,” Gensler explained after the meeting.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Coinbase and a Bitcoin Spot ETF</h2>
<p>In June, asset management giant BlackRock filed with the SEC to launch a NASDAQ-traded Bitcoin spot ETF – a product that has thus far been rejected at every turn.</p>
<p>For the regulator, applicants need to find an exchange with which to form a surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) to adequately oversee the Bitcoin spot market, and scan it for market manipulation.</p>
<p>Unlike applicants before it, BlackRock proposed partnering directly with a U.S.-based spot Bitcoin exchange. When asked to identify this exchange by the SEC, it quickly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-stock-surges-12-as-blackrock-names-it-as-surveillance-partner/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that it was Coinbase.</p>
<p>Though bullish for Coinbase at the time, concerns about the company&#8217;s mixed functions and lack of registration may leave the SEC dissatisfied with applicants using the platform to surveil the market.</p>
<p>According to Bloomberg’s Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas, the firm’s comments pour “cold water” on hopes of such a product getting approved. “This makes [it] seem like [an] SSA could be pointless if this is [a] problem for him,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1679240559985143810" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote</a> to Twitter.</p>
<p>The analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1679241973306146816" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">added</a>, however, that BlackRock may already be working with Coinbase to sort out these issues. “Nasdaq and BlackRock both knew [Gensler] had these kinds of problems [with exchanges],” he said.</p>
<p>Copying BlackRock, other applicants including ARK, Fidelity, and other Cboe-listed funds have also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coin-shares-climb-10-after-cboe-included-coinbase-in-amended-btc-etf-applications/" data-wpel-link="internal">named</a> Coinbase as a surveillance-sharing partner. BlackRock has a notorious 575:1 success rate of getting its products approved by the SEC.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/secs-gensler-skeptic-of-crypto-wash-trading-amid-a-plethora-of-bitcoin-etf-filings/" rel="nofollow">SEC&#8217;s Gensler Skeptic of Crypto Wash Trading Amid a Plethora of Bitcoin ETF Filings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Giant Dapper Labs Announces Laying off 51 Staff Members</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nft-giant-dapper-labs-announces-laying-off-51-staff-members/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 22:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260287</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dapper.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Dapper.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dapper Labs' third round of layoffs comes amidst the NFT market downturn.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The digital asset market continues to experience one of its longest, most bitter winters in recent history, leading established companies in the space to introduce a fresh round of crypto job cuts. Prominent NFT firm and creator of the NBA Top Shot marketplace announced laying off 51 of its staff members.</p>
<p>The latest round includes job cuts for full-time employees as well as C1 contractors.</p>
<h2>Dapper Labs&#8217; Another Round of Layoff</h2>
<p>Dapper Labs CEO Roham Gharegozlou <a href="https://twitter.com/roham/status/1679301700669296640" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> on July 13 that the move was necessary to ensure a &#8220;lean and efficient&#8221; company amidst the bear market.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We said goodbye to 51 brilliant colleagues and friends today Dapper Labs &#8211; this is the note I sent our team. We remain fully dedicated to our core communities and committed to building amazing products that push the world forward together.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This is the third round of layoffs following the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dapper-labs-axes-another-20-of-its-staff-as-crypto-layoffs-continue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">downsizing</a> of employees by 20% in February this year, during which Gharegozlou stated that the move was part of Dapper Labs&#8217; restructuring plans.</p>
<p>The NFT giant&#8217;s headcount had shot up from 100 to 600 employees within a span of less than two years. This rapid growth proved detrimental to Dapper&#8217;s business and communities, which led to the first round of layoffs in November last year. The company had then <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-giant-dapper-labs-lays-off-22-of-staff-citing-macroeconomic-environment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">axed</a> 22% of its staff.</p>
<p>In a statement, Gharegozlou insisted that both Dapper Labs and Flow blockchain remains well-capitalized despite the layoff. The latter is funded with a separate pool of capital so that the team has several years of cash runaway without the need to sell tokens to fulfill short-term goals, the exec iterated.</p>
<h2>NFT Market Feels the Chill</h2>
<p>The NFT landscape has changed drastically since the bear market took hold. The past few weeks alone witnessed the floor prices of some of the largest and most prominent NFT collections sink to levels not seen in months. Popular blue chip projects such as CryptoPunks, the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bayc-has-tanked-90-as-nft-collection-floor-prices-plummet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bored Ape Yacht Club</a>, Mutant Apes, and Azukis have not been spared either.</p>
<p>A recent <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/state-of-the-dapp-industry-in-q2-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by DappRadar also noted the troubling state of the NFT sector with trading volume tanking 38% to land at $2.9 billion in Q2. However, it stated that trading volume does not necessarily equate to the level of market excitement. The report read,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The NFT sector displays resilience amidst trading volume drops, with a less severe decrease in sales pointing to sustained interest.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-giant-dapper-labs-announces-laying-off-51-staff-members/" rel="nofollow">NFT Giant Dapper Labs Announces Laying off 51 Staff Members</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Announces the Relisting of Ripple (XRP) Following Court Ruling</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-announces-the-relisting-of-ripple-xrp-following-court-ruling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260509</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/coinbase_ripple.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/coinbase_ripple.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase has brought XRP back to its exchange for the first time in almost three years.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The entire crypto market is rallying after the judge overseeing Ripple V. SEC ruled that neither XRP, nor most situations in which it transacted, are securities.</p>
<p>The ruling has also prompted exchanges like Coinbase to relist XRP starting today.</p>
<ul>
<li>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1679581121976188928" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> on Thursday, Coinbase Assets confirmed that it will re-enable trading of XRP on XRP network, starting at 1:45 PT.</li>
<li>“Once sufficient supply of this asset is established trading on our XRP-USD, XRP-USDT, and XRP-EUR trading pairs will launch in phases,” the firm stated.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Trading is anticipated to begin later today, if liquidity conditions are met. Once sufficient supply of this asset is established trading on our XRP-USD, XRP-USDT and XRP-EUR trading pairs will launch in phases. Support for XRP may be restricted in some supported jurisdictions.</p>
<p>&mdash; Coinbase Assets <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f6e1.png" alt="🛡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@CoinbaseAssets) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1679575241415172096?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>The decision to relist is based on Judge Torres’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruling</a> that “programmatic” sales of XRP, including sales on secondary markets like digital asset exchanges, are not securities transactions.</li>
<li>Winklevoss-owned crypto exchange Gemini is also <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1679550388272283649" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">considering</a> a relisting of XRP. Tyler Winklevoss <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinbaseAssets/status/1679581121976188928" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> the ruling “highlights how the SEC is a failed institution.”</li>
<li>The SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged</a> this was the case when it first charged Ripple with securities law violations in December 2020. Coinbase and other exchanges soon delisted XRP in response.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, Coinbase stock (COIN) is up 24% on the day to $107,00, continuing a bullish trend after taking a firm defensive stance against its own SEC lawsuit last month.</li>
<li>The lawsuit alleged that over a dozen coins trading on Coinbase’s platforms were securities and that its staking service was also a securities offering.</li>
<li>Many of those coins are now rallying, including Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC), all of which are up over 20% on the day.</li>
<li>Even Bitcoin – which the SEC had already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal">labeled</a> a non-security – tapped a yearly high on Thursday, rising 4% to $31,700.</li>
<li>XRP has already risen 75% on the day, surpassing BNB as the fourth-largest crypto by market cap.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-announces-the-relisting-of-ripple-xrp-following-court-ruling/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Announces the Relisting of Ripple (XRP) Following Court Ruling</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Dismisses Employees to Strengthen its Balance Sheet (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circle-dismisses-employees-to-strengthen-its-balance-sheet-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260289</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the layoffs, Circle remains committed to expand its team that work in "key areas of focus."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Circle &#8211; the company behind the leading stablecoin USDC &#8211; has reportedly trimmed its staff in a bid to reinforce its balance sheet.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thus, it joined the likes of numerous crypto-related firms that laid off team members during the prolonged bear market to cope with the decreasing investor interest. Some examples are the exchanges Coinbase, Huobi, Gemini, Bybit, Crypto.com, and many more.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/crypto-firm-circle-cut-workforce-focus-core-activities-2023-07-12/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Reuters, the stablecoin issuer has reduced its team and ceased investments in non-core activities.</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Circle is redoubling its focus on core business activities and execution,&#8221; the organization said in an email to the media outlet. </span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, it assured that it will continue hiring new employees in &#8220;key areas of focus.&#8221;</span></li>
<li>The rumors have not affected the price of USDC, as it trades at its fixed level of $1. Its market capitalization has also been relatively unaffected, standing at approximately $27 billion.</li>
<li>However, this was not the case in mid-March when Circle <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-tumbles-to-0-93-as-circle-reveals-3-3-billion-held-at-svb-tether-and-binance-not-exposed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a massive $3.3 billion exposure to the collapsed Silicon Valley Bank (SVB).</span></li>
<li>While USDC slipped to $0.87 (per CoinGecko data) shortly after the disclosure, it quickly restored its correlation to the greenback after the company issued a reassuring statement, vowing to cover any investor losses due to the banking crisis.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-dismisses-employees-to-strengthen-its-balance-sheet-report/" rel="nofollow">Circle Dismisses Employees to Strengthen its Balance Sheet (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Releases Encrypted Decentralized Messaging Functionality in Wallets</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-releases-encrypted-decentralized-messaging-functionality-in-wallets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 19:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260199</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/coinbase_wallet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/coinbase_wallet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new messaging feature will securely store messages across the XMTP network.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has unveiled an end-to-end encrypted, private, and portable messaging feature for its self-custody wallet product &#8211; Coinbase Wallet to enable users to connect directly through their wallet, engage with communities, as well as send payments across thousands of coins.</p>
<p>The goal is to give Coinbase Wallet users full control and ownership over their identity and chats by eliminating unnecessary risk and potential losses with the help of messaging.</p>
<h2>Coinbase&#8217;s New Functionality</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/say-gm-with-messaging-on-coinbase-wallet" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, Coinbase Wallet has integrated with XMTP, which is an open protocol and network for web3 messaging. The new functionality aims to tackle common issues faced by Coinbase Wallet such as accidentally sending crypto to the wrong address, someone claiming ownership of an .eth username they do not possess, or fake online profiles on social media platforms.</p>
<p>In short, the wallet holders will be able to send messages to and from Ethereum accounts including ones with CB.IDs, ENS domains, Lens profiles, or Unstoppable Domains profiles. This flexibility in the service is expected to help users &#8220;make real connections, make offers on NFTs, and pay others directly,&#8221; the crypto giant said in a statement.</p>
<p>Furthermore, chats can be ported to any other XMTP-compatible app at any time. Users will also be allowed to send payments to others using the USDC stablecoin without incurring any gas fees.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Today, we’re announcing a new way to engage with the crypto community with built-in messaging on Coinbase Wallet powered by the XMTP protocol. Messaging on Coinbase Wallet is end-to-end encrypted, private, and portable.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Simplifying Transaction Process For Web3</h2>
<p>The latest development is an important milestone for the Web3 wallet space as it expands the traditional offerings of crypto wallets from solely buying, holding, trading, and transferring of digital assets. Incorporating an encrypted interaction functionality essentially eliminates a major drawback of using a different messaging platform to interact with someone, confirm their credentials, then go back to the wallet to send or receive tokens.</p>
<p>Currently, Coinbase is embroiled with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for allegedly operating as an unregistered securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency. More recently, the financial regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-was-aware-it-violated-us-securities-laws-claims-sec/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">claimed</a> that the crypto exchange was aware of violating securities law in the country.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-releases-encrypted-decentralized-messaging-functionality-in-wallets/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Releases Encrypted Decentralized Messaging Functionality in Wallets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple&#8217;s Secondary Sales of XRP Not an Investment Contract: Judge Rules Following Over 3-Year Long Legal Battle</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 19:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260491</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/secvripple_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Judge Torres still rules that “Institutional Sales” of XRP were still securities transactions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>XRP is booming after Judge Analisa Torres’s ruling on Thursday that most sales of the Ripple-issued cryptocurrency do not constitute securities transactions.</p>
<p>The ruling brings a conclusion to a three-year-long lawsuit that is expected to set a firm precedent for many crypto issuers’ legal standing in the United States going forward. Let’s dig into the details of the ruling, and examine how it could impact other cryptocurrencies in the near term.</p>
<h2>Institutional Sales VS Other Sales of XRP</h2>
<p>In its lawsuit filed in December 2020, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) alleged that virtually all sales of XRP are securities transactions, whether sold directly by Ripple, or on secondary markets.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.874.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">summary judgment</a> on Thursday, however, asserted that the SEC was only correct in terms of “institutional sales” of the asset. These included XRP sales to “sophisticated individuals and entities” through which Ripple raised $728 million.</p>
<p>According to Torres, institutional sales satisfied every prong of the Howey Test, meaning there was 1) an investment of money; 2) in a common enterprise; 3) with an expectation of profits; 4) based on the efforts of others.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The nature of the Institutional Sales also supports the conclusion that Ripple sold XRP as an investment rather than for consumptive use,” the judge wrote.</p></blockquote>
<p>Beyond institutional sales, programmatic sales – including secondary market sales on exchanges that raised $757 million for Ripple – were not deemed securities transactions because they didn’t satisfy prong three of Howey. XRP buyers on those exchanges couldn’t have known whether their money was going to Ripple or another owner of XRP.</p>
<p>Furthermore, payouts to employees using XRP were not investment contracts because they did not involve an investment of money to begin with.</p>
<p>Finally, Ripple co-founder Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larsen’s sales of XRP were not securities transactions, since they were made as programmatic sales.</p>
<h2>What About Other Cryptos?</h2>
<p>XRP itself– irrespective of the circumstances surrounding its sale – was also ruled a non-security. “XRP, as a digital token, is not in and of itself a “contract, transaction[,] or scheme” that embodies the Howey requirements of an investment contract,” read the filing.</p>
<p>This stipulation could have major implications for other top crypto assets like Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC), all of which were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-was-aware-it-violated-us-securities-laws-claims-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleged</a> to be securities by the SEC in a lawsuit against Coinbase last month.</p>
<p>Coinbase delisted XRP in December 2020 following the SEC’s lawsuit, alongside many other exchanges. After the latest ruling, however, crypto exchanges like Gemini are already showing interest in relisting the asset.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Given today&#39;s ruling that the sale of XRP on exchanges is not a security, <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Gemini</a> is exploring the listing of XRP for both spot and derivatives trading.</p>
<p>&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) <a href="https://twitter.com/Gemini/status/1679550388272283649?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>XRP is now <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">trading</a> 64% up on the day, and its market cap has surpassed Binance’s native token, BNB.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" rel="nofollow">Ripple&#8217;s Secondary Sales of XRP Not an Investment Contract: Judge Rules Following Over 3-Year Long Legal Battle</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Powering the Next Generation of Gaming: XBorg Sells Out $2 Million Seed Round Community Allocation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/powering-the-next-generation-of-gaming-xborg-sells-out-2-million-seed-round-community-allocation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 15:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260433</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/PR_Graphic_1689146399JrqtpbXCCD.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/PR_Graphic_1689146399JrqtpbXCCD.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 13th, 2023] XBorg, the Web3 company developing a collaborative credential infrastructure that allows players to create their digital identity and enjoy tailored user experiences within enhanced gaming applications, sold out their $2 million seed round community allocation in record time. The funds will facilitate the scaling and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 13th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://www.xborg.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">XBorg</a>, the Web3 company developing a collaborative credential infrastructure that allows players to create their digital identity and enjoy tailored user experiences within enhanced gaming applications, sold out their $2 million seed round community allocation in record time. The funds will facilitate the scaling and adoption efforts of XBorg&#8217;s infrastructure and applications to reach millions of players and fans worldwide.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Ahead of the raise, XBorg collected interest from more than 8,300 investors totalling $7M in soft commitments but decided to cap the community allocation at $2 million and maintain the remaining $3 million for leading VCs, closing out the $5 million seed round. The $XBG token, expected to be launched towards the end of 2023, is now sitting at a $50m valuation.</p>
<blockquote><p>XBorg Founder and CEO, Louis Regis reacted: “Since day one, we have included our community in the development of XBorg as we believe that the future of gaming will be built by its players. Allocating a large part of our seed round to our community showcases our support for this notion. The widespread enthusiasm of our community in the current market conditions has exceeded all of our expectations and demonstrates their trust in our vision to disrupt the gaming and fan engagement industry.”</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">In the coming months, XBorg is launching its first application in partnership with some of the most prominent esports teams in the industry. The current Rocket League world champions, Team BDS, were the first team to be announced, with many more in the pipeline. The XBorg app will enable players and fans to build their digital identity, meaningfully connect with their favourite gaming communities, and collect digital items with unique perks that unlock exclusive experiences. By the end of the year, XBorg aims to become the fastest-growing gaming credential infrastructure via its partnerships with tier-1 esports teams and popular gaming influencers.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Users can already create an XBorg account and get a taste of what their complete app will be like <a href="http://www.xborg.gg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">here</a>. Users are rewarding early supporters of their ecosystem, so they should be sure to be active participants and refer their friends if they want to take advantage of this.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>About XBorg</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">XBorg is developing a collaborative credential infrastructure that allows players to create their digital identity and enjoy tailored user experiences within enhanced gaming applications. XBorg is releasing its first application powered by its credential infrastructure, in partnership with the largest esports organisations in the world, to scale the adoption of its technology to millions of players and fans. XBorg is a spin-off of SwissBorg, a crypto wealth management application with over 750,000 users.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">For more information about XBorg, visit their <a href="http://www.xborg.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">website</a>, follow them on <a href="https://twitter.com/xborg_official" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a>, or join their community on <a href="https://discord.gg/xborg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/powering-the-next-generation-of-gaming-xborg-sells-out-2-million-seed-round-community-allocation/" rel="nofollow">Powering the Next Generation of Gaming: XBorg Sells Out $2 Million Seed Round Community Allocation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Explodes Over 70% as Judge Rules In Favor of Ripple in SEC Case</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260459</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/xrp_rocket_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/xrp_rocket_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XRP's price exploded immediately after the news broke out.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Ripple&#8217;s XRP has exploded minutes following reports that a judge has ruled in favor of Ripple in the case against the Securities and Exchange Commission of the United States.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to <a href="https://twitter.com/tier10k/status/1679512873498816519" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>, a Judge has ruled that Ripple&#8217;s sale of XRP doesn&#8217;t constitute an offer of investment contracts.</li>
<li>This seems to be a major win for the company, as the case has been ongoing for more than three years.</li>
<li>According to data by CoinGecko, XRP&#8217;s price exploded by approximately 15% immediately after the news broke out and over 70% in the following hours, reaching a 24-hour high of $0.86 (as of writing these lines).</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_260505" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-260505" style="width: 840px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-260505" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6.jpg" alt="xrp-jul13-6" width="840" height="485" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6.jpg 840w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6-300x173.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6-768x443.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xrp-jul13-6-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 840px) 100vw, 840px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-260505" class="wp-caption-text">XRP/USD. Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li>The move marks a major legal victory for Ripple and a slam for the US SEC, which was unable to establish that the sales of XRP constituted an investment contract.</li>
<li>XRP investors have taken the news incredibly positively, as the cryptocurrency has soared immediately since the news broke out.</li>
<li>It has now entered the top 5 largest cryptocurrencies by means of total market capitalization and continues trending higher.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price Explodes Over 70% as Judge Rules In Favor of Ripple in SEC Case</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Much Hyped Mr. Hankey Coin Presale Now Just Hours Away as Investors Prepare to Secure New Meme Token</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/much-hyped-mr-hankey-coin-presale-now-just-hours-away-as-investors-prepare-to-secure-new-meme-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260441</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mr_hankey_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mr_hankey_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One of the most hyped crypto launches of 2023 is now just hours away, with the Mr. Hankey Coin ICO set for an imminent launch. Mr. Hankey Coin&#8217;s ICO was only announced at the start of the week but has quickly spread across Web3, catching the attention of major alpha investment groups and numerous crypto [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most hyped crypto launches of 2023 is now just hours away, with the Mr. Hankey Coin ICO set for an imminent launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=much-hyped-mr-hankey-coin-presale-now-just-hours-away-as-investors-prepare-to-secure-new-meme-token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Mr. Hankey Coin&#8217;s ICO</a> was only announced at the start of the week but has quickly spread across Web3, catching the attention of major alpha investment groups and numerous crypto influencers on social media.</p>
<p>Based on the South Park favorite, Mr Hankey Coin is a quite literal shitcoin that some expect to see an uptake in its presale and massive liquidity once it launches on exchanges. The ICO is set to go live at 6 pm UTC time today.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260453" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="936" height="292" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12-300x94.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12-768x240.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-12-50x16.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<h2>What is Mr. Hankey Coin?</h2>
<p>$HANKEY is based on Mr. Hankey, the Christmas Poo, a beloved South Park character that first appeared on TV screens during the first season of the show back in 1997.</p>
<p>Amid the meme coin frenzy of 2023, many projects have come and gone, but Mr. Hankey Coin appears to be one that has ticked a lot of boxes for investors &#8211; with FOMO reaching its peak ahead of the ICO launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260452" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="936" height="506" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-15-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>Interest in the project is surging because of its small hard cap &#8211; with only $500k needing to be raised before the presale sells out &#8211; and its rapidly growing following.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/MrHankeythecoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter page</a> already has in excess of 7,000 followers, but it&#8217;s not just the presale that has investors excited.</p>
<p>Meme coins have been surging throughout 2023, and the Mr. Hankey Coin developers have also been linked with one of the top performers from earlier this year, $SPONGE, which saw 100x gains.</p>
<p>That could see them quickly secure major CEX listings that will allow $HANKEY to explode in price, much like what happened with $SPONGE and $PEPE, which both saw rapid growth in May.</p>
<h2>$HANKEY’s Potential</h2>
<p>During the presale, 40% of the max 1 billion supply will be made available to presale buyers.</p>
<p>With a hard cap of just $500k, that puts the price of each token at $0.00125.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260451" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="936" height="698" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15-300x224.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15-768x573.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-15-50x37.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>That price isn’t expected to last long as a huge amount of liquidity (40%) has been reserved for the DEX launch, which should spark trading volume.</p>
<p>The liquidity has also been locked, eliminating any worries of a rug pull.</p>
<p>The remaining Mr. Hankey Coin supply has been earmarked for marketing (10%), the team (5%), and CEXs (5%).</p>
<p>The large marketing budget will likely see the project continue to spread like wildfire through Web3, especially with the team’s experience and contacts in the industry.</p>
<p>A number of crypto analysts have already featured the token and its potential on their YouTube channels, with both <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rxL79EydSMI" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Jacob Crypto Bury</a> describing $HANKEY as having at least ‘10x potential.’</p>
<p>Read the <a href="https://mrhankey.vip/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Brownpaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Mr. Hankey Coin ‘brownpaper’</a> for more information and join the <a href="https://t.me/MrHankeyOfficial" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram</a> for news on the ICO launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=much-hyped-mr-hankey-coin-presale-now-just-hours-away-as-investors-prepare-to-secure-new-meme-token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Mr. Hankey Coin</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/much-hyped-mr-hankey-coin-presale-now-just-hours-away-as-investors-prepare-to-secure-new-meme-token/" rel="nofollow">Much Hyped Mr. Hankey Coin Presale Now Just Hours Away as Investors Prepare to Secure New Meme Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
