<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Crypto Exchange FTX and Alameda Seek to Retrieve $71 Million from Philanthropic and Life Science Entities</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-alameda-seek-retrieve-71-million-from-philanthropic-life-science-entities.htm</link><description>Defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX and its sister company Alameda Research are seeking clawbacks from FTX's philanthropic arm and other life science entities.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to court documents filed on Wednesday, the firms are seeking to recover more than $71 million that was allegedly diverted from the FTX Foundation and “Latona” – a “sham non-profit company organized in the Bahamas” – for ex-FTX boss Sam Bankman Fried (SBF)’s personal aggrandizement and political influence....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-alameda-seek-retrieve-71-million-from-philanthropic-life-science-entities.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange FTX and Alameda Seek to Retrieve $71 Million from Philanthropic and Life Science Entities&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-alameda-seek-retrieve-71-million-from-philanthropic-life-science-entities.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120325/319362/adobestock-558764668-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="77814"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: US Justice Department Revamps National Crypto Enforcement Team, Wormhole Releases Gateway Developed within Cosmos, Indonesia's Stock Market and Clearing House for Digital Assets Finally Operational</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-justice-department-revamps-national-crypto-enforcement-team-wormhole-releases-gateway-developed-within-cosmos-indonesias-stock-market-and-clearing-house-for-digital-assets-finally-operational.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-justice-department-revamps-national-crypto-enforcement-team-wormhole-releases-gateway-developed-within-cosmos-indonesias-stock-market-and-clearing-house-for-digital-assets-finally-operational.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: US Justice Department Revamps National Crypto Enforcement Team, Wormhole Releases Gateway Developed within Cosmos, Indonesia's Stock Market and Clearing House for Digital Assets Finally Operational&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crime</category><category>USA</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Scam</category><category>Social media</category><category>Wormhole</category><category>Cosmos</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Indonesia</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Solana</category><category>Optimism</category><category>Polyson</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>DAO</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-justice-department-revamps-national-crypto-enforcement-team-wormhole-releases-gateway-developed-within-cosmos-indonesias-stock-market-and-clearing-house-for-digital-assets-finally-operational.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120256/319298/adobestock-heidi-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="800883"/></item><item><title>FTX Founder SBF Accused by US DOJ of Leaking Ex-Alameda Research CEO's Private Diary</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sbf-accused-by-us-doj-of-leaking-ex-alameda-research-ceos-private-diary.htm</link><description>FTX founder and former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) faces multiple charges of fraud, wire fraud, money laundering, and more by US prosecutors.  &lt;br /&gt;
The nearly one-year-long criminal case has been on since his arrest from the Bahamas after the FTX collapse. &lt;br /&gt;
In a July 20 filing, the US Department of Justice (DOJ) accused the ex-FTX CEO of leaking Caroline Ellison’s private diary to the New York Times. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sbf-accused-by-us-doj-of-leaking-ex-alameda-research-ceos-private-diary.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Founder SBF Accused by US DOJ of Leaking Ex-Alameda Research CEO's Private Diary&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sbf-accused-by-us-doj-of-leaking-ex-alameda-research-ceos-private-diary.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120313/319347/screenshot-2023-07-21-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1222057"/></item><item><title>Alex Shevchenko, CEO of Aurora Labs, on EVMs, $NEAR, and Uniting Blockchain Ecosystems | Ep. 249</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/alex-shevchenko-ceo-of-aurora-labs-evms-near-uniting-blockchain-ecosystems-ep-249.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Alex Shevchenko, CEO of Aurora Labs, talks about building the biggest L2 on Near Foundation, Aurora's customized enterprise blockchain solution, and frictionless blockchain experiences for developers. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/alex-shevchenko-ceo-of-aurora-labs-evms-near-uniting-blockchain-ecosystems-ep-249.htm"&gt;Read More: Alex Shevchenko, CEO of Aurora Labs, on EVMs, $NEAR, and Uniting Blockchain Ecosystems | Ep. 249&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/alex-shevchenko-ceo-of-aurora-labs-evms-near-uniting-blockchain-ecosystems-ep-249.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120312/319335/alex-shevchenko-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="104342"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy ApeCoin? APE Price Rallies 10% in a Week But Global Investors are Stacking This Other Meme Coin Instead – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-apecoin-ape-price-rallies-10-week-but-global-investors-are-stacking-other-meme-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>As altcoin markets continue to slide south, ApeCoin ($APE) is not exception, with APE holders enduring a -67% decline since January - but a small rally is offering a glimmer of hope. &lt;br /&gt;
ApeCoin appears to be surging out of the pits of despair as a +10% rally this week has breathed much needed life into months of cascading price action....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-apecoin-ape-price-rallies-10-week-but-global-investors-are-stacking-other-meme-coin-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy ApeCoin? APE Price Rallies 10% in a Week But Global Investors are Stacking This Other Meme Coin Instead – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-apecoin-ape-price-rallies-10-week-but-global-investors-are-stacking-other-meme-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120276/319287/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="911562"/></item><item><title>The US Department Of Justice Will Double Its Crypto Enforcement Teams To Combat Crimes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-department-of-justice-will-double-its-crypto-enforcement-teams-combat-crimes.htm</link><description>The United States Department of Justice is set to expand its digital asset crime enforcement teams in the coming months as part of wider plans to reduce virtual-asset-related crimes.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a speech delivered on July 20, at the Center for Strategic and International Studies, Nicole Argentieri, the Principal Deputy Assistant Attorney General disclosed the department’s plans to revamp the division. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-department-of-justice-will-double-its-crypto-enforcement-teams-combat-crimes.htm"&gt;Read More: The US Department Of Justice Will Double Its Crypto Enforcement Teams To Combat Crimes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Enforcement</category><category>Justice Department</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-department-of-justice-will-double-its-crypto-enforcement-teams-combat-crimes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120306/319333/us-supreme-court-building.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="337566"/></item><item><title>FCA Launches Permanent Digital Sandbox to Foster Fintech Innovation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fca-launches-permanent-digital-sandbox-foster-fintech-innovation.htm</link><description>The UK's Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) has announced the launch of a permanent version of its Digital Sandbox.  &lt;br /&gt;
Building on the success of its trial phase, the sandbox will provide firms with a secure environment to test their products at an early stage of development, the regulator said on its website on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fca-launches-permanent-digital-sandbox-foster-fintech-innovation.htm"&gt;Read More: FCA Launches Permanent Digital Sandbox to Foster Fintech Innovation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FCA</category><category>Sandbox</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fca-launches-permanent-digital-sandbox-foster-fintech-innovation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120294/319296/adobestock-322304645-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="116192"/></item><item><title>China's Digital Yuan Hits $250 Billion Transaction Volume, Central Bank Governor Reports</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-digital-yuan-hits-250-billion-transaction-volume-central-bank-governor-reports.htm</link><description>The People’s Bank of China (PBoC) revealed that $250 billion worth of transactions have taken place using the country’s central bank-backed digital currency (CBDC) digital yuan in 18 months since the start of its pilot. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at a conference in Singapore, China’s central bank governor Yi Gang said that the central bank has transacted 1.8 trillion yuan as of the end of June....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-digital-yuan-hits-250-billion-transaction-volume-central-bank-governor-reports.htm"&gt;Read More: China's Digital Yuan Hits $250 Billion Transaction Volume, Central Bank Governor Reports&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>PBoC</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-digital-yuan-hits-250-billion-transaction-volume-central-bank-governor-reports.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120291/319291/digital-yuan-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="147729"/></item><item><title>US House Republicans Introduce Landmark Bill for Regulating Crypto: The Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-republicans-introduce-landmark-bill-for-regulating-crypto-financial-innovation-technology-for-21st-century-act.htm</link><description>On Thursday, Senior House Republicans presented legislation to resolve the regulatory ambiguity surrounding the digital asset industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
The proposed bill calls for mandatory definitions of "blockchain" and "digital asset" to be included within the existing financial laws by market regulators. &lt;br /&gt;
The "Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act," a 212-page bill, aims to create a crucial regulatory framework for the digital asset sector. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-republicans-introduce-landmark-bill-for-regulating-crypto-financial-innovation-technology-for-21st-century-act.htm"&gt;Read More: US House Republicans Introduce Landmark Bill for Regulating Crypto: The Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Republican</category><category>law</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-republicans-introduce-landmark-bill-for-regulating-crypto-financial-innovation-technology-for-21st-century-act.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120284/319278/getpaidstock-com-64ba6d4c.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="239353"/></item><item><title>Binance Coin Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $240 BNB Level – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-240-bnb-level-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Binance Coin (BNB) has remained flat in the past 24 hours, with its current level of $244 representing a 4% loss in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
BNB is also down by 1.5% in the last 30 days and has actually declined by 1% since the beginning of the year, in contrast to most other major cryptocurrencies (e.g. Bitcoin is up by more than 80% since January)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-240-bnb-level-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Coin Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $240 BNB Level – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-240-bnb-level-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120273/319273/binance-coin-price-predic.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1134973"/></item><item><title>Canadian Police Alert High-Value Crypto Investors Being Subject to Burglaries</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-police-alert-high-value-crypto-investors-being-subject-to-burglaries.htm</link><description>Canadian authorities have reported several incidents of robbery “whose victims are high-value cryptocurrency investors.” As a result, the country's federal police service issued a warning about this potential trend of home invasion-style burglaries targeting crypto investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-police-alert-high-value-crypto-investors-being-subject-to-burglaries.htm"&gt;Read More: Canadian Police Alert High-Value Crypto Investors Being Subject to Burglaries&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-police-alert-high-value-crypto-investors-being-subject-to-burglaries.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120268/319248/mounted-police-4142729-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="167839"/></item><item><title>Art for Everyone: Museums and Galleries Embrace Digital Art and AI at Christie's Summit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/art-for-everyone-museums-galleries-embrace-digital-art-ai-at-christies-summit.htm</link><description>Web3 and AI are helping art institutions reach audiences they didn't have access to before, with digital being among the most accessible art forms, argued a panel at the auction giant Christie's 'Art + Tech Summit'.  &lt;br /&gt;
The annual summit was held in partnership with crypto payments infrastructure provider MoonPay and luxury brand Gucci. Additional partners included Chainalysis and Outlier Ventures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/art-for-everyone-museums-galleries-embrace-digital-art-ai-at-christies-summit.htm"&gt;Read More: Art for Everyone: Museums and Galleries Embrace Digital Art and AI at Christie's Summit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Art</category><category>Fashion</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Web3</category><category>AI</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>Moonpay</category><category>Gucci</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/art-for-everyone-museums-galleries-embrace-digital-art-ai-at-christies-summit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120257/319269/adobestock-tobias-arhelger-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="195106"/></item><item><title>Fantom Coin is Going to Zero as FTM Price Plummets 15% But All Attention is On Evil Pepe After Raising $160,000 – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>Following a failed recovery rally, Fantom (FTM) is facing a continuation of the bleak price action that has plagued the mid-ranked Layer-1 since May 2022. &lt;br /&gt;
A short-lived +230% rally at the start of the year has given way to a multi-month cascading price action, which has seen a tough -60% bleed-out for dedicated Fantom holders. &lt;br /&gt;
With Fantom price now trading at a lowly $0.2575 (a 24 hour change of -0.08%) many are now wondering whether FTM is destined to fall to zero....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Fantom Coin is Going to Zero as FTM Price Plummets 15% But All Attention is On Evil Pepe After Raising $160,000 – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120264/319260/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="608509"/></item><item><title>Crypto-Based Bank Receives Support from Myanmar's Shadow Government</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm</link><description>Myanmar is all set to launch its first fully crypto-based banking institution, the Spring Development Bank, on July 22.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Spring Development Bank, named after the Spring Revolution, aims to grant the country’s shadow government National Unity Government (NUG) access to financial services and funding from within and outside the country for their fight against the ruling State Administration Council (SAC), which took over Myanmar in February 2021....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto-Based Bank Receives Support from Myanmar's Shadow Government&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Myanmar</category><category>Crypto Bank</category><category>USDT</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120271/319259/myanmar-flag-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161825"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Trading Volume Surges Past $800 Million – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>The Litecoin price has dropped by 2.5% in the past 24 hours, with its fall to $92.11 also marking an 8.5% fall in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC's losses today comes as the cryptocurrency market as a whole slides by 1% since yesterday, although the altcoin remains up by 10% in the last 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;
It's also up by 63% in the past year, while the coin's 24-hour trading volume has passed $800 million, in a sign that market activity remains elevated and could possibly help it recover soon....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Trading Volume Surges Past $800 Million – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120267/319254/litecoin-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1066632"/></item><item><title>DexTools Trending Crypto $HAMS and $MOG Prices Surge 30,000%, But Buy These 2 Coins Before They List Today – Burn Kenny and $EVILPEPE to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm</link><description>DexTools trending crypto $HAMS and $MOG have both seen their prices pump 30,000% since launch, as money continues to chase hot speculative coins listing directly on decentralized exchanges (DEXs). &lt;br /&gt;
And there is no shortage of launches. Burn Kenny ($KENNY) and Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE) are both likely to list today.  &lt;br /&gt;
Indeed, Kenny could be listing on DEXs in the next few hours as it closes in on its presale target of $500,000, with only around $120k to go....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: DexTools Trending Crypto $HAMS and $MOG Prices Surge 30,000%, But Buy These 2 Coins Before They List Today – Burn Kenny and $EVILPEPE to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120253/319245/hams-usd-uni-dextools-io-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="514044"/></item><item><title>FTX Launches Lawsuit Against Ex-Executives, Including Sam Bankman-Fried, to Reclaim $1 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm</link><description>Now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX has filed a complaint against former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried and other key executives to retrieve more than $1 billion in allegedly misappropriated funds.  &lt;br /&gt;
The lawsuit, filed by FTX under the direction of an executive team led by restructuring expert John Ray, named former Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison, FTX co-founder Gary Wang, former FTX engineering director Nishad Singh, and Bankman-Fried as defendants. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Launches Lawsuit Against Ex-Executives, Including Sam Bankman-Fried, to Reclaim $1 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Gary Wang</category><category>Caroline Ellison</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120265/319242/ftx-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="86751"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Seeks Data from FTX Wallets for SEC Lawsuit Defense</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm</link><description>Terraform Labs, the development firm behind Terra network and the failed stablecoin TerraUSD (USTC), is seeking permission from a court to get access to data from the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Terraform Labs, the failure of its UST stablecoin was the result of an attack by large short sellers, which the firm claimed included FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried’s trading firm Alameda Research....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Seeks Data from FTX Wallets for SEC Lawsuit Defense&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Terra</category><category>FTX</category><category>SEC</category><category>Do Kwon</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120263/319240/law.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="254349"/></item><item><title>DOGE 2.0 Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Whales Are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – 100x Potential?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm</link><description>So far 2023 has been a year characterized by explosive meme coin runs, perhaps none more successful than the incredible Pepecoin ($PEPE) pump which ignited Spring's ecstatic meme season. &lt;br /&gt;
But the altcoin pumps haven't stopped there, as the eye-watering gains have continued to flow from straight to DEX tokens in months since. &lt;br /&gt;
And in the latest sensation, Dogecoin ($DOGE) spin-off token $DOGE2.0 has surged in price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: DOGE 2.0 Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Whales Are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – 100x Potential?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120262/319239/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1105918"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as XRP Drops 5% in 24 Hours – Is the Rally Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm</link><description>The XRP price has fallen by 5% in the past 24 hours, with the coin's slide to $0.776800 coming as the cryptocurrency market drops by 1%. &lt;br /&gt;
Coming a week after Ripple's positive decision in its case with the SEC, XRP's move today means it's up by only 0.5% in the last week, although it remains 67% up in the last 14 days and up by 125% since the beginning of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as XRP Drops 5% in 24 Hours – Is the Rally Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120255/319228/xrp-price-prediction-as-x.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="974959"/></item></channel></rss>
