<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kraken Dethroned Coinbase as Most Liquid US Exchange for Altcoins in July: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kraken-dethroned-coinbase-as-most-liquid-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265854</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/KrakenUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/KrakenUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While Kraken records significant growth in its market share, Coinbase has faced regulatory challenges in recent months, possibly the reason for the decline in its volumes.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency trading platform Kraken dethroned its rival Coinbase to become the most liquid United States exchange for altcoins in July.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> by Dessislava Laneva, a research analyst at crypto data platform Kaiko, by the end of July, Kraken had claimed 47% of the market depth in the US for the top 10 altcoins.</p>
<h2>Kraken Claims Largest U.S. Market Depth for Altcoins</h2>
<p>As of January 2023, Kraken had only a 39% share of the market depth of altcoins, while Coinbase had 45%. At the same time, Binance.US, the American arm of the world’s largest crypto exchange Binance, had a market share of 7% while six other platforms collectively accounted for 9%.</p>
<p>However, data analyzed by Kaiko researchers found that Kraken’s market share has increased to 47%, leaving Coinbase with 41%, Binance.US with 1%, and the remaining exchanges with 10%. This means that Kraken now has a greater ability to absorb large market orders without significantly impacting the price of the altcoin in question.</p>
<p>Besides Kraken’s growing market depth, the exchange’s market share among platforms supporting USD deposits has also increased recently. Data from The Block’s USD Support Exchange Volume dashboard <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/crypto-markets/spot/usd-support-exchange-volume-market-share" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> Kraken’s market share rose from 14.78% in January to 21.1% in July. The growth is significant, as the platform had a share of 8.3% last August.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Faces challenges</h2>
<p>A spokesperson for Kraken told The Block that the exchange’s recent performance is due to the launch of its advanced trading platform Kraken Pro and the enhancement of several offerings. The representative said the exchange&#8217;s share of total volumes had hit an 18-month high since unveiling the new platform.</p>
<p>Kraken’s share of the EUR spot market has soared to 53% from 35%, and the exchange’s AUD spot market has also multiplied by six times in the past months, per the spokesperson.</p>
<p>While Kraken records significant growth in its digital asset market share, Coinbase has faced regulatory challenges in recent months, possibly due to the decline in its volumes. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> Coinbase in early June over several allegations, including operations as an unregistered broker, securities exchange, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wanted-coinbase-to-delist-all-crypto-assets-except-bitcoin-before-lawsuit-ft/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the Commission instructed the exchange to halt the trading of all altcoins as they were securities and violated federal laws.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kraken-dethroned-coinbase-as-most-liquid-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data/" rel="nofollow">Kraken Dethroned Coinbase as Most Liquid US Exchange for Altcoins in July: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here is How XRP Holders Can Apply for Evernode&#8217;s (Evers) Airdrop</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-xrp-holders-can-apply-for-evernodes-evers-airdrop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265818</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Evers_Airdrop.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Evers_Airdrop.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The decentralized platform will distribute 5,160,960 Evers to eligible XRP holders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evernode &#8211; a layer 2 smart contract solution built on top of the XRP Ledger (XRPL) &#8211; announced the first details of its airdrop intended to reach XRP holders.</p>
<p>Such investors should provide a snapshot of their possessions by the beginning of September and must hold their tokens on-chain.</p>
<ul>
<li>The team behind the decentralized platform <a href="https://twitter.com/EvernodeXRPL/status/1689805394460463104?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that it will airdrop 5,160,960 Evers to eligible XRP holders. Investors will be required to send a snapshot of their stash (stored directly on-chain and not through an exchange) until September 1.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Because we&#8217;ll launch on the Hooks sidechain and because that sidechain will include a burn2mint, we need to snapshot the XRP Ledger before the Hooks sidechain goes live,&#8221; Evernode explained.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The token distribution will mainly focus on investors with balances of up to 50,000 XRP. Those owning more will need to hold it in separate accounts to benefit from the contribution.</li>
<li>Evernode promised to give further details once there is more information about the launch of the Hooks sidechain.</li>
<li>Subsequently, the team reminded that the airdrop is a gift, meaning not all XRP holders will be granted portions of the new token:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While we&#8217;ll use our best endeavors, we don&#8217;t in any way promise/warrant that you&#8217;ll receive any particular number of Evers. For any reason &#8211; or for no reason &#8211; we may decide not to proceed with the airdrop in this manner, or at all.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-xrp-holders-can-apply-for-evernodes-evers-airdrop/" rel="nofollow">Here is How XRP Holders Can Apply for Evernode&#8217;s (Evers) Airdrop</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Price Continues Bullish Ascent, as Shibie Coin is Also Pumping</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-price-continues-bullish-ascent-as-shibie-coin-is-also-pumping/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265886</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shibainu_shibie_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shibainu_shibie_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Meme coins are once again gaining momentum, with Shiba Inu ($SHIB) continuing its recent bullish run. $SHIB has gained 14% since Monday, sparking speculation that the token may be gearing up for an extended surge. Meanwhile, the brand-new Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE), a $SHIB and Barbie hybrid, has also seen significant traction in its ongoing presale [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are once again gaining momentum, with Shiba Inu ($SHIB) continuing its recent bullish run.</p>
<p>$SHIB has gained 14% since Monday, sparking speculation that the token may be gearing up for an extended surge.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the brand-new Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE), a $SHIB and Barbie hybrid, has also seen significant traction in its ongoing presale phase.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu Technicals Point to Continued Price Momentum</h2>
<p>The world’s second-largest meme coin is showing signs of life again, with $SHIB posting three bullish daily closes in a row and heading for a fourth.</p>
<p>Looking at the price chart, $SHIB is now nearing a critical resistance level around $0.0000105, which was tapped on August 5 – resulting in a sharp sell-off.</p>
<p>However, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/shiba-inu/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from CoinMarketCap</a>, the trading volume of $SHIB reached $306 million in the past 24 hours, making it the 11<sup>th</sup> most-traded cryptocurrency globally.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265887" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-7.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="285" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-7.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-7-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-7-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Many $SHIB holders believe this increased volume could help the price break through the nearby resistance zone on its second attempt, setting the stage for an extended uptrend.</p>
<p>Adding more fuel to the bullish hypothesis is the fact that $SHIB broke through the crucial 200-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA) on the daily time frame.</p>
<p>This EMA is often used as a proxy for a token’s long-term trend, so the fact that $SHIB is now trading above it could signal that sentiment is shifting in favor of bulls.</p>
<h2>Numerous Fundamental Factors Drive Shiba Inu’s Momentum</h2>
<p>A combination of fundamental factors is driving the recent double-digit gains for $SHIB.</p>
<p>Firstly, the upcoming launch of Shibarium, Shiba Inu’s layer-2 scaling solution, has renewed interest in the $SHIB token.</p>
<p>Shibarium aims to reduce network fees and enable faster transactions, meaning its launch will be a significant milestone for the ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265888" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-15.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-15.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-15-300x144.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-15-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Additionally, $SHIB received an adoption boost after BitPay announced full support for bill payment services using the token.</p>
<p>Unsurprisingly, this integration with a major payment processor adds much-needed utility to the token.</p>
<p>Finally, the broader optimism in the crypto market, led by speculation around a spot Bitcoin ETF approval and interest rate decreases, has fueled optimism for meme coins like $SHIB.</p>
<p>With the token&#8217;s technicals and fundamentals aligning, $SHIB holders are increasingly confident that the token can sustain its current bullish momentum.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu-Inspired Shibie Coin Gaining Presale Momentum Ahead of Upcoming DEX Launch</h2>
<p>While Shiba Inu sees a resurgence in interest, the new meme coin <a href="https://bs_ff115a97.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-continues-bullish-ascent-as-shibie-coin-is-also-pumping" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibie Coin ($SHIBIE)</a> is also capturing the attention of investors.</p>
<p>The presale for $SHIBIE has been gaining traction ahead of the token’s official launch, having now raised $320,000 in just two weeks.</p>
<p>This early momentum has Shibie Coin on track to reach its reduced hard cap of $500,000 in the coming days.</p>
<p>Significantly, Shibie Coin’s team has also decided to burn 50% of the initial presale token allocation once it concludes – a deflationary tactic that could bolster $SHIBIE’s value if demand continues at its current pace.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265889" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-12.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="387" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-12.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-12-300x193.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-12-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>With just three days remaining in Shibie Coin&#8217;s presale, interest is building around this new token.</p>
<p>Many in the <a href="https://t.me/ShibieCoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Shibie Coin Telegram channel</a> speculate that the token could see dramatic price movements post-launch if the current momentum continues.</p>
<p>Moreover, given that the developers have reserved 20% of the total $SHIBIE supply for DEX liquidity, this should help avoid significant price volatility in the days following the token&#8217;s listing.</p>
<p>Given its low market cap at launch and unique branding, $SHIBIE positions itself as a token to watch in the coming days.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_ff115a97.cleardayboat.care/?referrer=shiba-inu-price-continues-bullish-ascent-as-shibie-coin-is-also-pumping" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Shibie Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-price-continues-bullish-ascent-as-shibie-coin-is-also-pumping/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu Price Continues Bullish Ascent, as Shibie Coin is Also Pumping</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Returns to $29K After Failing at $30K, Shiba Inu Pumps 16% in 7 Days: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-returns-to-29k-after-failing-at-30k-shiba-inu-pumps-16-in-7-days-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 14:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265786</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuATH.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuATH.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Rollbit Coin (RLB) has found a place within the top 100 alts following a massive 76% weekly surge. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After several weeks of sideways trading and failing to register any significant price movements in either direction, these past seven days provided more volatility that resulted in both multi-day lows and highs for BTC.</p>
<p>It all started on Monday when the primary cryptocurrency dumped by several hundred dollars after the quiet weekend to a weekly low of $28,700. However, the bulls intercepted the move and pushed the asset north. In fact, what followed was among the most notable leg-ups registered in the past few months, as bitcoin shot up to over $30,000 by Wednesday.</p>
<p>This became its highest price tag since July 23. The asset tried to remain above $30,000 but failed by the end of the day and the subsequent rejection pushed it back south to its current price tag of around $29,500. Interestingly, even the<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unfazed-as-cpi-for-july-increases-by-0-2-mom/" data-wpel-link="internal"> CPI numbers</a> that came out earlier this week didn&#8217;t result in enhanced volatility, which used to be the case up until a few months ago.</p>
<p>Some altcoins, though, have performed a lot better than BTC for the same 7-day period. Such is the case with Solana, Chainlink, TONCOIN, HBAR, and OKB. All of these have surged by somewhere between 6 and 9% on a weekly scale.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Shiba Inu has taken the main stage from the larger-cap alts. SHIB has soared by more than 16% since last Friday and trades above $0.00001.</p>
<p>Rollbit Coin has emerged as the top performer within the same timeframe, having added over 76% of value. This has helped RLB find a place within the top 100 largest digital assets by market cap.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,218B | 24H Vol: $29B | BTC Dominance: 47%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $29,435 (+0.7%) | ETH: $1,850 (+0.4%) | BNB: $240 (-0.7%)</p>
<figure id="attachment_265866" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265866" style="width: 1880px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265866" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1880" height="877" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins.png 1880w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-300x140.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-1024x478.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-768x358.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-1536x717.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1880px) 100vw, 1880px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265866" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Here’s How Much of ETH’s Total Supply is Held in the Top 10 Addresses.</strong> It turns out that ETH&#8217;s supply <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-of-eths-total-supply-is-held-in-the-top-10-addresses/" data-wpel-link="internal">held</a> by the 10 largest wallets has been increasing considerably since 2018. In fact, it increased by a whopping 27% throughout the period.</p>
<p><strong>Is Tether Really the 11th Biggest Bitcoin Holder? CryptoQuant Chips In. </strong>Recently, analysts were suggesting that Tether is the 11th biggest Bitcoin holder. However, the prominent data analytics firm CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-tether-really-the-11th-biggest-bitcoin-holder-cryptoquant-chips-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">took it</a> to Twitter to question these statements and provide additional clarifications.</p>
<p><strong>Ripple (XRP) Lead Lawyer Slams SEC’s Appeal Request, Reveals Important Date. </strong>Stuart Alderoty &#8211; the Chief Legal Officer at Ripple Labs &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-lead-lawyer-slams-secs-appeal-request-reveals-important-date/" data-wpel-link="internal">slammed</a> SEC&#8217;s appeal attempt and also revealed a timeline as to when users can expect the company to take action against the most recent filings.</p>
<p><strong>The US SEC Might Approve Numerous Spot BTC ETFs at the Same Time, Cathie Wood Thinks. </strong><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-sec-might-approve-numerous-spot-btc-etfs-at-the-same-time-cathie-wood-thinks/" data-wpel-link="internal">According</a> to Cathie Wood, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission might approve a number of spot Bitcoin ETFs at the same time. Wood is exposed to the market through a number of investments.</p>
<p><strong>El Salvador Becomes the Latest Country Where Binance Secures Regulatory Approval. </strong>El Salvador &#8211; the Bitcoin-friendly nation &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-becomes-the-latest-country-where-binance-secures-regulatory-approval/" data-wpel-link="internal">became</a> the latest country to approve and provide regulatory approval for the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance.</p>
<p><strong>Federal Reserve Launches New Program to Oversee Crypto Activities of Banks. </strong>The US Federal Reserve is launching a new program. It aims to help the institution oversee various cryptocurrency activities that banks carry out.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-returns-to-29k-after-failing-at-30k-shiba-inu-pumps-16-in-7-days-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Returns to $29K After Failing at $30K, Shiba Inu Pumps 16% in 7 Days: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Much Did Bitcoin Price Increase Since the Simpsons, Family Guy First Mentioned It?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-did-bitcoin-price-increase-since-the-simpsons-family-guy-first-mentioned-it/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265721</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Future.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Future.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here's how far BTC rallied since the Simpsons cryptocurrency episode that aired in Feb 2020.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As BTC&#8217;s USD exchange rate settled Thursday from a Tuesday high above $30,000 to the mid-$29Ks, a Family Guy crypto meme started making the rounds on X.com:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">JUST IN &#8211; If You Had Invested $100 In <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> When Peter From &#8216;Family Guy&#8217; Said &#8220;<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a>&#8221; For The First Time, You&#8217;d Have $6,637.08 today a profit of 6,537.08% <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/p75UlynUVM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/p75UlynUVM</a></p>
<p>— Simply Bitcoin (@SimplyBitcoinTV) <a href="https://twitter.com/SimplyBitcoinTV/status/1689611602729799680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>A $100 investment in Bitcoin the day Peter Griffin said, &#8220;Bitcoin&#8221; on Family Guy <a href="https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/23/08/33703584/if-you-had-invested-100-in-bitcoin-when-peter-from-family-guy-said-bitcoin-for-the-first-t" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">would be</a> worth $6,637.08 at today&#8217;s exchange rate. Apparently, the hit television cartoon mentioned Bitcoin very early on (Feb 2016.)</p>
<h2>Here&#8217;s BTC&#8217;s ROI Since Simpsons did it in 2020</h2>
<p>Asking Google Bard if &#8220;Simpsons did it first,&#8221; the large language model chatbot said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In the Season 31 episode &#8220;Frinkcoin&#8221;, Professor Frink creates a cryptocurrency called Frinkcoin. The episode aired in 2020, and some people believe that it is a prediction of the rise of Bitcoin.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>At first glance, it appears that Simpsons did it long after Family Guy on this one, Feb 23, 2020.</p>
<p>But still, any Family Guy fans who became Bitcoin investors with $100 that day could exchange their sats for $2,966 today and bag a 2,900% ROI in under four years.</p>
<p>Family Guy&#8217;s Bitcoin mention was remarkably early. Simpsons&#8217; was later, but it <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/video/simpsons-appearance-crypto-reveals-satoshi-164613669.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">also included</a> a very subtle easter egg joking that the Simpsons creators know who Satoshi Nakamoto is.</p>
<h2>Ok, Bard, When did the Simpsons Predict Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>Bard did also mention a wild fan theory that the Simpsons predicted Bitcoin in early 1997:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Simpsons have been known for their many predictions over the years, and some people believe that they also predicted the rise of Bitcoin. In the Season 8 episode &#8220;My Sister, My Sitter&#8221;, which aired in 1997, there is a scene where Bart and Lisa are walking past a store called &#8220;Crypto Barn&#8221;. The sign in the window of the store says &#8216;A place for codes&#8217;.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>There was no Bitcoin to invest in back in 1997, but one of Bitcoin&#8217;s early supporters, Adam Back, proposed hash cash that year. More recently, Back has been very bullish about the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/adam-back-bets-1-million-satoshi-for-btcs-price-to-reach-100k-before-2024-bitcoin-halving/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin price</a> over the next year.</p>
<h2>Bard Had Some Precautions for Investors Regarding Bitcoin</h2>
<p>&#8220;Some people have joked that Peter Griffin is a financial genius, as his suggestion to invest in Bitcoin has turned out to be very profitable. However, it is important to note that Bitcoin is a volatile investment, and its value can fluctuate wildly. It is never a good idea to invest more money than you can afford to lose.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-did-bitcoin-price-increase-since-the-simpsons-family-guy-first-mentioned-it/" rel="nofollow">How Much Did Bitcoin Price Increase Since the Simpsons, Family Guy First Mentioned It?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain Event onXDC Live Debuts in Austin, Texas on August 25-26</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-event-onxdc-live-debuts-in-austin-texas-on-august-25-26/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265546</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/onXDC_Banner_1691553811RFODKhDPf2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/onXDC_Banner_1691553811RFODKhDPf2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Austin, Texas, August 10th, 2023] The countdown to the first annual onXDC Live blockchain industry conference has begun. Taking center stage at the Long Center for the Performing Arts in Austin, Texas on August 25-26, this event will attract a diverse audience of blockchain enthusiasts. The onXDC Live conference will host luminaries, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Austin, Texas, August 10th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>The countdown to the first annual onXDC Live blockchain industry conference has begun. Taking center stage at the Long Center for the Performing Arts in Austin, Texas on August 25-26, this event will attract a diverse audience of blockchain enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The onXDC Live conference will host luminaries, experts, and thought leaders from around the globe as they converge for two days of talks, workshops, and panel discussions.</p>
<blockquote><p>Founder of onXDC, Tre’ Nelson, said: “We have been overwhelmed by the tremendous support and excitement surrounding the conference. With a distinguished roster of sponsors and keynote speakers from some of the world&#8217;s most innovative blockchain companies, we are poised to deliver an unforgettable experience. The conference is destined to become the premier networking event in Austin for blockchain technology.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Kicking off the event, the first annual onXDC Live Hackathon will be announced. This event aims to unite developers and hackers, fostering collaboration within the dynamic XDC Network community. This initiative is drawing attention from both the Austin Ethereum community and beyond, given the compatibility of XDC with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). This presents an unprecedented opportunity to leverage the decentralized, hybrid, permissionless, and self-sovereign technologies enabled by the EVM compatible XDC ecosystem.</p>
<p>The two-day conference will also provide ample opportunities for in-depth learning. onXDC Live will provide attendees with unparalleled access to industry thought leaders who will share their wisdom and personal experiences of navigating the blockchain space. Through thought-provoking panel discussions, fireside chats, and VIP networking opportunities, participants will gain insights that transcend the boundaries of traditional discourse.</p>
<p>The event boasts a distinguished list of sponsors, including Uphold, D’Cent Wallet, xSPECTAR, LootUp, Digital Ascension Group, VOY Finance, Prime Numbers, CryptoLaw,  XDC Foundation and Lockton. Speakers of exceptional caliber, such as Andre Casterman, Dr. Martin Heisboeck, Billy Sebell, John E. Deaton, Quincy Jones, Jake Claver, Crypto Eri,  and Ray Fuentes are primed to share their expertise and insights.</p>
<p>For a comprehensive list of speakers, please visit: <a href="https://www.onxdc.network/events" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://www.onxdc.network/events</a></p>
<h2>About onXDC Live</h2>
<p>The overarching mission of onXDC Live is to fuel exponential growth within the XDC blockchain ecosystem. By attracting dynamic blockchain technology companies and developers from across the globe, the event endeavors to catalyze innovation. The two-day gathering serves as a platform to explore the transformative potential of blockchain technology across various industries, encompassing Global Trade Finance, DeFi, Digitization, Tokenization, Instant Settlement, Gaming, Supply Chain, and more.</p>
<p>For more information about onXDC Live 2023 and to secure your spot, please visit <a href="https://chat.openai.com/www.onxdc.network/events" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">www.onxdc.network/events</a>.</p>
<p>Registration is recommended ASAP as limited tickets are available.</p>
<p>Connect with us on social media using #onXDCLive to stay up-to-date with the latest event news and announcements.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-event-onxdc-live-debuts-in-austin-texas-on-august-25-26/" rel="nofollow">Blockchain Event onXDC Live Debuts in Austin, Texas on August 25-26</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Sinks 4% as Uncertainty Ramps Up, But XRP20 Nears $2 Million Presale Raise</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-sinks-4-as-uncertainty-ramps-up-but-xrp20-nears-2-million-presale-raise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265806</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Investor uncertainty around XRP ($XRP) is ramping up again, with the token&#8217;s value dropping 4% since August 9. This uncertainty has been prompted by the SEC&#8217;s decision to appeal Ripple&#8217;s recent legal victory, hinting that the back-and-forth between the two entities could be set to resume. However, the excitement around the new XRP20 ($XRP20) token [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investor uncertainty around XRP ($XRP) is ramping up again, with the token&#8217;s value dropping 4% since August 9.</p>
<p>This uncertainty has been prompted by the SEC&#8217;s decision to appeal Ripple&#8217;s recent legal victory, hinting that the back-and-forth between the two entities could be set to resume.</p>
<p>However, the excitement around the new XRP20 ($XRP20) token continues to build – with the project’s presale now nearing the $2 million milestone.</p>
<h2>Recent Price Action Hints at Trend Reversal for $XRP</h2>
<p>$XRP had been enjoying a sharp reversal until Wednesday morning, with the price soaring 11% after experiencing an extended downtrend in the previous weeks.</p>
<p>After topping at $0.665, the price turned back – falling 4% to $0.632, where it trades today.</p>
<p>This turnaround coincides with $XRP’s price tapping the 20-day Exponential Moving Average (EMA), hinting that it could be acting as a minor resistance level.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-15.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265813" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-15.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="284" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-15.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-15-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-15-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Price is now hovering just above the 50-day EMA. This means it’s essentially trapped in a range between the two indicators.</p>
<p>The Relative Strength Index (RSI) has dropped to a value of 44 on the daily timeframe, further showcasing the recent bearish momentum.</p>
<p>Notably, $XRP’s 24-hour trading volume has also sunk by 35%, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from CoinMarketCap</a>.</p>
<p>The decreasing interest in the token may suggest that speculative crypto investors are seeking other options due to ongoing regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<h2>SEC Appeal Reintroduces Uncertainty as Ripple Legal Battle Resumes</h2>
<p>The uncertainty around $XRP stems from the SEC&#8217;s decision to appeal a ruling in its long-running lawsuit against Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>Back in July, Judge Analisa Torres delivered a partial victory to Ripple when she ruled that $XRP is not a security in the context of retail trader offerings.</p>
<p>However, as <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/08/09/sec-ripple-xrp-security-cryptocurrency-appeal-sdny/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">reported by Fortune.com</a>, the SEC is now set to appeal this decision.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265812" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-14.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="432" height="351" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-14.jpg 432w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-14-300x244.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-14-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 432px) 100vw, 432px" /></a></p>
<p>Unsurprisingly, this brought back much of the uncertainty surrounding $XRP before Torres&#8217; initial decision, dampening investor enthusiasm and demand.</p>
<p>With the SEC intent on continuing the legal battle, $XRP holders could face another extended period of doubts around the token&#8217;s status.</p>
<p>The good news for these holders is that <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1688309749610168320?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">pro-Ripple attorney John Deaton</a> tweeted that he’s willing to bet “significant funds” that Torres’ decision does not get overturned on appeal.</p>
<p>Regardless, the lingering uncertainty poses short-term headwinds for $XRP, even as longer-term optimism still exists within the investor base.</p>
<h2>Rising Presale Traction &amp; Clean Audit Build Excitement for Trending XRP20 Token</h2>
<p>With uncertainty swirling around $XRP, the developers behind a new token called <a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=xrp-price-sinks-4-as-uncertainty-ramps-up-but-xrp20-nears-2-million-presale-raise" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20 ($XRP20)</a> aim to make their mark on the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>The recently launched XRP20 presale has seen impressive early traction, raising over $1.9 million.</p>
<p>Branded by the developers as &#8220;the next evolution of XRP,&#8221; XRP20 aims to tap into crypto investor nostalgia and offer a &#8220;second chance&#8221; to those who missed out on the original $XRP&#8217;s 2017 bull run.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-17.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265811" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-17.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="267" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-17.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-17-300x133.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-17-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>With less than half of the allotted presale tokens remaining, the buzz around XRP20 is intensifying as investors rush to get involved at the low price of $0.000092 – 30 times cheaper than $XRP&#8217;s all-time low.</p>
<p>As noted in <a href="https://xrp20coin.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20’s whitepaper</a>, once this presale concludes, the token will be launched on a DEX – with 10% of the total token supply used to boost liquidity for traders.</p>
<p>Moreover, the XRP20 project recently underwent a <a href="https://xrp20coin.com/assets/documents/audit.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">comprehensive smart contract audit</a> conducted by blockchain security firm 0xGuard.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265810" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-11.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="180" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-11.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-11-300x90.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-11-50x15.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>No high-risk vulnerabilities were noted in the audit, providing assurances to early investors regarding the safety of XRP20.</p>
<p>As the presale heads towards its $3.68 million hard cap, numerous crypto influencers are taking note, with <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DBRpK8gFVDU&amp;pp=ygUFeHJwMjA%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">YouTuber Michael Wrubel</a> uploading a video detailing how optimistic he is about $XRP20’s prospects.</p>
<p>If XRP20’s momentum continues at this pace, there’s no doubt it’s a token to monitor closely ahead of its open market debut.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=xrp-price-sinks-4-as-uncertainty-ramps-up-but-xrp20-nears-2-million-presale-raise" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit XRP20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-sinks-4-as-uncertainty-ramps-up-but-xrp20-nears-2-million-presale-raise/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price Sinks 4% as Uncertainty Ramps Up, But XRP20 Nears $2 Million Presale Raise</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fed Most Likely Won&#8217;t Raise Interest Rates Anymore: Tom Lee</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-fed-most-likely-wont-raise-interest-rates-anymore-tom-lee/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tom Lee]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265729</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["I think that the Fed is done hiking for this cycle," Lee stated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tom Lee &#8211; Managing Partner and the Head of Research at Fundstrat Global Advisors &#8211; believes there is an 80% chance that the US Federal Reserve will pivot from its aggressive interest rate hike policy. He suggested that the main reason behind such a decision could be the positive CPI numbers which recently showed that inflation in America has slowed down its spread.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous experts have argued that the end of the Fed&#8217;s anti-inflationary program could potentially catalyze a new rally of the crypto market, specifically bitcoin.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">No More Hikes Expected</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/08/10/i-think-the-fed-is-done-hiking-for-this-cycle-says-fundstrats-tom-lee.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for CNBC, Lee pointed out the latest inflation report in America, calling it &#8220;very good.&#8221; He thinks the numbers will further fall in the next following months, resulting in a revival for financial markets.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I think as people peel the onion, this was a very good inflation report because it&#8217;s setting up for the next two months to see inflation slowing even further.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_133355" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-133355" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-133355" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg" alt="Tom Lee. Source: CNBC" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/TomLee-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-133355" class="wp-caption-text">Tom Lee, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American investor believes this is an appropriate timing for the Federal Reserve to stop raising interest rates. The US central bank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-raises-rates-again-by-0-25-bitcoin-trades-flat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lifted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the benchmark 11 times between March 2020 and July 2023 to tackle the economic crisis caused by the COVID-19 pandemic and other setbacks.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I was originally in the 60% chance that July was the last hike. I think it&#8217;s now in the 80% range, I think that the Fed is done hiking for this cycle,&#8221; Lee said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, Fundstrat&#8217;s analyst forecasted that the Federal Reserve will even start cutting interest rates at the beginning of 2024 because a high benchmark could hurt America&#8217;s economy (assuming that inflation keeps slowing its pace):</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Most people believe it&#8217;s the second half because the Fed doesn&#8217;t want to tighten rates, but if inflation&#8217;s falling, they have to cut rates. Otherwise, it&#8217;s actually stricting the economy more.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bullish for BTC?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some people have suggested that a possible pivot from the Fed could make investors turn their attention toward riskier assets, such as cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One example is Galaxy Digital&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Mike Novogratz &#8211; who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-04-06/novogratz-says-bitcoin-will-go-to-the-moon-once-fed-pauses?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=bd&amp;cmpId=google&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall&amp;in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">predicted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that bitcoin will &#8220;go to the moon&#8221; once the financial institution ceases the interest rate hike policy.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Anthony Scaramucci – the Founder of SkyBridge Capital and former White House official &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bull-market-to-start-once-us-inflation-drops-to-4-5-scaramucci/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shares</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the same stance. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I do believe that the Fed declares victory at 4% to 5% inflation. If I&#8217;m right, there will be a resurgence in the market. There&#8217;ll be a lot of short covering in crypto, and there&#8217;ll be a rebirth of risk assets,&#8221; he said earlier this year.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fed-most-likely-wont-raise-interest-rates-anymore-tom-lee/" rel="nofollow">The Fed Most Likely Won&#8217;t Raise Interest Rates Anymore: Tom Lee</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is an XRP ETF Possible? Expert Weighs In</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-an-xrp-etf-possible-expert-weighs-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265793</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_etf_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp_etf_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Is an XRP ETF with the current SEC possible? An expert gives his two cents on the matter.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Filings for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds have been pushed around for years with no success in the US so far. The Securities and Exchange Commission remains reluctant.</p>
<p>Ideas for ETH ETFs have also been floating around but XRP? That&#8217;s something new, but apparently, there&#8217;s some sort of interest in it.</p>
<ul>
<li>The primary reason why cryptocurrency investors have been pushing for a spot Bitcoin ETF approved by the US SEC is that it will thoroughly legitimate Bitcoin as an investable asset.</li>
<li>This would, in turn, open the door for many institutions that are looking for a safe way to invest in BTC without having to necessarily worry about its safekeeping.</li>
<li>Let&#8217;s face it &#8211; storing large amounts of BTC isn&#8217;t for anyone, and it can be particularly risky.</li>
<li>With BlackRock now filing for a Bitcoin ETF, chances for approval, according to many &#8211; have improved. This is mainly because of the fact that it&#8217;s the largest asset manager in the world, and it has a tremendously successful track record in getting its ETF applications approved. Shocker.</li>
<li>But now, an asset management expert &#8211; James Seyffart &#8211; weighed in on the possibility of an XRP ETF getting approved.</li>
<li>His comments came in response to the recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-listed-on-gemini-following-ripples-partial-court-victory/" data-wpel-link="internal">listing</a> of XRP on Gemini.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Gemini following Coinbase and Listing XRP. Been asked a few times in last weeks about an XRP ETF. Don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s enough to launch an XRP ETF with this SEC. And there seems to be essentially zero demand from issuers to try.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Gemini following <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@coinbase</a> and listing <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/XRP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#XRP</a>. Been asked a few times in last few weeks about an XRP ETF. Don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s enough to launch an XRP ETF with this SEC. And there seems to be essentially zero demand from issuers to try <a href="https://t.co/t3PQeqbKvI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/t3PQeqbKvI</a></p>
<p>— James Seyffart (@JSeyff) <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1689749994557804544?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-an-xrp-etf-possible-expert-weighs-in/" rel="nofollow">Is an XRP ETF Possible? Expert Weighs In</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stagnant Above $29K as RLB Skyrockets to $0.2 (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stagnant-above-29k-as-rlb-skyrockets-to-0-2-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265775</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price remains rangebound but there's one coin that's making all sorts of rounds today.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market is taking an interesting turn throughout the past few days. Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been unable to make any improvements, but a coin that&#8217;s native to an online crypto casino is all the industry is talking about.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Unable to Escape $29K Range</h2>
<p>The past 24 hours failed to deliver anything interesting in terms of Bitcoin&#8217;s price development as it&#8217;s completely devoid of volatility and any kind of action.</p>
<p>The price remains in the tight consolidation range of around $29K, and if we exclude the recent attempt to break $30K, the market is completely paralyzed.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265780" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265780" style="width: 1520px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265780" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1108231" width="1520" height="971" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231.jpg 1520w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231-300x192.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231-1024x654.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231-768x491.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_1108231-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1520px) 100vw, 1520px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265780" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>In all fairness, it&#8217;s not just Bitcoin. The entire market seems unable to produce any volatility with certain exceptions.</p>
<h2>RollBit Coin (RLB) Leads Altcoins With Massive Surge</h2>
<p>The major news throughout the past couple of days is the performance of RLB &#8211; the native cryptocurrency of the crypto casino RollBit.</p>
<p>RollBit came to prominence a few months ago, with many popular crypto-oriented influencers promoting it heavily.</p>
<p>The native cryptocurrency of the platform recently exploded following news that RollBit will be burning a considerable portion of it. This created additional hype that drove its price higher amid an otherwise stagnating market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265781" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265781" style="width: 1481px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265781" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231" width="1481" height="753" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231.jpg 1481w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231-300x153.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231-1024x521.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231-768x390.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_1108231-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1481px) 100vw, 1481px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265781" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>Elsewhere, as seen in the heatmap above, most of the major altcoins have failed to chart any considerable gains. Shiba Inu (SHIB) is one of the exceptions as its rally continues. The coin is up 4% on the day and it shows little signs of slowing down.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stagnant-above-29k-as-rlb-skyrockets-to-0-2-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Stagnant Above $29K as RLB Skyrockets to $0.2 (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
