<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:41:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Keiser: Ripple is a Ponzi Scheme, SEC Will Kill XRP</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/keiser-ripple-is-a-ponzi-scheme-sec-will-kill-xrp/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256969</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/keiser.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/keiser.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Max Keiser took the opportunity to once again bash Ripple. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent Bitcoin proponent and permabull Max Keiser has taken to Twitter to bash Ripple once again.</p>
<ul>
<li>Keiser, who&#8217;s also El Salvador&#8217;s President Bitcoin advisor, openly bashed Ripple, its CEO Brad Garlinghouse, and the company&#8217;s native cryptocurrency &#8211; XRP.</li>
<li>He admitted that the US Securities and Exchange Commission is overreaching, but he&#8217;s also of the opinion that this &#8220;won&#8217;t stop them from killing off XRP and every other shitcoin.&#8221;</li>
<li>The only exception, according to Keiser, is Bitcoin.</li>
<li>Going forward, he also said that:</li>
</ul>
<p>&#8220;&#8230; there&#8217;s virtually no rule of law whatsoever in Wall St/finance for those with $ and clout. Brad Garlinghouse has been spending a lot to keep his Ponzi scheme going, but he can&#8217;t outspend the Feds &amp; Jamie Dimon.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a matter of when, not if when XRP gets cut down.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Of course the SEC is ‘overreaching’ but that won’t stop them from killing off XRP and every other shitcoin. (Except BTC, of course. It’s untouchable).</p>
<p>Because there is virtually no rule of law whatsoever in Wall St/finance for those with $ and clout. Brad Garlinghouse has been… <a href="https://t.co/NwH9sH6qk8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/NwH9sH6qk8</a></p>
<p>— Max Keiser, sr. bitcoin advisor pres. Bukele <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f30b.png" alt="🌋" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9e2.png" alt="🧢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@maxkeiser) <a href="https://twitter.com/maxkeiser/status/1672228492765741056?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/keiser-ripple-is-a-ponzi-scheme-sec-will-kill-xrp/" rel="nofollow">Keiser: Ripple is a Ponzi Scheme, SEC Will Kill XRP</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 Crypto Presales to Watch Next Week</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/5-crypto-presales-to-watch-next-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256954</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/presales_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/presales_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, crypto presales have emerged as a lucrative venture for savvy investors. However, with so many tokens slated to debut each week, it can be challenging to identify those with true potential. In this article, we simplify this task for investors by exploring the top five crypto presales set [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, crypto presales have emerged as a lucrative venture for savvy investors.</p>
<p>However, with so many tokens slated to debut each week, it can be challenging to identify those with true potential.</p>
<p>In this article, we simplify this task for investors by exploring the top five crypto presales set to shake up the market next week.</p>
<h2>1. Wall Street Memes (WSM)</h2>
<p>First up is Wall Street Memes (WSM) – a new meme coin that aims to &#8220;tokenize&#8221; a colossal community inspired by Reddit&#8217;s triumph over Wall Street in January 2021.</p>
<p>This meme coin, called WSM, will allow holders to benefit financially from the community’s continued growth, with over 1.1 million “degens” already spread across various social media channels.</p>
<p>The community revolves around hilarious memes based on investing in crypto and stocks – although the Wall Street Memes team has previously tasted market success through the launch of the <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT collection</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256961" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-18.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="360" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-18-300x179.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-18-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This collection sold out in 32 minutes in 2021 and raised a staggering $2.5 million for the creators.</p>
<p>The previous success of Wall Street Memes&#8217; team has led many to speculate that this meme coin could be one of the breakout stars in the latter half of 2023.</p>
<p>Early-bird investors can purchase WSM tokens through the ongoing presale, which is inching closer to the $10 million funding milestone.</p>
<p>With tokens priced at just $0.0301, many believe now is the ideal time to get involved before the price takes off upon CEX listings later this year.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>2. yPredict (YPRED)</h2>
<p>Another crypto presale that investors may wish to watch next week is yPredict (YPRED).</p>
<p>yPredict is a brand-new platform that aims to provide traders with data-driven insights to improve their market performance.</p>
<p>The yPredict ecosystem leverages the considerable power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) technology to provide these insights, ensuring all information is objective and relevant.</p>
<p>Importantly, yPredict is built on the Polygon network, which offers high scalability and low fees.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-22.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256960" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-22.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="237" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-22.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-22-300x118.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-22-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Not only that, but the platform uses a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) model, meaning YPRED holders have a real say in how the project operates.</p>
<p>Per yPredict’s <a href="https://docs.ypredict.ai/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the total supply of YPRED will be capped at 100 million, although 80 million of these tokens have been set aside for presale investors.</p>
<p>The presale is currently in Stage 6 out of 8, meaning early investors can purchase YPRED for just $0.09, which is 33% lower than the planned CEX listing price.</p>
<p>Given yPredict’s innovative use of AI and ML technologies, it’s no surprise that the project has already raised over $2.5 million in funding – and counting.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>3. Ecoterra (ECOTERRA)</h2>
<p>Ecoterra (ECOTERRA) is a crypto project that aims to solve climate change issues using blockchain technology.</p>
<p>The project’s creators have developed an innovative Recycle2Earn mobile app, which rewards users for recycling unwanted clothing items and used materials.</p>
<p>Rewards are paid out in ECOTERRA – Ecoterra’s native ERC-20 token.</p>
<p>Alongside the Recycle2Earn app, Ecoterra’s ecosystem will also feature a carbon offset marketplace, a recycled materials marketplace, and a trackable “Impact Profile” for each user.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256959" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-18.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-18-300x99.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-18-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Combining all these features has created a massive buzz around Ecoterra&#8217;s future, leading to over 6,500 people joining the project&#8217;s <a href="https://t.me/ecoterraio" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a>.</p>
<p>Also, since Ecoterra is being developed by people with extensive experience in the European recycling sector, it harnesses industry-specific expertise to tackle challenges pragmatically.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, Ecoterra’s ongoing presale has amassed over $5.3 million in funding, with investors able to purchase ECOTERRA tokens for just $0.00925.</p>
<p>However, only one stage is left before the presale concludes, so interested investors must act quickly to secure ECOTERRA at a below-market rate.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>4. Launchpad XYZ (LPX)</h2>
<p>Launchpad XYZ (LPX) is an Ethereum-based crypto project that aims to simplify the process of investing in Web3 technologies for retail investors.</p>
<p>The Launchpad XYZ team has developed an all-in-one hub that provides the tools and services investors require to navigate the ever-evolving world of Web3.</p>
<p>Some of Launchpad XYZ’s most exciting features include a super-fast trading terminal, a play-to-earn (P2E) game library, a metaverse experience hub, and even an NFT decentralized exchange (DEX).</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-9.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256958" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-9.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="229" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-9.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-9-300x114.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-9-50x19.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>As outlined in the project’s <a href="https://launchpad.xyz/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, Launchpad XYZ will also have a feature called the &#8220;Launchpad Quotient,&#8221; a score assigned to all assets featured on the platform.</p>
<p>This score uses hundreds of data points to showcase the future potential of an asset – making it easy for investors to identify which assets they should consider adding to their portfolio (and which they should avoid).</p>
<p>Launchpad XYZ’s presale has recently breached the $1 million milestone, with the developers gearing up for CEX listings later this year.</p>
<p>However, early-bird investors can still buy LPX, Launchpad XYZ’s native token, for just $0.0445 – 26% lower than the planned listing price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_596f215c.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong> </strong>5. DeeLance (DLANCE)</h2>
<p>Last but not least, DeeLance (DLANCE) is a cutting-edge freelancing and recruitment platform aiming to streamline the process for freelancers and clients.</p>
<p>Built on the Ethereum blockchain, the DeeLance platform incorporates various Web3 technologies to create a transparent (and cost-effective) environment for all.</p>
<p>These technologies include cryptocurrency, NFTs, and metaverse concepts – the latter of which is designed to provide a one-of-a-kind immersive experience for freelancer-client interactions.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256957" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-3.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="395" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-3-300x197.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-3-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Per DeeLance’s <a href="https://docs.deelance.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the platform will also boast a smart contract escrow system, which helps eradicate payment disputes.</p>
<p>Moreover, since payments are settled using DLANCE, the platform&#8217;s native token, freelancers can benefit from instant withdrawals – which isn&#8217;t possible with centralized platforms like Fiverr and Upwork.</p>
<p>Finally, DeeLance will even boast AI-powered chatbots for customer service and on-chain KYC to prevent bad actors, underlining its commitment to a secure, user-friendly freelancing marketplace.</p>
<p>DeeLance’s presale is still in progress and has raised over $1.4 million thus far – with prospective investors able to buy DLANCE tokens for just $0.038 during the current stage.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_3bcb6414.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit DeeLance Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-crypto-presales-to-watch-next-week/" rel="nofollow">5 Crypto Presales to Watch Next Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Bulls Aim at $2K But is a Retest of $1.8K Coming First? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-bulls-aim-at-2k-but-is-a-retest-of-1-8k-coming-first-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256941</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price recently received support at the 200-day moving average and subsequently embarked on a strong bullish rally, breaking above the 100-day MA. This could be a positive indicator for Ethereum&#8217;s mid-term prospects, but it also carries the risk of being a bull trap. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart After a period of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price recently received support at the 200-day moving average and subsequently embarked on a strong bullish rally, breaking above the 100-day MA. This could be a positive indicator for Ethereum&#8217;s mid-term prospects, but it also carries the risk of being a bull trap.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>After a period of correction and a significant downtrend, the price reached the $1.6K level, which coincided with the 200-day moving average and found support. The significant buying pressure at this level triggered a rapid reversal and an upward trend toward the critical resistance zone around $2K.</p>
<p>Additionally, the price surpassed the 100-day moving average at $1.8K, suggesting a bullish bias for Ethereum in the mid-term. However, to confirm the presence of a bull market in 2023 and restore sufficient demand to the market, Ethereum&#8217;s price still needs to overcome the substantial resistance at the $2K region and consolidate above.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256938" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256938" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256938 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2506231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256938" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>In general, the Fibonacci retracement tool is helpful for identifying potential reversal points and correction targets during impulsive trends. As previously mentioned, Ethereum&#8217;s price experienced a mid-term correction phase after reaching the yearly high of $2.1K through an impulsive uptrend.</p>
<p>Examining the chart reveals that the bearish correction leg found support and reversed at the 61.8% retracement level, a commonly observed target for correction phases. The prevailing buying pressure within this critical range resulted in a robust bullish trend towards the $2K region.</p>
<p>If the price successfully surpasses the significant resistance around $2K, it will pave the way for a mid-term bullish trend, as this level holds psychological significance. However, it is worth considering the bearish divergence between the price and the RSI indicator, which suggests the possibility of a slight rejection and short-term consolidation before Ethereum makes its next move.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256937" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256937" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256937 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2506232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-5-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256937" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>Ethereum has been consolidating below the $2K level for the past few months after being rejected from that level. The uncertainty seen on the price chart is also reflected in the futures market sentiment.</p>
<p>This chart displays the Funding Rates metric, which indicates whether the futures market sentiment is bullish or bearish. Recently, after a period of correction in the market, which coincided with a downtrend in the funding rates metric, the price found support and began a strong rally.</p>
<p>However, the metric has started to show a slight uptrend during this bullish rally, suggesting increased buying pressure and a greater tendency among participants to take long positions rather than short positions.</p>
<p>While this could be seen as a bullish sign for the market, traders should exercise caution as it may actually be a bull trap, potentially leading to a long-squeeze event.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256939" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256939" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256939 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_funding_rates_chart_2506231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Funding-Rates-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256939" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-bulls-aim-at-2k-but-is-a-retest-of-1-8k-coming-first-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Bulls Aim at $2K But is a Retest of $1.8K Coming First? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Consolidates Around $0.5, Calm Before the Storm? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-consolidates-around-0-5-calm-before-the-storm-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256931</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price has remained stagnant and lacks bullish momentum, as it has been in a consolidation phase for several months. The situation is similar when trading against Bitcoin. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: Ripple&#8217;s price faced strong rejection at the $0.6 resistance zone a few weeks ago. Currently, the cryptocurrency is finding support at [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price has remained stagnant and lacks bullish momentum, as it has been in a consolidation phase for several months. The situation is similar when trading against Bitcoin.</p>
<h2><strong>Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s price faced strong rejection at the $0.6 resistance zone a few weeks ago. Currently, the cryptocurrency is finding support at the $0.49 level, where the 50-day moving average is located.</p>
<p>If this level is breached, the next targets would be the $0.43 resistance and the 200-day moving average around the same price. Rebounding from this area would be likely.</p>
<p>However, if these support levels are unable to hold, Ripple&#8217;s price could experience a significant decline, potentially dropping towards $0.3 and even lower within a short timeframe.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256936" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256936" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256936 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2506231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-25-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256936" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Against BTC, it becomes apparent that Ripple&#8217;s price has experienced a sharp decline after failing to maintain its position above the 2000SAT level. Currently, the market is approaching a crucial support area at 1600 SAT, accompanied by an oversold signal from the RSI indicator.</p>
<p>As a result, a potential short-term rebound is seemingly likely. However, for investors to regain confidence in the price trajectory, XRP must surpass the 1800 SAT resistance level, as well as the convergence of the 50-day and 200-day moving averages around that point.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256935" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256935" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-256935 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2506232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-25-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256935" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-consolidates-around-0-5-calm-before-the-storm-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Consolidates Around $0.5, Calm Before the Storm? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CryptoPunks NFT Collection Turns Six: Here&#8217;s the Journey So Far</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cryptopunks-nft-collection-turns-six-heres-the-journey-so-far/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CryptoPunks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256917</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cryptopunks_featured_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/cryptopunks_featured_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Yuga Labs plans to publish a CryptoPunks book to celebrate the project’s sixth birthday. 
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CryptoPunks, one of the first non-fungible token (NFT) collections on the Ethereum blockchain, has reached a significant milestone as it celebrates its sixth anniversary.</p>
<p>Since its launch in June 2017, CryptoPunks has captivated the world with its 10,000 digital collectibles, leaving an indelible mark on the NFT realm as the largest NFT collection by market cap.</p>
<p>According to data compiled by blockchain analytics firm Nansen, CryptoPunks currently has an estimated market cap of over 806,801 ETH, worth more than $1.53 billion.</p>
<h2>The Journey So Far</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/nansen_ai/status/1672234941739048960" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet thread</a>, Nansen explained that CryptoPunks had a &#8220;humble beginning&#8221; on June 23, 2017, when only 287 wallets claimed the digital collectibles for free as soon as they were released. Canadian software developers Matt Hall and John Watkinson comprised the two-person team from Larva Labs studio, which launched the collection.</p>
<p>By the end of the launch date, 291 unique wallets had CryptoPunks after the first claimers had sold some of the assets. A week later, the NFTs reached an average price of 0.5 ETH with a volume of 124 ETH. Ether was worth $300 at the time.</p>
<p>Nearly a year later, in April 2018, fewer than 500 unique wallets held CryptoPunks, and by November 2020, the number had grown to 1,000. The growth could be linked to the emergence of wrapped punks in September 2020.</p>
<p>Wrapped punks are ERC-721 NFTs, backed by original ERC-20 punks, and tradeable on marketplaces like OpenSea and Rarible. To date, 770 punks are still wrapped, and the contract is the largest punk holder, followed by NFT company Yuga Labs with 422 punks.</p>
<h2>The Most Expensive CryptoPunk Transaction</h2>
<p>In 2021, the value of CryptoPunks rapidly surged alongside the number of new collectors. While wallets holding at least one punk reached 3693, the prices of the collectibles, particularly those with rare attributes like alien and ape, soared.</p>
<p>By February 18, 2021, CryptoPunks reached a weekly volume of 24,969 ETH ($48 million). On the same date, punk #4156 was sold for 650 ETH ($1.25 million), marking the first time a collectible was sold for more than a million dollars.</p>
<p>The most extraordinary CryptoPunk transaction happened a year later when punk #5822 was sold for 8,000 ETH ($23.7 million), making it the most expensive punk to date.</p>
<h2>Yuga Labs to Publish CryptoPunks Book</h2>
<p>In commemoration of the sixth anniversary, Yuga Labs, the owner of CryptoPunks, has <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/yuga-labs-joins-forces-with-zak-group-to-publish-first-of-its-kind-book-of-cryptopunks-301860752.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">partnered</a> with Zak Group to publish official documentation of the NFT collection in a first-of-its-kind book.</p>
<p>The catalog will bring to life the untold stories of the collection, detailing every punk, pixel by pixel.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptopunks-nft-collection-turns-six-heres-the-journey-so-far/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPunks NFT Collection Turns Six: Here&#8217;s the Journey So Far</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man Involved in Twitter’s Infamous 2020 Hack Bags Five Years Jail Term for Crypto Theft</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/man-involved-in-twitters-infamous-2020-hack-bags-five-years-jail-term-for-crypto-theft/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256915</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In addition to O’Connor’s prison term, he was sentenced to three years of supervised release and ordered to pay a forfeiture of $794,000. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joseph James O’Connor, a U.K. citizen and one of the perpetrators of the 2020 Twitter hack, has been sentenced to five years in prison for his role in several cybercrime offenses.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/uk-citizen-sentenced-five-years-prison-cybercrime-offenses" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> by the United States Attorney’s Office for the Southern District of New York, Judge Jed S. Rakoff sentenced O’Connor for two sets of charges: conspiracy to commit computer hacking and the theft of cryptocurrencies via a SIM swap attack; his role in the 2020 Twitter hack, cyberstalking two separate victims, and computer intrusions related to takeovers of TikTok and Snapchat user accounts.</p>
<h2>O’Connor Lands Five-Year Jail Term</h2>
<p>The 24-year-old convict was extradited from Spain on April 26, 2023, and he pled guilty to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/man-behind-twitters-infamous-2020-hack-charged-with-crypto-theft-worth-784000/" data-wpel-link="internal">charges</a> brought against him on May 9, 2023. He was faced with a 20-year jail term or more.</p>
<p>Among his offenses, O’Connor used a SIM swap attack to steal bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), and Litecoin (LTC) worth $794,000 at the time from three executives in a Manhattan-based crypto company. The fraudulent scheme lasted from March to May 2019. The stolen assets are currently worth more than $1.6 million, and O’Connor, alongside his co-conspirators, laundered them through several crypto exchange accounts.</p>
<p>In addition, O’Connor participated in a range of crimes associated with exploiting TikTok and Snapchat accounts, online extortion, and cyberstalking between 2019 and 2020. On one occasion, O’Connor and his accomplices obtained unauthorized access to a public figure’s TikTok account with millions of followers and posted self-promotional messages, threatening to release sensitive materials to a designated group of individuals.</p>
<h2>O’Connor’s Role in the 2020 Twitter Hack</h2>
<p>Furthermore, O’Connor participated in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/breaking-scam-alert-binance-coinbase-and-other-major-crypto-twitter-accounts-hacked/" data-wpel-link="internal">a massive 2020 Twitter hack</a> that saw the accounts of top politicians and celebrities breached. Some victims include U.S. President Joe Biden, former President Barack Obama, Tesla CEO Elon Musk, and Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos.</p>
<p>Twitter accounts of major crypto companies and personalities like Binance, Bitfinex, Coinbase, Changpeng Zhao, and Justin Sun were affected. O’Connor and his cohorts also amassed over $118,000 in crypto through tweets about fake giveaways.</p>
<p>In addition to O’Connor’s prison term, he was sentenced to three years of supervised release and ordered to pay a forfeiture of $794,000.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, O’Connor’s partner and teenage mastermind of the Twitter hack, Graham Ivan Clark, is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-hacker-gets-a-three-year-sentence-after-pleading-guilty/" data-wpel-link="internal">serving</a> a three-year jail sentence in a juvenile prison after pleading guilty in March 2021.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/man-involved-in-twitters-infamous-2020-hack-bags-five-years-jail-term-for-crypto-theft/" rel="nofollow">Man Involved in Twitter’s Infamous 2020 Hack Bags Five Years Jail Term for Crypto Theft</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>AAVE Explodes 25% Daily, ETH Pushes Above $1.9K (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aave-explodes-25-daily-eth-pushes-above-1-9k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 07:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256907</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AAVE_BTC_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/AAVE_BTC_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market remains relatively calm during the weekend but AAVE makes an exception. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has managed to maintain positive momentum going into the weekend, with the majority of coins holding their gains through the diminished volatility and trading volume.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Fighting for $31K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price pushed above $31K on Friday but was unable to maintain above that level. It subsequently retraced, but it appears that bulls are now preparing for another attempt.</p>
<p>The price is up slightly over the past 24 hours and is trading slightly below $31K as seen in the chart below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256908" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256908" style="width: 1183px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-256908" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22.png" alt="BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22" width="1183" height="434" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22.png 1183w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22-300x110.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22-1024x376.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22-768x282.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT_2023-06-25_10-26-22-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1183px) 100vw, 1183px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256908" class="wp-caption-text">Source_ TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s also apparent that Bitcoin is consolidating through the past couple of days, following the major move toward $30K and $31K, respectively. This could suggest that there&#8217;s another period of volatility coming.</p>
<h2>AAVE Explodes 25% Daily</h2>
<p>The majority of the altcoin market has remained relatively flat throughout the day, charting either slight gains or slight declines but nothing too serious, as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_256909" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-256909" style="width: 1491px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-256909" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231" width="1491" height="783" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231.jpg 1491w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231-300x158.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231-1024x538.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231-768x403.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cryptocurrency_heatmap_2506231-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1491px) 100vw, 1491px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-256909" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>Of course, there are some exceptions. The most notable one is AAVE, which exploded by over 25% throughout the past 24 hours. This move also brings the cryptocurrency&#8217;s total weekly gains above 40%, making it one of the best performers altogether.</p>
<p>Synthetix Network (SNX) is also doing brilliantly. It&#8217;s up by almost 20% during the day and 25% during the week.</p>
<p>On the other end of the spectrum, Kaspa (KAS) is trading for a 5% loss, followed by Render (RNDR), which is down 4% for the day.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth mentioning that Ethereum is pushing above $1.9K and it is seemingly up against the crucial technical and psychological level of $2K.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aave-explodes-25-daily-eth-pushes-above-1-9k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">AAVE Explodes 25% Daily, ETH Pushes Above $1.9K (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mercado Bitcoin to Support Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Efforts (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mercado-bitcoin-to-support-brazils-cbdc-efforts-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 07:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256844</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Brazil.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Brazil.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Mercado Bitcoin joined the likes of Mastercard and Sinqia on the CBDC initiative. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mercado Bitcoin &#8211; the largest cryptocurrency exchange in Brazil &#8211; will reportedly participate in the country&#8217;s pilot project to launch a digital real.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The central bank intends to issue such a financial product in 2024.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The List of Contributors</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <a href="https://valor.globo.com/financas/criptomoedas/noticia/2023/06/22/bc-reabilita-consrcio-do-mercado-bitcoin-no-piloto-do-real-digital.ghtml" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by a local media outlet, Banco Central do Brasil has authorized Mercado Bitcoin to take part in the CBDC development. Speaking on the matter was Fabricio Tota &#8211; director of new business at the exchange:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our participation validates the Central Bank&#8217;s intention to bring innovation to the financial system with those who had already been working with this technology and not just with the incumbents who appropriated it.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other project participants include well-known companies such as the payment processing giant Mastercard, the financial software fintech Sinqia, brokerage firm Genial, and others.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brazil&#8217;s central bank has previously outlined that only regulated financial institutions with direct access to the National Financial System (SFN) network can assist the CBDC efforts.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The consortium intends to participate in all aspects of the test, including wholesale, retail, and National Treasury securities negotiations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The central bank </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazil-begins-cbdc-pilot-with-public-use-scheduled-for-2024-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">aims</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to release a CBDC next year. According to the initial plan, the monetary product will be a blockchain-based instrument that supports retail transactions and is backed by customer bank deposits. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This could reduce the cost of credit, the cost of improving the return on investments. There is a great potential for new service providers, fintechs, democratizing access to the market and offering new services,&#8221; Fabio Araujo &#8211; the coordinator of the CBDC project &#8211; added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Additional Crypto Jurisdiction for the Central Bank</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides being responsible for issuing a digital real, Brazil&#8217;s central bank was recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazils-president-empowers-the-central-bank-as-crypto-regulator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">assigned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> as the country&#8217;s crypto regulator. The legislation, signed by President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, became official on June 20.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the rules, local companies can not provide crypto services without obtaining approval from the financial institution. The bank will also monitor if organizations abide by anti-money laundering procedures and whether they are linked to criminal activities, including financing terrorism.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brazil&#8217;s SEC will play a role in the regulatory process, too. It will partner with Banco do Brasil to supervise digital currencies classified as securities. It is worth mentioning that current domestic law does not designate which assets fit in that category and which are seen as commodities. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mercado-bitcoin-to-support-brazils-cbdc-efforts-report/" rel="nofollow">Mercado Bitcoin to Support Brazil&#8217;s CBDC Efforts (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin As It Hits $10M in Presale?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/could-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin-as-it-hits-10m-in-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 22:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256880</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_cash_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_cash_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Amid the recent meme coin surge that saw the likes of Pepe gain more than 7,000%, new meme crypto Wall Street Memes (WSM) has stepped into the limelight. Over the past month, when most cryptos tanked amid market uncertainty, Wall Street Memes has raised over $10 million during its presale. This highlighted the project&#8217;s potential [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the recent meme coin surge that saw the likes of Pepe gain more than 7,000%, new meme crypto Wall Street Memes (WSM) has stepped into the limelight.</p>
<p>Over the past month, when most cryptos tanked amid market uncertainty, <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> has raised over $10 million during its presale.</p>
<p>This highlighted the project&#8217;s potential and the strong support it enjoys from its community, which has a million followers across various social media platforms.</p>
<p>The token has been developed from the same creators of the Wall St Bulls NFT collection, which quickly <a href="https://thedalesreport.com/crypto-nfts/wall-street-bulls-nft-collection-sells-out-in-half-an-hour/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">sold out within 32 minutes after its launch</a> on Ethereum.</p>
<p>The team&#8217;s understanding of crypto trends has only improved since then, leading to the successful launch of the Bitcoin Ordinals NFTs and, now, the <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> meme coin. This aligns quite well with the market&#8217;s current inclination toward meme coins.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes whitepaper highlights that the token aims to merge memes with blockchain to disrupt the modern financial landscape through the power of community.</p>
<p>The project believes memes can connect people, inspire new ideas, and question established norms. Leveraging the power of decentralization, Wall Street Memes aims to create a movement designed to return control to its rightful owners &#8211; the people.</p>
<h2><strong>Wall Street Memes: Community-Backed Meme Token That Has Already Raised $10 Million</strong></h2>
<p>In the initial day following the commencement of the project, the WSM token raised more than $300k, and just four weeks since launch it has now attracted over $10 million, showing significant interest from investors.</p>
<p>Given its current expansion rate and strong financial backing, the WSM token could become an attractive option for large crypto exchanges, including leading platforms.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-256881" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="695" height="349" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24.jpg 695w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-24-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></a></p>
<p>WSM token is presently in the presale stage, priced at $0.0301 during stage 18 of 30. While inherently risky, presales yield substantial returns, particularly when a robust community supports the project.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes has a solid community base of a million followers spread across various social media platforms, reaffirming the token&#8217;s strong support and potential.</p>
<h2><strong>Why Should Buyers Consider WSM?</strong></h2>
<p>Apart from a thriving community, the platform has also caught the attention of influential figures like Elon Musk, who has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1636924379086077954" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">engaged with Wall Street Memes’ tweets</a> on multiple occasions.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s well-known how Musk&#8217;s tweets have previously caused the price of meme coins like Dogecoin to spike massively and his engagement with the platform could turn out well for WSM, helping the coin gain even more followers.</p>
<p>The WSM token&#8217;s distribution underlines the project&#8217;s community-centric approach. Of the capped supply of 2 billion tokens, 50% has been allocated for the presale, 30% for community rewards, and 20% for exchange liquidity.</p>
<p>Notably, no allocation has been made for the team, indicating the project&#8217;s transparency and commitment towards ensuring a &#8216;rug pull&#8217; scenario is off the table.</p>
<p>Moreover, Wall Street Memes has announced a <a href="https://t.me/jd1234_d" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">massive airdrop</a> for presale investors. By participating in the project’s social media channels and completing simple tasks, five lucky winners will stand a chance to win $50,000 worth of WSM tokens.</p>
<h2><strong>The Strategic Growth and Potential of Wall Street Memes</strong></h2>
<p>The Wall Street Memes project sets an ambitious target, aiming to disrupt the traditional financial landscape and democratize investing through the power of memes.</p>
<p>A clear roadmap has been set to achieve this, with the journey divided into three parts: Foundation, Launch, and Community Empowerment.</p>
<p>The WSM token&#8217;s growth roadmap comprises three phases &#8211; phase one establishes a strong community and a secure smart contract, alongside initiating a branding campaign.</p>
<p>Phase two involves the WSM token&#8217;s launch, strategic partnerships, and listings on multiple exchanges. The final phase targets community empowerment and seeking listings on top-tier exchanges.</p>
<p>Also, many analysts point out that a dedicated, vibrant community, a strong brand, and a timely entry into the meme coin market make WSM a potential <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDbEfCiPYy4" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">next huge meme crypto</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/could-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin-as-it-hits-10m-in-presale/" rel="nofollow">Could Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin As It Hits $10M in Presale?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Doubles Down on AI by Investing $100 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-doubles-down-on-ai-by-investing-100-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=256781</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/amazon1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ai is going to be "the next big thing that pushes even more customers to want to be in the cloud," CEO Selipsky forecasted.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amazon Web Services (AWS) &#8211; the cloud unit of the e-commerce giant &#8211; said it will distribute $100 million for a center to help entities employ generative artificial intelligence (AI). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Microsoft and Google &#8211; two other giant corporations &#8211; have made even bigger investments in AI. </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">AWS&#8217; CEO Adam Selipsky revealed the plans in a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/22/aws-invests-100-million-in-generative-ai-as-it-sees-a-long-race-ahead.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for CNBC, showing that the company realizes the potential of the new technology:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;You ask yourself the question — where are the different runners three steps into a 10K race? Does it really matter? The point is, you&#8217;re three steps in, and it&#8217;s a 10K race.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exec explained that the new feature will not function as a physical center but rather as a &#8220;program.&#8221; He added that RyanAir, Lonely Planet, Highspot, and Twilio have already jumped on board.</span></li>
<li>Selipsky sees an optimistic future for artificial intelligence, calling it &#8220;the next wave of innovation in the cloud.&#8221; According to him, it will be &#8220;the next big thing&#8221; that pushes clients to want to be in the cloud.</li>
<li>Amazon has already hopped on the AI bandwagon by introducing the virtual assistant technology Alexa. However, those efforts and the upcoming $100 million investment are no match for what other leading corporations have done.</li>
<li>The multinational tech giant &#8211; Microsoft &#8211; <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-23/microsoft-makes-multibillion-dollar-investment-in-openai" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">distributed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $10 billion into OpenAI several months ago. This has been the third investment into the AI startup, with the previous made in 2019 and 2021. </span></li>
<li>Shortly after, Google <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.ft.com/content/583ead66-467c-4bd5-84d0-ed5df7b5bf9c" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">invested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $300 million in Anthropic. Formed in 2021 by former members of OpenAI, the latter is an artificial intelligence safety and research company based in San Francisco.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-doubles-down-on-ai-by-investing-100-million/" rel="nofollow">Amazon Doubles Down on AI by Investing $100 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
