<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:49:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Pepe Price Falls 15% In 7 Days -  Smart Money Is Turning To Wall Street Memes As New Top Gainer For 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-falls-15-in-7-days-smart-money-is-turning-to-wall-street-memes-as-new-top-gainer-for-2023.htm</link><description>In the volatile world of cryptocurrency, Pepe has experienced a significant decline of 15% over the past seven days.  &lt;br /&gt;
As investors seek alternative options, a new frontrunner has emerged in the form of Wall Street Memes.  &lt;br /&gt;
With its innovative approach and potential for substantial gains, Wall Street Memes is capturing the attention of smart money investors, positioning itself as a top contender for the year 2023. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-falls-15-in-7-days-smart-money-is-turning-to-wall-street-memes-as-new-top-gainer-for-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Price Falls 15% In 7 Days -  Smart Money Is Turning To Wall Street Memes As New Top Gainer For 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-falls-15-in-7-days-smart-money-is-turning-to-wall-street-memes-as-new-top-gainer-for-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115177/277809/pepe.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="335209"/></item><item><title>FLOKI Price Prediction - 400% Volume Rise as FLOKI Featured On China's CCTV-5, Can It Flip Pepe?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/floki-inu-price-prediction-400-volume-spike-as-floki-featured-on-chinas-cctv-5-channel-can-it-flip-pepe.htm</link><description>The Floki price spiked double digits this weekend following the meme token appearing on Chinese television, on a 'powered by Floki.com' billboard for the World Table Tennis Championships. Could it overtake Pepe? &lt;br /&gt;
Sun Yingsha defeated Olympic champion Chen Meng 4-2 on Sunday, May 28th....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/floki-inu-price-prediction-400-volume-spike-as-floki-featured-on-chinas-cctv-5-channel-can-it-flip-pepe.htm"&gt;Read More: FLOKI Price Prediction - 400% Volume Rise as FLOKI Featured On China's CCTV-5, Can It Flip Pepe?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 20:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/floki-inu-price-prediction-400-volume-spike-as-floki-featured-on-chinas-cctv-5-channel-can-it-flip-pepe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115180/277810/floki-crypto-billboard-ch.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="630630"/></item><item><title>Chinese Healthcare, Energy Firms Enable CBDC Pay – Digital Yuan Adoption Accelerating?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-healthcare-energy-firms-enable-cbdc-pay-digital-yuan-adoption-accelerating.htm</link><description>Chinese healthcare and energy sector providers will allow patients and customers to pay with the digital yuan, in new breakthroughs for the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Chinese media outlet WXRB, both outpatients and hospitalized mental healthcare patients can now use the CBDC to pay for medical treatment. &lt;br /&gt;
Deposits, medication, and hospitalization fees can be paid via the central bank’s digital yuan app, WXRB explained....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-healthcare-energy-firms-enable-cbdc-pay-digital-yuan-adoption-accelerating.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Healthcare, Energy Firms Enable CBDC Pay – Digital Yuan Adoption Accelerating?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-healthcare-energy-firms-enable-cbdc-pay-digital-yuan-adoption-accelerating.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115173/277801/china-2805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="371761"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Coin Gains 3% in 24 Hours – Will US Debt Ceiling Deal Propel SHIB to $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-coin-gains-3-24-hours-will-us-debt-ceiling-deal-propel-shib-1.htm</link><description>As Shiba gains 3% within 24 hours, predictions for its price are being made. Many speculate whether the potential US debt ceiling deal will drive SHIB to reach $1.  &lt;br /&gt;
Let's explore the factors influencing the price movement of Shiba Inu and the possible implications of the debt ceiling deal on its future value....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-coin-gains-3-24-hours-will-us-debt-ceiling-deal-propel-shib-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Coin Gains 3% in 24 Hours – Will US Debt Ceiling Deal Propel SHIB to $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-coin-gains-3-24-hours-will-us-debt-ceiling-deal-propel-shib-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115162/277807/shiba-inu.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="288107"/></item><item><title>Beijing Unveils 'Web3 White Paper' to Foster Innovation and Advancing the Industry</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/beijing-unveils-web3-white-paper-foster-innovation-advancing-industry.htm</link><description>The Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission has released a white paper in a bid to foster innovation and development within the Web3 industry. &lt;br /&gt;
Dubbed the "Web3 Innovation and Development White Paper," the paper was unveiled at the Zhongguancun Forum by the Beijing Municipal Science and Technology Commission, also known as the Administrative Commission of Zhongguancun Science Park, local news outlet The Paper reported. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/beijing-unveils-web3-white-paper-foster-innovation-advancing-industry.htm"&gt;Read More: Beijing Unveils 'Web3 White Paper' to Foster Innovation and Advancing the Industry&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Web3</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Hong Kong</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/beijing-unveils-web3-white-paper-foster-innovation-advancing-industry.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115170/277799/china-blockchain-media-li.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="204828"/></item><item><title>XRP to Exceed All Expectations In 2023? Latest New Value Report Boosts Altcoin Forecast 100x</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-exceed-all-expectations-2023-latest-new-value-report-boosts-altcoin-forecast-100x-1.htm</link><description>Ripple's 2023 New Value Report reveals strong and widespread excitement regarding the potential of cryptocurrencies despite regulatory issues between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and many crypto firms, including Ripple.  &lt;br /&gt;
The report noted that more than 70% of global finance leaders emphasized an increase in their confidence in the crypto industry over the past six months. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-exceed-all-expectations-2023-latest-new-value-report-boosts-altcoin-forecast-100x-1.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP to Exceed All Expectations In 2023? Latest New Value Report Boosts Altcoin Forecast 100x&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-exceed-all-expectations-2023-latest-new-value-report-boosts-altcoin-forecast-100x-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115165/277765/6df92d13-4d58-4b64-8385-0.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="89489"/></item><item><title>Web3 Freelancing Metaverse DeeLance Makes History: Secures Massive $1.12 Million Investment from Prominent VC Firm as Public Presale Exceeds $1.1 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-metaverse-deelance-makes-history-secures-massive-112-million-investment-from-prominent-vc-firm-as-public-presale-exceeds-11-million.htm</link><description>Groundbreaking web3 freelancing and remote work metaverse platform DeeLance just secured a massive strategic investment from a top venture capital (VC) investment firm. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitgert Ventures will invest $1.12 million in DeeLance to help fund the development of its blockchain-powered metaverse, which is already generating huge hype in web3 circles and some observers think could upend the still very web2 platform-centric freelance/gig work economy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-metaverse-deelance-makes-history-secures-massive-112-million-investment-from-prominent-vc-firm-as-public-presale-exceeds-11-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 Freelancing Metaverse DeeLance Makes History: Secures Massive $1.12 Million Investment from Prominent VC Firm as Public Presale Exceeds $1.1 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>ICO news</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-metaverse-deelance-makes-history-secures-massive-112-million-investment-from-prominent-vc-firm-as-public-presale-exceeds-11-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115160/277749/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="270514"/></item><item><title>HK Police Launch CyberDefender to Help Protect Citizens in the Metaverse</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hk-police-launch-cyberdefender-help-protect-citizens-metaverse.htm</link><description>The Hong Kong Police Force has launched CyberDefender, a new metaverse platform aimed at educating the public about the potential dangers associated with Web3 and the metaverse.  &lt;br /&gt;
The platform, developed by the Cyber Security and Technology Crime Bureau (CSTCB), was created to prepare Hong Kong citizens for the challenges ahead in the digital age, with a focus on technology crime prevention, the government said in a recent statement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hk-police-launch-cyberdefender-help-protect-citizens-metaverse.htm"&gt;Read More: HK Police Launch CyberDefender to Help Protect Citizens in the Metaverse&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 10:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hk-police-launch-cyberdefender-help-protect-citizens-metaverse.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115158/277748/adobestock-f11photo-1-med.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="233195"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction: BTC and ETH Experience Nearly 2% Spike; Is More Upside Ahead?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-experience-nearly-2-spike-more-upside-ahead.htm</link><description>In the volatile world of cryptocurrencies, Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have recently shown a notable spike, with both digital assets experiencing a nearly 2% increase in their prices.  &lt;br /&gt;
This upward movement has left investors wondering if there is further upside potential shortly. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-experience-nearly-2-spike-more-upside-ahead.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction: BTC and ETH Experience Nearly 2% Spike; Is More Upside Ahead?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 07:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-experience-nearly-2-spike-more-upside-ahead.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115147/277742/28-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="530144"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Can SHIB Reach $1 As Trading Volume Spikes 75% To Over $100m</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-price-prediction-can-shib-reach-1-after-100m-trading-volume.htm</link><description>In addition to major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum, the cryptocurrency market is also witnessing the rise of alternative coins that show significant potential for growth.  &lt;br /&gt;
One such coin is WSM (Wall Street Memes), which has been gaining attention for its unique approach to blending finance and humor.  &lt;br /&gt;
Another notable altcoin is yPredict, a platform that leverages blockchain technology to provide accurate predictions and insights. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-price-prediction-can-shib-reach-1-after-100m-trading-volume.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction: Can SHIB Reach $1 As Trading Volume Spikes 75% To Over $100m&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-price-prediction-can-shib-reach-1-after-100m-trading-volume.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115143/277730/shiba.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="270592"/></item><item><title>Wall Street Memes Price Prediction 2023 - 2030 - $WSM Price Potential</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-price-prediction.htm</link><description>Inspired by how the little guy challenged Wall St in the GameStop short squeeze, Wall Street Memes (WSM) is one of the newest meme tokens, currently on presale....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-price-prediction.htm"&gt;Read More: Wall Street Memes Price Prediction 2023 - 2030 - $WSM Price Potential&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>ICO news</category><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-price-prediction.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115144/277727/wall-street-memes-price-p.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="155744"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price to Hit $1 While Wall St Memes to Rocket 100x in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-hit-1-while-wall-st-memes-rocket-100x-2023.htm</link><description>In 2023, the cryptocurrency market is poised for exciting developments as speculations surround the potential price movements of Dogecoin and Wall St Memes.  &lt;br /&gt;
Dogecoin, the popular meme-inspired cryptocurrency, has garnered significant attention, and discussions revolve around the possibility of its price reaching the milestone of $1.  &lt;br /&gt;
On the other hand, Wall St Memes, a rising player in the crypto space, is generating buzz with predictions of a 100x surge in its value. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-hit-1-while-wall-st-memes-rocket-100x-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price to Hit $1 While Wall St Memes to Rocket 100x in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-hit-1-while-wall-st-memes-rocket-100x-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115123/277722/doge.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="292993"/></item><item><title>Cardano's Charles Hoskinson Shares Vision For 'Cardano Summer'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardanos-hoskinson-shares-vision-for-cardano-summer.htm</link><description>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has shared an over-optimistic vision for the future of the proof-of-stake blockchain platform, claiming that it could climb to the top of the cryptocurrencies list soon.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent video, the crypto veteran talked about "Cardano Summer," claiming that the blockchain's native token ADA could surpass Bitcoin, Ethereum, and all other cryptocurrencies, thanks to a series of updates and proposals set to be released in the coming weeks. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardanos-hoskinson-shares-vision-for-cardano-summer.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano's Charles Hoskinson Shares Vision For 'Cardano Summer'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>ADA</category><category>Charles Hoskinson</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardanos-hoskinson-shares-vision-for-cardano-summer.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115132/277715/cardano-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="190344"/></item><item><title>Ecoterra, an Exciting Green Web3 Project, Partners with Prominent Brands like Coca-Cola to Expand its Recycle-to-Earn Ecosystem - Funding Reaches $4.4 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-an-exciting-green-web3-project-partners-with-prominent-brands-like-coca-cola-to-expand-its-recycle-earn-ecosystem-funding-reaches-44-million.htm</link><description>Revolutionary web3 Recycle-to-Earn (R2E) platform ecoterra just introduced a fresh batch of major beverage brands into its ecosystem, including the likes of Coca Cola, Carlsberg and Evian, further boosting the environmentally conscious protocol’s utility....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-an-exciting-green-web3-project-partners-with-prominent-brands-like-coca-cola-to-expand-its-recycle-earn-ecosystem-funding-reaches-44-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Ecoterra, an Exciting Green Web3 Project, Partners with Prominent Brands like Coca-Cola to Expand its Recycle-to-Earn Ecosystem - Funding Reaches $4.4 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>ICO news</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-an-exciting-green-web3-project-partners-with-prominent-brands-like-coca-cola-to-expand-its-recycle-earn-ecosystem-funding-reaches-44-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115163/277759/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="765725"/></item><item><title>JP Morgan Chase Files Trademark for Finance-Themed Chatbot in US</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jp-morgan-chase-files-trademark-for-finance-themed-chatbot-in-us.htm</link><description>JP Morgan Chase has filed a trademark application with the US Patent and Trademark Office for a finance-themed AI chatbot named “IndexGPT.” &lt;br /&gt;
According to the application filed earlier this month, the tool is intended to assist investors in selecting financial securities and financial assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jp-morgan-chase-files-trademark-for-finance-themed-chatbot-in-us.htm"&gt;Read More: JP Morgan Chase Files Trademark for Finance-Themed Chatbot in US&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>JPMorgan Chase</category><category>Trademark</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jp-morgan-chase-files-trademark-for-finance-themed-chatbot-in-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115118/277691/jpmorgan-media-library-or.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="67947"/></item><item><title>Useful Ambiguity, UnMixed Binance, Repealed Bail and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/useful-ambiguity-unmixed-binance-repealed-bail-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/useful-ambiguity-unmixed-binance-repealed-bail-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Useful Ambiguity, UnMixed Binance, Repealed Bail and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/useful-ambiguity-unmixed-binance-repealed-bail-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114992/277405/naiivememe-twitter-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="381820"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Completes 61.8% Fibonacci Retracement; Daily Outlook</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-completes-618-fibonacci-retracement-daily-outlook.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the world's leading cryptocurrency, has recently completed a significant milestone in its price movement as it successfully reached the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level.  &lt;br /&gt;
This retracement pattern, based on the mathematical ratios derived from the Fibonacci sequence, is often used by traders and analysts to identify potential support and resistance levels in the market. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-completes-618-fibonacci-retracement-daily-outlook.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Completes 61.8% Fibonacci Retracement; Daily Outlook&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-completes-618-fibonacci-retracement-daily-outlook.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115107/277678/27-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="528388"/></item><item><title>ecoterra Presale Adds Coca Cola, Carlsberg, Evian to Sustainable Cryptocurrency Ecosystem - $4.35 Million Raised So Far</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-presale-adds-coca-cola-carlsberg-evian-to-sustainable-cryptocurrency-ecosystem-435-million-raised-so-far.htm</link><description>Bridging the worlds of sustainability and digital currency, ecoterra has carved out a unique niche in the green Web3 sector. &lt;br /&gt;
Utilizing the potential of blockchain technology, ecoterra fosters eco-friendly practices while simultaneously highlighting the viability of sustainable cryptocurrencies. &lt;br /&gt;
The company's ongoing crypto presale has been remarkably successful, amassing a significant $4.35 million in investments....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-presale-adds-coca-cola-carlsberg-evian-to-sustainable-cryptocurrency-ecosystem-435-million-raised-so-far.htm"&gt;Read More: ecoterra Presale Adds Coca Cola, Carlsberg, Evian to Sustainable Cryptocurrency Ecosystem - $4.35 Million Raised So Far&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Sustainable Cryptocurrency</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Global Warming</category><category>Climate change</category><category>Climate Crisis</category><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ecoterra-presale-adds-coca-cola-carlsberg-evian-to-sustainable-cryptocurrency-ecosystem-435-million-raised-so-far.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115101/277657/fw58hayx0aad-vd.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="143826"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 26 May – AGIX, AXS, AI, ECOTERRA, OKB, YPRED, HT</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm</link><description>As May comes to an end, Bitcoin and Ether are struggling to gain momentum and are at risk of closing out the month lower. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin has plateaued this week and may post its first monthly loss of 2023. Ether has ticked slightly higher but could also end May down from its open. &lt;br /&gt;
Given the recent slow movements in the cryptocurrency market, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 26 May – AGIX, AXS, AI, ECOTERRA, OKB, YPRED, HT&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AGIX</category><category>AXS</category><category>AI</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>OKB</category><category>YPRED</category><category>HT</category><category>SingularityNET</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>Axie Shards</category><category>Huobi Token</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115096/277650/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>US Sen. Lummis Says President Biden Is Picking ‘Winners and Losers’ With Proposed Crypto Mining Tax</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm</link><description>The Biden administration is picking “winners and losers” in a proposal to tax cryptocurrency miners, US Sen. Cynthia Lummis said in a tweet on Thursday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Wyoming Republican called Biden’s proposed 30 percent tax a “blatant attempt by the administration to pick winners and losers.” &lt;br /&gt;
“I will not let President Biden tax the digital asset industry out of existence,” Lummis said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm"&gt;Read More: US Sen. Lummis Says President Biden Is Picking ‘Winners and Losers’ With Proposed Crypto Mining Tax&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115090/277640/cl-official-portrait-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="720776"/></item></channel></rss>
