<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:38:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mark Cuban Says the SEC Approach to Crypto Led to Billions in Losses</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mark-cuban-says-the-sec-approach-to-crypto-led-to-billions-in-losses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mark Cuban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258733</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Mark_Cuban.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Mark_Cuban.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cuban thinks the SEC should have required "the separation of customer and business funds and clear wallet requirements" to prevent investor losses.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The prominent American businessman, TV personality, investor, and owner of the Dallas Mavericks &#8211; Mark Cuban &#8211; lambasted the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for choosing &#8220;the wrong path&#8221; to regulate crypto. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes its approach has been one reason why FTX investors in America have parted with substantial sums. On the other hand, he praised the actions of the Japanese regulators, outlining that &#8220;no one in FTX Japan lost money.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cuban Goes on the Offensive</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Billionaire Mark Cuban is the latest person to bash America&#8217;s securities regulator. In one of his recent tweets, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/mcuban/status/1676258204924407808" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">blamed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it for not setting appropriate standards in the cryptocurrency industry and thus triggering colossal investor losses:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If the USA/SEC had followed their example by setting clear regulations that required the separation of customer and business funds and clear wallet requirements, NO ONE HERE WOULD HAVE LOST MONEY ON FTX.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_105082" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-105082" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-105082" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover.jpg" alt="mark_cuban_cover" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mark_cuban_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-105082" class="wp-caption-text">Mark Cuban, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He went further, claiming the SEC has picked the &#8220;wrong course&#8221; by turning its back on the cryptocurrency sector. The regulator is &#8220;not infallible,&#8221; it &#8220;makes mistakes,&#8221; and &#8220;was arrogant&#8221; in thinking that its rules have covered every possible situation, he concluded.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cuban believes Japan is among the countries that have introduced a comprehensive regulatory framework on crypto. According to him, those efforts have protected local investors from the devastating impact of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX meltdown</a>. Recall that the Japanese subsidiary of the once-leading cryptocurrency exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/ftx-japan-allow-asset-withdrawals-starting-tuesday-2023-02-21/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> asset withdrawals at the end of February. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stark&#8217;s Reaction</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">John Reed Stark &#8211; President of John Reed Stark Consulting LLC and a former executive at the US SEC &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/JohnReedStark/status/1676284150037225487" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">thinks</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> blaming the watchdog for catastrophes such as FTX, Celsius Network, Terra, and more &#8220;seems a bit of a stretch.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also reminded Cuban that the Commission has saved &#8220;millions, perhaps even billions&#8221; in investor crypto-losses. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For one, it stopped Telegram from scamming individuals with an emergency temporary restraining order (TRO), prevented BlockFi from &#8220;doing to its investors what Celsius did to theirs (and fined them $100M),&#8221; and halted Coinbase from selling a crypto-lending product. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stark believes the digital asset sector is an &#8220;anarchical financial industry&#8221; with no insurance, cybersecurity standards, and licensing program, making the SEC&#8217;s job quite difficult. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also claimed that the crypto community is hard to be pleased with since they reject and find flaws in each proposed legislation:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;For example, whenever any government law, rule, or regulation gets specific about crypto, crypto lobbying groups protest and file interminable lawsuits challenging the action.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mark-cuban-says-the-sec-approach-to-crypto-led-to-billions-in-losses/" rel="nofollow">Mark Cuban Says the SEC Approach to Crypto Led to Billions in Losses</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How a Froggy Trader Turned $900 Into $176K in 24hrs With Pepe 2.0</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-a-froggy-trader-turned-900-into-176k-in-24hrs-with-pepe-2-0/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258661</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/fresh_money_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/fresh_money_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Launched just weeks ago, PEPE 2.0 brought at least one anonymous trader a spectacular ROI.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The demand for Pepe Coin ROI is insatiable. 2.0 knockoffs have already racked up enormous gains in July. As Pepe 2.0 rallied through the roof on Ethereum during the last week in June, one trader made $175,000 in just a day of riveting profit-taking.</p>
<p>Due to the relative anonymity of Web 3.0 users, we don&#8217;t know who the mystery trader is. But they left their tracks all over the blockchain. The on-chain transaction data tells the entire story.</p>
<p>Using the popular decentralized exchange, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-to-use-uniswap-guide-and-must-read-risks-before-swapping/" data-wpel-link="internal">Uniswap</a>, the crypto trader locked in 8.3T Pepe 2.0 tokens on June 28 at 8 am for $900.</p>
<p>They got into Pepe 2.0 at the right time.</p>
<h2>Pepe 2.0 Melt-up Earns Trader $175,000 in a Day</h2>
<p>Just ten hours later, from June 28, 6 pm until 3 am the following morning, this hero began selling. The project heated up <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe-2-0/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">so fast</a> that they were able to sell PEPE2 back to the market in cool 2ETH increments 43 times.</p>
<p>As Pepe 2.0 really started to melt up, this trader&#8217;s activity peaked in their final two hours of trading. From 1 am to 3 am early June 29, they sold the alt-right altcoin for 2ETH every three to seven minutes.</p>
<p>In total, this stunningly profitable caper earned a 19,400% ROI on a $900 investment in under 24 hours. That&#8217;ll put some pep in anyone&#8217;s portfolio if not their step.</p>
<p>A 100x altcoin gem hunter, Dami-Defi, <a href="https://twitter.com/DamiDefi/status/1674719460790358016" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">remarked</a> on this Pepe 2.0 trade:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This might be the cleanest entry and exit I’ve seen a while!</p>
<p>This #crypto wallet got into #PEPE2 before anyone had heard about it.</p>
<p>Turning $900 to $176k in less than 24hrs!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In a tweet thread, Dami-Defi offered some advice for when making these kinds of trades. &#8220;If you don’t have a strategy, greed won’t allow you to take profit, and you’ll most likely end up losing all your profit to the market,&#8221; they averred.</p>
<p>So what they do instead is wait for a new position to 2x &#8211; 3x, then pull out their principal sum to &#8220;get your money back.&#8221; After that, they take profits each time the asset posts another 100% gain.</p>
<h2>Background on PEPE Coin</h2>
<p>An ERC-20 PEPE token launched in April this year went parabolic the first week in May. By May 10, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-explodes-1200-weekly-while-crypto-markets-stagnate-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE was</a> &#8220;the number one cryptocurrency by means of overall market performance, acquiring a market capitalization upwards of $1 billion in less than three weeks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Here are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-price-madness-how-to-find-the-next-meme-surprise/" data-wpel-link="internal">some tips</a> for finding the next big meme surprise in Defi.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-a-froggy-trader-turned-900-into-176k-in-24hrs-with-pepe-2-0/" rel="nofollow">How a Froggy Trader Turned $900 Into $176K in 24hrs With Pepe 2.0</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Why the Verge Coin Price Has Exploded: Could Wall Street Memes and Ecoterra Pump Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258826</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wsm_ecoterra_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/wsm_ecoterra_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Verge ($XVG) has recently exploded with a staggering 380% surge, sparking curiosity among traders about its prospects. Given its impressive rise, many are now wondering whether $XVG will continue pumping – or whether its momentum is only temporary. However, Verge isn’t the only crypto catching the attention, with Wall Street Memes ($WSM) and Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA) [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Verge ($XVG) has recently exploded with a staggering 380% surge, sparking curiosity among traders about its prospects.</p>
<p>Given its impressive rise, many are now wondering whether $XVG will continue pumping – or whether its momentum is only temporary.</p>
<p>However, Verge isn’t the only crypto catching the attention, with Wall Street Memes ($WSM) and Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA) also on traders’ radar.</p>
<h2>Verge’s Remarkable Surge Puts Spotlight on “Dinosaur Coins”</h2>
<p>Verge is a decentralized and open-source cryptocurrency that focuses on privacy and security, aiming to provide completely anonymous transactions.</p>
<p>Originating in 2014 as DogeCoinDark and rebranded as Verge in 2016, this early crypto player has carved out its niche by offering a level of safety beyond what many in the market offer.</p>
<p>This is achieved by obfuscating the IP addresses and locations of the participants in each transaction.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258832" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-4.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="287" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-4-300x143.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-4-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Moreover, Verge’s unique multi-algorithm Proof-of-Work (PoW) system diversifies mining access to ensure fair rewards distribution – making it more democratic than most other PoW cryptos.</p>
<p>These factors are providing the platform for $XVG to stage an incredible comeback, with the token’s price up 380% in the past seven days.</p>
<p>According to one CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/community/articles/64a4319202407c748bac13cd/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">community member</a>, this increase is part of a broader trend where older cryptos, also known as &#8220;dinosaur coins,&#8221; are becoming more prominent.</p>
<p>This certainly appears to be the case, with <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/verge" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinGecko</a> revealing that $249 million worth of $XVG was traded in the past 24 hours alone – higher than Polygon ($MATIC) and Cardano ($ADA).</p>
<h2>XVG Lays Foundation for Growth Thanks To Privacy-Focused Approach</h2>
<p>Now that Verge is on an explosive uptrend, many in the crypto community question whether the token can sustain its meteoric rise.</p>
<p>The key to Verge’s endurance lies in its unique offering – with privacy and security as its pillars, Verge delivers a product that’s becoming increasingly sought after in a world grappling with data infringements.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258831" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-5.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-5-300x122.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-5-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>However, the revival of the aforementioned dinosaur coins is the real shift in the market.</p>
<p>Coins like Litecoin ($LTC) and Bitcoin SV ($BSV) have been soaring lately, fueled by investors looking to rediscover the value in these established but under-the-radar cryptos.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the resurgence in these projects could indicate a new era in the market – one that looks set to benefit Verge tremendously.</p>
<h2>Which Other Coins Could Be Set to Surge?</h2>
<p>While Verge is currently dominating the spotlight, traders remain actively looking for emerging altcoins that might match or surpass the momentum.</p>
<p>Two noteworthy contenders in this regard are Wall Street Memes and Ecoterra, which have been generating significant buzz during their ongoing presale phases.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Draws Influencer Support Amid Presale Buzz</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is a brand-new meme coin that benefits from a strong community foundation, with a network that extends to over 1.1 million followers across various social media platforms.</p>
<p>This thriving community is a crucial pillar of the project, driving engagement and drawing people into the official <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>What makes the community particularly noteworthy is its capacity for generating hilarious content surrounding financial markets – particularly cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>This has created an environment for the $WSM token to thrive, leading to over $12.6 million being raised through the project&#8217;s presale.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258830" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-5.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="291" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-5-300x145.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-5-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Notably, Wall Street Memes has also managed to attract high-profile personalities to the project.</p>
<p>Leading influencers like <a href="https://twitter.com/RealCryptoJamie" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Crypto Jamie</a> and <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@aaron_cryptonoob?_t=8dT7rgz3ikE&amp;_r=1" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Aaron CryptoNoob</a> have joined as brand ambassadors, lending their credibility and reach to the project.</p>
<p>Moreover, a yet-to-be-revealed third ambassador role has led to intrigue from investors – further enhancing the buzz around Wall Street Memes.</p>
<p>With Wall Street Memes&#8217; presale now in Stage 21 out of 30, investors only have a limited time to purchase $WSM before the token&#8217;s CEX debut.</p>
<p>Currently, tokens are priced at just $0.031 – although this price will only last for a few days before it increases in the subsequent stage.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Ecoterra Harnesses Ethereum Blockchain for Sustainable Change</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA)</a> is a visionary blockchain project that aims to promote positive climate change action.</p>
<p>Built on the Ethereum blockchain, this new project utilizes the $ECOTERRA token to reward users for eco-friendly actions.</p>
<p>Ecoterra’s innovative Recyle2Earn app incentivizes waste reduction through tokenized rewards for recycling via Reverse Vending Machines (RVMs).</p>
<p>In addition, a novel carbon offset marketplace facilitates the reduction of carbon footprints by purchasing verified offsets using $ECOTERRA (or other tokens).</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258829" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-3.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="381" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-3-300x190.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-3-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>However, Ecoterra isn’t stopping there – per the <a href="https://www.ecoterra.io/documents/whitepaper-ecoterra.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the project will even offer a recycled materials marketplace for providing a platform where businesses can trade recycled resources.</p>
<p>Ecoterra has already established partnerships with industry leaders such as Verra, making it a project worth watching.</p>
<p>Currently, Ecoterra’s presale is in its final stage, where investors have a narrow window to purchase $ECOTERRA for just $0.01 – while also receiving a 10% token bonus.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-the-verge-coin-price-has-exploded-could-wall-street-memes-and-ecoterra-pump-next/" rel="nofollow">This is Why the Verge Coin Price Has Exploded: Could Wall Street Memes and Ecoterra Pump Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized Hedge Fund VC Spectra (SPCT) Raises $2.4 Million in Seed Sale Round</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-hedge-fund-vc-spectra-spct-raises-2-4-million-in-seed-sale-round/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258816</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-05_12-35-39_1688549938MXh06negwY.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-05_12-35-39_1688549938MXh06negwY.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, July 5th, 2023] VC Spectra (SPCT), a decentralized hedge fund, is currently 70% into the first stage of its public presale. The private seed sale, which raised $2.3 million in just two weeks, has filtered through into the public presale. A leading firm in the fintech and blockchain space, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, July 5th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VC Spectra</a> (SPCT), a decentralized hedge fund, is currently 70% into the first stage of its public presale. The private seed sale, which raised $2.3 million in just two weeks, has filtered through into the public presale.</p>
<p>A leading firm in the fintech and blockchain space, VC Spectra aims to provide financial growth through strategic investments and initial coin offerings (ICOs). With a sustainable development approach and a focus on reducing risks and uncertainties, VC Spectra offers investors access to a wide range of blockchain ventures.</p>
<p>Interest in VC Spectra has been piqued by its promise to secure unparalleled access to promising blockchain projects. With a team of experienced investment professionals, VC Spectra employs a rigorous selection process to identify high-potential opportunities in the blockchain and technology sectors.</p>
<p>SPCT is a BRC-20 standard token built on the Bitcoin blockchain, with is also being cross-chain to ERC20 for its presale. Serving as a medium of exchange, it facilitates decentralized trading, asset management, and transaction fees on the VC Spectra platform. Token-holders will enjoy a range of benefits, including exposure to promising web3 projects at an early stage.</p>
<p>VC Spectra is on a mission to democratize access to venture capital-style investments, something that is traditionally unavailable to the public. Its team, using a combination of human experts and artificial intelligence, identifies opportunities that have the potential to generate outsized returns. After devising a shortlist of outstanding projects, these are subjected to further scrutiny before the best candidates are added to VC Spectra’s investment portfolio.</p>
<h2>About VC Spectra</h2>
<p>Spectra is a leading firm driving innovation in Fintech and blockchain through strategic investments and ICOs, empowering financial growth by harnessing cutting-edge technologies.</p>
<p>Spectra VC is a venture capital fund that invests in blockchain and technology-based projects with the goal of generating returns for investors.</p>
<p>Find out more about the VC Spectra presale here:</p>
<p><a href="https://invest.vcspectra.io/login" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Buy Presale</a> | <a href="https://vcspectra.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a>  | <a href="https://t.me/VCSpectra" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/spectravcfund" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-hedge-fund-vc-spectra-spct-raises-2-4-million-in-seed-sale-round/" rel="nofollow">Decentralized Hedge Fund VC Spectra (SPCT) Raises $2.4 Million in Seed Sale Round</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Academy Taps Coursera to Make Web3 Education Accessible to Everyone</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-academy-taps-coursera-to-make-web3-education-accessible-to-everyone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258715</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance_Academy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance_Academy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The programs will be developed by Binance Academy experts.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance Academy &#8211; the educational arm of crypto exchange Binance &#8211; announced a partnership with Coursera.</p>
<p>The collaboration with the leading online learning platforms that boast more than 124 million learners globally aims to bring educational opportunities to everyone in the form of a comprehensive suite of learning programs that are slated for launch over the next few months and beyond.</p>
<h2>Binance Academy Partners With Coursera</h2>
<p>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the programs will encompass a broad range of topics and will be designed for individuals seeking to gain a foundational understanding of blockchain, Web3, and crypto technologies, as well as for the ones looking to build the right skills to pursue a career in the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>Moreover, the learners will earn a digital certificate upon successful completion. Experts from Binance Academy will be tasked with developing the programs, each of which will incorporate several courses. The programs will include video lectures, readings, practice assessments or projects, and graded assessments.</p>
<p>Commenting on the latest collaboration, Binance co-founder and Chief Marketing Officer Yi He said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Today, we&#8217;re thrilled to announce our partnership with Coursera. Together, we&#8217;re combining the strengths of two industry leaders with a shared vision &#8211; to provide best-in-class education that will drive adoption and build the foundations for Web.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance Academy also said organizations that leverage blockchain are experiencing a period of growth. While citing PWC&#8217;s &#8220;Time for trust&#8221; report, the platform said blockchain technology is poised to improve over 40 million jobs globally by 2030.</p>
<h2>Tapping Chatbot Powered by ChatGPT</h2>
<p>The latest expansion comes months after Binance <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-academy-launches-a-chatbot-powered-by-chatgpt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">rolled out</a> an AI-driven learning tool to streamline user searches and subsequently elevate the learning experience. Dubbed &#8216;Binance Sensei,&#8217; the tech is powered by OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT technology and aims to make the educational process more productive and engaging for the crypto community.</p>
<p>Earlier, Binance unveiled Binance Bicasso, which is an AI NFT generator that allows its users to create custom images using AI that can then be minted into NFTs on BNB Chain.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-academy-taps-coursera-to-make-web3-education-accessible-to-everyone/" rel="nofollow">Binance Academy Taps Coursera to Make Web3 Education Accessible to Everyone</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Primex Finance Unveils Mainnet Plans, Set to Launch in September 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/primex-finance-unveils-mainnet-plans-set-to-launch-in-september-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258719</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Primex.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Primex.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Non-custodial prime brokerage protocol Primex Finance is thrilled to announce the upcoming launch of its highly anticipated mainnet. With the code frozen and the auditing process underway, the Primex core team is making significant strides toward the release. With independent auditors expected to complete the auditing process in the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>Non-custodial prime brokerage protocol <a href="https://primex.finance/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Primex Finance</a> is thrilled to announce the upcoming launch of its highly anticipated mainnet. With the code frozen and the auditing process underway, the Primex core team is making significant strides toward the release.</p>
<p>With independent auditors expected to complete the auditing process in the next 12 weeks, Primex Finance is scheduled to launch its mainnet Beta in September 2023. Meanwhile, the team is actively developing subsequent protocol versions, which will be rolled out in early 2024 to align with the Primex V1 release.</p>
<p>For its initial deployment, Primex will be launching on the Polygon PoS network, leveraging the network&#8217;s fast-growing ecosystem. The mainnet launch will introduce support for leveraged trading of Wrapped Ether (wETH), Wrapped Bitcoin (wBTC), Polygon (MATIC), USD Coin (USDC), and Tether USD (USDT). These five assets will be available for trading in Primex Credit Buckets, specialized smart contracts that facilitate margin trading on the platform. Lenders will have the opportunity to earn yield by supplying liquidity to the Buckets, while traders can borrow assets for spot margin trading.</p>
<p>In addition to margin trading, Primex&#8217;s initial deployment will enable users to engage in non-leveraged trading through Spot1X trades and decentralized limit swaps. Following the mainnet launch, the list of supported assets for these trade types is expected to expand significantly.</p>
<p>Beyond the Polygon network, Primex has plans to deploy on one or two additional chains in the near future. The team is actively exploring various options, including Arbitrum and the Ethereum mainnet.</p>
<p>Ethereum mainnet stands as the leading DeFi ecosystem, with over $26 billion locked in decentralized finance protocols on its mainnet. Considering Ethereum&#8217;s established infrastructure, it presents an attractive choice for Primex&#8217;s expansion, particularly catering to traders with large position sizes. Simultaneously, the protocol aims to support the broader community by leveraging more L2 blockchains to accommodate lower position sizes.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled about the upcoming mainnet launch, as it signifies a significant milestone on our roadmap,&#8221; said Dmitry Tolok, Co-founder of Primex. &#8220;In the meantime, Primex continues to be available to early users on the testnet, offering a risk-free environment to explore and test the platform&#8217;s capabilities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Alongside the mainnet update, the Primex team has unveiled additional information regarding the protocol&#8217;s documentation. Users can now conveniently access the project&#8217;s <a href="https://docsend.com/view/2gfm7c57ckna9g57" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Whitepaper</a> and the highly anticipated <a href="https://docsend.com/view/vx2q2fwnx7svdrwu" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Yellow Paper</a>.</p>
<h2>About Primex Finance</h2>
<p>Founded in 2021, Primex Finance is a non-custodial prime brokerage protocol that bridges the gap between lenders and traders. With a focus on enhancing the trading experience on existing decentralized exchanges (DEXs), Primex enables spot margin trading backed by lender liquidity. The platform revolutionizes trading on DEXs by offering a wide range of limit orders with decentralized execution, providing traders with more options and flexibility in their trading strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/primex-finance-unveils-mainnet-plans-set-to-launch-in-september-2023/" rel="nofollow">Primex Finance Unveils Mainnet Plans, Set to Launch in September 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Greed Takes Over the Markets as Bitcoin Maintains $30K</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/greed-takes-over-the-markets-as-bitcoin-maintains-30k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258746</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/bitcoin_green_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/bitcoin_green_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The increased greed in the market is fueled by several factors, including institutional BTC accumulation, two consecutive green quarters, and positive on-chain metrics. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Market sentiment shows that crypto investors have renewed their bullishness and confidence in BTC as the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency continues to flirt with the $31,000 mark.</p>
<p>According to the Fear and Greed Index &#8211; a popular tool used to measure overall sentiment &#8211; greed has taken over the market as investors are getting too comfortable with bitcoin at its current price.</p>
<h2>Greed Takes Over</h2>
<p>The Fear and Greed Index evaluates market sentiment by analyzing key factors, including volatility, market momentum, social media trends, and bitcoin&#8217;s dominance. It uses a scale of 0 to 100, where 0 represents &#8220;Extreme Fear&#8221; and 100 means &#8220;Extreme Greed.&#8221;</p>
<p>Over the past week, the <a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">greed index</a> has consistently climbed above 50, reaching a high of 64, coinciding with Bitcoin&#8217;s price surpassing $30,000.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258747" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258747" style="width: 693px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img class="wp-image-258747" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index-300x187.jpg" alt="" width="693" height="431" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index-300x187.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index-1024x639.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index-768x479.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index-50x31.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Greed-index.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 693px) 100vw, 693px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258747" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Fear and Greed. Source: Alternative.me</figcaption></figure>
<p>The increased greed in the market is fueled by several factors, including institutional BTC accumulation, two consecutive green quarters, and positive on-chain metrics.</p>
<h2>Institutional Bitcoin Accumulation Surges</h2>
<p>One of the key drivers behind the resurgence of greed in the crypto market is the exponential increase in institutional Bitcoin accumulation.</p>
<p>Over the past few months, prominent institutional players, including major financial institutions and corporations, have been actively acquiring bitcoin as part of their investment strategies, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutional-bitcoin-btc-accumulation-sees-exponential-increase-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">according</a> to blockchain analytics firm CryptoQuant.</p>
<p>This wave of institutional adoption validates bitcoin as a store of value while signaling institutional confidence in its long-term potential. The strategic move by institutional investors to accumulate BTC is underpinned by the belief that the crypto asset can act as a hedge against inflation and provide diversification in traditional investment portfolios.</p>
<p>The institutional accumulation has also contributed to the positive sentiment surrounding bitcoin and has drawn the attention of retail investors seeking to capitalize on the growing institutional interest.</p>
<h2>2 Consecutive Green Quarters Ignite Optimism</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s recent milestone of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-posts-2-consecutive-green-quarters-for-the-first-time-since-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">posting</a> two consecutive green quarters for the first time since 2021 has further fueled optimism among investors. After a period of market uncertainty and bearish sentiment throughout last year, bitcoin&#8217;s back-to-back positive quarterly performances signify a potential shift in market dynamics.</p>
<p>The consecutive green quarters demonstrate BTC&#8217;s resilience as it navigates through the bear market and emerges stronger. This accomplishment has instilled confidence in investors, signaling a possible reversal in the market trend. The bullish sentiment resulting from the milestone has ignited renewed greed among market participants.</p>
<h2>Investors&#8217; Behavior Points to a Bull Run</h2>
<p>Beyond institutional accumulation and two consecutive positive quarterly performances, on-chain metrics and investor behavior provide further evidence of a potential bull run in the crypto market.</p>
<p>According to Bitfinex&#8217;s latest weekly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/on-chain-metrics-and-investor-behavior-suggest-signs-of-a-bull-run-bitfinex-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a>, on-chain data, such as Bitcoin&#8217;s Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) and Net Unrealized Profit and Loss (NUPL) indicators, show that almost all bitcoin trades have been profitable since the crypto asset broke above $29,500.</p>
<p>Investor behavior also reflects an increasing appetite for risk and the potential for substantial returns. The report noted that traders are confident about their spot position as they are unwilling to sell at a loss.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/greed-takes-over-the-markets-as-bitcoin-maintains-30k/" rel="nofollow">Greed Takes Over the Markets as Bitcoin Maintains $30K</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders Think This New Meme Coin Could Explode After Raising $12.5m</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:08:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258760</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_cash_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_cash_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the crypto community continues to ride the wave of meme coins, a new contender is turning heads – Wall Street Memes ($WSM). During a massively successful presale that has now raised $12.5m, Wall Street Memes ($WSM) has positioned itself as a token with the potential to erupt. With an established community and an endearing [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the crypto community continues to ride the wave of meme coins, a new contender is turning heads – Wall Street Memes ($WSM).</p>
<p>During a massively successful presale that has now raised $12.5m, <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> has positioned itself as a token with the potential to erupt.</p>
<p>With an established community and an endearing legacy, Wall Street Memes seeks to leverage the current meme coin craze to its advantage.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Harnesses the Power of Virality &amp; Breaks $12.5m Barrier</h2>
<p>Following its presale launch in late May, Wall Street Memes quickly caught the attention of crypto enthusiasts worldwide – leading to the project recently breaching the $12.5m milestone.</p>
<p>What sets Wall Street Memes apart from the other meme coins that are flooding the space is the project’s impressive pedigree.</p>
<p>The team behind Wall Street Memes is no stranger to the digital space, having successfully launched a popular NFT collection called “<a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls</a>” in 2021.</p>
<p>This collection sold all 10,000 pieces in just 32 minutes – raising a whopping $2.5 million for the creators.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258766" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-3.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="301" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-3-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-3-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Aside from that, Wall Street Memes also harnesses the potential of a community that extends beyond 1.1 million followers across several social media platforms, including <a href="https://www.instagram.com/wallstbets/?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a>.</p>
<p>Its internet community is celebrated for engaging and hilarious content surrounding financial markets, including stocks and cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the $WSM token was launched to tokenize this movement, fuelling a deeper level of engagement within the community.</p>
<p>Moreover, with high-profile names like Elon Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1636924379086077954" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">interacting</a> with Wall Street Memes content, the foundation has already been laid for Tier-1 CEX listings – which are scheduled for once the presale concludes.</p>
<h2>WSM Tokenomics Help Foster a True Community Spirit</h2>
<p>Wall Street Memes’ team has made a bold move in structuring its tokenomics.</p>
<p>Unlike many other meme coin projects, the team has decided not to set aside any <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$WSM tokens</a> for themselves.</p>
<p>Instead, they’ve designed a structure where 100% of the token supply, capped at two billion $WSM, is distributed among the community.</p>
<p>This setup will see 50% of the tokens used for the presale, 20% for CEX/DEX liquidity, and the remaining 30% for community rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258765" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-4.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="209" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-4-300x104.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-4-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Naturally, this tokenomics structure aligns the developers&#8217; incentives with the $WSM holders, solidifying the project&#8217;s focus on community.</p>
<p>The developers have also initiated a $50,000 airdrop as part of the presale launch celebration, stimulating engagement within the community.</p>
<p>Community members must join the official <a href="https://discord.com/invite/4E538pzeGX" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Discord server</a> and complete various social media-related tasks to participate in the airdrop.</p>
<p>The prize of $50,000 worth of $WSM will be split among five winners once the presale concludes, providing an exciting opportunity for early adopters to increase their holdings.</p>
<h2>Final Countdown Begins</h2>
<p>With Wall Street Memes&#8217; presale in its final stages, interested investors can buy $WSM tokens for just $0.031 – a discount to the planned exchange listing price.</p>
<p>Given the presale&#8217;s impressive fundraise, it&#8217;s clear that Wall Street Memes has leveraged the meme coin frenzy, but the team isn&#8217;t stopping there.</p>
<p>As the official website notes, Wall Street Memes has set a clear goal to reach a $1 billion market cap.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258764" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-4.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="311" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-4-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-4-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Not only that, but the developers plan to foster partnerships with well-known influencers and even launch an exclusive “gated community” for $WSM holders.</p>
<p>Two prominent crypto personalities, <a href="https://twitter.com/RealCryptoJamie" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Crypto Jamie</a> and <a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@aaron_cryptonoob?_t=8dT7rgz3ikE&amp;_r=1" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Aaron CryptoNoob</a>, have also become brand ambassadors.</p>
<p>Excitingly, Wall Street Memes&#8217; team has left the third ambassador role blank, with a message saying &#8220;Coming Soon,&#8221; – leading investors to speculate that another high-profile endorsement could be on the horizon.</p>
<p>The next few months could be pivotal for Wall Street Memes, but with huge YouTubers like <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QIq4jd5UlGs&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CryptoWendy0</a> already taking note, it’s no surprise that many early investors believe $WSM is primed to explode.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Thug Life Also Gaining Traction as Investors Seek the Next Big Meme Coin</h2>
<p>Alongside Wall Street Memes, another meme coin has caught the eye of investors – <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a>.</p>
<p>This new meme token has now raised nearly $400,000 via its ongoing presale phase, which indicates growing investor interest.</p>
<p>Driven by the famous “Thug Life” meme, $THUG is already creating ripples in the meme coin space.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258763" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-2.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="337" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-2-300x168.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Its appealing tokenomics setup, in which 70% of the $THUG supply is reserved for presale investors, provides a strong incentive for early investment.</p>
<p>Moreover, Thug Life has captured the attention of notable figures in the crypto industry; for example, crypto influencer Michael Wrubel recently <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WR9Tt9Q_Kgk&amp;t=3s&amp;pp=ygUQdGh1ZyBsaWZlIGNyeXB0bw%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">endorsed</a> the token.</p>
<p>Early investors can buy $THUG tokens for just $0.0007 – a price that will be fixed for the duration of the presale.</p>
<p>However, given that the presale has a hard cap of just over $2 million, opportunities to secure $THUG at such a low rate could be limited, so investors are piling in while they can.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-think-this-new-meme-coin-could-explode-after-raising-12-5m/" rel="nofollow">Traders Think This New Meme Coin Could Explode After Raising $12.5m</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Whales Are to Meet at Blockchain Life 2023 in Dubai</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-whales-are-to-meet-at-blockchain-life-2023-in-dubai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258735</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/19201080_en_1688543756RnUY6qzxmQ.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/19201080_en_1688543756RnUY6qzxmQ.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 5th, 2023] Influential figures such as heads of global funds, government officials, investors, business owners, and promising startups come together in Dubai to shape the future of cryptocurrencies and Web3 at the 11th International Blockchain Life Forum on October 24-25 in Dubai, Festival Arena. Buy your ticket now at [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 5th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Influential figures such as heads of global funds, government officials, investors, business owners, and promising startups come together in Dubai to shape the future of cryptocurrencies and Web3 at the 11th International Blockchain Life Forum on October 24-25 in Dubai, Festival Arena.</p>
<p>Buy your ticket now at the presale price: <a href="https://blockchain-life.com/asia/en/?utm_campaign=chainwire/#tickets-row" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blockchain-life.com/asia/en/ </a></p>
<p>The event remains as a meeting point for Crypto Whales, attracting over 7,000 visitors from 120 countries.</p>
<p>Attendees can look forward to informative sessions led by leaders in the crypto industry, an innovative expo featuring 100 companies, and amazing networking with key decision-makers.</p>
<p>Over 80 speakers are going to share their analytics and world-changing ideas.</p>
<p>Among them:</p>
<ul>
<li>H.E. Justin Sun (Founder of TRON)</li>
<li>Alexander Chehade (General Manager at MENA, Binance)</li>
<li>Xinxi Wang (Co-Founder and Director of Litecoin Foundation)</li>
<li>Sergei Khitrov (Founder of Jets.Capital and Listing.Help)</li>
<li>Carl Runefelt (Crypto Entrepreneur, Founder of CryptoJobs.com)</li>
<li>Chris MMCrypto (Cryptotrader, Founder of MMCrypto)</li>
<li>Tone Vays (Trader, Economic Trends Expert and Analyst, ex-VP at JP Morgan Chase)</li>
<li>Dr. Sameer Al Ansari (CEO of Ras Al Khaimah DAO and ICC, UAE Government)</li>
</ul>
<p>Hurry up and buy your ticket with a 10% discount with promo code MALife10: <a href="https://blockchain-life.com/asia/en/?utm_campaign=chainwire/#tickets-row" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blockchain-life.com/asia/en/ </a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-whales-are-to-meet-at-blockchain-life-2023-in-dubai/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Whales Are to Meet at Blockchain Life 2023 in Dubai</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Bill Empowering Authorities to Confiscate Crypto Approved by House of Lords</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-bill-empowering-authorities-to-confiscate-crypto-approved-by-house-of-lords/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258706</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/UnitedKingdom.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/UnitedKingdom.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The legislation needs to pass "Consideration of Amendments" and "Royal Assent" before going live. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The UK&#8217;s Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill passed a third reading after a meeting of the House of Lords (the Parliament&#8217;s upper chamber). If officially approved, the legislation will allow the authorities to seize cryptocurrencies should they have a relation to some sort of financial crime.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On another note, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCI) of the United Kingdom reminded that all domestic firms marketing cryptocurrencies to British consumers must comply with a designated promotion regime. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Marching Toward a &#8216;Royal Assent&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/UKHouseofLords/status/1676165979393409024" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on Twitter, the House of Lords made &#8220;small changes to make sure the bill is effective.&#8221; The legislation was initially introduced in 2022 in an effort to combat financial crime and offer protection to locals.</span></p>
<p>The Economic Crime and Corporate Transparency Bill would also grant the British authorities additional jurisdiction to confiscate digital currencies that participate in criminal activities, such as terrorism financing.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The officials have previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/1147515/6.8300_HO_Economic_Crime_Plan_2_v6_Web.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">argued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that crypto assets are &#8220;an attractive technological enabler for criminal activity.&#8221; They also claimed that detecting wrongdoers could be difficult due to &#8220;the pseudo-anonymous and transnational nature&#8221; of bitcoin and the altcoins. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The National Assessment Center maintained that illicit crypto transactions in the UK equaled approximately $1.5 billion in 2021 (a mere 1% of the total transaction value). Nonetheless, the entity believes the real figures could be much higher.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Following the House of Lords&#8217; approval, the bill is now heading towards &#8220;Consideration of Amendments,&#8221; where both chambers of the Parliament (the House of Commons and the House of Lords) can discuss any changes and must eventually reach a mutual agreement.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The last step of the legislation before becoming official is a signature from King Charles III, known as &#8220;Royal Assent.&#8221; It is worth noting that the last British monarch to reject a law passed by both chambers was Queen Anne in 1708. She </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scottish_Militia_Bill" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">withheld</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8220;Royal Asset&#8221; on the Scottish Militia Bill after her minister advised her that such a division would not be loyal to the crown. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FCA&#8217;s Recommendation</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides the possible upcoming rules, Britain&#8217;s top regulator &#8211; the FCA &#8211; has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.fca.org.uk/publication/correspondence/letter-to-cryptoasset-firms-financial-promotions-regime.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">issued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a warning to &#8220;all firms marketing crypto assets to UK consumers&#8221; to comply with the financial promotion regime by October 8, 2023. As such, the watchdog expects to put most digital asset firms that offer services to British retail customers under its scope. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After that deadline, crypto entities must introduce promotions via an authorized person and ensure their product complies with the FCA&#8217;s anti-money laundering requirements. Those who fail to register face up to two years imprisonment, an unlimited fine, or both. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We will take robust action against persons illegally promoting to UK consumers. This may include but is not limited to placing firms on our warning list requesting takedowns of websites, social media accounts, apps, and all other promotions that are in breach, and enforcement action,&#8221; the regulator outlined.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-bill-empowering-authorities-to-confiscate-crypto-approved-by-house-of-lords/" rel="nofollow">UK Bill Empowering Authorities to Confiscate Crypto Approved by House of Lords</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
