<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:41:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>“Citizens Have Every Right To Do Bitcoin”: Ron De Santis Announces Presidential Bid</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/citizens-have-every-right-to-do-bitcoin-ron-de-santis-announces-presidential-bid/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252248</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/230315183223-ron-desantis-0310.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/230315183223-ron-desantis-0310.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Florida’s governor is running for President on the Republican side – and he’s pro-Bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Florida Governor Ron De Santis has officially announced that he’s entering the United States 2024 Presidential race, poised to be former President Donald Trump’s greatest opponent within the Republican primary. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Unlike Trump, De Santis has pushed pro-crypto policy multiple times in the past and is staunchly opposed to Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).</span></p>
<h2>De Santis Would Protect Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">De Santis announced his plans to run in a <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1661498079386931206" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter Spaces</a> alongside the platform’s owner, Elon Musk, on Wednesday. Musk has </span><a href="https://twitter.com/MarioNawfal/status/1648128894979956736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1648128894979956736%7Ctwgr%5Ee49bdc41d2b7ccb906a7d10ce200a18b9ce17ef2%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2Fnews%2F23%2F04%2F31852077%2Felon-musk-reveals-he-voted-for-biden-in-2020-now-he-wants-a-normal-person-with-common-sense-as-next" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">expressed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> regret for voting for Joe Biden in the 2020 election, but also wasn’t interested in Trump since he desired a “normal person for president.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Both Musk and De Santis found common ground in their opposition to “woke” ideology, and their support for free speech. They also happen to both be </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-issues-warning-for-dogecoin-investors-explains-why-doge-is-his-favorite-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">crypto-friendly</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, while Trump has repeatedly called Bitcoin a “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-bitcoin-looks-like-a-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">scam</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When asked about his view on crypto’s regulatory situation in the United States, De Santis said that citizens have “every right to do Bitcoin,” and would oppose any statute to ban its use. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“As President, we’ll protect the ability to do things like Bitcoin,” said De Santis. “I just do not have the itch to control everything that people may be doing in this space.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">De Santis echoed comments from other crypto-supportive Republicans in agreeing that the Biden Administration is attempting to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/regulators-want-crypto-to-stay-the-f-away-caitlin-long-erik-voorhees-consensus-2023-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">kill the crypto industry</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in the United States through regulation. After a string of regulators’ enforcement actions against </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-addresses-the-cftc-in-house-trading-allegations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">exchanges</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, stablecoin issuers, and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fdic-chair-blames-crypto-exposure-for-signature-banks-demise/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">crypto-supportive banks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, firms like Coinbase are desperate for clarity on the rules of the road surrounding crypto in the United States. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The current regime – clearly they have it out for Bitcoin, and if it continues for another four years, they’ll probably end up killing it,” he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At Bitcoin Miami 2023 last week, Democratic Presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-pledges-inviolable-right-to-hold-and-use-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pledged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to protect citizens’ “inviolable right” to hold and use Bitcoin. Miami Mayor Francis Suarez is himself a Bitcoin believer, believing it </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftxs-collapse-miamis-mayor-is-still-a-bitcoin-believer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">provides advantages</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> over the fiat currency system. </span></p>
<h2>No CBDCs for De Santis</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By contrast, the Biden White House has expressed interest in implementing a potential CBDC to “bring the U.S. financial infrastructure into the digital era… without the risks or irrational exuberance brought by crypto assets.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Similar to Republic Congressmen Tom Emmer and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sen-ted-cruz-introduces-a-bill-to-prevent-the-fed-from-issuing-a-cbdc/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ted Cruz</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, De Santis is outright opposed to CBDCs. He introduced legislation in March to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-says-governor-ron-desantis/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">ban</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> any such technology from being used in Florida. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I see it as a massive transfer of power from individual consumers to a central authority, and I don’t think that’s good for a free society,” he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citizens-have-every-right-to-do-bitcoin-ron-de-santis-announces-presidential-bid/" rel="nofollow">“Citizens Have Every Right To Do Bitcoin”: Ron De Santis Announces Presidential Bid</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea&#8217;s PPP Seeks to Speed Up Bill Requiring Lawmakers&#8217; Crypto Holdings Disclosure</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-koreas-ppp-seeks-to-speed-up-bill-requiring-lawmakers-crypto-holdings-disclosure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251950</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/south_korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/south_korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The politician had recently quit the party over the crypto scandal.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Korea&#8217;s ruling party has called for early enforcement of the law that seeks the country&#8217;s lawmakers and high-level government officials to declare their cryptocurrency-related assets.</p>
<p>The proposed bill would require local officials and lawmakers to declare all personal crypto holdings over 1 million Korean won (worth around $760). The move was prompted by a major crypto scandal involving a former lawmaker of the opposing party.</p>
<h2>Calls to Expedite Bill</h2>
<p>A report by Yonhap news agency <a href="https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20230523005800315?section=news" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">suggests</a> that People Power Party&#8217;s floor leader unveiled a bill last Friday proposing all public officials and candidates disclose their crypto holdings.</p>
<p>The original bill was previously scheduled for implementation in December this year. However, Rep. Yun Jae-ok, a third-term lawmaker, who was elected as the new floor leader of the conservative PPP last month, deemed the set date to be &#8220;too late&#8221; and added that the bill needs to be amended to add a clause moving up the enforcement.</p>
<p>The lawmaker said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Given the current high level of public interest, especially regarding lawmakers, it&#8217;s not appropriate to enforce the law six months later after the promulgation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Yun further revealed that he asked the leader of the Public Administration Committee to propose a modified version of the law. The bill is reportedly scheduled to be put to a vote on May 26.</p>
<p>The latest development emerges on the heels of the ongoing scandal surrounding former Democratic Party lawmaker Kim Nam-kuk who has been at the center of controversy over his cryptocurrency investments. He is currently under investigation by local prosecutors for alleged campaign finance violations and tax portals, as well as for hiding criminal proceeds of his crypto possessions and transactions.</p>
<p>Kim announced leaving the party last week and continued to maintain his innocence. While responding to allegations, the now-independent lawmaker asserted that he was not required to disclose activities surrounding his crypto assets and denied liquidating his holdings.</p>
<p>As part of the investigation against the politician, authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-prosecutors-raided-upbit-and-bithumb-hqs-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raided</a> the offices of prominent crypto exchanges  &#8211; Upbit and Bithumb.</p>
<h2>South Korea&#8217;s Regulatory Standpoint</h2>
<p>South Korean lawmakers have increased regulatory scrutiny of the crypto-asset industry after the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-authorities-seize-terra-executives-assets-worth-160m-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse</a> of the Terra ecosystem tokens last May.</p>
<p>As such, the legislators passed a first phase review of proposed regulations that offers the Financial Services Commission authority to investigate and monitor financial activity related to the asset class with stipulations ranging from governing the sale, storage, and trading. Consumer protection and compliance reporting were some of the aspects that were particularly stressed.</p>
<p>If passed, the bill would require digital asset service providers to distinguish internal holdings from consumer assets, carry insurance and maintain reserves in the event of non-market-related losses.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-koreas-ppp-seeks-to-speed-up-bill-requiring-lawmakers-crypto-holdings-disclosure/" rel="nofollow">South Korea&#8217;s PPP Seeks to Speed Up Bill Requiring Lawmakers&#8217; Crypto Holdings Disclosure</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NBA Star Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit for Promoting Solana-Based Crypto Project Astrals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nba-star-shaquille-oneal-faces-lawsuit-for-promoting-solana-based-crypto-project-astrals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252121</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shaq.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shaq.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[O'Neal has been summoned to court again over his involvement in promoting Astrals token, an alleged unregistered security.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American basketball legend Shaquille O&#8217;Neal is facing a new lawsuit for promoting the Solana-based crypto project, Astrals.</p>
<p>According to the class action lawsuit filed with a Floridan court by plaintiff Daniel Harper, Shaquille shilled the Astrals token through posts and videos on several of his social media handles.</p>
<h2>O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit Over Astrals Project</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/647748832/Harper-v-O-Neal#" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lawsuit</a>, Astrals is a 3D-modeled NFT collection founded by the NBA celebrity alongside his son, Mylers O&#8217;Neal. Shaq&#8217;s son headed the role of &#8220;Investors Relations&#8221; while his music manager, Brian Bayati, acted as the project&#8217;s CEO.</p>
<p>Building on the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-solana/" data-wpel-link="internal">Solana network</a>, Astrals seeks to onboard users into an ecosystem that offers gaming and metaverse experiences. These services are accessible through the Solana-based NFT marketplace Magic Eden.</p>
<p>Encouraging users to engage with Astrals&#8217; native cryptocurrency, the project launched the Shaq Signature Pass as an exclusive 50-piece collection of NFTs. These collectibles can only be claimed with the native token.</p>
<p>Harper&#8217;s lawsuit, which claims that Astrals tokens are unregistered securities, means that the assets will be subjected to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-launches-its-own-ico-howeycoin-to-educate-investors/" data-wpel-link="internal">Howey test</a>. This is a process used to determine whether a cryptocurrency (or any other type of asset) falls under the category of security or an investment contract.</p>
<p>If the Astrals token passes the Howey test, it will be classified as a security and must be registered with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As such, the SEC will likely take legal action against Astrals and its executives, demanding a settlement.</p>
<h2>Not the First</h2>
<p>Since joining the industry, O&#8217;Neal has found himself in several crypto-related lawsuit cases. Earlier this month, he was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-icon-shaquille-oneal-describes-his-ftx-summons-as-inadequate-seeks-dismisal-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">involved</a> in a court case regarding the collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>After being summoned to the court regarding his interaction with FTX, the NBA celebrity stated that the notice was inadequate, as it was tossed at his moving car and not served at his home.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-star-shaquille-oneal-faces-lawsuit-for-promoting-solana-based-crypto-project-astrals/" rel="nofollow">NBA Star Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit for Promoting Solana-Based Crypto Project Astrals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase: SEC Has Made Up its Mind to Deny Petition</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sec-has-made-up-its-mind-to-deny-petition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252093</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase lashed out on the SEC saying the agency has no plans to consider the crypto exchange's petition on any timeline. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In response to the SEC&#8217;s arguments against its petition for a writ of mandamus, Coinbase said the financial regulator &#8220;is talking out of both sides of its mouth, and it is wrong at each end.&#8221; The crypto exchange&#8217;s chief legal officer Paul Grewal described the mandamus as &#8220;the tailor-made remedy for the extraordinary facts.&#8221;</p>
<p>The longstanding dispute between the crypto exchange and the market regulator is at the heart of the battle. Last month, Coinbase sued the SEC, claiming that the latter failed to provide a response as the former sought a formal notice-and-comment process that would enable the public to weigh in. The SEC later responded, deeming Coinbase&#8217;s allegations to be &#8220;baseless.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Coinbase vs. SEC</h2>
<p>In a 23-page <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/4Y8RdHCBOhXBvqYH51pw5P/564dd375bfeaaf866180888ef9a96432/2023.05.22_-_Dkt._27_-_Coinbase_Mandamus_Reply.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> to the Third Circuit of the United States Court of Appeals, the crypto exchange said the SEC&#8217;s broad enforcement campaign on the same topic posed by Coinbase&#8217;s rulemaking petition renders the agency&#8217;s delay &#8220;unreasonable.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coinbase argued that mandamus is warranted and blamed the SEC for &#8220;making up its mind&#8221; to deny the petition. It also said the Commission&#8217;s enforcement actions confirm that it is not considering Coinbase&#8217;s Petition.</p>
<p>The filing also cited that the SEC has instituted over 25 digital asset-related enforcement actions since the filing of the petition in July 2022.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;These actions presuppose that the agency believes the securities laws are clear and workable as applied to digital assets and that additional rulemaking is unnecessary. And many of these enforcement actions require the Commission to take positions on the central questions in Coinbase’s rulemaking petition, such as the standard for identifying whether a digital asset is a security.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase also hit back at the SEC, saying the latter&#8217;s argument that &#8211; regulated entities should wait to be sued &#8211; ignores its obligations to create significant new legal standards through rulemaking and not enforcement.</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Earlier Response</h2>
<p>After failed attempts to get a response from the SEC about its stance on proposing and adopting rules to govern the regulation of securities that are offered and traded via digitally native methods, a US court <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the commission to respond to Coinbase’s complaint in ten days.</p>
<p>The Commission then argued that it is under no obligation to issue new regulations and added that Coinbase has no standing to sue the agency. It also said the digital asset industry already has rules and regulations governing it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sec-has-made-up-its-mind-to-deny-petition/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase: SEC Has Made Up its Mind to Deny Petition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO Says This Recent Event Might Signal a Bull Market</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-says-this-recent-event-might-signal-a-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252224</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CZ-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CZ-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Chinese broadcasters are starting to cover crypto, and CZ is bullish about it. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) published a tweet on Wednesday noting that China Central Television (CCTV) recently put out a broadcast related to digital assets. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The executive claimed that similar coverage has served as a catalyst for crypto bull runs in the past. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1661391542504902664" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">provided</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a link to the </span><a href="https://t.co/2wcArnPI93" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">broadcast</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> which aired on May 23, and included a 98-second segment about Hong Kong regulators “Implementing a mandatory licensing system for virtual asset trading platforms,” beginning June 1. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The news itself wasn’t entirely positive for the industry, with </span><a href="https://apps.sfc.hk/edistributionWeb/gateway/EN/news-and-announcements/news/doc?refNo=23PR53" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">SFC guidelines</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> including rules not to incentivize retail trading through stablecoins, and others explicitly banning crypto “gifts” (likely including airdrops). </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, CZ viewed the act of broadcasting crypto alone to be a massively bullish development, calling it a “big deal.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“The Chinese-speaking communities are buzzing,” he said. “Historically, coverages like these led to bull runs.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The CEO clarified that his tweet was not “financial advice,” and that the past does not predict the future. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Mainland China has banned crypto altogether, but Hong Kong has chosen to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-confirms-crypto-commitment-at-web3-conference-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">press on</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with ambitions to become a regional crypto hub. Even after China’s ban, a sizable portion of Bitcoin mining activity still continues to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/china-emerges-as-leading-bitcoin-mining-hub-a-year-after-crackdown-cambridge-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">flourish</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in the region. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In his replies, CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1661392242341183489" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">agreed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with a commenter that a bull market effectively can’t happen without Chinese people being involved. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">CZ was born in China, but has been a Canadian citizen since the age of 12. He’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-not-a-chinese-company-declares-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">asserted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on multiple occasions that Binance is not a Chinese company. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-says-this-recent-event-might-signal-a-bull-market/" rel="nofollow">Binance CEO Says This Recent Event Might Signal a Bull Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Multichain Token Crashes Over 20% Amid Reports of Users&#8217; Funds Being Stuck</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/multichain-token-crashes-over-20-amid-reports-of-users-funds-being-stuck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252188</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/crash_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/crash_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The delay in the completion of Multichain's backend upgrade has caused users' transactions to be stucked on the protocol for three days.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Users of the cross-chain router protocol Multichain have been reportedly experiencing delays in receiving their funds following an upgrade.</p>
<p dir="ltr">There have also been rumors about the arrest of the Multichain team, which is yet to be confirmed.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MULTI Sinks 24% in 24 Hours</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Several Multichain users have complained about their funds being stuck in the protocol for as long as 72 hours. Part of the problem seems to stem from a backend upgrade, which the team said is taking longer than usual.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to an operation update provided on May 23, Multichain <a href="https://multichain.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/7036431417103-Multichain-23-May-Operation-Update" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">The upgrade of the back-end node is taking longer than expected. Most of the routes are working as usual, as some routes (Kava, zkSync, Polygon zkEVM) are suspended temporarily for now. All the affected transactions will arrive once the upgrade is complete.</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, ongoing discussions on Multichain&#8217;s Telegram channel as of May 24 revealed that all but one router was undergoing an upgrade. One of the admins in the group said, &#8220;Only one router left in the upgrade progress. Other 6 routers work fine now,&#8221; with another one stating that the team was working on the final router and operations will be &#8220;back to normal once it is finished.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Multichain&#8217;s token MULTI has fallen over 24% in the last 24 hours, from $7.09 to $5.39, according to Coingecko. The crash in the token&#8217;s value could be a result of panic selling from holders.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Multichain Team Allegedly Arrested in China</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Lookonchain also reported that some investors have likely been <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1661351267795636224?t=Pa5WjYlSOalHbQpFjiAzWQ&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">selling</a> their multichain tokens.</p>
<p dir="ltr">One address deposited 494,200 MULTI (valued at $2.75 million) to the crypto exchange Gate.io on May 24. Digital asset financial services group Hashkey also transferred $247,000 worth of MULTI to the same crypto exchange today.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, an address with the ENS name hwg.eth sold over 36,000 MULTI tokens to get $200,000 on May 23. Notably, Fantom Foundation also <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1661356745367908358?t=q94iNZaMnKpha_PnO2ED9A&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recently removed</a> approximately 450,000 MULTI (worth $2.4 million) tokens from liquidity on SushiSwap.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Amid reports of delayed transactions and token price slump, there have also been rumors of the Chinese authorities arresting the Multichain project team and with over $1 billion in contract funds &#8220;under control.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">However, Multichain has neither confirmed nor refuted the ongoing rumors, but we shall give an update as this is a developing story.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multichain-token-crashes-over-20-amid-reports-of-users-funds-being-stuck/" rel="nofollow">Multichain Token Crashes Over 20% Amid Reports of Users&#8217; Funds Being Stuck</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hestia Launches a Blockchain-Based Freelance Platform, Redefining the Crypto Landscape</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/hestia-launches-a-blockchain-based-freelance-platform-redefining-the-crypto-landscape/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252186</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Banner_1684866399ZK5k8AfqMd.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Banner_1684866399ZK5k8AfqMd.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Marseille, France, May 24th, 2023] In an age where the crypto world is dominated by GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins, Hestia is revolutionizing the industry by demonstrating how cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology can be applied to traditional economic projects. Hestia, a groundbreaking decentralized freelance platform, is harnessing the power of decentralization [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Marseille, France, May 24th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>In an age where the crypto world is dominated by GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins, Hestia is revolutionizing the industry by demonstrating how cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology can be applied to traditional economic projects.</p>
<p><a href="https://hestia-project.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Hestia</a>, a groundbreaking decentralized freelance platform, is harnessing the power of decentralization to hustle the gig economy and empower freelancers and clients alike.</p>
<p>The Hestia project stands out from its crypto counterparts by focusing on real-world applications and creating a sustainable ecosystem for a broad range of industries. By leveraging the advantages of blockchain technology, Hestia offers an innovative economic model that enables fair distribution of power, wealth, and community governance.</p>
<h2>A New Economic Model: Decentralization at Its Core</h2>
<p>Hestia&#8217;s decentralized approach sets it apart from traditional freelance platforms, which often suffer from centralization issues and associated inefficiencies. By eliminating the need for a central authority, Hestia provides a more transparent, equitable, and efficient ecosystem for freelancers and clients to connect and collaborate.</p>
<p>Hestia&#8217;s dual-token system, comprising the stable HTX token and the growth-focused HTI token, enables seamless transactions within the platform while fostering the development of the ecosystem. The HTX token is indexed to USDT, providing a stable medium of exchange, while the HTI token is designed for use in exchanging HTX for other tokens or fiat currencies, as well as financing the Hestia ecosystem.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s unique tokenomics ensures that users can access its services without subscription fees or hidden costs. A modest 5% fee on token swaps between HTX and HTI is the only charge, which is used to support the platform&#8217;s ongoing operation, maintenance, and evolution.</p>
<p><strong>Community Governance: Empowering Users</strong></p>
<p>Hestia&#8217;s commitment to community governance allows users to participate directly in decision- making processes, creating a more inclusive, transparent, and democratic ecosystem. Token holders can vote on proposals, contribute to platform development, and help shape the future of the Hestia network.</p>
<p><strong>Bridging the Gap Between Crypto and Traditional Industries</strong></p>
<p>By combining the best of blockchain technology with a focus on real-world applications, Hestia is challenging the notion that cryptocurrencies are only suitable for niche projects like GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins. The platform&#8217;s innovative approach demonstrates how blockchain can transform traditional industries and drive meaningful change in people&#8217;s lives.</p>
<h2>About Hestia</h2>
<p>Hestia is a testament to the versatility and potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. By creating a decentralized, user-driven freelance platform, Hestia is paving the way for a more equitable, transparent, and efficient future for freelancers and clients around the globe.</p>
<p>For more information please visit the Hestia project, website: <a href="https://hestia-project.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://hestia-project.com/</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hestia-launches-a-blockchain-based-freelance-platform-redefining-the-crypto-landscape/" rel="nofollow">Hestia Launches a Blockchain-Based Freelance Platform, Redefining the Crypto Landscape</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Web3.Conference United Industry’s Brightest Minds in Amsterdam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-web3-conference-united-industrys-brightest-minds-in-amsterdam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252184</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Frame_890_1684929977AFYpJuMJI3.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Frame_890_1684929977AFYpJuMJI3.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 24th, 2023] The organizers of The Web3.Conference are celebrating a successful day-long event that brought together the industry’s leading lights. Held in Amsterdam on May 19th, the annual event from the AroundB team discussed hot topics and gathered industry insights from Web3 experts. With more than 20 speakers, four [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 24th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>The organizers of <a href="https://www.theweb3.wtf/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">The Web3.Conference</a> are celebrating a successful day-long event that brought together the industry’s leading lights. Held in Amsterdam on May 19th, the annual event from the AroundB team discussed hot topics and gathered industry insights from Web3 experts.</p>
<p>With more than 20 speakers, four panel discussions, and six startup pitch sessions during seven hours, the agenda contained something to suit every guest. Mark Eid from <a href="https://qlindo.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Qlindo</a>, the main sponsor of the event, spoke about green real estate and renewable energy investment opportunities. The subject of how to invest in Web3 was continued by a lively panel discussion between Rachel Pipan (Maneuvre), Nick van der Heiden (Hodl), Sofia Chikara (4wrdtech), and Sandro Potenza (Global Coin Research).</p>
<p>Nirmala Shome’s (The Fabricant) speech was dedicated to Web3 fashion and its possibilities. The future of Web3 identity and social networks was covered by Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab) as well as panel participants Gijs Ertemann (Secret Network), Joonatan Lintala, (Phaver), Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab), Nico Gallardo (Troop Labs), and Sara Anna Mamel (KILT Protocol).</p>
<p>An intense panel discussion titled “The Role of NFTs and the Metaverse in Web3” was conducted by Nishera Sachdev from Luna PR, Lianna Adams (Web3/NFT GTM Advisor), Cosmin Gafta (YOM), and Mickelle Weber (House of Peregrine). The topic “Metaverses as Jurisdictions” was led by James Haft (DLTX), while the section “Web3 Infrastructure: Building DAOs” was supported by Philippe Honigman (Mangrove DAO), Jamie Holmes (Perpetual Protocol), Soumaya Erradi (Scaling Parrots), Vincent Plaisier (The Graph AdvocatesDAO), and Ben Hoelzl (FTW DAO).</p>
<p>One of the special panels was dedicated to startups that presented their future-proofed vision: TrueBlocks, Rail, Ping, Tribal.market, Tide, Aidonic, and 1inch hardware wallet.</p>
<blockquote><p>Natalie Gavrilenko, AroundB CEO, said: “Thank you to everyone who attended. The AroundB team is grateful for every participant at The Web3.Conference. The goal of the event was to bring together people from different countries, with their own vision of the Web3 future, to share their thoughts with the audience, and make our own impact on the Web3 development industry.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The Web3.Conference was held in Felix Meritis, known for its winning design by the architect Jacob Otten Husly. He built it for a new society called Felix Meritis that was established in 1776 for Music, Drawing, Physics, Commerce and Literature in the modern neo-classical style.</p>
<p>AroundB thanks the main sponsor of the event <a href="https://qlindo.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Qlindo</a> that bridges the gap between blockchain and green real estate investment opportunities, paving the way to a sustainable future, and thanks all the participants, speakers, and media partners for making this event happen.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-web3-conference-united-industrys-brightest-minds-in-amsterdam/" rel="nofollow">The Web3.Conference United Industry’s Brightest Minds in Amsterdam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tulipart.com Launches a Collection of Tulip NFTs Minted Daily Over 7 Years</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252193</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/tulip2_1684933180JYp6q6vxc8.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/tulip2_1684933180JYp6q6vxc8.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Zug, Switzerland, May 24th, 2023] Tulipart.com is a collection of 10,000 unique tulip NFTs. Over a period of 7 years, 4 Tulip NFTs will be minted every day until the goal of 10,000 is reached. Each Tulip NFT consists of six different components, which range from common to exclusive, making them more [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Zug, Switzerland, May 24th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://www.tulipart.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Tulipart.com</a> is a collection of 10,000 unique tulip NFTs. Over a period of 7 years, 4 Tulip NFTs will be minted every day until the goal of 10,000 is reached. Each Tulip NFT consists of six different components, which range from common to exclusive, making them more or less rare.</p>
<p>New Tulip NFTs aren&#8217;t available for direct purchase; they are solely distributed to $LAND token holders via a lottery system. Participation involves holding and staking $LAND tokens. Staking a higher amount of $LAND tokens elevates the chances of acquiring a Tulip NFT each day.</p>
<p>$LAND tokens may be procured at no cost via the ongoing airdrop at <a href="http://Tulipart.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Tulipart.com</a>. Any Ethereum address holder can verify their participation eligibility. Ineligibility for the airdrop doesn&#8217;t impede the opportunity to procure $LAND on Uniswap, effectively enhancing the probability of winning a Tulip NFT.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/48fPAzeqcLg?showinfo=0"></iframe></div></p>
<h2>About Tulipart</h2>
<p>Tulipart.com is a cutting-edge platform fostering the innovation and creativity within the cryptocurrency and NFT landscapes. Based in Zug, Switzerland, a global hub for blockchain technology, Tulipart.com is the epicenter of a unique collection of 10,000 one-of-a-kind tulip NFTs, set to be minted over a period of seven years.</p>
<p>Those interested can visit <a href="http://www.tulipart.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Tulipart.com</a> to claim their $LAND tokens, stake them, and win a Tulip NFT.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tulipart-com-launches-a-collection-of-tulip-nfts-minted-daily-over-7-years/" rel="nofollow">Tulipart.com Launches a Collection of Tulip NFTs Minted Daily Over 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Lending Protocol Fintoch Reportedly Rug Pulls Investors for $31.6M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defi-lending-protocol-fintoch-reportedly-rug-pulls-investors-for-31-6m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252101</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Rug_Pull_2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Rug_Pull_2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The DeFi platform disappeared with over $30M of users' assets after claiming it was affiliated with multinational banking giant Morgan Stanley. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fintoch, a decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol that offers peer-to-peer (P2P) lending and investment services, has absconded with $31.6 million in cryptocurrencies belonging to investors in an apparent exit scam.</p>
<p>Multiple tweets from Fintoch users complaining about being unable to withdraw their assets were seen on Twitter earlier today, confirming suspicions that the platform had vanished with investors’ funds.</p>
<h2>Fintoch Rug Pulls Users</h2>
<p>Famous Web3 expert and on-chain analyst ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1661129110062788608?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> the rug pull on Twitter late Tuesday, suggesting that the team behind Fintoch had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/largest-exit-scam-on-arbitrum-hope-finance-drained-for-2m/" data-wpel-link="internal">scammed</a> users on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC).</p>
<p>Zach disclosed that Fintoch had <a href="https://bscscan.com/tx/0xa5e64161928ee40f6af02a32fc5c1fb9efa05cca6b91d88326279329b71c7ea2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">transferred</a> 31.6 million worth of Tether (USDT) to multiple addresses on the Tron and Ethereum networks on May 22 around 12:58 pm UTC. The platform’s move caused panic among investors as they reported being unable to withdraw their assets.</p>
<p>Following Fintoch’s silence on the withdrawal issue, several users flocked to the comment section of the platform’s last tweet, published on May 23, demanding an explanation. Users who tried to reach out to the company via its customer support channel were greeted with automated responses.</p>
<h2>A Ponzi Scheme?</h2>
<p>Fintoch lured investors with the promise of a 1% daily return on investment (ROI) and claims of affiliation with American multinational investment banking and financial services company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/morgan-stanley-publishes-comprehensive-cryptocurrency-guide-for-wealth-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal">Morgan Stanley.</a></p>
<p>However, Morgan Stanley <a href="https://www.morganstanley.com/content/dam/msdotcom/global-offices/pdf/Indonesia/Indonesia_Fintoch_Important_Notice.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">debunked</a> any affiliations with Fintoch, clarifying that it had no relationship with the DeFi protocol, which used its trademark without authorization. The multinational firm distanced itself from any responsibility pertaining to transactions or results that would arise from Fintoch.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) added Fintoch to its Investor Alert List earlier this month. The list contained firms that “may have been wrongly perceived as being licensed or in any other way authorized or regulated by MAS.”</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Zach argued that Bob Lambert, the CEO of Fintoch – as <a href="https://www.fintoch.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stated</a> on the platform’s website – does not exist and is a paid actor.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-lending-protocol-fintoch-reportedly-rug-pulls-investors-for-31-6m/" rel="nofollow">DeFi Lending Protocol Fintoch Reportedly Rug Pulls Investors for $31.6M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
