<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Sun Sets on Venezuela’s Petro – Is the State-backed Crypto Now ‘Dead?’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sun-sets-on-venezuelas-petro-is-the-state-backed-crypto-now-dead.htm</link><description>The sun may have set on Venezuela’s crypto dream, experts say – with some claiming that the nation’s oil-pegged Petro coin may be “dead.” &lt;br /&gt;
The coin was launched in October 2018, and made headlines when its masterminds claimed it was the first state-backed cryptoasset. &lt;br /&gt;
The government said that the coin was backed by oil, albeit reserves that had yet to be drilled....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sun-sets-on-venezuelas-petro-is-the-state-backed-crypto-now-dead.htm"&gt;Read More: Sun Sets on Venezuela’s Petro – Is the State-backed Crypto Now ‘Dead?’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Venezuela</category><category>Petro</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sun-sets-on-venezuelas-petro-is-the-state-backed-crypto-now-dead.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118596/315995/adobestock-402165830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="491628"/></item><item><title>Belarus Looks to Ban P2P Crypto Trading – Crackdown Incoming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-looks-ban-p2p-crypto-trading-crackdown-incoming.htm</link><description>Belarus is set to ban peer-to-peer (P2P) crypto “exchanges” – in a blow to traders operating in the country. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Telegram post from the Ministry of Internal Affairs, government officials said they were “preparing proposals for legislation” that would “prohibit the exchange of cryptocurrency between individuals in Belarus.” &lt;br /&gt;
The ministry said that it wants to “legally prohibit transactions for the exchange of cryptocurrencies.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-looks-ban-p2p-crypto-trading-crackdown-incoming.htm"&gt;Read More: Belarus Looks to Ban P2P Crypto Trading – Crackdown Incoming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Belarus</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-looks-ban-p2p-crypto-trading-crackdown-incoming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118532/315898/blrus-0207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="360332"/></item><item><title>Nasdaq Submits Revised Application for BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF to SEC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-submits-revised-application-for-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-sec.htm</link><description>What NASDAQ has resubmitted an application to the SEC for the listing of a Bitcoin ETF by BlackrockWhy The SEC had raised concerns last week about the details of the original submissionWhat Next The SEC has not provided a date for its final decision &lt;br /&gt;
Nasdaq has resubmitted an application to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to list a bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) by BlackRock. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-submits-revised-application-for-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-sec.htm"&gt;Read More: Nasdaq Submits Revised Application for BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF to SEC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nasdaq-submits-revised-application-for-blackrocks-bitcoin-etf-sec.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118600/316012/istockphoto-1293330840-61.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260827"/></item><item><title>Coinbase to Partner with Fidelity and Other Bitcoin ETFs for Surveillance – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-partner-with-fidelity-other-bitcoin-etfs-for-surveillance-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Last week, a Wall Street Journal (WSJ) report unveiled the dissatisfaction of SEC insiders with the recent batch of spot bitcoin ETF applications from prominent financial institutions like Blackrock, Wisdomtree, Valkyrie, Fidelity, Ark Investment, and Invesco.  &lt;br /&gt;
Following this revelation, four of the firms mentioned, namely Fidelity, Vaneck, Invesco, and Wisdomtree took action and resubmitted their filings....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-partner-with-fidelity-other-bitcoin-etfs-for-surveillance-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase to Partner with Fidelity and Other Bitcoin ETFs for Surveillance – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Etf Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-partner-with-fidelity-other-bitcoin-etfs-for-surveillance-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118598/316007/pexels-jonathan-borba-148.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="284287"/></item><item><title>Hut 8 Is Keen On AI Computing As It Relocates 6,400 Rigs, Eyes Growth Amid Legal Battle</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hut-8-keen-ai-computing-as-it-relocates-6400-rigs-eyes-growth-amid-legal-battles.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) mining firm Hut 8 has announced plans to relocate 6,400 rigs from its facility in Ontario, Canada as the demand for AI and high-performance computing surges.  &lt;br /&gt;
This is part of the firm’s wider plan to revive its dwindling activities after it faced a few hurdles including a legal tussle with its third-party energy supplier Validus back in Nov 2022 leading to a closure of the facility. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hut-8-keen-ai-computing-as-it-relocates-6400-rigs-eyes-growth-amid-legal-battles.htm"&gt;Read More: Hut 8 Is Keen On AI Computing As It Relocates 6,400 Rigs, Eyes Growth Amid Legal Battle&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Hut 8</category><category>Miners</category><category>AI</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hut-8-keen-ai-computing-as-it-relocates-6400-rigs-eyes-growth-amid-legal-battles.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118544/315938/bitcoin-g56f7dfef7-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="213602"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 3, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Pogai (POGAI) &lt;br /&gt;
BinanceListings:Pendle (PENDLE)Added Trading Pairs:BCH/TUSDCFX/TUSD...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 3, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118551/315940/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange OKX Signs $70 Million Deal to Become Official Sleeve Sponsor of Manchester City</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-okx-signs-70-million-deal-become-official-sleeve-sponsor-of-manchester-city.htm</link><description>The crypto exchange OKX has signed a sponsorship deal with the English football club Manchester City to become its “official sleeve partner.” &lt;br /&gt;
The new sponsorship deal marks an expansion of OKX’s existing deal as Manchester City’s “Official Training Kit Partner” for the 2022 to 2023 season, an announcement from Manchester City on Friday said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-okx-signs-70-million-deal-become-official-sleeve-sponsor-of-manchester-city.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange OKX Signs $70 Million Deal to Become Official Sleeve Sponsor of Manchester City&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>OKX</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-okx-signs-70-million-deal-become-official-sleeve-sponsor-of-manchester-city.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118581/315982/manchester-city.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="417039"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Aims to Modernize Direct Deposit Systems via Blockchain Stablecoin Settlements</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-aims-modernize-direct-deposit-systems-via-blockchain-stablecoin-settlements.htm</link><description>Coinbase has said it wants to modernize its direct deposit system using blockchain-based stablecoin settlements instead of the traditional ACH deposits. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a blog post written by Yuga Cohler, a senior software engineer at Coinbase, the company's goal is to update the financial system and promote the adoption of crypto worldwide, with a focus on consumer rights and security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-aims-modernize-direct-deposit-systems-via-blockchain-stablecoin-settlements.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Aims to Modernize Direct Deposit Systems via Blockchain Stablecoin Settlements&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-aims-modernize-direct-deposit-systems-via-blockchain-stablecoin-settlements.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118575/315976/stablecoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1845553"/></item><item><title>BNY Mellon, Franklin Templeton Heads to Co-Chair New Digital Asset Panel</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bny-mellon-franklin-templeton-heads-to-co-chair-new-digital-asset-panel.htm</link><description>BNY Mellon and Franklin Templeton have been appointed as co-chairs of the new Digital Assets Market Subcommittee by the US derivatives and commodities regulator.  &lt;br /&gt;
Caroline Butler, the global head of digital assets at BNY Mellon, and Sandy Kaul, the head of digital and industry advisory services at Franklin Templeton, will lead the subcommittee, which focuses specifically on digital assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bny-mellon-franklin-templeton-heads-to-co-chair-new-digital-asset-panel.htm"&gt;Read More: BNY Mellon, Franklin Templeton Heads to Co-Chair New Digital Asset Panel&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>BNY Mellon</category><category>Franklin Templeton</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bny-mellon-franklin-templeton-heads-to-co-chair-new-digital-asset-panel.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118580/315980/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="203716"/></item><item><title>Regulatory Investigation Targets South Korean Crypto Lender Delio</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulatory-investigation-targets-south-korean-crypto-lender-delio.htm</link><description>South Korea-based Delio is currently under scrutiny as the country's Financial Services Commission (FSC) investigates the crypto lending firm for alleged fraud, embezzlement, and breach of trust. &lt;br /&gt;
According to reports from local news outlet Digital Asset, the investigation sprouts from Delio's unilateral decision to suspend users' deposits and withdrawals on June 14, raising concerns among investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/regulatory-investigation-targets-south-korean-crypto-lender-delio.htm"&gt;Read More: Regulatory Investigation Targets South Korean Crypto Lender Delio&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>South Korea</category><category>South Korean</category><category>FSA</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulatory-investigation-targets-south-korean-crypto-lender-delio.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118557/315948/skorea.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="148647"/></item><item><title>Why are NFT Prices Crashing? Azuki Plummets 11% and Bored Apes Falls 16% – Here's What You Need to Know.</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-are-nft-prices-crashing-azuki-plummets-11-bored-apes-falls-16-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The NFT market has recently witnessed a price decline, causing concern among investors and enthusiasts. Several prominent NFTs have experienced significant price declines within the past few days.  &lt;br /&gt;
One notable example is the Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), whose decline in the NFTs floor prices can be attributed to the community backlash that followed the Azuki Elementals drop last week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/why-are-nft-prices-crashing-azuki-plummets-11-bored-apes-falls-16-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Why are NFT Prices Crashing? Azuki Plummets 11% and Bored Apes Falls 16% – Here's What You Need to Know.&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-are-nft-prices-crashing-azuki-plummets-11-bored-apes-falls-16-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118569/315970/screenshot-2023-07-03-160003.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1595741"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 3 July – Compound, The Graph, Filecoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-3-july-compound-graph-filecoin.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH) are both trading with a positive bias amid a quiet start to the week. &lt;br /&gt;
BTC was last hovering in the upper $30,000s, close to its recent highs above $31,000, while ETH just hit its highest level since May in the $1,970s, with the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency looking to retest the $2,000 level. &lt;br /&gt;
Tuesday is independence day in the US, so crypto trading volumes will likely be low amid market closures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-3-july-compound-graph-filecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 3 July – Compound, The Graph, Filecoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>The Graph</category><category>GRT</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>FIL</category><category>Compound</category><category>COMP</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-3-july-compound-graph-filecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118573/315974/bestcrypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="291846"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: South Korea Passes the Virtual Asset User Protection Legislation, Poly Network Exploit Affected 57 Cryptos on 10 Blockchains, Crypto Miners Are Turning to AI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-south-korea-passes-the-virtual-asset-user-protection-legislation-poly-network-exploit-affected-57-cryptos-on-10-blockchains-crypto-miners-are-turning-to-ai.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-south-korea-passes-the-virtual-asset-user-protection-legislation-poly-network-exploit-affected-57-cryptos-on-10-blockchains-crypto-miners-are-turning-to-ai.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: South Korea Passes the Virtual Asset User Protection Legislation, Poly Network Exploit Affected 57 Cryptos on 10 Blockchains, Crypto Miners Are Turning to AI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Thailand</category><category>SEC</category><category>Security</category><category>Hack</category><category>PeckShield</category><category>NFT</category><category>Mining</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-south-korea-passes-the-virtual-asset-user-protection-legislation-poly-network-exploit-affected-57-cryptos-on-10-blockchains-crypto-miners-are-turning-to-ai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118541/315964/adobestock-agnormark-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="255991"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Blasts Up 22% in a Week – Can LTC Reach $1,000?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-blasts-up-22-week-can-ltc-reach-1000.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC), the cryptocurrency that powers the decentralized payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, is consolidating just under $110 after hitting its highest level in over a year earlier in the session at $113.61. &lt;br /&gt;
As per crypto price data website CoinGecko, LTC is up an impressive 22% in the last seven days, making it the eighth best-performing cryptocurrency in the top 100 by market cap over this period....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-blasts-up-22-week-can-ltc-reach-1000.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Blasts Up 22% in a Week – Can LTC Reach $1,000?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-blasts-up-22-week-can-ltc-reach-1000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118571/315966/ltc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="554228"/></item><item><title>Hive Blockchain to Allow AI Training, Cites Superior Privacy Over OpenAI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hive-blockchain-allow-ai-training-cites-superior-privacy-over-openai.htm</link><description>Hive Blockchain (HIVE), a major Bitcoin mining farm, intends to provide customers with access to its data centers, where they could train large language AI models.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to the company, its solution offers much better privacy, compared to rivals like OpenAI’s ChatGPT.  &lt;br /&gt;
During an earnings call, the company shared its intentions last Friday, June 30th. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the firm’s CEO and President, Aydin Kilic, ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hive-blockchain-allow-ai-training-cites-superior-privacy-over-openai.htm"&gt;Read More: Hive Blockchain to Allow AI Training, Cites Superior Privacy Over OpenAI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hive-blockchain-allow-ai-training-cites-superior-privacy-over-openai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118552/315943/hive-blockchain-to-allow-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="180123"/></item><item><title>DeGods NFT Project Ditches 'Stupid' Roadmaps, Embraces 'Early Facebook' Vibes for Next Moves</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/degods-nft-project-ditches-stupid-roadmaps-embraces-early-facebook-vibes-for-next-moves.htm</link><description>Creator of PFP NFT projects DeGods and Yoots, DeLabs, has launched a new website ahead of the upcoming unveiling of its DeGods Season III and yoots2 feature expansion in July 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptic website appears inspired by the early Facebook days. DeLabs founder Rohun Frank Vora dubbed the site "performance art."  &lt;br /&gt;
The website would be an alternative to the conventional written roadmap approach, which it claimed is obtuse. According to the website, “Roadmaps are stupid.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/degods-nft-project-ditches-stupid-roadmaps-embraces-early-facebook-vibes-for-next-moves.htm"&gt;Read More: DeGods NFT Project Ditches 'Stupid' Roadmaps, Embraces 'Early Facebook' Vibes for Next Moves&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/degods-nft-project-ditches-stupid-roadmaps-embraces-early-facebook-vibes-for-next-moves.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118566/315959/nfts.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="242742"/></item><item><title>Flow Price Prediction as $300 Million Pushes FLOW Up 35% – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/flow-price-prediction-as-300-million-pushes-flow-up-35-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>FLOW, the cryptocurrency that powers the NFT-focused Flow blockchain, has continued its strong rebound from the all-time lows it hit in June. &lt;br /&gt;
FLOW was last trading close to $0.75, up a further 4% on the day and up around 35% in the last seven....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/flow-price-prediction-as-300-million-pushes-flow-up-35-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Flow Price Prediction as $300 Million Pushes FLOW Up 35% – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FLOW</category><category>Flow blockchain</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/flow-price-prediction-as-300-million-pushes-flow-up-35-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118562/315956/flow.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="521699"/></item><item><title>Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Platform Raise $1.4 Million – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-raise-14-million-time-buy.htm</link><description>DeeLance has recently achieved a remarkable milestone in its ongoing presale.  &lt;br /&gt;
The platform, designed to revolutionize the recruitment industry, has successfully raised an impressive $1.46 million in the presale of its native token, $DLANCE. &lt;br /&gt;
This outstanding achievement has garnered significant attention from crypto analysts, who predict a tremendous growth trajectory for the Web3-powered token in the coming days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-raise-14-million-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Platform Raise $1.4 Million – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-raise-14-million-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118556/315947/deelance-ai-raises-1-4mil.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="435761"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Price Pumps Up 50% While AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Raises $2.7 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-pumps-up-50-while-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm</link><description>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) is holding close to the $300 level after an intense melt-up in the last few weeks. &lt;br /&gt;
BCH/USD was last changing hands around $291, down a little on the day amid a subdued tone to broader cryptocurrency market trade. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite now trading around 10% lower versus last Friday’s more than one-year peaks around $330, BCH is still up more than 200% versus earlier monthly lows around $90....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-pumps-up-50-while-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Price Pumps Up 50% While AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Raises $2.7 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin Cash</category><category>BCH</category><category>Is It Too Late</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-price-pumps-up-50-while-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118558/315951/bch.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4550909"/></item><item><title>Report: Over $204 Million Lost to DeFi Hacks and Scams in Q2</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-over-204-million-lost-defi-hacks-scams-q2.htm</link><description>More than $204 million was lost in various hacks and scams in the decentralized finance (DeFi) space during the second quarter of 2023, a new report by crypto portfolio app De.Fi has found. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the report, the initial loss for the quarter was as high as $208.5 million before $4.5 million were recovered through law enforcement action and deals with hackers....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/report-over-204-million-lost-defi-hacks-scams-q2.htm"&gt;Read More: Report: Over $204 Million Lost to DeFi Hacks and Scams in Q2&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-over-204-million-lost-defi-hacks-scams-q2.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118553/315946/hack.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="208736"/></item></channel></rss>
