<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance&#8217;s Yi He Speaks About SEC Battle and Her Relationship With CZ</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binances-yi-he-speaks-about-sec-battle-and-her-relationship-with-cz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 11:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258010</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1200x-1-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1200x-1-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance’s lowkey profile is one of the most powerful women in crypto, as well as the mother of CZ’s children.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A low-profile but highly influential senior executive at Binance has spoken out as the company begins legal battles against two top market regulators in the United States.</p>
<p>Yi He, who boasts a massive fortune as one of the company’s early shareholders, has also had children with Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ).</p>
<h2>The SEC Lawsuit</h2>
<p>He <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-s-most-powerful-woman-speaks-out-as-crisis-rocks-binance-1.1939022" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">spoke</a> to Bloomberg in a series of interviews – one of which took place in Dubai last month, shortly before the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">136-page lawsuit</a> against her company.</p>
<p>At that time, the Commodities and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) had already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-binance-and-cz-being-accused-of-a-closer-look-at-the-cftc-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> the company on some overlapping charges, such as serving U.S.-based customers from its international platform. He struck a conciliatory tone with such regulators, saying she respects their “attitude” and “intentions.”</p>
<p>Nevertheless, she still thinks their actions are misguided. “If they really took the time to understand our industry, they would see that if Binance isn’t compliant, then practically no other global trading platform or offshore company is,” she said.</p>
<p>Binance published a <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/community/playing-by-the-rules-an-overview-of-binances-compliance-program-7787599269355947143" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> on Thursday outlining the lengths to which it tries to remain legally compliant worldwide. The company’s 8000-person workforce includes “750 core and supporting compliance staff” consisting of “former law enforcement officers, regulators, crypto, fintech, and traditional banking compliance experts.”</p>
<p>The exchange is known for having no formal headquarters, thus making it theoretically harder to sue or regulate. It’s also been criticized for being shrouded in opacity, from its governance structure to its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-responds-to-reuters-claims-about-mixing-user-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">handling</a> of client assets.</p>
<p>According to He, Binance offers more transparency than its critics often claim and strives to cooperate with regulators rather than evade them. “The trend of regulations is inevitable globally,&#8221; she said. &#8220;It&#8217;s not something you can solve by shouting ‘fight’ a couple of times.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Yi He and CZ: What’s Going On?</h2>
<p>He’s history with CZ stretches back years to her time at OKCoin in 2014, where she later hired him as a Chief Technology Officer (CTO). CZ later asked her to be a consultant at Binance in 2017, where she helped rewrite parts of the company’s whitepaper.</p>
<p>She’s also the mother of CZ’s children – an open secret among crypto industry insiders. “What do they call it in the entertainment industry? CP?” she said when questioned on the topic. CP is a Chinese internet slang term for ‘shipping.’</p>
<p>He referred to Zhao less as a romantic partner and more as a “comrade in arms,” rejecting comparisons of their relationship to that of failed FTX and Alameda CEOs Sam Bankman-Fried and Caroline Ellison.</p>
<p>In fact, He claimed she and CZ’s relationship went beyond dating in some capacity. “A co-founder relationship is about comradeship, a dating relationship is about chemistry. The former is based on shared beliefs and goes beyond gender, the latter is based on physical attraction and selfish desires,” she said.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy Of Bloomberg</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binances-yi-he-speaks-about-sec-battle-and-her-relationship-with-cz/" rel="nofollow">Binance&#8217;s Yi He Speaks About SEC Battle and Her Relationship With CZ</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin (LTC) Soars to 14-Month High Above $100, Bitcoin (BTC) Reclaims $30K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-ltc-soars-to-14-month-high-above-100-bitcoin-btc-reclaims-30k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258059</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BitcoinSV is today's best performer from the top 50 with a 18% surge. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin went on a short-lived roller-coaster yesterday but has reclaimed $30,000 after dumping to a 10-day low.</p>
<p>Yet, its dominance over the altcoins has declined a lot on a daily scale, as some, such as LTC, LDO, VET, and BSV, have shot up.</p>
<h2>BTC&#8217;s Dump and Pump</h2>
<p>After last week&#8217;s massive price surge, which drove bitcoin from $26,500 to over $31,000 at one point, the cryptocurrency had calmed and remained in a tighter range between $30,000 and $31,000.</p>
<p>It tried to overcome the latter yesterday when the bulls drove it to a daily high of $31,250. Despite failing there, it initially lost only $200 and remained above $31,000 for a few hours.</p>
<p>However, it all changed after a WSJ <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> emerged claiming that the SEC deemed the recent BTC Spot ETF filings, from the likes of BlackRock and Fidelity, as &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;</p>
<p>Bitcoin reacted with an immediate price drop that drove it south by $1,500 to a 10-day low of $29,500. However, the bulls stepped up once again and recovered almost all losses, with BTC currently sitting around a grand higher.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization stands close to $600 billion as of now, but its dominance over the alts has taken a major hit and is down below 50%. In fact, the metric has declined by almost 1% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258060" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258060" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258060" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258060" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LTC Sees 14-Month High</h2>
<p><em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoins-hash-rate-hits-ath-as-halving-countdown-narrows-and-ltc-nears-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> yesterday that Litecoin&#8217;s price action drove it to a multi-month high of its own, just under $100. This comes as the network&#8217;s hash rate jumped to an ATH ahead of the next halving. However, the landscape for LTC holders changed for the better once again in the past 24 hours as the asset soared to over $110 for the first time since April 2022.</p>
<p>Dogecoin, Polkadot, Ethereum Classic, and Lido DAO are the other notable performers from the larger-cap alts, with gains of up to 7% daily.</p>
<p>BitcoinSV has skyrocketed the most from the top 50 alts, having surged by 18% to over $50.</p>
<p>ETH and BNB are up by 1.5% and sit above $1,900 and $240, respectively.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has remained relatively stagnant at just under $1.2 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_258061" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258061" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-258061" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="843" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1024x459.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-768x345.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-1536x689.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258061" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-ltc-soars-to-14-month-high-above-100-bitcoin-btc-reclaims-30k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Litecoin (LTC) Soars to 14-Month High Above $100, Bitcoin (BTC) Reclaims $30K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Name Service Gears up for Layer 2 Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-gears-up-for-layer-2-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 05:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257965</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There are nearly 700,000 owners of ENS domains.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Name Service &#8211; the distributed, open, and extensible naming system operating on the Ethereum blockchain &#8211; announced plans for Layer 2 expansion.</p>
<p>The growing popularity of Ethereum significantly increased gas prices forcing market participants to look for cost-effective alternatives. Ethereum Name Service (ENS) is one such project that had earlier said that Layer 2 interoperability has been on the pipeline for quite some time via &#8211; ENSIP-10: Wildcard Resolution and EIP-3668: CCIP Read: Secure offchain data retrieval.</p>
<ul>
<li>On a community <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iKXtWaVn-tM" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">call</a> this week, the team behind ENS emphasized the importance of the upgrade that would lead to Layer 2 expansion to improve scalability and reduce costs.</li>
<li>They said facilitating the interaction of existing solutions with ENS domains would help in domain name registrations and transactions becoming more accessible to a wider user base.</li>
<li>Going forward, the devs behind the Ethereum-based naming system intend to leverage off-chain resolvers via an ENS off-chain registrar contract and different service providers, such as Coinbase-operated project cb.id, Polygon-based Lens Protocol, Optimism-based OptiNames, etc.</li>
<li>Unfazed by the market turmoil in the digital asset space last year, ENS <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-ens-wrapped-2022-with-over-2-2m-registrations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">clocked</a> in more than 2.2 million domain names.</li>
<li>The figure has been on a steady rise and currently stands at 2.73 million across nearly 700,000 unique addresses.</li>
<li>ENS <a href="https://www.moonpay.com/newsroom/ens" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">rolled</a> out a new fiat on-ramp for domain registrations via Web3 fiat payment gateway MoonPay in April this year.</li>
<li>The move enabled Web3 users to register decentralized .eth domains on the platform using various popular fiat payment options, such as Apple Pay and Google Pay, in addition to debit and credit cards as well.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-gears-up-for-layer-2-expansion/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Name Service Gears up for Layer 2 Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase&#8217;s Base Applies Security First Mindset Ahead of Mainnet Launch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-applies-security-first-mindset-ahead-of-mainnet-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 22:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257878</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exact date for Base's mainnet launch has not been revealed yet.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase&#8217;s developed Layer 2 network &#8211; Base &#8211; is gearing up for a mainnet launch. Since its deployment on testnet earlier this year, Base has already met 4 out of 5 of the criteria for the upcoming event while giving security the top-most priority in its goal to attract the next million developers and a billion users on-chain.</p>
<p>As such, the team tasked with protocol security has doubled down efforts to improve the security of Base and Optimism over the last six months. The experts haven&#8217;t detected any major flaws so far.</p>
<h2>Base&#8217;s Security First Mindset</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://base.mirror.xyz/_SiAx8dQRYJJ4lygkJc0QvBKvf16VVm7_-mdWMdFv20" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, the devs have audited all Optimism pre-deploys and contracts on both L1 and L2 to detect bugs and risks in the technology stack.</p>
<p>&#8216;Fuzzing&#8217; methods were leveraged for critical components such as the L2 bridge and the sequencer in addition to developing operational runbooks for different kinds of risk scenarios as well as distress events.</p>
<p>The team also reviewed and audited the key management setup and contracts for Base.</p>
<p>Following the completion of these audits, no critical severity bugs were discovered by over 100 external security researchers that were employed for the purpose. This boosted Base&#8217;s confidence to proceed toward the mainnet launch, the platform said in a statement.</p>
<p>The team is currently working on ensuring appropriate action for any informative or minor issues that were reported during the process.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our goal with all our security work is to see around corners and blunt the effectiveness of these attacks. We’re proud of the work we’ve done to secure Base and while even the best controls will sometimes fail, we will always learn and do better.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Going Foward</h2>
<p>Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launch-eth-layer-2-network-based-on-optimism-op-token-pumps-6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> its own Ethereum layer-2 network in February, which is being developed in collaboration with Optimism. Its mainnet launch is slated for sometime in 2023. As part of the agreement, the crypto exchange joined Optimism as a core dev on the open-source OP Stack.</p>
<p>Moving forward, Base revealed the addition of an open-source monitoring tool, dubbed Pessimism, which is designed to notify builders of any anomalies such as account balance irregularities, contract events, or disparities between L1 and L2 states.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the new tool will be put alongside existing OP Labs monitoring tools, Coinbase&#8217;s native blockchain monitoring capabilities, as well as third-party tools for detecting malicious and out-of-pattern events.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-applies-security-first-mindset-ahead-of-mainnet-launch/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase&#8217;s Base Applies Security First Mindset Ahead of Mainnet Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Citigroup Reviews Partnership With Ripple-Owned Metaco: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/citigroup-reviews-partnership-with-ripple-owned-metaco-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 20:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257934</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Citibank.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Citibank.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It is not known if Ripple's takeover is connected to this. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American multinational investment giant &#8211; Citigroup Inc. &#8211; is reportedly reviewing its partnership with Metaco. The Swiss firm, which specializes in crypto custody for institutional investors, had partnered with Citi a year back to develop and pilot the latter&#8217;s digital asset custody capabilities.</p>
<p>The latest development comes amidst tumultuous market conditions that have significantly strained the relationships of traditional financial firms that tapped into the digital assets industry.</p>
<h2>Strain in Citi and Metaco&#8217;s Relationship?</h2>
<p>According to Bloomberg&#8217;s sources familiar with the matter, both Citi and Metaco have <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/citigroup-reviews-partnership-with-crypto-custodian-metaco-1.1939963" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">started</a> informal talks with other providers. However, the deliberations are private, and hence, the sources have chosen to remain anonymous.</p>
<p>The reason for the decision has not been revealed yet, as a Citi representative declined to comment. The latest wave of uncertainty that has gripped the crypto industry induced several of its dedicated banking partners to go under or step back from crypto firms.</p>
<p>The report cited examples such as the recently-launched platform EDX Markets, a crypto exchange backed by firms including Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, and Charles Schwab Corp., that scrapped its plan to leverage Paxos as a custodian.</p>
<p>Similarly, banking giant State Street Corp. also ended its licensing agreement with crypto custody firm Copper last month, thereby winding down its enterprise infrastructure business to bridge banks and hedge funds with digital assets. Copper&#8217;s association with State Street lasted for over a year since its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/state-street-partners-with-copper-to-offer-crypto-custody-for-institutional-clients/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnership</a> last March.</p>
<h2>Ripple Partnership to Blame?</h2>
<p>Last month, blockchain firm Ripple <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-enters-a-250-million-deal-to-acquire-metaco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> spending $250 million to acquire Metaco in a bid to expand its services to enable customers custody their digital assets with its forthcoming product suite. Commenting on the development, Metaco Founder and CEO Adrien Treccani said that the acquisition will allow the Swiss company to scale up in the market.</p>
<p>But with Ripple itself being embroiled in a long-drawn lawsuit with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and custody becoming a bone of contention for the crypto industry, Citi&#8217;s decision to review the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citi-partners-with-metaco-for-digital-asset-custody-pilot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnership</a>, which has been in place since last summer, appears to be alarming.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citigroup-reviews-partnership-with-ripple-owned-metaco-report/" rel="nofollow">Citigroup Reviews Partnership With Ripple-Owned Metaco: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Will Begin Selling Altcoin Portfolio Into BTC and ETH</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-will-begin-selling-altcoin-portfolio-into-btc-and-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258014</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC’s crackdown on altcoins has pushed Celsius to alter its plan for distributing assets back to creditors. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius has been granted permission to begin liquidating its altcoins into Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This will occur before distributions to creditors take place, who expect to receive their assets denominated only in the top two cryptocurrencies by market cap. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">According to <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174906302380000000027.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Bankruptcy judge Martin Glenn</a>, Celsius “may sell or convert any non-BTC and non-ETH cryptocurrency, crypto tokens, or other cryptocurrency assets other than such tokens that are associated with Withhold or Custody accounts … to BTC or ETH commencing on or after July 1, 2023,”  </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The approval comes after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) named a slew of top altcoins as </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">unregistered securities</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in two major crypto industry lawsuits. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Celsius has been in contact with the SEC to “ensure that all such distributions are in full compliance with applicable federal and state laws and regulations,” the filing stated.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">A consortium of crypto investors called Farenheit </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-bankruptcy-struggles-coming-to-an-end-as-fahrenheit-clinches-win-in-auction/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">won an auction</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to acquire Celsius’ assets last month. The consortium includes US Bitcoin Corp, Proof Group Capital Management LLC, Ravi Kaza, former Algorand CEO Steven Kokinos, and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Celsius had a reported 1.7 million users when it failed last year, including 300,000 with balances of over $100. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-will-begin-selling-altcoin-portfolio-into-btc-and-eth/" rel="nofollow">Celsius Will Begin Selling Altcoin Portfolio Into BTC and ETH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Which Low Market Cap Crypto Might Have Upside Potential: Why Big Eyes Coin, RenQ Finance Failed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/which-low-market-cap-crypto-might-have-upside-potential-why-big-eyes-coin-renq-finance-failed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258023</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thuglife_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thuglife_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One issue facing many new cryptocurrency projects in 2023 is that they set a large hard cap target for their presale fundraising stage, then launched with a high market capitalization by the time of their IEO or IDO. Crypto presales that have several price stages of incentivizing early buyers with a discount also add to [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One issue facing many new cryptocurrency projects in 2023 is that they set a large hard cap target for their presale fundraising stage, then launched with a high market capitalization by the time of their IEO or IDO.</p>
<p>Crypto presales that have several price stages of incentivizing early buyers with a discount also add to that problem &#8211; inflating the market cap and FDV further and causing the common ‘ICO dump’ chart pattern in which early investors dump their coins on the market to take profit.</p>
<p>Analysts predict one upcoming low market cap crypto with huge potential upside is <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life Token</a> (THUG), based on it having just one price stage throughout its presale &#8211; $0.0007 &#8211; and a low hard cap of $2,058,000.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Thug Life Presale</a></p>
<h2>Big Eyes Price Prediction</h2>
<p>The Big Eyes crypto presale was one of the largest public token presales of 2023, initially setting a hard cap of 51.2 million USDT, and taking almost a year from its August 2022 launch to raise close to that, with various delays and other red flags.</p>
<p>The Big Eyes presale also set fifteen price stages, with a 600% increase built in, from $0.0001 to $0.0006, which incentivized early-stage investors to want to secure that profit. Its Uniswap listing in fact took place at a considerably lower price than the final presale stage price, also angering some investors.</p>
<p>However, even if it had been listed at $0.0006, with its 200 billion total supply that would mean a fully diluted market cap valuation (FDV) of $0.0006 x 200 billion = $120 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258026" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="758" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32-300x131.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap</a>, Big Eyes token would have then ranked as the 7th largest meme coin on the market instantly, with only Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, Pepe, FLOKI, Baby Doge Coin, and Bone ShibaSwap having a higher market capitalization &#8211; all of which launched much lower in their early development, before building up to a higher valuation.</p>
<p>Even if it had then held that market cap without a sell-off from early buyers looking to take profit, it would have limited upside potential &#8211; a less than 10x move would break the $1 billion mark, which very few meme coins are capable of, Pepe being one recent exception &#8211; and even Pepe has now retraced to a $600 million market cap.</p>
<p>Big Eyes coin currently has a market of $2 million and may struggle to recover to the upside and regain investor confidence after the issues surrounding its launch.</p>
<h2>RenQ Finance Price Prediction</h2>
<p>The RenQ Finance price chart is similar to that of the Big Eyes token &#8211; a post-ICO sell-off with few bounces. The RENQ market cap is currently $15 million, lower than its presale hard cap of $19.3 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258025" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="758" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30-300x131.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>The RenQ Finance presale had eight price stages, with the RENQ token price varying from $0.02 &#8211; $0.055, a 275% difference.</p>
<p>Having faced similar issues to Big Eyes coin over its launch and roadmap, the RenQ price forecast in the short term doesn’t appear bullish.</p>
<h2>Upside Potential of Low Market Cap Crypto Projects</h2>
<p>Many new meme coins that pump tend to have their blow-off top around the $100 million market cap level, even if they do have a successful launch and initial rally without investors immediately selling their tokens.</p>
<p>For that reason, it’s optimal to find low market cap cryptocurrencies &#8211; one launching at a $1 million market cap for example, will return a 100x ROI if reaching the psychological resistance level of $100 million.</p>
<p>A new coin launching at $2 million will return a 50x ROI, one launching at $20 million return only a 5x ROI, and so on. If early investors are also already in profit based on different presale stages, they make take profit earlier than expected.</p>
<h2>Thug Life Token Presale</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life presale</a> has a set a level playing field with just one presale price stage, and has a low hard cap of $2.058 million.</p>
<p>70% of the total token supply of 4.2 billion $THUG is also available to buy during the presale, with the liquidity pool locked for three months after launch.</p>
<p>15% of the supply is allocated to marketing, and 15% to community rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258024" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="758" height="381" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">thuglifetoken.com</a> website describes the meme coin project as a ‘second chance for those who have been played, influenced and used as a cash-out, leaving held tokens valueless in a blink of an eye.’</p>
<p>The project aims to build a movement fuelled by the ‘shared struggle of hustling this web3 world, turning the bitter landscape of dumped presales into a prosperous place’ &#8211; its community focus centers around addressing the issues faced by the crypto ICOs of this year.</p>
<p>Its liquidity pool is set to be locked by Team Finance, and its community rewards program will take the form of airdrops once $THUG is listed on its first DEX, Uniswap.</p>
<p>$THUG can be invested in prior to its listing at one single price &#8211; $0.0007 &#8211; using a MetaMask wallet and swapping ETH or USDT for $THUG.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, $150,000 has been raised in the 48 hours since the Thug Life presale’s launch, showing the high level of interest in its concept and tokenomics that aim to offer investors a higher potential ROI than other 2023 crypto presales.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Thug Life Presale</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/which-low-market-cap-crypto-might-have-upside-potential-why-big-eyes-coin-renq-finance-failed/" rel="nofollow">Which Low Market Cap Crypto Might Have Upside Potential: Why Big Eyes Coin, RenQ Finance Failed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Much Money Does it Take to ‘Moon’ Bitcoin? Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-money-does-it-take-to-moon-bitcoin-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257869</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/bitcoin_moon_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/bitcoin_moon_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoiners have many things to be bullish about in the next few months, but analysts think the ‘halving’ may not be one of them.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The resurgence of institutional interest in Bitcoin this month has investors and analysts pondering just how high its price could go within the next two years – especially with the ‘halving’ just around the corner.</p>
<p>Here’s what analysts have to say regarding Bitcoin’s price cycles and what kind of money it would take to send it to the moon.</p>
<h2>Institutional Involvement</h2>
<p>Throughout June, a number of high net-worth asset managers, including BlackRock and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">Fidelity</a>, filed applications to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States.</p>
<p>Major banks and investment managers, including BNY Melon, Invesco, Morgan Stanley, and others, have already dabbled in launching Bitcoin-related products, such as OTC trading or custody services.</p>
<p>When taking a look at some of the largest financial companies involved in the space already, their total assets under management come out to at least $27 trillion, according to Meltem Demirors – Chief Strategy Officer of CoinShares.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ last week&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/BlackRock?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@BlackRock</a> spot Bitcoin ETF filing was big news!</p>
<p>but, it&#8217;s not the only story. many of the largest financial institutions in the US are actively working to provide access to Bitcoin and more.</p>
<p>a quick glance &#8211; $27 trillion of client assets here! <a href="https://t.co/azmHZmUL2a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/azmHZmUL2a</a></p>
<p>— Meltem Demirors (@Melt_Dem) <a href="https://twitter.com/Melt_Dem/status/1673362112653975554?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Theoretically, Bitcoin’s price could multiply by several times if these firms enter the market with just a small fraction of their wealth – especially given the market’s current liquidity levels.</p>
<p>In an email to <em>CryptoPotato</em>, James Check – Lead On-chain analyst at Glassnode – explained that roughly 450,000 BTC (~$13.5 billion) are “highly active in spot markets and predominantly participate in price discovery.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is extremely difficult to measure a dollar in == market move, but this at least allows us to provide a range / bound the problem,” he said.</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2021, ARK Invest’s Cathie Wood – whose firm is also trying to launch a Bitcoin ETF – predicted that Bitcoin could reach $500,000 if institutional investors allocate 5% of their portfolios to the asset.</p>
<h2>HODLer Behaviour</h2>
<p>As Bitcoin’s price rises, it&#8217;s possible that prior investors choose to take profits by selling their assets, thus absorbing the bullish impact of any liquidity entering the market.</p>
<p>However, many market intelligence firms, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hodlers-increase-at-a-record-pace-santiment/" data-wpel-link="internal">Santiment</a> and Glassnode, have noted an “ongoing transfer of wealth from investors with high time preferences towards HODLers” in recent months. Meanwhile, Bitcoin on exchanges is also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-bitcoins-surge-above-30k-btc-on-exchanges-lowest-since-december-2017/" data-wpel-link="internal">lower than ever</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257870" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257870" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1-.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257870 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1024x590.png" alt="" width="1024" height="590" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1024x590.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--300x173.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--768x443.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1536x885.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--50x29.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1-.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257870" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Long and Short Term Holder Supply. Source: Glassnode</figcaption></figure>
<p>CryptoQuant data from this month appears to back this up, showing that long-term holders have largely reduced their selling activity over the past six months. “This change in LTH behavior may signal the beginning of a new bull cycle,” wrote analyst Axel Adler Jr in a <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/648eff282ec8802caad37154-The-Secret-Signal-of-Bitcoins-Rise-Why-are-LTH-Holding-Their-Assets" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post</a>.</p>
<p>Investors have noted in the past that Bitcoiners have remarkable conviction, in general, to keep their holdings on hand &#8211; regardless of price. Paul Tudor Jones, for example, added that 86% of Bitcoin holders did not sell their assets when their price dropped from $17,000 to $3,000 between 2017 and 2018. <a href="https://thehustle.co/stanley-druckenmiller-q-and-a-trung-phanin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Stanley Druckenmiller</a> was also bullish on the asset last month due to its holders being “religious zealots.”</p>
<h2>What About The Halving?</h2>
<p>Ironically, some analysts don’t think the halving – the event of Bitcoin’s inflation rate falling by 50% every four years – may have a strong impact on the market after its arrival in April 2024.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s historic bull runs in 2013, 2017, and 2021 have all followed one year after a halving. While the connection may seem self-evident, a report from Coinbase this month <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/institutional/research-insights/research/monthly-outlook/bitcoin-halvings-and-liquidity-problem-june-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">argues</a> that each cycle may not have been so connected to the halving as much as other factors.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Outside of the third halving, evidence that these halving events supported bitcoin price action is not entirely clear cut,” it states. 2013 and 2020 were coupled with central banks conducting major rounds of quantitative easing, while 2016 was when the Bank of England resumed its bond-buying program in response to Brexit.</p></blockquote>
<p>CryptoQuant’s Head of Marketing backs this more skeptical view. “I also agree with the fact that the halving impact on the Bitcoin price is decreasing as the new supply limit decreases significantly,” he told <em>CryptoPotato</em> via DM.</p>
<p>However, Chung noted other factors are worth being bullish about – such as institutional involvement after BlackRock’s ETF filing. “You can see that the fund holding volume spiked after the BlackRock announcement,” he said.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257871" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257871" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257871 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-1024x645.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="645" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-50x31.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257871" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Fund Holdings. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>China’s growing involvement in crypto is also likely to increase liquidity and demand. Hong Kong is offering licenses to exchanges, such firms are giving banking access to the industry, and retail traders in the region are being allowed to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hsbc-hong-kong-lets-clients-trade-btc-and-eth-etfs-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">trade major crypto assets</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-money-does-it-take-to-moon-bitcoin-analysis/" rel="nofollow">How Much Money Does it Take to ‘Moon’ Bitcoin? Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner of Manchester City in Expansion of Partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257989</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MANCITY_X_OKX_HERO_ENDFRAME_16x9_16881336124JGrE7RzuK.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MANCITY_X_OKX_HERO_ENDFRAME_16x9_16881336124JGrE7RzuK.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023] Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club’s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement. As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club’s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement.</p>
<p>As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of both the men’s and women’s first-team playing kits and will retain its position on the left sleeve of the first-team training kits, in addition to appearing across further digital and physical club assets.</p>
<p>OKX&#8217;s partnership with Manchester City began in March 2022, first expanding in July 2022 to become the Club’s Official Training Kit Partner for the 2022/23 season. To date, the partnership has helped introduce the brand to millions of football fans around the world through innovative Web3 experiences like the <a href="https://www.okx.com/activities/okxcollectivemetaverse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">OKX Collective</a>, through which fans can get up close and personal with Manchester City players and OKX Ambassadors such as Jack Grealish and Alex Greenwood.</p>
<p>The partnership expansion was unveiled at an exclusive reveal at the Etihad Stadium featuring City Football Group Chief Executive Officer Ferran Soriano and OKX Global Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique. As part of the event, the sleeve was unveiled in a &#8216;virtual reveal&#8217; with a hero video featuring player avatars. Manchester City legend Gaël Clichy was also in attendance for a media Q&amp;A.</p>
<p>In a session moderated by Manchester City presenter <a href="https://www.mancity.com/wnrh/natalie-pike" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Natalie Pike</a>, Rafique and Soriano spoke about OKX&#8217;s vision of reaching City fans around the world through the partnership. They also discussed the role Web3 technology can play in fan engagement, especially when it comes to designing engaging, immersive experiences for fans.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Ferran Soriano, Chief Executive Officer at City Football Group, said:</strong> &#8220;We are very proud to have OKX represented on the sleeve of the Manchester City shirt. Both OKX and Manchester City are leading companies driven by a passion for innovation. We have already seen great Web3 experiences designed by OKX for Manchester City’s global fan base and there will be many more to come. This is a very exciting partnership.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><strong>Haider Rafique, CMO at OKX, said:</strong> &#8220;The journey with the Man City team has been incredible. Manchester City was our first official global brand partnership and in just a year and a half we have come a long way. We always intended to integrate with the sport and help the Club lead on leaning into Web3. Fast forward fifteen months, we now have a metaverse, an NFT initiative and a number of other new projects that we are excited about.</p></blockquote>
<p>The sleeve partnership brings us closer to City fans across the globe, and we look forward to collaborating to create unique, exciting and innovative engagements through Web3 technology. As the Club&#8217;s Official Cryptocurrency Exchange Partner, fans can expect amazing things every time they interact with OKX.&#8221;</p>
<h2>About OKX</h2>
<p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of trading and Web3. Its leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world’s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Proof of Reserves</a> on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit:<a href="http://okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> okx.com</a></p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Manchester City Football Club</h2>
<p>Manchester City FC is an English Premier League club initially founded in 1880 as St Mark’s West Gorton. It officially became Manchester City FC in 1894 and has since then gone onto win the UEFA Champions League, European Cup Winners’ Cup, nine League Championship titles, seven FA Cups, and eight League Cups. Manchester City FC is one of 13 clubs comprising the City Football Group.</p>
<p>Under manager Pep Guardiola, one of the most highly-decorated managers in world football, the Club plays its domestic and UEFA Champions League home fixtures at the Etihad Stadium, a spectacular 53,500-seat arena that City has called home since 2003. Today, the stadium sits on the wider Etihad Campus, which also encompasses the City Football Academy, a state-of-the-art performance training and youth development facility located in the heart of East Manchester. Featuring a 7,000-capacity Academy Stadium, the City Football Academy is also where Manchester City Women’s Football Club and the Elite Development Squad train on a daily basis and play their competitive home games.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p><em>OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AS THE VALUE OF YOUR ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/" rel="nofollow">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner of Manchester City in Expansion of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Buys More BTC but Bitcoin Wobbles Around $30K Amid SEC-ETF Rejection Rumors: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-but-bitcoin-wobbles-around-30k-amid-sec-etf-rejection-rumors-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257987</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BCH is the undesputed top performer within the top 100 crypto assets for the past week, following a triple-digit price surge.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lot can change in the cryptocurrency industry within a week, and the waves indeed fluctuated in the past seven days. The market rejoiced recently as several multinational financial giants filed for a Bitcoin Spot ETF, but the tides could be turning now, according to a WSJ report from Friday.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s unpack.</p>
<p>BlackRock shook the crypto market two weeks ago when it filed an application to release a BTC Spot ETF in the States, which would make it the first such product greenlighted by the SEC.</p>
<p>Being the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, its actions had immediate consequences as ARK Invest <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-amends-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-to-copy-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">changed</a> its own application to copy that of BlackRock, while Fidelity reapplied less than a week later.</p>
<p>That also impacted the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price trajectory as BTC skyrocketed from $26,500 last week to roughly $31,000 earlier today. However, a Wall Street Journal report emerged on Friday claiming that the SEC found the recent filings &#8220;inadequate,&#8221; which prompted speculation that they could be rejected, similar to all previous ones.</p>
<p>BTC reacted immediately with a sharp price dump that drove it south by $1,500. As a result, the asset charted a 10-day low of $29,500 (on Bitstamp). It managed to bounce off rather quickly and reclaimed some ground. Nevertheless, it&#8217;s still uncertain at around $30,000.</p>
<p>This price decline erased all of BTC&#8217;s weekly gains. In comparison, numerous altcoins have charted notable 7-day price increases, such as ETC (15%), SOL (15%), Aave (18%), XLM (24%), and Bitcoin SV (36%).</p>
<p>The one that stands out the most, though, is Bitcoin Cash. The BTC hard fork has soared by over 110% on a weekly scale and earlier today charted a 14-month high above $320 amid <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/" data-wpel-link="internal">massive trading volumes</a> on smaller markets, such as the South Korean one.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-49046" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" alt="Bitcoin ETF" width="1000" height="668" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-768x513.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,214B | 24H Vol: $67B | BTC Dominance: 48.3%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $30,082 (+0.3%) | ETH: $1,848 (-1.0%) | BNB: $234 (-2.7%)</p>
<h2>This Week’s Crypto Headlines You Can’t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Dumps Below $30K as SEC Warns That Recent BTC Spot ETF Filings Are ‘Inadequate’ (WSJ)</strong>. As mentioned above, the WSJ <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">cited</a> people familiar with the matter who claimed that the SEC believes the most recent BTC Spot ETF filings could have been &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Fidelity Refiles Bitcoin Spot ETF Application After BlackRock</strong>. But before that, Fidelity Digital Assets <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">followed</a> BlackRock&#8217;s example and reapplied for a Bitcoin Spot ETF less than a week after the world&#8217;s largest asset manager.</p>
<p><strong>FTT Explodes 35% on FTX Revival Idea</strong>. Just several months after the once-prominent crypto exchange filed for bankruptcy, the new CEO hinted that FTX could be revived at some point. As a result, the native token <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftt-explodes-35-on-ftx-revival-idea/" data-wpel-link="internal">jumped</a> to a 2-month high.</p>
<p><strong>MicroStrategy Buys 12,333 BTC for $350 Million at $28K Per Bitcoin</strong>. Perhaps fueled by BlackRock&#8217;s filing, the largest corporate holder of BTC decided to double down by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-12333-btc-for-350-million-at-28k-per-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">allocating</a> another $350 million and accumulating 12,333 BTC.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood Cuts Staff Again as Trading Volume and Engagement Dwindle</strong>. The Vlad Tenev-spearheaded trading company continues to struggle as it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-cuts-staff-again-as-trading-volume-and-engagement-dwindle/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the lay-off of another 150 employees (7%). This is the second round of cut-offs for the Wall Street-traded firm in less than a year.</p>
<p><strong>Swiss Prosecutors Freeze $26M Worth of Do Kwon Assets Following his Prison Sentence (Report)</strong>. After being sentenced to four months in prison in Montenegro, Kwon&#8217;s situation has reportedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-prosecutors-freeze-26m-worth-of-do-kwon-assets-following-his-prison-sentence-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">worsened</a> as $26 million worth of his assets were frozen</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-but-bitcoin-wobbles-around-30k-amid-sec-etf-rejection-rumors-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Buys More BTC but Bitcoin Wobbles Around $30K Amid SEC-ETF Rejection Rumors: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
