<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>$150M in Liquidations as Bitcoin Dumped to 2-Month Low: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/150m-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-dumped-to-2-month-low-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250323</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_Red_Mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The total crypto market cap declined by over $40 billion in just a day.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The landscape around bitcoin took another turn for the worse in the past 24 hours as the asset fell to its lowest price position in almost two months.</p>
<p>The altcoins are in no better shape, with ETH, MATIC, SHIB, DOT, LDO, and many others dumping hard in the past 48 hours.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Falls Toward $26K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin was trading sideways for a few days until Tuesday and sat calmly around $27,500, anticipating the US CPI announcement, which was scheduled for Wednesday. Once the numbers came out and it turned out that the inflation increase is slightly lower than expected, the cryptocurrency actually <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-above-28k-as-us-april-inflation-lower-than-expected/" data-wpel-link="internal">went on the offensive</a> and spiked by $800 to just under $28,400.</p>
<p>However, that was short-lived, and BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-pumped-and-dumped-1-5k-following-us-cpi-numbers-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">fell hard</a> in the following hours to under $27,000. Despite recovering some ground at first, the asset started losing value once again in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>This culminated in a drop to $26,100 (on Bitstamp) early today, which was bitcoin&#8217;s lowest price position since mid-March. Despite recovering a few hundred dollars since then, BTC is still over 4% down on the day.</p>
<p>As such, its market cap has slipped to $510 billion, and its dominance over the alts has taken a hit and is down to 46.3%.</p>
<p>Somewhat expectedly, the enhanced volatility has resulted in roughly $150 million in liquidations on a daily scale, <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to CoinGlass.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250325" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250325" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250325" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-11-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250325" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Alts in Red</h2>
<p>Ethereum is another notable loser in the past 48 hours. Despite the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-crashes-to-6-week-lows-despite-eth-on-exchanges-declining/" data-wpel-link="internal">declining amount of ETH</a> sitting on exchanges, the asset&#8217;s price has slumped by $250 in this timeframe to drop to a 6-week low registered earlier today.</p>
<p>Binance Coin is close to breaking below $300 after a 2.3% daily drop. MATIC, DOGE, SOL, DOT, TRX, LTC, and SHIB are also well in the red from the larger-cap alts. Interestingly, XRP is the only alt with a minor daily increase.</p>
<p>Further losses are evident from TONCOIN and LDO &#8211; both are down by around 6%.</p>
<p>In total, the crypto market cap has seen $40 billion gone daily, and the metric is at just over $1.1 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250329" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250329" style="width: 1875px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250329" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1875" height="884" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2.png 1875w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2-300x141.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2-1024x483.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2-768x362.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2-1536x724.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-2-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1875px) 100vw, 1875px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250329" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/150m-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-dumped-to-2-month-low-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">$150M in Liquidations as Bitcoin Dumped to 2-Month Low: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Crashes to 6-Week Lows Despite ETH on Exchanges Declining</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-crashes-to-6-week-lows-despite-eth-on-exchanges-declining/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 07:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250302</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/ethereum_cover-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/ethereum_cover-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ETH is down by over $200 in the past few days alone.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The number of ETH sitting on crypto exchanges continues to decrease and is now down to its lowest position since public trading began almost a decade ago.</p>
<p>However, that has not stopped the price of the second-largest cryptocurrency from further dropping to a new 6-week low.</p>
<ul>
<li><em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/for-the-first-time-since-2015-nearly-90-of-the-eth-supply-now-in-self-custody/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> in late March that the Ethereum supply held on exchanges had declined to just 10.31%.</li>
<li>It seems investors have only continued withdrawing their ETH portions from trading platforms, as Santiment updated that the percentage has further declined to 10.1%.</li>
<li>The analytics resource asserted that this is the lowest figure since the asset began public trading after its launch in 2015.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f45b.png" alt="👛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> As <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Ethereum</a> has dipped to $1,780 today, we&#8217;ve seen exchange supply continue to decrease. The percentage of <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a> on exchanges is at its lowest (10.1%) since public trading began in 2015. This is essentially the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AllTimeHigh?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#AllTimeHigh</a> for non-exchange holdings. <a href="https://t.co/WVmeAJhhMM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/WVmeAJhhMM</a> <a href="https://t.co/eMXoRh9R76" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/eMXoRh9R76</a></p>
<p>— Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1656748605787766784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>At first, this data should sound bullish for the asset. This is because the selling pressure should be lower, given the fact that there are fewer coins sitting on trading platforms.</li>
<li>However, this has not been the case for the past few days. ETH touched $2,000 less than a week ago, but the subsequent rejection pushed it down hard.</li>
<li>After the CPI <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-above-28k-as-us-april-inflation-lower-than-expected/" data-wpel-link="internal">announcement</a> on Wednesday, it pumped to $1,900 once again. Since then, though, ETH has plummeted by over $200 and earlier today charted a 6-week low of $1,740 (on Bitstamp).</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-crashes-to-6-week-lows-despite-eth-on-exchanges-declining/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Crashes to 6-Week Lows Despite ETH on Exchanges Declining</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>D-Central Launches Innovative &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; Promotion Across North America</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 05:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250265</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ASIC_Repair_Technician_1683833564u30VkMwXYB.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ASIC_Repair_Technician_1683833564u30VkMwXYB.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Laval, Canada, May 11th, 2023] Groundbreaking Initiative Revolutionizes ASIC Repair Services, Encourages Sustainability and Decentralization in Cryptocurrency Mining. D-Central Technologies Inc., a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining industry, is excited to announce the expansion of its revolutionary &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program to all cryptocurrency miners in North America. This innovative initiative, previously [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Laval, Canada, May 11th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Groundbreaking Initiative Revolutionizes ASIC Repair Services, Encourages Sustainability and Decentralization in Cryptocurrency Mining.</p>
<p>D-Central Technologies Inc., a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining industry, is excited to announce the expansion of its revolutionary &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program to all cryptocurrency miners in North America. This innovative initiative, previously accessible only to select clients, is now available to miners of all scales, dramatically transforming the landscape of ASIC repair services.</p>
<p>The &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program allows D-Central to provide high-quality repair services for mining hardware at no cash cost, instead accepting broken hardware as payment. This innovative approach is a testament to D-Central&#8217;s commitment to fostering sustainable, accessible, and cost-effective solutions for miners.</p>
<p>&#8220;In the rapidly evolving world of cryptocurrency mining, the need for efficient and affordable repair services is more important than ever,&#8221; said Jonathan Bertrand, CEO of D-Central. &#8220;With the &#8216;Hash No Cash&#8217; program, we&#8217;re making it easier for miners to maintain and repair their hardware, allowing them to keep their capital for strategic investments such as new hardware purchases.&#8221;</p>
<p>The &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program also contributes to environmental sustainability by reducing electronic waste. By repairing and repurposing broken hardware, D-Central minimizes the demand for new equipment production, thereby reducing the environmental impact of cryptocurrency mining.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the program promotes decentralization in cryptocurrency mining. By making repaired hardware available to retail customers at affordable prices, D-Central is putting the power of ASICs into more hands, fostering the wider distribution of mining power.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;D-Central is committed to driving change within the cryptocurrency mining industry,&#8221; said Jonathan Bertrand. &#8220;Our goal is not just to provide repair services, but to create solutions that are financially viable, environmentally friendly, and conducive to the decentralization of mining power.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Miners across North America are invited to take advantage of the &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; program. To learn more about the program or to get started, please visit: https://d-central.tech/</p>
<h2>About D-Central</h2>
<p>D-Central is a leading provider of cryptocurrency mining services, offering a wide range of solutions, including ASIC repair services, mining support, and disinfection services. Since its establishment in 2016, D-Central has been committed to providing professional services tailored to the unique needs of the cryptocurrency mining industry. With a track record of delivering high-quality services and innovative solutions, D-Central continues to shape the future of cryptocurrency mining.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/d-central-launches-innovative-hash-no-cash-promotion-across-north-america/" rel="nofollow">D-Central Launches Innovative &#8220;Hash No Cash&#8221; Promotion Across North America</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Memecoin LOVESNOOPY Aims to Steal PEPE’s Crown and Become Meme King</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-memecoin-lovesnoopy-aims-to-steal-pepes-crown-and-become-meme-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 05:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250260</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/imageedit_2_2915172935_1683830757dRyJqA4eEq.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/imageedit_2_2915172935_1683830757dRyJqA4eEq.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Seattle, USA, May 11th, 2023] A new memecoin has emerged with more than 70 years of history behind it and the goal of unseating current meme king PEPE. $LOVESNOOPY is a meme token with a Snoopy theme backed by the love of fans and armed with formidable meme power. With a fandom [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Seattle, USA, May 11th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>A new memecoin has emerged with more than 70 years of history behind it and the goal of unseating current meme king PEPE. <a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">$LOVESNOOPY</a> is a meme token with a Snoopy theme backed by the love of fans and armed with formidable meme power. With a fandom that has grown over generations, the anticipated impact of $LOVESNOOPY is high.</p>
<p>$LOVESNOOPY is the latest in a long line of dogcoins including Dogecoin (DOGE), Shiba Inu (SHIB), FLOKI (FLOKI), and Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge). The Snoopy-themed token arrives on the market at a time when interest in memecoins is at a two-year high. The trading volume of meme coins reached $2.3 billion last week, the highest since May 2021</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/sonnpy_1024_1_1683821251esXrapbndf.jpg" /></p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">official website</a> of $LOVESNOOPY supports all languages in the world including English, Arabic, Chinese, Japanese, French, German, and Vietnamese, showcasing its global ambitions. $LOVESNOOPY has made a powerful entrance onto the scene by trading on Uniswap and announcing listings on five centralized exchanges (CEXs). Its rapid rise has prompted speculation that it could quickly ascend to become a blue-chip player in the world of memecoins.</p>
<p>Since its debut, $LOVESNOOPY has captured the attention of cryptocurrency investors, rapidly gaining a foothold in the market. Observers will be watching closely to see whether it can surpass Pepe token and Dogecoin and claim its position as the &#8216;Meme King&#8217; amidst the flood of contenders.</p>
<h2>About LOVESNOOPY</h2>
<p>The main utility of <a href="https://www.snoopy.land/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">$LOVESNOOPY</a> is to establish a vibrant and impassioned meme community that we can embrace with all our hearts. LOVESNOOPY’s path to global domination is simple! Just enjoy and ‘LOVE SNOOPY’! The more people enjoy and LOVE SNOOPY, the more indelible his legacy as a beloved meme will become.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-memecoin-lovesnoopy-aims-to-steal-pepes-crown-and-become-meme-king/" rel="nofollow">New Memecoin LOVESNOOPY Aims to Steal PEPE’s Crown and Become Meme King</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC Issuer Circle Rebalances Treasury Holdings Amid US Debt Ceiling Crisis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-issuer-circle-rebalances-treasury-holdings-amid-us-debt-ceiling-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 04:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250117</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/circlenyse.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/circlenyse.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Circle is preparing to avoid potential lapse as debt ceiling crisis loom with no agreement in sight.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoin issuer Circle no longer has Treasury holdings that mature beyond early June as it does not want to get tangled in a potential US debt default.</p>
<p>The development follows US Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen&#8217;s warning that the government could be unable to pay its bills by June 1st and could default on its debt at a later date, sparking widespread concern.</p>
<ul>
<li>In a recent <a href="https://www.politico.com/newsletters/morning-money/2023/05/10/rewriting-crypto-00096124" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">interview</a>, Chief Jeremy Allaire noted that Circle doesn’t want to carry exposure &#8220;through a potential breach of the ability of the US government to pay its debts.&#8221;</li>
<li>As such, the fintech firm has adjusted its mix of reserves that back USDC by switching to short-dated US Treasuries to avoid a catastrophic fallout.</li>
<li>Circle Reserve Fund Disclosures, which are managed by BlackRock, <a href="https://www.blackrock.com/cash/en-us/products/329365/circle-reserve-fund" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that current holdings mature no later than May 31.</li>
<li>A Treasury bill, aka T-Bill, is a short-term government debt obligation backed by the US Treasury that can have maturities ranging from four weeks to 52 weeks.</li>
<li>The Republicans and Democrats failing to reach a deal might put the country at risk of defaulting on the national debt. To avoid a default, both sides will have to raise the debt ceiling.</li>
<li>However, negotiations on raising the debt ceiling got off to a rocky start this week as White House talks concluded with no agreement.</li>
<li>As for Circle, its US Dollar-pegged stablecoin &#8211; USDC &#8211; suffered a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-did-usdc-depeg-circle-ceo-gives-the-inside-story/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">depeg</a> after the collapse of the Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) earlier this year. The token has since stabilized and is currently sitting at a $30.12 billion market cap.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-issuer-circle-rebalances-treasury-holdings-amid-us-debt-ceiling-crisis/" rel="nofollow">USDC Issuer Circle Rebalances Treasury Holdings Amid US Debt Ceiling Crisis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York to Embrace Stablecoins as Payment Method for Bail Bonds</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-to-embrace-stablecoins-as-payment-method-for-bail-bonds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 23:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250146</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/NewYorkCity.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/NewYorkCity.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Assembly Bill 7024 seeks to give stablecoins a status of official means of payment for bail bonds inside the state of New York.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of New York state proposed certain amendments to the law that could allow residents to settle bail bonds in stablecoins instead of fiat currency. The bill could become official six months after the relevant regulators greenlight it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Domestic lawmakers have previously introduced legislation that aims to make certain cryptocurrencies an official means of payment for civil penalties, fines, taxes, and other fees.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Crypto Step for New York State</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">New York Assembly Bill 7024, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://legiscan.com/NY/text/A07024/id/2804773" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">presented</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on May 10, seeks to establish a system for &#8220;the administration of the acceptance, recording, and processing of stablecoins as a means of securing bail.&#8221; However, the officials did not disclose which assets will be included in the potential legislation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmakers pointed out the volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market, outlining that the court might require further guarantees if the valuation of stablecoins dropped over 50% from the value when bail was posted.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If the court directs that bail be posted as provided in paragraph (j) of subdivision of this section and the value of the stablecoins falls more than fifty percent from the value of the stablecoins at the time bail was posted, the court may in its discretion, request the posting of additional bail as provided in subdivision one of this section,&#8221; the bill reads.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stablecoins pegged to fiat currencies or precious metals are supposed to have a fixed price, but there have been some examples of the opposite. USDC (the second largest stablecoin) dropped to as low as $0.87 in March this year after Circle (the company behind the asset) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-tumbles-to-0-93-as-circle-reveals-3-3-billion-held-at-svb-tether-and-binance-not-exposed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a multi-billion exposure to the collapsed Silicon Valley Bank. The firm fixed the issues in the following days by transferring the funds to another bank, and the token reclaimed its $1 price target.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Previous Bills</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The New York Senate has recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-senate-bill-proposes-legalizing-crypto-for-payment-in-state-agencies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">proposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> another amendment that could enable locals to settle various fees (taxes, fines, civil penalties, and more) in Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legislation classifies crypto assets as &#8220;any form of digital currency in which encryption techniques are used to regulate the generation of units of currency and verify the transfer of funds, operating independently of a central bank.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The state of Arizona has also emerged as a crypto-friendly region. Senator Wendy Rogers </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/arizona-state-senator-proposes-a-bill-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">introduced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a bill in 2022 that seeks to make BTC legal tender. While not succeeding with her attempt, she </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.aa.com.tr/en/americas/arizona-state-senator-introduces-bill-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender/2798666" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">proposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> another legislation that could turn the primary cryptocurrency into an official means of payment in the area. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-to-embrace-stablecoins-as-payment-method-for-bail-bonds/" rel="nofollow">New York to Embrace Stablecoins as Payment Method for Bail Bonds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is PacWest Next to Fall? Bank Stock Falls 22% Following Decline in Deposits</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-pacwest-next-to-fall-bank-stock-falls-22-following-decline-in-deposits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 22:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250266</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PacWest lost over $10 billion in deposits since the start of the banking crisis. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">California lender PacWest Bancorp (PACW) fell over 20% on Thursday after the company revealed it had lost a significant portion of its deposits. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This follows a string of US regional bank failures this year that were preceded by similar red flags. </span></p>
<h2>Depositors Flee From PacWest</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per its quarterly report filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission, PacWest said its deposits declined by 9.5% last week – mostly occurring on May 4 and 5. This, according to the bank, was in response to “heightened market and customer fears” surrounding the bank after First Republic Bank was closed by regulators on May 1st. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“On the afternoon of May 3, 2023, PacWest was featured prominently in the financial news headlines with reports that PacWest was &#8220;exploring all of its options and having talks with potential investors and partners&#8221;,” wrote the firm. “The news headlines increased our customers&#8217; fears of the safety of their deposits.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Among the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-slide-while-bitcoin-pumps-after-first-republic-failure/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">many banks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> caught up in banking sector fear during First Republic’s fall, PacWest was one the hardest hit. During the week from April 28 to May 5, its stock price fell from $10.15 to $5.96, and trades for $4.70 as of Thursday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The bank clarified that it has already funded its decline in deposits with available on-balance-sheet liquidity. As of May 10, the firm held immediately available liquidity of $15 billion, against uninsured deposits of $5.2 billion, representing a coverage ratio of 288%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Much of that liquidity stemmed from having pledged $5.1 billion on Wednesday to the Federal Reserve’s discount window, giving PacWest another $3.9 billion in additional borrowing capacity. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">PacWest was also hit hard during the initial string of bank failures in March that claims Silvergate, Signature Bank, and Silicon Valley Bank (SVB). The event caused PacWest to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-stop-trading-amid-post-svb-volatility/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">plummet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> 47% the day after SVB depositors were bailed out, and to lose deposits in excess of what federal deposit insurance could cover. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the first quarter, PacWest’s deposits fell by $16.9% total – or $5.7 billion. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“These recent events, and the ongoing news coverage of these events, has increased certain risks and uncertainties related to our business and future prospects,” stated the bank. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2>The Current State of Banks</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Phoenix-based bank Western Alliance (WAL) also underwent significant volatility after March’s bank failures, dropping a whopping 76% on March 13. After First Republic went down, its stock </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-bank-stocks-slide-while-bitcoin-pumps-after-first-republic-failure/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">slid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> 20% on May 2 from $36.18 to $28.96. It currently trades for $28.96. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The bank </span><a href="https://investors.westernalliancebancorporation.com/news-releases/news/news-details/2023/Western-Alliance-Bancorporation-Issues-Deposit-Update/default.aspx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">appeared</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to fare better than PacWest on the deposit front, however, reporting a $600 million increase in deposits between May 2 and May 9. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After First Republic’s failure, BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes predicted that PacWest would be the next bank to fall in the ongoing banking crisis. “Guess we know who is next to be deaded by the FDIC,” he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoHayes/status/1653403052899192833" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweeted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in response to its sliding stock prices. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last week, US Senator John Kennedy </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-calls-banks-sophisticated-ponzi-schemes/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">referred</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to banks as “sophisticated Ponzi schemes” due to their reliance on their depositors’ trust in them.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-pacwest-next-to-fall-bank-stock-falls-22-following-decline-in-deposits/" rel="nofollow">Is PacWest Next to Fall? Bank Stock Falls 22% Following Decline in Deposits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another Crypto Influencer Reportedly Dumped HODL Coin on Followers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/another-crypto-influencer-reportedly-dumped-hodl-coin-on-followers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250165</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto unfluencer untagged himself from the post. shortly after the development.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ZachXBT has accused several influencers of engaging in pump-and-dump scams and profiting from the misery of others. This time, the on-chain sleuth has targetted yet another figure who goes by the name &#8216;DannyCrypt,&#8217; for allegedly dumping on his followers.</p>
<p>The crypto influencer in question was accused of receiving 2% of the supply of a certain token to assist with marketing. However, 15 minutes after receiving the tokens, he allegedly dumped the majority of them for $57k (31 ETH) to his unsuspecting followers.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1656375551819497478" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">thread</a> by ZackXBT, DannyCrypt was actively promoting a new coin called &#8220;HODL&#8221; on social media and tweeted about &#8220;hodling&#8221; its tokens.</li>
<li>He is accused of telling his 26K Telegram channel subscribers that he believes the token&#8217;s price to have &#8220;stabilized,&#8221; but immediately after which he sold his stash.</li>
<li>DannyCrypt&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/DannyCrypt/status/1656419214012436481" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweet</a> that appears to address ZackXBT&#8217;s claims read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Team is not angry that I sold but cos they all couldn’t sell before me after keeping over 70% of the presale Whitelist for themselves. Same thing they do with NFT projects. That being said if you come for me, I’ll block you, go and cry on your timeline.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>ZachXBT continued to maintain that DannyCrypt &#8220;made a post-playing victim&#8221; and even untagged himself from the post in an attempt to distance himself from the claims. The influencer subsequently blocked him.</li>
<li>Last September, ZackXBT accused popular crypto influencer Lark Davis of profiting over $1 million while promoting low-cap crypto projects and dumping them on his followers. The latter had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lark-davis-dismisses-ridiculous-pump-and-dump-allegations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">dismissed</a> the allegations.</li>
<li>Youtuber and influencer Ben Armstrong, a.k.a BitBoy, was also accused of carrying out at least seven scams of shilling and dumping.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-crypto-influencer-reportedly-dumped-hodl-coin-on-followers/" rel="nofollow">Another Crypto Influencer Reportedly Dumped HODL Coin on Followers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will The Lightning Network Save the Day for Bitcoin&#8217;s Mempool Pileup?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-lightning-network-save-the-day-for-bitcoins-mempool-pileup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250111</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_lightning_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_lightning_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lightning Network could take the pressure off Bitcoin's waiting area for new transactions. While the BTC mempool remains congested midway through the week, a lightning quick fix using the Bitcoin L2 could save the day.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While Bitcoin had whittled down waitlisted transaction orders by Wednesday, network congestion remains high. Median confirmation time hovered markedly above ten minutes. The on-chain metric for Bitcoin network fulfillment sits at a high unseen since Feb 2023 and Dec 2022.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, hundreds of thousands of transactions at a time sit waiting to be confirmed. That&#8217;s far above normal levels in the tens of thousands. The extent of network lag is so high that at least one longtime Bitcoin proponent says it&#8217;s a DDoS attack by BTC senders attaching BRC-20 ordinals scripts.</p>
<h2>Binance Turns to Lightning Network</h2>
<p>Processing time started looking better during the week, but the network <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/charts/median-confirmation-time" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">hasn&#8217;t nearly recovered</a> to normal speeds. To handle long wait times and high fees, Binance had to pause withdrawals for a few hours Sunday. It restored Bitcoin withdrawals Monday but then paused them again before restoring services.</p>
<p>But Binance is hoping some quick work with Lightning Network could speed things along. The exchange <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1655419624962527233" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> over the weekend that it has a team working to enable BTC Lightning Network withdrawals.</p>
<p>Lightning Network is a &#8220;Layer-2&#8221; blockchain scaling platform that handles Bitcoin transactions. It periodically updates with the &#8220;Layer-1&#8221; or base chain to update it in a flash with what happened between updates. While waiting on the mempool to clear up, the L2 can keep track of Bitcoin orders.</p>
<h2>BTC Network Jam Sends Bitcoin Transaction Fee Soaring</h2>
<p>The memory pool of unconfirmed transactions has <a href="https://bitcoinvisuals.com/bitcoind-mempool" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">remained high</a> this week in the hundreds of thousands. That&#8217;s much higher than their normal level. It&#8217;s usually in the tens of thousands at any given time during periods of low network congestion.</p>
<p>The total backlog of BTC orders since the weekend, starting May 6, is a magnitude of network latency unseen since June 2021. That was with the Bitcoin price flying up in a cyclical crypto bull run. Order senders using the BRC-20 token standard to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-support-bitcoin-ordinals-in-its-ntf-marketplace/" data-wpel-link="internal">mint &#8220;ordinal&#8221; NFTs</a> using the BTC blockchain caused the current jam.</p>
<p>The blockchain has slowed very suddenly as a result of senders adding these scripts. One veteran Bitcoin supporter and software, John W. Ratcliff says that it amounts to an attack on the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>On Twitter, he cited the unnecessary data-wasting format most BRC-20 users are inserting. He says it&#8217;s a level of incompetence too staggering to believe. It would be an odd way to attack the network, though, that results in its miners earning higher fees. Regardless, necessity would appear again to be the mother of innovation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-lightning-network-save-the-day-for-bitcoins-mempool-pileup/" rel="nofollow">Will The Lightning Network Save the Day for Bitcoin&#8217;s Mempool Pileup?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Institutions Intend to Buy Bitcoin in Late 2023: Interview With CryptoQuant</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-intend-to-buy-bitcoin-in-late-2023-interview-with-cryptoquant/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250107</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/institutions_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/institutions_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Representatives from CryptoQuant believe Bitcoin could return to its previous all-time high by early next year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin is up (YTD), banks are collapsing, and the Federal Reserve seems to be approaching the end of its monetary tightening mission. Does that mean the bull market is back in action?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CryptoPotato spoke with crypto market analytics firm CryptoQuant at Consensus 2023 to discuss all things related to Bitcoin’s price – including its place in the market cycle, its correlation to gold, and its role during the ongoing US banking crisis.</span></p>
<h2>Bullish Times Ahead for Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When asked about whether the bull market had returned, CryptoQuant’s Head of BD &amp; Strategy Benjamin Brannan told CryptoPotato that Bitcoin appears to be “out of the depths of the bear market.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Though he personally views corrections as “always on the table,” the business development head said he’s received word from institutional clients intending to invest in Bitcoin and crypto in Q3 and Q4 2023. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“These are from conversations that I&#8217;ve been having mainly with institutional allocators and also people who are fundraising core funds as well,” said Brannan during an interview. “They&#8217;ve been speaking with various institutions or high net worth individuals.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Brannan added that institutions are waiting for the latter half of the year for confirmation that Bitcoin has exited the bear market, which so far is “looking to be the case.”</span></p>
<h2>Bitcoin and Gold</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Trading at roughly $16,500 at the start of the year, Bitcoin has rapidly appreciated to over $27,000 in response to this year’s US banking crisis, which has seen the likes of </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Silicon Valley Bank</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Silvergate, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">First Republic</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and other banking institutions fall between the cracks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The event has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-to-gold-correlation-surges-amid-banking-turmoil-surpasses-stocks/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">coincided</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with a falling correlation between Bitcoin and stocks, and a rising correlation with gold. This phenomenon is especially apparent in Bitcoin’s newfound resilience to Federal Reserve interest rate hikes, which pummeled stocks and crypto alike last year. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Bitcoin&#39;s correlation to Gold is the highest that its been in years, surpassing its correlation to the S&amp;P</p>
<p>(h/t <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@KaikoData</a>) <a href="https://t.co/5TDOtlm5zq" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/5TDOtlm5zq</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Will Clemente (@WClementeIII) <a href="https://twitter.com/WClementeIII/status/1642889074993143809?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Branaan said the “rush to Bitcoin” was a sign that the market was, at least for the moment, viewing the digital currency as a “safe haven asset.” In the long term, he predicted it will behave like a mixture of stocks and gold. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, Cryptoquant’s Head of Marketing, Ho Chan Chung surmised that Bitcoin is viewed as a commodity that performs well when the fiat system is not doing well. Unlike other cryptocurrencies, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">regulators</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in the United States are only in agreement that Bitcoin is a commodity, while altcoins may be securities. </span></p>
<h2>The 4-Year Market Cycle</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin is notorious for </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hodl-patterns-indicate-cycle-shift-to-bull-market/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">moving cyclically</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> between bull and bears markets every four years, based on its supply issuance schedule that reduces its inflation rate within the same time intervals. While the general pattern is predictable, getting the exact timing of crypto market tops and bottoms can be tricky business. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Brannan, there are some reliable indicators to identify bottoms from an on-chain perspective. One of them is Market-Value to Realized-Value ratio (MVRV), which divides an asset’s market capitalization by its realized capitalization (which values all Bitcoin based on the price each coin was last moved, and presumably sold.)</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“When coins are being held at a very high unrealized loss, then I think it&#8217;s a good time to buy,” said Brannan. “If a lot of the participants are holding their coins at unrealized gains, very high unrealized gains, you can think that a lot of people are looking to sell, realize some profits.”</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure style="width: 4032px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/693983534737522688/1101159206880563272/20230426_141113.jpg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/693983534737522688/1101159206880563272/20230426_141113.jpg" alt="" width="4032" height="2268" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Ho Chan Chung (Centre); Brannan (Right).</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Derivations of MVRV, including Spent Output Profit Ratio (SOPR) and net unrealized profit and loss (NUPL), can also help in identifying market tops and bottoms – especially when they pass key threshold ratios. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CryptoQuant tracks MVRV ratios based on different age bands for when coin movements took place – including one day, one week, one month, and so on.</span></p>
<h2>Price Predictions</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">When asked about price predictions for the near future, both Brannan and Chung agreed that Bitcoin likely won’t retest its $16,000 lows. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“If there are no such black swan events such as  Russia blowing a nuclear weapon into Ukraine, or Binance is blowing up …then we should be pretty stable in terms of meeting the low lows,” said Chung.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chung added that Bitcoin may even surpass its previous all-time high by Q2 2024 – right around the time the next Bitcoin halving takes place. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the long term, Brannan said Bitcoin could realistically reach $1 million by the year 2030. Even the tightening regulatory situation in the United States could serve to benefit the asset, in his view.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“I think Bitcoin is difficult to regulate, compared to &#8220;crypto.&#8221; I think it can benefit,” he said. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-intend-to-buy-bitcoin-in-late-2023-interview-with-cryptoquant/" rel="nofollow">Institutions Intend to Buy Bitcoin in Late 2023: Interview With CryptoQuant</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
