<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:13:08 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bank of China Tokenises Securities on Ethereum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bank-of-china-tokenises-securities-on-ethereum</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/boc.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/boc.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/boc.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:02:36 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bank-of-china-tokenises-securities-on-ethereum</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bank of China (BOCI) has made history by issuing tokenised securities on the Ethereum blockchain in Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This revolutionary development signifies a significant stride forward in the adoption of decentralised finance and highlights Hong Kong's efforts to attract major players in the cryptocurrency industry, including Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
Tokenised Securities: Pioneering a New Era in Finance
<p>The Bank of China's decision to issue tokenized securities on the Ethereum blockchain is a bold testament to the institution's acknowledgment of the tremendous potential of blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By harnessing the smart contract capabilities of Ethereum, BOCI aims to amplify the efficiency, transparency, and accessibility of traditional securities. Tokenisation paves the way for fractional ownership, heightened liquidity, and streamlined settlement processes, ushering in a revolutionary approach to trading, selling, and purchasing assets.</p>
Hong Kong's Crypto-Friendly Stance
<p>Hong Kong's ambitions to establish itself as a global hub for digital assets and cryptocurrencies have taken a significant leap forward with the Bank of China's introduction of tokenised securities. This milestone aligns seamlessly with the city's concerted efforts to allure leading cryptocurrency exchanges, with Coinbase expressing its interest in expanding its footprint in the region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hong Kong's proactive approach to embracing digital innovation and its regulatory framework, striking a balance between investor protection and industry growth, positions it as a potential destination for companies operating in the crypto space.</p>
Unprecedented Accessibility and Enhanced Liquidity
<p>By tokenising securities on the Ethereum blockchain, the Bank of China paves the way for investors, both institutional and retail, to access traditional financial assets with newfound ease and flexibility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tokenisation empowers fractional ownership, allowing investors to buy and trade smaller portions of high-value assets, thereby rendering previously illiquid investments more accessible. This democratisation of investment opportunities has the potential to revolutionise financial markets, expanding participation and fostering financial inclusion.</p>
Advancing Blockchain Adoption
<p>The Bank of China's pioneering initiative to issue tokenized securities represents a substantial stride in the adoption of blockchain technology within the conventional financial system. As a prominent financial institution, BOCI's embrace of blockchain validates its transformative potential to reshape the global financial landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This progressive move is poised to inspire other institutions to explore the utility of blockchain and cryptocurrencies, propelling further innovation and nurturing a more inclusive and efficient financial ecosystem.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Bank of China (BOCI) has made history by issuing tokenised securities on the Ethereum blockchain in Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This revolutionary development signifies a significant stride forward in the adoption of decentralised finance and highlights Hong Kong's efforts to attract major players in the cryptocurrency industry, including Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>
Tokenised Securities: Pioneering a New Era in Finance
<p>The Bank of China's decision to issue tokenized securities on the Ethereum blockchain is a bold testament to the institution's acknowledgment of the tremendous potential of blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By harnessing the smart contract capabilities of Ethereum, BOCI aims to amplify the efficiency, transparency, and accessibility of traditional securities. Tokenisation paves the way for fractional ownership, heightened liquidity, and streamlined settlement processes, ushering in a revolutionary approach to trading, selling, and purchasing assets.</p>
Hong Kong's Crypto-Friendly Stance
<p>Hong Kong's ambitions to establish itself as a global hub for digital assets and cryptocurrencies have taken a significant leap forward with the Bank of China's introduction of tokenised securities. This milestone aligns seamlessly with the city's concerted efforts to allure leading cryptocurrency exchanges, with Coinbase expressing its interest in expanding its footprint in the region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hong Kong's proactive approach to embracing digital innovation and its regulatory framework, striking a balance between investor protection and industry growth, positions it as a potential destination for companies operating in the crypto space.</p>
Unprecedented Accessibility and Enhanced Liquidity
<p>By tokenising securities on the Ethereum blockchain, the Bank of China paves the way for investors, both institutional and retail, to access traditional financial assets with newfound ease and flexibility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tokenisation empowers fractional ownership, allowing investors to buy and trade smaller portions of high-value assets, thereby rendering previously illiquid investments more accessible. This democratisation of investment opportunities has the potential to revolutionise financial markets, expanding participation and fostering financial inclusion.</p>
Advancing Blockchain Adoption
<p>The Bank of China's pioneering initiative to issue tokenized securities represents a substantial stride in the adoption of blockchain technology within the conventional financial system. As a prominent financial institution, BOCI's embrace of blockchain validates its transformative potential to reshape the global financial landscape.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This progressive move is poised to inspire other institutions to explore the utility of blockchain and cryptocurrencies, propelling further innovation and nurturing a more inclusive and efficient financial ecosystem.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Mid-Year Conference: Building a Web3 Finance Hub in the Metaverse]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/huobi-mid-year-conference-building-a-web3-finance-hub-in-the-metaverse</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/a48e96c9-b8ca-432d-8e50-13d5afba060a_1686593840eYgMML0FW9.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/a48e96c9-b8ca-432d-8e50-13d5afba060a_1686593840eYgMML0FW9.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/a48e96c9-b8ca-432d-8e50-13d5afba060a_1686593840eYgMML0FW9.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/huobi-mid-year-conference-building-a-web3-finance-hub-in-the-metaverse</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The, Caribbean, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Recently, Huobi held its mid-year conference to review the overall progress from the first half of 2023 including a development plan for the second half of the year. H.E. Justin Sun, a member of the Huobi Advisory Board, shared his unique insights into the development of the blockchain industry.</p><p class="ql-align-center">&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Becoming a Household Name</p><p>Huobi and Poloniex witnessed a significant improvement in operational performance during Q2 compared to Q1 2023. This can be attributed to various factors, including the meme coin frenzy and the regulatory crackdown on other exchanges.</p><p>However, in terms of total on-chain assets, Huobi and Poloniex equated to $4 billion which falls behind Binance's $60 billion and OKX's $10 billion.&nbsp;</p><p>Huobi stated that in the next six months, it will continue to restore its brand confidence, increase platform assets and trading volume, and achieve profitability targets. It aims to become a stronger player and a household name within the cryptocurrency exchange industry.</p><p>With months of cost reduction and efficiency improvement efforts, Huobi has overcome survival challenges and will make future decisions based on long-term perspectives. Huobi is committed to actively embracing the ever-changing crypto industry and prioritizing user needs. The company firmly doesn&rsquo;t believe in sacrificing user interests for short-term gains. The focus will be on constantly creating value for users while achieving greater business wins.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Crypto Market's Three Pillars: Exchange, Public Chain, and Stablecoin</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-center">&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Sun expressed that Huobi has always been following their global compliance strategy by actively embracing regulation and exploring diverse compliance operations. Numerous crypto companies are entering the Hong Kong market because of its new regulatory rules. Huobi is gaining exposure in the Hong Kong crypto market by launching Huobi Hong Kong, which allowed registration for Hong Kong residents on June 1 2023. Huobi is also the first exchange to become a member of the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC). Additionally, Huobi is in continuous communication with the Hong Kong government to apply for a cryptocurrency exchange license.</p><p>Sun analyzed that exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins will become the main core of the entire blockchain industry. These three pillars for the decentralized financial landscape will influence long-time development in the industry. Sun stated that their mission is to build a Web3 finance hub in the metaverse and give an option to people worldwide to pursue financial freedom in the metaverse. Public chains serve as the foundation for creating a financial world in the metaverse, while exchanges play a crucial role as the gatekeepers.</p><p>Sun believes that Huobi holds a leading position within the industry. However, in terms of integration capabilities, Huobi stands out as the sole decentralized financial ecosystem platform with a structure encompassing all three pillars mentioned earlier. The three core businesses consisting of exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins will strive to enhance the user experience from multiple angles. It focuses on long-term industry development, covering the majority of industry traffic, and building a globally influential Web3 financial hub.</p><p></p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The, Caribbean, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Recently, Huobi held its mid-year conference to review the overall progress from the first half of 2023 including a development plan for the second half of the year. H.E. Justin Sun, a member of the Huobi Advisory Board, shared his unique insights into the development of the blockchain industry.</p><p class="ql-align-center">&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Becoming a Household Name</p><p>Huobi and Poloniex witnessed a significant improvement in operational performance during Q2 compared to Q1 2023. This can be attributed to various factors, including the meme coin frenzy and the regulatory crackdown on other exchanges.</p><p>However, in terms of total on-chain assets, Huobi and Poloniex equated to $4 billion which falls behind Binance's $60 billion and OKX's $10 billion.&nbsp;</p><p>Huobi stated that in the next six months, it will continue to restore its brand confidence, increase platform assets and trading volume, and achieve profitability targets. It aims to become a stronger player and a household name within the cryptocurrency exchange industry.</p><p>With months of cost reduction and efficiency improvement efforts, Huobi has overcome survival challenges and will make future decisions based on long-term perspectives. Huobi is committed to actively embracing the ever-changing crypto industry and prioritizing user needs. The company firmly doesn&rsquo;t believe in sacrificing user interests for short-term gains. The focus will be on constantly creating value for users while achieving greater business wins.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Crypto Market's Three Pillars: Exchange, Public Chain, and Stablecoin</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-center">&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>Sun expressed that Huobi has always been following their global compliance strategy by actively embracing regulation and exploring diverse compliance operations. Numerous crypto companies are entering the Hong Kong market because of its new regulatory rules. Huobi is gaining exposure in the Hong Kong crypto market by launching Huobi Hong Kong, which allowed registration for Hong Kong residents on June 1 2023. Huobi is also the first exchange to become a member of the Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC). Additionally, Huobi is in continuous communication with the Hong Kong government to apply for a cryptocurrency exchange license.</p><p>Sun analyzed that exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins will become the main core of the entire blockchain industry. These three pillars for the decentralized financial landscape will influence long-time development in the industry. Sun stated that their mission is to build a Web3 finance hub in the metaverse and give an option to people worldwide to pursue financial freedom in the metaverse. Public chains serve as the foundation for creating a financial world in the metaverse, while exchanges play a crucial role as the gatekeepers.</p><p>Sun believes that Huobi holds a leading position within the industry. However, in terms of integration capabilities, Huobi stands out as the sole decentralized financial ecosystem platform with a structure encompassing all three pillars mentioned earlier. The three core businesses consisting of exchanges, public chains, and stablecoins will strive to enhance the user experience from multiple angles. It focuses on long-term industry development, covering the majority of industry traffic, and building a globally influential Web3 financial hub.</p><p></p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uwerx (WERX) Announces Upcoming Listing On Uniswap as Presale Winds Down]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uwerx-werx-announces-upcoming-listing-on-uniswap-as-presale-winds-down</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-12-at-171746.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-12-at-171746.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-12-at-171746.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uwerx-werx-announces-upcoming-listing-on-uniswap-as-presale-winds-down</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Uwerx is positioned to be the best freelance platform for all freelancers worldwide. Through the platform&rsquo;s unique features, freelancers will have a community that hears their needs and helps them grow. Uwerx&rsquo;s presale is coming to a quick close. In this article, we discuss why Uwerxwill be your best investment.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): The Hub of Freelancing Solutions
<p>Freelancers all over the globe struggle with a plethora of challenges and obstacles on different freelancing platforms. From high flat fees to the inability to land gigs on these platforms, it has become a battle zone for freelancers seeking more gigs. Uwerx aims to solve these challenges and more.</p>
<p>Uwerx aims to solve several problems that freelancers face in the cryptocurrency industry. This is why the platform offers users a 1% flat fee, a significant reduction compared to the 10% and 20% flat fees offered by freelancing platforms such as Upwork and Fiverr. </p>
<p>Uwerx is growing beyond expectations. Within a few weeks of launching, the Uwerx platform has grown to over 6,000 signups. The social media platforms are not left out, as Uwerx&rsquo;s Twitter now has 1,627 followers, with Telegram boasting 1,456 subscribers. These numbers have only just begun to grow. With Uwerx&rsquo;s current listing on CoinSniper, and its scheduled listing on Uniswap by the 1st of August, these numbers are bound to quadruple in the coming months.</p>
<p>Uwerx is here to stay. Uwerx communicates this message to its growing community by announcing a 25-year liquidity lock on its tokens. After 82.8% of Uwerx&rsquo;s users voted for the lock to happen imminently, unlike after the presale as planned, the Uwerx team will make this lock happen before the end of the presale. </p>
<p>Uwerx has already exceeded all standards of the cryptocurrency industry. The platform proves this with its successful audit undergone by InterFi Network and SolidProof, both renowned authorities in the industry. Once Uwerx is launched on centralized exchanges, the Uwerx team will be renouncing contract ownership, thus ensuring transparency with the platform and reducing taxes to zero..</p>
<p>The Uwerx Team is also taking steps to transition the platform from the Alpha platform to the Beta platform. Through the Beta platform, Uwerx users can test the platform for themselves, and they are encouraged to share all forms of feedback with the Uwerx team at feedback@uwerx.network. </p>
The Uwerx (WERX) Presale is Exceeding Expectations!
<p>Due to the unexpectedly high demands for Uwerx, the Uwerx team has had to make essential token modifications to accommodate these demands. 98.2% of Uwerx users voted via a Twitter Poll for the Uwerx team to launch a Test Airdrop for the platform. This will be launched on the 31st of July, 2023. &nbsp;Uwerx itself will be launched on the 4th of August, 2023, opening freelancers and crypto investors up to a whole new world. </p>
<p>The Uwerx team has also unveiled the Uwerx Vault. Through this vault, Uwerx users can store their WERX tokens for different periods and access rewards based on the variables within the platform. </p>
<p>Uwerx&rsquo;s first presale stage was completed in only 17 days, while its second was completed within eight days. Uwerx is in its fifth presale stage, selling at $0.041 per token, with a 15% bonus on every purchase. Uwerx&rsquo;s hard-cap presale end date has been scheduled for the 31st of July, 2023.</p>
<p>Are you ready to step into the future and unlock a 15% bonus on your purchases? Click on any of these links to join the Uwerx Presale:</p>
<p>Presale: www.invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uwerx is positioned to be the best freelance platform for all freelancers worldwide. Through the platform&rsquo;s unique features, freelancers will have a community that hears their needs and helps them grow. Uwerx&rsquo;s presale is coming to a quick close. In this article, we discuss why Uwerxwill be your best investment.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): The Hub of Freelancing Solutions
<p>Freelancers all over the globe struggle with a plethora of challenges and obstacles on different freelancing platforms. From high flat fees to the inability to land gigs on these platforms, it has become a battle zone for freelancers seeking more gigs. Uwerx aims to solve these challenges and more.</p>
<p>Uwerx aims to solve several problems that freelancers face in the cryptocurrency industry. This is why the platform offers users a 1% flat fee, a significant reduction compared to the 10% and 20% flat fees offered by freelancing platforms such as Upwork and Fiverr. </p>
<p>Uwerx is growing beyond expectations. Within a few weeks of launching, the Uwerx platform has grown to over 6,000 signups. The social media platforms are not left out, as Uwerx&rsquo;s Twitter now has 1,627 followers, with Telegram boasting 1,456 subscribers. These numbers have only just begun to grow. With Uwerx&rsquo;s current listing on CoinSniper, and its scheduled listing on Uniswap by the 1st of August, these numbers are bound to quadruple in the coming months.</p>
<p>Uwerx is here to stay. Uwerx communicates this message to its growing community by announcing a 25-year liquidity lock on its tokens. After 82.8% of Uwerx&rsquo;s users voted for the lock to happen imminently, unlike after the presale as planned, the Uwerx team will make this lock happen before the end of the presale. </p>
<p>Uwerx has already exceeded all standards of the cryptocurrency industry. The platform proves this with its successful audit undergone by InterFi Network and SolidProof, both renowned authorities in the industry. Once Uwerx is launched on centralized exchanges, the Uwerx team will be renouncing contract ownership, thus ensuring transparency with the platform and reducing taxes to zero..</p>
<p>The Uwerx Team is also taking steps to transition the platform from the Alpha platform to the Beta platform. Through the Beta platform, Uwerx users can test the platform for themselves, and they are encouraged to share all forms of feedback with the Uwerx team at feedback@uwerx.network. </p>
The Uwerx (WERX) Presale is Exceeding Expectations!
<p>Due to the unexpectedly high demands for Uwerx, the Uwerx team has had to make essential token modifications to accommodate these demands. 98.2% of Uwerx users voted via a Twitter Poll for the Uwerx team to launch a Test Airdrop for the platform. This will be launched on the 31st of July, 2023. &nbsp;Uwerx itself will be launched on the 4th of August, 2023, opening freelancers and crypto investors up to a whole new world. </p>
<p>The Uwerx team has also unveiled the Uwerx Vault. Through this vault, Uwerx users can store their WERX tokens for different periods and access rewards based on the variables within the platform. </p>
<p>Uwerx&rsquo;s first presale stage was completed in only 17 days, while its second was completed within eight days. Uwerx is in its fifth presale stage, selling at $0.041 per token, with a 15% bonus on every purchase. Uwerx&rsquo;s hard-cap presale end date has been scheduled for the 31st of July, 2023.</p>
<p>Are you ready to step into the future and unlock a 15% bonus on your purchases? Click on any of these links to join the Uwerx Presale:</p>
<p>Presale: www.invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  25364 at Risk Again - 13 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25364-at-risk-again-13-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-12-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-12-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-12-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25364-at-risk-again-13-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25634 at Risk Again:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 13 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to orbit the 26000 figure early in the Asian session as the pair climbed to the 26108.64 area after trading as low as the 25616.98 area, a previous move lower that represented a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25474.98 to 26219.10.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were recently elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid depreciation, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that recently intensified around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26393.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25859.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25634 at Risk Again:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 13 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to orbit the 26000 figure early in the Asian session as the pair climbed to the 26108.64 area after trading as low as the 25616.98 area, a previous move lower that represented a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25474.98 to 26219.10.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were recently elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid depreciation, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that recently intensified around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26393.21 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25859.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bored Pepe VIP Club (BPVC) Is Now Available for Trading on LBank Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bored-pepe-vip-club-bpvc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686582948bdUvj0kRBA.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686582948bdUvj0kRBA.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686582948bdUvj0kRBA.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:28:31 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bored-pepe-vip-club-bpvc-is-now-available-for-trading-on-lbank-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, listed Bored Pepe VIP Club (BPVC) on Jun 12, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the BPVC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023.</p><p>Bored Pepe Vip Club is a Coin named $BPVC and a collection of 10,000 Bored Pepe NFTs unique digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain. Its native token, BPVC, was listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023, with the goal of expanding its global footprint and supporting the realization of its forward-thinking objectives.</p><p>Introducing Bored Pepe VIP Club</p><p>LBank Exchange is thrilled to announce the upcoming listing of Bored Pepe VIP Club (BPVC), a Coin named $BPVC and a collection of 10,000 Bored Pepe NFTs unique digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain.</p><p>Possessing a Bored Pepe NFT not only offers ownership of a unique digital asset but also functions as a VIP Club membership card, endowing holders with exclusive members-only benefits. The primary benefit provided is access to PEPE LOUNGE, a collaborative graffiti board. Furthermore, the community has the ability to unlock future areas and perks through the activation of the roadmap.</p><p>Every Bored Pepe is distinctive and algorithmically created from a pool of over 70 potential traits, such as expression, headwear, clothing, and more. While all pepes are appealing, some are rarer than others. The pepes are held as ERC-721 tokens on the Ethereum blockchain and are hosted on IPFS for guaranteed proof of ownership and authenticity (See Record and Proof). The purchase of a Bored Pepe comes at a cost of 0.08 ETH. In order to gain access to members-only areas like the PEPE LOUNGE, holders of Bored Pepe will need to be signed into their Metamask Wallet.</p><p>Upon purchasing a Bored Pepe, one isn't simply acquiring an avatar or a provably rare piece of art. Instead, purchasers are becoming a member of an exclusive club, the benefits and offerings of which are poised to expand over time. A Bored Pepe can act as a digital identity and unlock virtual opportunities for its owner.</p><p>The BPVC Lounge, an exclusive area for Pepe holders, will become operational once the sale period concludes. It features a canvas that is only accessible to wallets that contain at least one pepe. As one might expect in any quality bar, this is the place for users to draw, jot down thoughts, or write expletives.</p><p>Every fifteen minutes, each pepe-holder is granted the privilege to paint a pixel on the bathroom wall. This can be seen as a collective art experiment in the cryptosphere: a members-only canvas for the sophisticated minds of crypto Twitter.</p><p>About BPVC Token</p><p>Based on ERC-20, BPVC has a fixed total supply of 1 trillion (i.e. 1,000,000,000,000). It was listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023, investors who are interested in BPVC can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange now. The listing of BPVC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p><p>Learn More about BPVC Token:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Telegram | Opensea | Contract</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;</p><p>Telegram l&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;YouTube</p><p></p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, listed Bored Pepe VIP Club (BPVC) on Jun 12, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the BPVC/USDT trading pair is now officially available for trading at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023.</p><p>Bored Pepe Vip Club is a Coin named $BPVC and a collection of 10,000 Bored Pepe NFTs unique digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain. Its native token, BPVC, was listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023, with the goal of expanding its global footprint and supporting the realization of its forward-thinking objectives.</p><p>Introducing Bored Pepe VIP Club</p><p>LBank Exchange is thrilled to announce the upcoming listing of Bored Pepe VIP Club (BPVC), a Coin named $BPVC and a collection of 10,000 Bored Pepe NFTs unique digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain.</p><p>Possessing a Bored Pepe NFT not only offers ownership of a unique digital asset but also functions as a VIP Club membership card, endowing holders with exclusive members-only benefits. The primary benefit provided is access to PEPE LOUNGE, a collaborative graffiti board. Furthermore, the community has the ability to unlock future areas and perks through the activation of the roadmap.</p><p>Every Bored Pepe is distinctive and algorithmically created from a pool of over 70 potential traits, such as expression, headwear, clothing, and more. While all pepes are appealing, some are rarer than others. The pepes are held as ERC-721 tokens on the Ethereum blockchain and are hosted on IPFS for guaranteed proof of ownership and authenticity (See Record and Proof). The purchase of a Bored Pepe comes at a cost of 0.08 ETH. In order to gain access to members-only areas like the PEPE LOUNGE, holders of Bored Pepe will need to be signed into their Metamask Wallet.</p><p>Upon purchasing a Bored Pepe, one isn't simply acquiring an avatar or a provably rare piece of art. Instead, purchasers are becoming a member of an exclusive club, the benefits and offerings of which are poised to expand over time. A Bored Pepe can act as a digital identity and unlock virtual opportunities for its owner.</p><p>The BPVC Lounge, an exclusive area for Pepe holders, will become operational once the sale period concludes. It features a canvas that is only accessible to wallets that contain at least one pepe. As one might expect in any quality bar, this is the place for users to draw, jot down thoughts, or write expletives.</p><p>Every fifteen minutes, each pepe-holder is granted the privilege to paint a pixel on the bathroom wall. This can be seen as a collective art experiment in the cryptosphere: a members-only canvas for the sophisticated minds of crypto Twitter.</p><p>About BPVC Token</p><p>Based on ERC-20, BPVC has a fixed total supply of 1 trillion (i.e. 1,000,000,000,000). It was listed on LBank Exchange at 10:00 UTC on Jun 12, 2023, investors who are interested in BPVC can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange now. The listing of BPVC token on LBank Exchange will undoubtedly help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p><p>Learn More about BPVC Token:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Telegram | Opensea | Contract</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;</p><p>Telegram l&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;YouTube</p><p></p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Massive Gaming Celebrates Global Launch of House of Poker With 100% USDC Rewards Guaranteed in Free Bonus Giveaway Event]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/massive-gaming-celebrates-global-launch-of-house-of-poker-with-100-usdc-rewards-guaranteed-in-free-bonus-giveaway-event</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/thumbnail_230601_HOP_P2E__1920x1080_2_1686157264jPuursmdct.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/thumbnail_230601_HOP_P2E__1920x1080_2_1686157264jPuursmdct.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/thumbnail_230601_HOP_P2E__1920x1080_2_1686157264jPuursmdct.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:00:18 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/massive-gaming-celebrates-global-launch-of-house-of-poker-with-100-usdc-rewards-guaranteed-in-free-bonus-giveaway-event</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Seattle, United States, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Massive Gaming is thrilled to announce the successful launch of House of Poker, a groundbreaking online hold'em game that revolutionizes the poker gaming experience. To commemorate this momentous occasion, Massive Gaming invites players from around the world to join in the excitement of the 100% USDC Rewards Guaranteed Free Bonus Giveaway Event, which has a minimum total prize pool of $6,000 USD worth of rewards, this event promises to deliver thrilling gameplay and incredible prizes.&nbsp;</p><p>Check out the House of Poker Launch Trailer on YouTube.</p><p></p><p>The House of Poker Free Bonus Giveaway Event offers a wide range of engaging missions. Some of the exciting missions include:&nbsp;</p><ul><li>House of Poker Log-in mission (Total prize: GEMS worth in $1,000 USDC)</li><li>Shark of the Week's mission (Total prize: $3,000 USDC worth of GEM &uarr; / 100% Reward Guaranteed)</li><li>Friends Invitation mission (Total prize: $2,000 USDC worth of GEM)</li></ul><p>The total prize pool is set to increase as more participants engage in the event, making it an even more enticing opportunity to win big. For full event details and to participate, please visit the event page.</p><p>House of Poker stands out from other online hold'em games with its outstanding features, including ITECH RNG certification, an extensive range of hold'em tournament contents, and the best live face chat feature that allows players to engage with opponents in real-time. The game also boasts a decentralized Play and Earn system and embraces the adoption of USDC for seamless and secure transactions.&nbsp;</p><p>To stay up-to-date on the latest news and developments from Massive Gaming, please visit Massive Gaming's official homepage. House of Poker officially launched on June 12, 2023, offering players an unmatched and immersive online hold'em experience.</p><p>Download House of Poker now from the following links:</p><p>Google &amp; Apple | Mycard APK</p><p>About Massive Gaming</p><p>Massive Gaming is an affiliate of NEOWIZ, focused on the production and publication of Crypto-enabled games and services.</p><p>For more information and to stay updated, please visit Massive Gaming's official website or follow us on social media:</p><p>Homepage | Twitter | Discord | Blog | Facebook Fanpage | Telegram | Medium | Coinmarketcap</p>ContactPress RelationsBill MurphyMassive Gamingbill@massivegaming.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seattle, United States, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Massive Gaming is thrilled to announce the successful launch of House of Poker, a groundbreaking online hold'em game that revolutionizes the poker gaming experience. To commemorate this momentous occasion, Massive Gaming invites players from around the world to join in the excitement of the 100% USDC Rewards Guaranteed Free Bonus Giveaway Event, which has a minimum total prize pool of $6,000 USD worth of rewards, this event promises to deliver thrilling gameplay and incredible prizes.&nbsp;</p><p>Check out the House of Poker Launch Trailer on YouTube.</p><p></p><p>The House of Poker Free Bonus Giveaway Event offers a wide range of engaging missions. Some of the exciting missions include:&nbsp;</p><ul><li>House of Poker Log-in mission (Total prize: GEMS worth in $1,000 USDC)</li><li>Shark of the Week's mission (Total prize: $3,000 USDC worth of GEM &uarr; / 100% Reward Guaranteed)</li><li>Friends Invitation mission (Total prize: $2,000 USDC worth of GEM)</li></ul><p>The total prize pool is set to increase as more participants engage in the event, making it an even more enticing opportunity to win big. For full event details and to participate, please visit the event page.</p><p>House of Poker stands out from other online hold'em games with its outstanding features, including ITECH RNG certification, an extensive range of hold'em tournament contents, and the best live face chat feature that allows players to engage with opponents in real-time. The game also boasts a decentralized Play and Earn system and embraces the adoption of USDC for seamless and secure transactions.&nbsp;</p><p>To stay up-to-date on the latest news and developments from Massive Gaming, please visit Massive Gaming's official homepage. House of Poker officially launched on June 12, 2023, offering players an unmatched and immersive online hold'em experience.</p><p>Download House of Poker now from the following links:</p><p>Google &amp; Apple | Mycard APK</p><p>About Massive Gaming</p><p>Massive Gaming is an affiliate of NEOWIZ, focused on the production and publication of Crypto-enabled games and services.</p><p>For more information and to stay updated, please visit Massive Gaming's official website or follow us on social media:</p><p>Homepage | Twitter | Discord | Blog | Facebook Fanpage | Telegram | Medium | Coinmarketcap</p>ContactPress RelationsBill MurphyMassive Gamingbill@massivegaming.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[IoTeX releases W3bstream’s Devnet, world’s first infra for DePIN projects]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/iotex-releases-w3bstreams-devnet-worlds-first-infra-for-depin-projects</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-12-135239.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-12-135239.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-12-135239.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/iotex-releases-w3bstreams-devnet-worlds-first-infra-for-depin-projects</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>IoTeX has made waves with the official release of W3bstream Devnet, positioning itself as the first-ever provider of comprehensive tools and infrastructure for building transformative Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) dApps.</p>
<p>This groundbreaking launch is set to speed up the DePIN sector&rsquo;s development process, slashing costs by 10x and accelerating go-to-market time for developers from two years to about two months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>W3bstream, IoTeX's flagship technology, empowers developers to quickly and easily build dynamic dApps for mobility networks, energy systems, sensor networks, AI computing frameworks, and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the advent of Devnet, developers gain unprecedented access to cutting-edge features, enabling seamless connectivity between billions of smart devices and smart contracts, unlocking a world of limitless innovation and societal impact.</p>

<p>"At IoTeX, we are trailblazers in offering developers out-of-the-box services to create DePIN dApps that reward users for their actions or incentivize specific behaviors," explains Raullen Chai, CEO and Founder of IoTeX.</p>
<p>"The release of W3bstream Devnet marks a turning point for the DePIN sector, projected to become the most significant trend in the Web3 industry, akin to the rise of DeFi in recent years," he added.</p>

<p>DePIN has emerged as a driving force propelling the next wave of Web3 adoption. By addressing the limitations of centralized smart device connectivity and applications, such as security, reliability, privacy, and data ownership, the DePIN market will grow to a staggering $3 trillion by 2028.&nbsp;</p>
<p>IoTeX's W3bstream aims to reshape the smart device landscape, ushering in a new era of enhanced user experiences and improved quality of life.</p>
The Power of W3bstream Devnet
<p>Devnet is the first public implementation of W3bstream's chain and device-agnostic architecture and represents a significant milestone in IoTeX's quest to simplify DePIN network development and data-driven dApp creation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Devnet provides developers with a chain-agnostic environment, facilitating the seamless crowdsourcing of real-world data from smart devices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These verifiable "proofs of real-world activity" trigger smart contracts, enabling the direct delivery of digital assets such as cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, Soulbound Tokens (SBTs), and NFTs to users.</p>
<p>Central to Devnet is the powerful W3bstream Studio, an intuitive control center equipped with an array of developer-centric features.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the Studio's streamlined interface, developers can effortlessly orchestrate every aspect of their DePIN projects, from data reception to application logic and seamless blockchain interaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Devnet also offers essential components such as mobile Software Development Kits (SDKs) and Web Assembly (WASM), providing developers unparalleled flexibility and convenience in creating their decentralized applications.</p>
<p>IoTeX is committed to continuously expanding W3bstream's capabilities, with future Devnet releases set to introduce a range of out-of-the-box DePIN solutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These include trusted token metrics for visualizing and analyzing device data on the blockchain, token proofs to validate off-chain data and facilitate token incentives, trusted location services for proof of humanity and presence, and various geo-based use cases.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
IoTeX's Devnet Launch Partners
<p>Numerous pioneering DePIN projects are already poised to harness W3bstream's potential. Drife, a disruptive force in the global ridesharing market, is notable among these, which has already amassed over 30,000 drivers, 100,000 registered users, and completed 250,000 rides.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By utilizing W3bstream, Drife integrates verifiable mobile geo-location into its tech stack, ensuring secure tracking of routes driven and providing a trusted environment for drivers and riders alike.</p>
<p>React Network, another prominent partner, consists of thousands of connected batteries deployed across homes, businesses, and multi-family living spaces. This innovative energy network supports the power grid during times of high demand and utilizes W3bstream to effectively manage and visualize the diverse footprint of smart devices contributing to its network. The platform efficiently processes the high volume of real-time data generated by these devices, enabling a more optimized and sustainable energy grid system.</p>
<p>These partnerships exemplify the real-world applications of W3bstream and highlight the transformative potential of Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks. By leveraging the power of blockchain and smart contracts, IoTeX and its partners are revolutionizing industries and empowering users with greater control over their data and participation in the machine economy.</p>
<p>As the world's first provider of DePIN infrastructure and tools, IoTeX is leading the way in unlocking the full potential of decentralized IoT. With the launch of W3bstream's Devnet, developers now have access to a comprehensive framework that simplifies the development process, reduces costs, and accelerates time-to-market for data-driven dApps. The possibilities for innovation and social impact are boundless as W3bstream connects billions of intelligent devices to smart contracts, creating a more inclusive and decentralized future.</p>
Sparking a new wave of adoption
<p>With Devnet, IoTeX is spearheading the DePIN revolution and paving the way for the next wave of Web3 adoption. By addressing the limitations of centralized IoT solutions and providing developers with the necessary tools and infrastructure, IoTeX is driving the transition toward a more secure, reliable, and privacy-preserving ecosystem.</p>
<p>The launch of W3bstream's Devnet marks a significant milestone in developing Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks. IoTeX's commitment to democratizing IoT and empowering developers is revolutionizing the machine economy and opening up endless possibilities for innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its unique features, chain-agnostic environment, and strong partnerships, W3bstream will shape the future of IoT and drive the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IoTeX has made waves with the official release of W3bstream Devnet, positioning itself as the first-ever provider of comprehensive tools and infrastructure for building transformative Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) dApps.</p>
<p>This groundbreaking launch is set to speed up the DePIN sector&rsquo;s development process, slashing costs by 10x and accelerating go-to-market time for developers from two years to about two months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>W3bstream, IoTeX's flagship technology, empowers developers to quickly and easily build dynamic dApps for mobility networks, energy systems, sensor networks, AI computing frameworks, and more.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the advent of Devnet, developers gain unprecedented access to cutting-edge features, enabling seamless connectivity between billions of smart devices and smart contracts, unlocking a world of limitless innovation and societal impact.</p>

<p>"At IoTeX, we are trailblazers in offering developers out-of-the-box services to create DePIN dApps that reward users for their actions or incentivize specific behaviors," explains Raullen Chai, CEO and Founder of IoTeX.</p>
<p>"The release of W3bstream Devnet marks a turning point for the DePIN sector, projected to become the most significant trend in the Web3 industry, akin to the rise of DeFi in recent years," he added.</p>

<p>DePIN has emerged as a driving force propelling the next wave of Web3 adoption. By addressing the limitations of centralized smart device connectivity and applications, such as security, reliability, privacy, and data ownership, the DePIN market will grow to a staggering $3 trillion by 2028.&nbsp;</p>
<p>IoTeX's W3bstream aims to reshape the smart device landscape, ushering in a new era of enhanced user experiences and improved quality of life.</p>
The Power of W3bstream Devnet
<p>Devnet is the first public implementation of W3bstream's chain and device-agnostic architecture and represents a significant milestone in IoTeX's quest to simplify DePIN network development and data-driven dApp creation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Devnet provides developers with a chain-agnostic environment, facilitating the seamless crowdsourcing of real-world data from smart devices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These verifiable "proofs of real-world activity" trigger smart contracts, enabling the direct delivery of digital assets such as cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, Soulbound Tokens (SBTs), and NFTs to users.</p>
<p>Central to Devnet is the powerful W3bstream Studio, an intuitive control center equipped with an array of developer-centric features.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the Studio's streamlined interface, developers can effortlessly orchestrate every aspect of their DePIN projects, from data reception to application logic and seamless blockchain interaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Devnet also offers essential components such as mobile Software Development Kits (SDKs) and Web Assembly (WASM), providing developers unparalleled flexibility and convenience in creating their decentralized applications.</p>
<p>IoTeX is committed to continuously expanding W3bstream's capabilities, with future Devnet releases set to introduce a range of out-of-the-box DePIN solutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>These include trusted token metrics for visualizing and analyzing device data on the blockchain, token proofs to validate off-chain data and facilitate token incentives, trusted location services for proof of humanity and presence, and various geo-based use cases.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
IoTeX's Devnet Launch Partners
<p>Numerous pioneering DePIN projects are already poised to harness W3bstream's potential. Drife, a disruptive force in the global ridesharing market, is notable among these, which has already amassed over 30,000 drivers, 100,000 registered users, and completed 250,000 rides.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By utilizing W3bstream, Drife integrates verifiable mobile geo-location into its tech stack, ensuring secure tracking of routes driven and providing a trusted environment for drivers and riders alike.</p>
<p>React Network, another prominent partner, consists of thousands of connected batteries deployed across homes, businesses, and multi-family living spaces. This innovative energy network supports the power grid during times of high demand and utilizes W3bstream to effectively manage and visualize the diverse footprint of smart devices contributing to its network. The platform efficiently processes the high volume of real-time data generated by these devices, enabling a more optimized and sustainable energy grid system.</p>
<p>These partnerships exemplify the real-world applications of W3bstream and highlight the transformative potential of Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks. By leveraging the power of blockchain and smart contracts, IoTeX and its partners are revolutionizing industries and empowering users with greater control over their data and participation in the machine economy.</p>
<p>As the world's first provider of DePIN infrastructure and tools, IoTeX is leading the way in unlocking the full potential of decentralized IoT. With the launch of W3bstream's Devnet, developers now have access to a comprehensive framework that simplifies the development process, reduces costs, and accelerates time-to-market for data-driven dApps. The possibilities for innovation and social impact are boundless as W3bstream connects billions of intelligent devices to smart contracts, creating a more inclusive and decentralized future.</p>
Sparking a new wave of adoption
<p>With Devnet, IoTeX is spearheading the DePIN revolution and paving the way for the next wave of Web3 adoption. By addressing the limitations of centralized IoT solutions and providing developers with the necessary tools and infrastructure, IoTeX is driving the transition toward a more secure, reliable, and privacy-preserving ecosystem.</p>
<p>The launch of W3bstream's Devnet marks a significant milestone in developing Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks. IoTeX's commitment to democratizing IoT and empowering developers is revolutionizing the machine economy and opening up endless possibilities for innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its unique features, chain-agnostic environment, and strong partnerships, W3bstream will shape the future of IoT and drive the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Minting and Selling NFTs for Fun and Profit]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/minting-and-selling-nfts-for-fun-and-profit</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920-1080-f16x9nftcollage01f-copy.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920-1080-f16x9nftcollage01f-copy.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920-1080-f16x9nftcollage01f-copy.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/minting-and-selling-nfts-for-fun-and-profit</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Non-Fungible Token (NFT) market in 2023 shows strong signs of recovery after the uncertainty and volatility of 2022.</p>
What are NFTs?
<p>Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are digital assets on a blockchain representing anything from artwork to music to in-game items.</p>
<p>The NFT market landscape has been transformed by the emergence of new projects, platforms, and technologies and changing trends in the cryptocurrency space.</p>
How to Mint NFTs
<p>To mint an NFT, you must create a digital asset and then "mint" it or turn it into an NFT.</p>
Here are the steps on how to mint an NFT:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Choose a blockchain. Many blockchains support NFTs, such as Ethereum, Solana, and Flow. Each blockchain has its advantages and disadvantages, so you must choose one that is right for you.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Create a digital asset. This can be anything from artwork to a song to a video. The digital asset must be unique and cannot be easily copied. For example, you can create unique DUCKIES NFTs in an educational NFT minting &amp; melding game to turn common NFTs into legendary and mythic ones.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Choose an NFT marketplace. There are many different NFT marketplaces where you can mint and sell your NFTs. Some popular marketplaces include OpenSea, Rarible, and SuperRare.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Connect your wallet. To mint and sell NFTs, you must connect a crypto wallet to the NFT marketplace. Some popular crypto wallets include MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Trust Wallet.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Mint your NFT. Once you have connected your wallet to the NFT marketplace, you can mint your NFT. The minting process will vary depending on the marketplace but typically involves paying a gas fee.</li>
</ul>
Where to Sell NFTs
<p>Once you have minted your NFT, you can sell it on an NFT marketplace. There are many different NFT marketplaces, so you must choose one that is right for you. Some factors to consider include the marketplace's fees, the number of users, and the type of NFTs typically sold.</p>
Here are some of the most popular NFT marketplaces:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">OpenSea: OpenSea is the largest NFT marketplace, with over 2 million users. It supports various NFTs, including artwork, music, and in-game items. You can host entire NFT collections. Here&rsquo;s an example of DUCKIES NFTs hosted for sale at OpenSea.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Rarible: Rarible is a popular NFT marketplace that allows users to create and sell their NFTs. It also supports a wide variety of NFTs.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">SuperRare: SuperRare is a high-end NFT marketplace that focuses on high-quality artwork. It has a smaller user base than OpenSea or Rarible but also has higher prices.</li>
</ul>
<p>Tips for Selling NFTs</p>
Here are some tips for selling NFTs:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Set a fair price. When setting a price for your NFT, it is important to consider the value of similar NFTs sold. You do not want to price your NFT too high, or it will not sell. For example, the Mythic DUCKIES are sold for over $1,000 at OpenSea.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Promote your NFT. Once you have listed your NFT for sale, you must promote it to attract buyers. You can do this by sharing it on social media, listing it on other NFT marketplaces, or joining NFT communities.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Be patient. It may take some time to sell your NFT. Do not get discouraged if it does not sell immediately. Just keep promoting it, and eventually, you will find a buyer.</li>
</ul>
Conclusion
<p>Minting and selling NFTs can be a great way to showcase your creativity and make money out of it. However, it is important to research and understand the risks involved before you start.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Non-Fungible Token (NFT) market in 2023 shows strong signs of recovery after the uncertainty and volatility of 2022.</p>
What are NFTs?
<p>Non-fungible tokens (NFTs) are digital assets on a blockchain representing anything from artwork to music to in-game items.</p>
<p>The NFT market landscape has been transformed by the emergence of new projects, platforms, and technologies and changing trends in the cryptocurrency space.</p>
How to Mint NFTs
<p>To mint an NFT, you must create a digital asset and then "mint" it or turn it into an NFT.</p>
Here are the steps on how to mint an NFT:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Choose a blockchain. Many blockchains support NFTs, such as Ethereum, Solana, and Flow. Each blockchain has its advantages and disadvantages, so you must choose one that is right for you.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Create a digital asset. This can be anything from artwork to a song to a video. The digital asset must be unique and cannot be easily copied. For example, you can create unique DUCKIES NFTs in an educational NFT minting &amp; melding game to turn common NFTs into legendary and mythic ones.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Choose an NFT marketplace. There are many different NFT marketplaces where you can mint and sell your NFTs. Some popular marketplaces include OpenSea, Rarible, and SuperRare.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Connect your wallet. To mint and sell NFTs, you must connect a crypto wallet to the NFT marketplace. Some popular crypto wallets include MetaMask, Coinbase Wallet, and Trust Wallet.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Mint your NFT. Once you have connected your wallet to the NFT marketplace, you can mint your NFT. The minting process will vary depending on the marketplace but typically involves paying a gas fee.</li>
</ul>
Where to Sell NFTs
<p>Once you have minted your NFT, you can sell it on an NFT marketplace. There are many different NFT marketplaces, so you must choose one that is right for you. Some factors to consider include the marketplace's fees, the number of users, and the type of NFTs typically sold.</p>
Here are some of the most popular NFT marketplaces:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">OpenSea: OpenSea is the largest NFT marketplace, with over 2 million users. It supports various NFTs, including artwork, music, and in-game items. You can host entire NFT collections. Here&rsquo;s an example of DUCKIES NFTs hosted for sale at OpenSea.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Rarible: Rarible is a popular NFT marketplace that allows users to create and sell their NFTs. It also supports a wide variety of NFTs.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">SuperRare: SuperRare is a high-end NFT marketplace that focuses on high-quality artwork. It has a smaller user base than OpenSea or Rarible but also has higher prices.</li>
</ul>
<p>Tips for Selling NFTs</p>
Here are some tips for selling NFTs:
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Set a fair price. When setting a price for your NFT, it is important to consider the value of similar NFTs sold. You do not want to price your NFT too high, or it will not sell. For example, the Mythic DUCKIES are sold for over $1,000 at OpenSea.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Promote your NFT. Once you have listed your NFT for sale, you must promote it to attract buyers. You can do this by sharing it on social media, listing it on other NFT marketplaces, or joining NFT communities.</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Be patient. It may take some time to sell your NFT. Do not get discouraged if it does not sell immediately. Just keep promoting it, and eventually, you will find a buyer.</li>
</ul>
Conclusion
<p>Minting and selling NFTs can be a great way to showcase your creativity and make money out of it. However, it is important to research and understand the risks involved before you start.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Should you try PrimeXBT crypto futures? An honest review]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/should-you-try-primexbt-crypto-futures-an-honest-review</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/real-d29602ec-08bc-424e-8168-697b85f46521.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/real-d29602ec-08bc-424e-8168-697b85f46521.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/real-d29602ec-08bc-424e-8168-697b85f46521.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/should-you-try-primexbt-crypto-futures-an-honest-review</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency trading has taken the financial world by storm, offering exciting opportunities for both seasoned traders and newcomers to the market. If you're looking to dig deep into the world of crypto futures trading, one platform that has gained attention recently is PrimeXBT. But should you try PrimeXBT crypto futures? In this honest review, we'll explore the platform's key features, usability, security measures, and more to help you make an educated decision.</p>
Crypto futures trading on PrimeXBT
<p>The first thing you will notice is the diverse selection of cryptocurrencies available for trading. PrimeXBT offers a wide range of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Ripple, Dogecoin and many more. This extensive offering allows traders to diversify their portfolios and take advantage of different market dynamics and opportunities. Whether you're interested in major cryptocurrencies or seeking exposure to promising altcoins, PrimeXBT has you covered.</p>
<p>Another aspect that sets PrimeXBT apart is its user-friendly interface. Navigating the platform is a breeze, even for those new to trading. The intuitive layout provides easy access to key features and tools, allowing you to focus on making informed trading decisions. Plus, PrimeXBT offers a customizable user interface, allowing you to tailor the platform to your preferences. Whether you prefer a clean and minimalist workspace or a more comprehensive view of charts and market data, PrimeXBT gives you the flexibility to create your ideal trading environment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>When it comes to risk management, PrimeXBT provides a range of tools to help protect your capital. One notable feature is the ability to set stop-loss orders. These orders automatically close your positions if the market moves against you, limiting potential losses. PrimeXBT also offers other risk management tools, such as take-profit orders and adjustable leverage settings. These tools allow you to control your exposure to the market and optimize your trading strategies based on your risk tolerance and market conditions.</p>
<p>In addition to its user-friendly interface and risk management tools, PrimeXBT stands out with its integration of TradingView's advanced charting tools. TradingView is a popular platform among traders for its comprehensive technical analysis features. PrimeXBT's collaboration with TradingView provides users with access to over 50 pre-built technical indicators and more than 50 drawing tools. These tools empower experienced traders to analyze price charts, identify patterns, and make more successful trading decisions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Additional trading opportunities at PrimeXBT
<p>Unlike most other crypto futures platforms, PrimeXBT also provides access to Contract for Difference (CFD) trading on traditiaonl assets. This allows traders to speculate on the price movements of forex, commodities, and stock indices. With CFD trading on PrimeXBT, you can diversify your trading portfolio and take advantage of opportunities in multiple financial markets, all from a single platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another unique feature offered by PrimeXBT is copy trading. This innovative tool allows you to follow and automatically replicate the trades of successful traders on the platform. If you're new to trading or simply want to learn from experienced traders, copy trading provides an excellent opportunity to observe and potentially profit from their strategies. With PrimeXBT's copy trading feature, you can browse through a list of top-performing traders, analyze their historical performance, and choose to copy their trades with a few clicks.</p>
<p>PrimeXBT Trading Academy and Contests further enrich the platform's offerings. The Trading Academy provides educational resources, including articles, tutorials, videos, and webinars, covering a wide range of trading topics. Additionally, PrimeXBT's weekly trading contests add an element of excitement and competition. These contests allow you to showcase your trading skills and compete for crypto-based prizes. Using virtual demo funds, provides a risk-free way to test your strategies, gain experience, and potentially win rewards, all while sharpening your trading abilities.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
PrimeXBT crypto futures review conclusion
<p>Now, let's address the crucial question: should you try PrimeXBT crypto futures? The answer is a resounding yes. PrimeXBT offers a comprehensive and user-friendly platform for crypto futures trading. Its extensive selection of cryptocurrencies, customizable user interface, risk management tools, and integration of advanced charting features make it an attractive option for both novice and experienced traders.</p>
<p>Moreover, PrimeXBT prioritizes security and user safety. The platform stores the majority of user funds in cold storage wallets, ensuring their protection against online threats. Two-factor authentication (2FA) adds an extra layer of security, reducing the risk of unauthorized access. PrimeXBT also adheres to industry best practices, such as Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) policies, to ensure a safe and compliant trading environment.</p>
<p>PrimeXBT has received positive user reviews and recognition within the industry, further solidifying its reputation as a reliable and trustworthy platform. The company's commitment to providing excellent customer service, as evidenced by its 24/7 live chat support and extensive help center, demonstrates its dedication to user satisfaction. For all these reasons and more, we recommend you give it a try.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency trading has taken the financial world by storm, offering exciting opportunities for both seasoned traders and newcomers to the market. If you're looking to dig deep into the world of crypto futures trading, one platform that has gained attention recently is PrimeXBT. But should you try PrimeXBT crypto futures? In this honest review, we'll explore the platform's key features, usability, security measures, and more to help you make an educated decision.</p>
Crypto futures trading on PrimeXBT
<p>The first thing you will notice is the diverse selection of cryptocurrencies available for trading. PrimeXBT offers a wide range of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Ripple, Dogecoin and many more. This extensive offering allows traders to diversify their portfolios and take advantage of different market dynamics and opportunities. Whether you're interested in major cryptocurrencies or seeking exposure to promising altcoins, PrimeXBT has you covered.</p>
<p>Another aspect that sets PrimeXBT apart is its user-friendly interface. Navigating the platform is a breeze, even for those new to trading. The intuitive layout provides easy access to key features and tools, allowing you to focus on making informed trading decisions. Plus, PrimeXBT offers a customizable user interface, allowing you to tailor the platform to your preferences. Whether you prefer a clean and minimalist workspace or a more comprehensive view of charts and market data, PrimeXBT gives you the flexibility to create your ideal trading environment.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>When it comes to risk management, PrimeXBT provides a range of tools to help protect your capital. One notable feature is the ability to set stop-loss orders. These orders automatically close your positions if the market moves against you, limiting potential losses. PrimeXBT also offers other risk management tools, such as take-profit orders and adjustable leverage settings. These tools allow you to control your exposure to the market and optimize your trading strategies based on your risk tolerance and market conditions.</p>
<p>In addition to its user-friendly interface and risk management tools, PrimeXBT stands out with its integration of TradingView's advanced charting tools. TradingView is a popular platform among traders for its comprehensive technical analysis features. PrimeXBT's collaboration with TradingView provides users with access to over 50 pre-built technical indicators and more than 50 drawing tools. These tools empower experienced traders to analyze price charts, identify patterns, and make more successful trading decisions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Additional trading opportunities at PrimeXBT
<p>Unlike most other crypto futures platforms, PrimeXBT also provides access to Contract for Difference (CFD) trading on traditiaonl assets. This allows traders to speculate on the price movements of forex, commodities, and stock indices. With CFD trading on PrimeXBT, you can diversify your trading portfolio and take advantage of opportunities in multiple financial markets, all from a single platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another unique feature offered by PrimeXBT is copy trading. This innovative tool allows you to follow and automatically replicate the trades of successful traders on the platform. If you're new to trading or simply want to learn from experienced traders, copy trading provides an excellent opportunity to observe and potentially profit from their strategies. With PrimeXBT's copy trading feature, you can browse through a list of top-performing traders, analyze their historical performance, and choose to copy their trades with a few clicks.</p>
<p>PrimeXBT Trading Academy and Contests further enrich the platform's offerings. The Trading Academy provides educational resources, including articles, tutorials, videos, and webinars, covering a wide range of trading topics. Additionally, PrimeXBT's weekly trading contests add an element of excitement and competition. These contests allow you to showcase your trading skills and compete for crypto-based prizes. Using virtual demo funds, provides a risk-free way to test your strategies, gain experience, and potentially win rewards, all while sharpening your trading abilities.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
PrimeXBT crypto futures review conclusion
<p>Now, let's address the crucial question: should you try PrimeXBT crypto futures? The answer is a resounding yes. PrimeXBT offers a comprehensive and user-friendly platform for crypto futures trading. Its extensive selection of cryptocurrencies, customizable user interface, risk management tools, and integration of advanced charting features make it an attractive option for both novice and experienced traders.</p>
<p>Moreover, PrimeXBT prioritizes security and user safety. The platform stores the majority of user funds in cold storage wallets, ensuring their protection against online threats. Two-factor authentication (2FA) adds an extra layer of security, reducing the risk of unauthorized access. PrimeXBT also adheres to industry best practices, such as Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) policies, to ensure a safe and compliant trading environment.</p>
<p>PrimeXBT has received positive user reviews and recognition within the industry, further solidifying its reputation as a reliable and trustworthy platform. The company's commitment to providing excellent customer service, as evidenced by its 24/7 live chat support and extensive help center, demonstrates its dedication to user satisfaction. For all these reasons and more, we recommend you give it a try.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz To Open Crypto Office in London]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/andreessen-horowitz-to-open-crypto-office-in-london</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ah-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ah-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ah-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:54:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/andreessen-horowitz-to-open-crypto-office-in-london</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Silicon Valley-based venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz will open its first international office in London. The firm cites the UK&rsquo;s welcoming crypto climate. </p>
<p>The crypto investment arm of venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, a16z, announced it would be opening its first overseas office in London. The firm celebrated the UK&rsquo;s welcoming embrace of the crypto industry as the motivating factor behind its decision.</p>
<p>Under the leadership of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, the UK has established a warm climate for crypto companies as the industry battles regulatory confusion from the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Big news to share: @a16z is expanding to the UK 🇬🇧We plan to open our first international office in London later this year, and will host the next Crypto Startup School there in 2024.Why the UK? 👇https://t.co/PQ7GuNEn77</p>
&mdash; cdixon.eth (@cdixon) June 11, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports the new office will open later this year and will be led by Sriram Krishnan, one of the firm&rsquo;s general partners. &nbsp;</p>
<p>a16z said in a statement:</p>

<p>While there is still work to be done, we believe that the UK is on the right path to becoming a leader in crypto regulation. The UK also has deep pools of talent, world-leading academic institutions, and a strong entrepreneurial culture.</p>
<p>It is home to more &ldquo;unicorns&rdquo; than Germany, France, and Sweden combined; to some of the world&rsquo;s largest financial markets and pools of capital; and to highly-sophisticated, world-class regulators. All of these make the UK strongly positioned to lead in web3.</p>

<p>Prime Minister Sunak welcomed the firm&rsquo;s decision and underscored the UK&rsquo;s commitment to establishing the country as the &ldquo;world&rsquo;s Web3 centre.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Great news that @a16z &ndash; one of the world&rsquo;s leading tech investment firms, is opening a new base here in London.Another huge vote of confidence in the UK as a place to build and grow tech businesses of the future. https://t.co/Ey1ykALkSU pic.twitter.com/caP6nNXfow</p>
&mdash; Rishi Sunak (@RishiSunak) June 12, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The Prime Minister said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;As we cement the UK&rsquo;s place as a science and tech superpower, we must embrace new innovations like Web3, powered by blockchain technology, which will enable start-ups to flourish here and grow the economy.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Crypto Firms Are Being Driven Offshore
<p>The US SEC recently launched severe regulatory action against two of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges. On June 5, the agency filed suit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, for alleged securities violations. The following day, the agency filed a similar case against Coinbase. It charged the exchange with &ldquo;the unregistered offer and sale of securities in connection with its staking-as-a-service program.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The US&rsquo;s aggressive approach led the market to spiral, with major altcoins seeing double-digit losses.</p>
UK&rsquo;s Regulatory Approach
<p>Recognising the need for regulatory guidance, crypto firms such as Coinbase have long asked the US to provide clarity regarding crypto assets. The US has, however, been reluctant to comply, which only creates further tension in the industry.</p>
<p>Crypto firms have, therefore, been testing the waters in other countries where guidance has been offered.</p>
<p>When Prime Minister Sunak was still Chancellor of the Exchequer, he made it clear that he would guide the UK into becoming a safe space for digital assets where innovation and industry development are encouraged. While the UK has been lagging in regulatory guidance compared to the European Union, it has recently published several planned regulations.</p>
<p>The UK Treasury Committee released a report in May advising the government to regulate retail crypto trading not as financial assets but as gambling instruments. The Committee said that unbacked mainstream crypto assets and their inherent volatility pose a risk to investors and threaten economic stability.</p>
<p>Last week, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) released a set of crypto marketing rules that take effect on October 8.</p>
<p>Under its stricter marketing guidelines, the agency banned incentive bonuses, free NFTs and airdrops for promotional purposes and introduced a &ldquo;cooling-off&rdquo; period for first-time crypto buyers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Silicon Valley-based venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz will open its first international office in London. The firm cites the UK&rsquo;s welcoming crypto climate. </p>
<p>The crypto investment arm of venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, a16z, announced it would be opening its first overseas office in London. The firm celebrated the UK&rsquo;s welcoming embrace of the crypto industry as the motivating factor behind its decision.</p>
<p>Under the leadership of Prime Minister Rishi Sunak, the UK has established a warm climate for crypto companies as the industry battles regulatory confusion from the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Big news to share: @a16z is expanding to the UK 🇬🇧We plan to open our first international office in London later this year, and will host the next Crypto Startup School there in 2024.Why the UK? 👇https://t.co/PQ7GuNEn77</p>
&mdash; cdixon.eth (@cdixon) June 11, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports the new office will open later this year and will be led by Sriram Krishnan, one of the firm&rsquo;s general partners. &nbsp;</p>
<p>a16z said in a statement:</p>

<p>While there is still work to be done, we believe that the UK is on the right path to becoming a leader in crypto regulation. The UK also has deep pools of talent, world-leading academic institutions, and a strong entrepreneurial culture.</p>
<p>It is home to more &ldquo;unicorns&rdquo; than Germany, France, and Sweden combined; to some of the world&rsquo;s largest financial markets and pools of capital; and to highly-sophisticated, world-class regulators. All of these make the UK strongly positioned to lead in web3.</p>

<p>Prime Minister Sunak welcomed the firm&rsquo;s decision and underscored the UK&rsquo;s commitment to establishing the country as the &ldquo;world&rsquo;s Web3 centre.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Great news that @a16z &ndash; one of the world&rsquo;s leading tech investment firms, is opening a new base here in London.Another huge vote of confidence in the UK as a place to build and grow tech businesses of the future. https://t.co/Ey1ykALkSU pic.twitter.com/caP6nNXfow</p>
&mdash; Rishi Sunak (@RishiSunak) June 12, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The Prime Minister said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;As we cement the UK&rsquo;s place as a science and tech superpower, we must embrace new innovations like Web3, powered by blockchain technology, which will enable start-ups to flourish here and grow the economy.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Crypto Firms Are Being Driven Offshore
<p>The US SEC recently launched severe regulatory action against two of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges. On June 5, the agency filed suit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, for alleged securities violations. The following day, the agency filed a similar case against Coinbase. It charged the exchange with &ldquo;the unregistered offer and sale of securities in connection with its staking-as-a-service program.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The US&rsquo;s aggressive approach led the market to spiral, with major altcoins seeing double-digit losses.</p>
UK&rsquo;s Regulatory Approach
<p>Recognising the need for regulatory guidance, crypto firms such as Coinbase have long asked the US to provide clarity regarding crypto assets. The US has, however, been reluctant to comply, which only creates further tension in the industry.</p>
<p>Crypto firms have, therefore, been testing the waters in other countries where guidance has been offered.</p>
<p>When Prime Minister Sunak was still Chancellor of the Exchequer, he made it clear that he would guide the UK into becoming a safe space for digital assets where innovation and industry development are encouraged. While the UK has been lagging in regulatory guidance compared to the European Union, it has recently published several planned regulations.</p>
<p>The UK Treasury Committee released a report in May advising the government to regulate retail crypto trading not as financial assets but as gambling instruments. The Committee said that unbacked mainstream crypto assets and their inherent volatility pose a risk to investors and threaten economic stability.</p>
<p>Last week, the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) released a set of crypto marketing rules that take effect on October 8.</p>
<p>Under its stricter marketing guidelines, the agency banned incentive bonuses, free NFTs and airdrops for promotional purposes and introduced a &ldquo;cooling-off&rdquo; period for first-time crypto buyers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Surges to 50%, Crypto Daily TV 12/6/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-dominance-surges-to-50-crypto-daily-tv-12-6-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/video-12.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/video-12.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/video-12.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:51:54 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-dominance-surges-to-50-crypto-daily-tv-12-6-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Today&rsquo;s Headlines TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>SEC lawsuits spur huge deposits from main exchanges</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuits against Binance, Binance.US and Coinbase have spurred the exodus of some $4 billion of deposits from the crypto exchange giants, according to blockchain data.</p>
<p>Crypto.com Arena will retain its name despite corporate shuffling</p>
<p>Crypto.com is shutting down a portion of its business, but its name will remain on the downtown Los Angeles arena that is home to the Lakers, Clippers, Kings and Sparks. Crypto.com said it is closing its institutional exchange in the US.</p>
<p>Bitcoin dominance surges to 50%</p>
<p>Bitcoin's dominance rate or share in the total crypto market capitalization rose during the weekend, nearing the 50% mark for the first time since April 2021. The uptick came as many altcoins suffered double-digit losses.</p>
BTC/USD exploded 1.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 24876.6667, and Resistance is at 27052.6667.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded by 1.1% in the last session.&nbsp;
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.1% in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1646.591, and Resistance is at 1896.611.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 3.5% in the last session.&nbsp;
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.5% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4437, and Resistance is at 0.5702.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded by 1.5% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.5% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 65.9833, and Resistance is at 94.9233.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>The US Consumer Price Index will be released at 12:30 GMT, the US Consumer Price Index Core at 12:30 GMT, the Eurozone's ZEW Survey &ndash; Economic Sentiment at 09:00 GMT.</p>
<p>US Consumer Price Index Core</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy.</p>
<p>EMU ZEW Survey &ndash; Economic Sentiment</p>
<p>The ZEW Survey - Economic Sentiment measures institutional investor sentiment, reflecting the difference between the share of investors that are optimistic and pessimistic.</p>
<p>DE ZEW Survey &ndash; Current Situation</p>
<p>The ZEW Survey - Current Situation measures the current institutional investor sentiment, reflecting the difference between the share of investors that are optimistic and pessimistic.</p>
<p>Germany's ZEW Survey &ndash; Current Situation will be released at 09:00 GMT, the UK's Claimant Count Change at 06:00 GMT, and the UK's ILO Unemployment Rate at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Claimant Count Change</p>
<p>The Claimant Count Change presents the change in the number of unemployed people in the UK.</p>
<p>UK ILO Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The ILO Unemployment Rate is the number of unemployed workers divided by the total civilian labour force.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Today&rsquo;s Headlines TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>SEC lawsuits spur huge deposits from main exchanges</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission lawsuits against Binance, Binance.US and Coinbase have spurred the exodus of some $4 billion of deposits from the crypto exchange giants, according to blockchain data.</p>
<p>Crypto.com Arena will retain its name despite corporate shuffling</p>
<p>Crypto.com is shutting down a portion of its business, but its name will remain on the downtown Los Angeles arena that is home to the Lakers, Clippers, Kings and Sparks. Crypto.com said it is closing its institutional exchange in the US.</p>
<p>Bitcoin dominance surges to 50%</p>
<p>Bitcoin's dominance rate or share in the total crypto market capitalization rose during the weekend, nearing the 50% mark for the first time since April 2021. The uptick came as many altcoins suffered double-digit losses.</p>
BTC/USD exploded 1.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 24876.6667, and Resistance is at 27052.6667.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded by 1.1% in the last session.&nbsp;
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.1% in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1646.591, and Resistance is at 1896.611.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 3.5% in the last session.&nbsp;
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair exploded 3.5% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4437, and Resistance is at 0.5702.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded by 1.5% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.5% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis. Support is at 65.9833, and Resistance is at 94.9233.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>The US Consumer Price Index will be released at 12:30 GMT, the US Consumer Price Index Core at 12:30 GMT, the Eurozone's ZEW Survey &ndash; Economic Sentiment at 09:00 GMT.</p>
<p>US Consumer Price Index Core</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy.</p>
<p>EMU ZEW Survey &ndash; Economic Sentiment</p>
<p>The ZEW Survey - Economic Sentiment measures institutional investor sentiment, reflecting the difference between the share of investors that are optimistic and pessimistic.</p>
<p>DE ZEW Survey &ndash; Current Situation</p>
<p>The ZEW Survey - Current Situation measures the current institutional investor sentiment, reflecting the difference between the share of investors that are optimistic and pessimistic.</p>
<p>Germany's ZEW Survey &ndash; Current Situation will be released at 09:00 GMT, the UK's Claimant Count Change at 06:00 GMT, and the UK's ILO Unemployment Rate at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Claimant Count Change</p>
<p>The Claimant Count Change presents the change in the number of unemployed people in the UK.</p>
<p>UK ILO Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The ILO Unemployment Rate is the number of unemployed workers divided by the total civilian labour force.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Veteran Howard Yuan Joins LBank Labs as Venture Partner]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-veteran-howard-yuan-joins-lbank-labs-as-venture-partner</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230609__PR_article_cover_images-01_1686555719X8BCKiDSKy.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230609__PR_article_cover_images-01_1686555719X8BCKiDSKy.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230609__PR_article_cover_images-01_1686555719X8BCKiDSKy.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 09:05:29 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-veteran-howard-yuan-joins-lbank-labs-as-venture-partner</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, the leading venture fund of global crypto exchange LBank, is thrilled to announce the addition of Howard Yuan to its team. Yuan brings a wealth of experience and expertise in the crypto industry, making him a valuable asset to the organization.</p><p>With a background as a crypto OG and extensive experience as a venture capitalist, Yuan has played a pivotal role in the success of numerous projects throughout his career. Prior to joining LBank Labs, Yuan served as the managing partner for Fundamental Labs, and also held significant management positions at prestigious companies such as IBM and E&amp;Y. Yuan&rsquo;s long-term optimistic outlook on the crypto industry has consistently guided his decision-making and investments.&nbsp;</p><p>During his tenure at Fundamental Labs, Howard Yuan made strategic investments in prominent projects such as Coinbase (Coin), Binance (BNB), Polkadot (DOT), Avalanche (AVAX), Conflux (CFX), Stacks (STX), Certik (CTK), NEAR, Mask, and RSS3.</p><p>In Yuan's new role as Venture Partner at LBank Labs, Yuan will leverage his extensive experience and expertise to propel the fund to new heights. Yuan aims to position LBank Labs as the leading global VC fund for blockchain and decentralized finance, facilitating the growth of innovative startups and contributing to the development of a prosperous Web3 future.</p>While acknowledging the inherent volatility of crypto markets, Yuan is confident in the underlying order and innovation within the industry. &ldquo;I will work closely with the LBank Labs team to identify and support the most talented entrepreneurs, overcoming challenges and building a thriving ecosystem,&rdquo; Yuan said. When asked about the most remarkable trends he has witnessed in the industry, he highlighted the exciting mass adoption, maturing infrastructure, and emergence of new protocols. &ldquo;Despite the current bearish sentiment in the crypto market, I believe that this is an opportune time to help early-stage Web3 startups navigate the bear cycle and achieve success,&rdquo; he explained.<p>LBank Labs is delighted to welcome Howard Yuan to the team and is excited to harness his insights and knowledge. With Yuan's addition, LBank Labs reinforces its global commitment to nurturing and empowering the next generation of blockchain and cryptocurrency startups.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 12th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, the leading venture fund of global crypto exchange LBank, is thrilled to announce the addition of Howard Yuan to its team. Yuan brings a wealth of experience and expertise in the crypto industry, making him a valuable asset to the organization.</p><p>With a background as a crypto OG and extensive experience as a venture capitalist, Yuan has played a pivotal role in the success of numerous projects throughout his career. Prior to joining LBank Labs, Yuan served as the managing partner for Fundamental Labs, and also held significant management positions at prestigious companies such as IBM and E&amp;Y. Yuan&rsquo;s long-term optimistic outlook on the crypto industry has consistently guided his decision-making and investments.&nbsp;</p><p>During his tenure at Fundamental Labs, Howard Yuan made strategic investments in prominent projects such as Coinbase (Coin), Binance (BNB), Polkadot (DOT), Avalanche (AVAX), Conflux (CFX), Stacks (STX), Certik (CTK), NEAR, Mask, and RSS3.</p><p>In Yuan's new role as Venture Partner at LBank Labs, Yuan will leverage his extensive experience and expertise to propel the fund to new heights. Yuan aims to position LBank Labs as the leading global VC fund for blockchain and decentralized finance, facilitating the growth of innovative startups and contributing to the development of a prosperous Web3 future.</p>While acknowledging the inherent volatility of crypto markets, Yuan is confident in the underlying order and innovation within the industry. &ldquo;I will work closely with the LBank Labs team to identify and support the most talented entrepreneurs, overcoming challenges and building a thriving ecosystem,&rdquo; Yuan said. When asked about the most remarkable trends he has witnessed in the industry, he highlighted the exciting mass adoption, maturing infrastructure, and emergence of new protocols. &ldquo;Despite the current bearish sentiment in the crypto market, I believe that this is an opportune time to help early-stage Web3 startups navigate the bear cycle and achieve success,&rdquo; he explained.<p>LBank Labs is delighted to welcome Howard Yuan to the team and is excited to harness his insights and knowledge. With Yuan's addition, LBank Labs reinforces its global commitment to nurturing and empowering the next generation of blockchain and cryptocurrency startups.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Responds to SEC’s Claim of MATIC Being a Security]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-responds-to-secs-claim-of-matic-being-a-security</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:57:29 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-responds-to-secs-claim-of-matic-being-a-security</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Polygon Labs has responded to the SEC&rsquo;s claims that its native token MATIC is an unregistered security. </p>
<p>The US SEC last week labelled Polygon and other popular cryptocurrencies unregistered securities in a lawsuit filed against crypto exchange Binance.</p>
<p>The SEC named Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS) as unregistered securities.</p>
Robinhood Delists Solana, Cardano and Polygon
<p>Following the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits, trading app Robinhood announced it would end support for SOL, ADA, and MATIC on June 27.</p>
<p>Robinhood limited its delisting to SOL, ADA, and MATIC and said to users that no other coins would be affected and would remain safe on its platform.</p>
Polygon Responds to SEC Claims
<p>Polygon Labs responded to the SEC&rsquo;s allegations on Friday.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are proud of the history of the Polygon network &ndash; developed outside the US, deployed outside the US, and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network. MATIC was a necessary part of the Polygon technology from Day 1, ensuring that the network would be&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Polygon (Labs) (@0xPolygonLabs) June 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>They stated that the token was &ldquo;developed outside the U.S., deployed outside the U.S. and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network.&rdquo;</p>
<p>It further claimed:</p>

<p>MATIC was a necessary part of the Polygon technology from Day 1, ensuring that the network would be secure &mdash; and remains so to this day.</p>

<p>Polygon also noted that its actions did not target the US at any time:</p>

<p>Given our focus on network security, we made sure MATIC was available to a wide group of persons, but only with actions that did not target the US at any time.</p>

Market Takes a Dive
<p>In the days following the SEC&rsquo;s claims against Binance and rival exchange Coinbase, the overall crypto market appeared to hold firm.</p>
<p>However, Saturday was an absolute bloodbath, with ADA, SOL and MATIC seeing double-digit losses.</p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap reveals MATIC&rsquo;s price declined by 33% in the past week. At the time of writing, MATIC changed hands at $0.64.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polygon Labs has responded to the SEC&rsquo;s claims that its native token MATIC is an unregistered security. </p>
<p>The US SEC last week labelled Polygon and other popular cryptocurrencies unregistered securities in a lawsuit filed against crypto exchange Binance.</p>
<p>The SEC named Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS) as unregistered securities.</p>
Robinhood Delists Solana, Cardano and Polygon
<p>Following the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits, trading app Robinhood announced it would end support for SOL, ADA, and MATIC on June 27.</p>
<p>Robinhood limited its delisting to SOL, ADA, and MATIC and said to users that no other coins would be affected and would remain safe on its platform.</p>
Polygon Responds to SEC Claims
<p>Polygon Labs responded to the SEC&rsquo;s allegations on Friday.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are proud of the history of the Polygon network &ndash; developed outside the US, deployed outside the US, and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network. MATIC was a necessary part of the Polygon technology from Day 1, ensuring that the network would be&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Polygon (Labs) (@0xPolygonLabs) June 10, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>They stated that the token was &ldquo;developed outside the U.S., deployed outside the U.S. and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network.&rdquo;</p>
<p>It further claimed:</p>

<p>MATIC was a necessary part of the Polygon technology from Day 1, ensuring that the network would be secure &mdash; and remains so to this day.</p>

<p>Polygon also noted that its actions did not target the US at any time:</p>

<p>Given our focus on network security, we made sure MATIC was available to a wide group of persons, but only with actions that did not target the US at any time.</p>

Market Takes a Dive
<p>In the days following the SEC&rsquo;s claims against Binance and rival exchange Coinbase, the overall crypto market appeared to hold firm.</p>
<p>However, Saturday was an absolute bloodbath, with ADA, SOL and MATIC seeing double-digit losses.</p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap reveals MATIC&rsquo;s price declined by 33% in the past week. At the time of writing, MATIC changed hands at $0.64.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: SEC’s View On SOL, ADA, MATIC, And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-weekly-roundup-secs-view-on-sol-ada-matic-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:05:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-weekly-roundup-secs-view-on-sol-ada-matic-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In its latest salvo against crypto, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has called popular cryptocurrencies such as Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA) unregistered securities.</p>
Bitcoin
ZEBEDEE And Fiatjaf Launch Nostr Social Media Client
<p>ZEBEDEE and Nostr co-creator Fiatjaf have launched the ZBD app, touted as the most decentralized social media yet. The app is built on Bitcoin, allowing users to own their content and send microtransactions.</p>
Ethereum
Vitalik Buterin Unveils Roadmap For Ethereum&rsquo;s Future
<p>Ethereum co-founder, Vitalik Buterin, has unveiled a roadmap for Ethereum&rsquo;s future. The roadmap consists of three significant technical transitions, which according to Buterin, are crucial for ensuring the long-term success of Ethereum.</p>
Optimism Prepares For Bedrock Upgrade
<p>Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution Optimism unveiled its Bedrock upgrade on the 6th of June. The step is a significant stride in Optimism&rsquo;s vision of becoming a utility-oriented Superchain with lower gas fees and faster transaction finality.</p>
DeFi
Federal Judge Dismisses Lawsuit Against PoolTogether
<p>A federal judge has thrown out a lawsuit against decentralized finance (DeFi) startup PoolTogether. The judge stated that the federal court system was not the appropriate platform for concerns regarding the startup and its operations.</p>
Technology
Deutsche Telekom Joins Polygon As Validator Node
<p>Technology giant Deutsche Telekom has joined the Polygon blockchain as a validator node as it looks to establish itself as a critical infrastructure provider in the Web3 space.</p>
Russia&rsquo;s Rosbank Announces Launch Of Crypto Payments Solution
<p>Rosbank, one of Russia&rsquo;s most important banks, has announced the launch of a crypto payments solution. According to the bank, the payment solution will help facilitate cross-border settlements.</p>
Business
Changpeng Zhao Was Binance.US Shadow CEO, Alleges Brian Brooks
<p>Binance.US former CEO Brian Brooks has revealed that he left his position as CEO in court documents submitted earlier in the week. Brooks stated that after a point of time, it became clear that Zhao was the CEO of BAM Trading.</p>
Circle Obtains Major Payment Institution License
<p>Circle Internet Singapore Pte. Ltd. has revealed that it has received a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). This will allow Circle to offer users in Singapore digital payment services, cross-border money transfer services, and domestic money transfer services.</p>
Regulation
Australia&rsquo;s Commonwealth Bank Restricts Payments To Certain Exchanges
<p>Australia&rsquo;s Commonwealth Bank has announced the implementation of new processes designed to protect customers from possible scams associated with certain cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
Draft Bill Proposes Clear Roles For SEC And CFTC
<p>A draft bill introduced by Republican lawmakers Glen Thompson and Patrick McHenry aims to define clear roles for the Securities and Exchange Commission and the CFTC. It also charts out a clear regulatory plan to enable the trading of digital assets on conventional platforms.</p>
SEC Alleges SOL, ADA, and MATIC Are Unregistered Securities
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission has called Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA) unregistered securities in its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
Cboe Digital Receives Approval For Margin Trades On Crypto Futures Exchange
<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has given approval to an amended order of registration, clearing the path for Cboe Digital to clear additional products as a derivatives clearing organization.</p>
Will SEC Go After Tether Next?
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission has gone all guns blazing against crypto recently, targeting some of the most prominent exchanges in Binance and Coinbase. With the SEC looking for a new target, could Tether be in its crosshairs next?</p>
Coinbase CEO Unfazed By SEC Lawsuit
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has revealed that he is unfazed by the SEC lawsuit. Instead, Armstrong has stated that a court battle will help establish much-needed clarity around crypto.</p>
Billionaire Mark Cuban Launches Scathing Attack On SEC
<p>Billionaire Mark Cuban has heavily criticized the SEC for what he calls a clear lack of support for companies trying to comply with securities regulations in the country.</p>
Robinhood Reviewing Crypto Offerings Following SEC Crackdown
<p>Robinhood is reportedly reviewing crypto offerings on its platform as the SEC cracks down on major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase.</p>
UK FCA Announces New Crypto Marketing Rules
<p>The UK Financial Conduct Authority has announced a new set of crypto marketing rules, which are set to take effect from the 8th of October.</p>
Did Gary Gensler Want To Join Binance?
<p>Binance lawyers have alleged that current SEC Chair Gary Gensler discussed the possibility of an informal advisor for the crypto exchange in 2019.</p>
UK Announces Ban On Airdrops And Free Promotional NFTs
<p>The Financial Conduct Authority has announced the prohibition of free promotional NFTs and crypto airdrops in a new set of stricter marketing rules announced earlier in the week.</p>
NFTs
Louis Vuitton Debuts New NFT Collection
<p>Luxury fashion house Louis Vuitton has announced the launch of a new NFT collection called Treasure Trunks, exclusively for its top customers.</p>
Web3
Ankr Launches Enterprise RPC Services On Azure
<p>Web3 developer hub Ankr has announced the official launch of Enterprise Remote Procedure Call on Microsoft&rsquo;s Azure Marketplace.</p>
Security
Elliptic To Integrate ChatGPT
<p>Crypto risk management firm Elliptic has revealed that it would be integrating ChatGPT for its risk management and intelligence-gathering operations.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In its latest salvo against crypto, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has called popular cryptocurrencies such as Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA) unregistered securities.</p>
Bitcoin
ZEBEDEE And Fiatjaf Launch Nostr Social Media Client
<p>ZEBEDEE and Nostr co-creator Fiatjaf have launched the ZBD app, touted as the most decentralized social media yet. The app is built on Bitcoin, allowing users to own their content and send microtransactions.</p>
Ethereum
Vitalik Buterin Unveils Roadmap For Ethereum&rsquo;s Future
<p>Ethereum co-founder, Vitalik Buterin, has unveiled a roadmap for Ethereum&rsquo;s future. The roadmap consists of three significant technical transitions, which according to Buterin, are crucial for ensuring the long-term success of Ethereum.</p>
Optimism Prepares For Bedrock Upgrade
<p>Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution Optimism unveiled its Bedrock upgrade on the 6th of June. The step is a significant stride in Optimism&rsquo;s vision of becoming a utility-oriented Superchain with lower gas fees and faster transaction finality.</p>
DeFi
Federal Judge Dismisses Lawsuit Against PoolTogether
<p>A federal judge has thrown out a lawsuit against decentralized finance (DeFi) startup PoolTogether. The judge stated that the federal court system was not the appropriate platform for concerns regarding the startup and its operations.</p>
Technology
Deutsche Telekom Joins Polygon As Validator Node
<p>Technology giant Deutsche Telekom has joined the Polygon blockchain as a validator node as it looks to establish itself as a critical infrastructure provider in the Web3 space.</p>
Russia&rsquo;s Rosbank Announces Launch Of Crypto Payments Solution
<p>Rosbank, one of Russia&rsquo;s most important banks, has announced the launch of a crypto payments solution. According to the bank, the payment solution will help facilitate cross-border settlements.</p>
Business
Changpeng Zhao Was Binance.US Shadow CEO, Alleges Brian Brooks
<p>Binance.US former CEO Brian Brooks has revealed that he left his position as CEO in court documents submitted earlier in the week. Brooks stated that after a point of time, it became clear that Zhao was the CEO of BAM Trading.</p>
Circle Obtains Major Payment Institution License
<p>Circle Internet Singapore Pte. Ltd. has revealed that it has received a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). This will allow Circle to offer users in Singapore digital payment services, cross-border money transfer services, and domestic money transfer services.</p>
Regulation
Australia&rsquo;s Commonwealth Bank Restricts Payments To Certain Exchanges
<p>Australia&rsquo;s Commonwealth Bank has announced the implementation of new processes designed to protect customers from possible scams associated with certain cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>
Draft Bill Proposes Clear Roles For SEC And CFTC
<p>A draft bill introduced by Republican lawmakers Glen Thompson and Patrick McHenry aims to define clear roles for the Securities and Exchange Commission and the CFTC. It also charts out a clear regulatory plan to enable the trading of digital assets on conventional platforms.</p>
SEC Alleges SOL, ADA, and MATIC Are Unregistered Securities
<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission has called Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and Cardano (ADA) unregistered securities in its lawsuit against Binance.</p>
Cboe Digital Receives Approval For Margin Trades On Crypto Futures Exchange
<p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has given approval to an amended order of registration, clearing the path for Cboe Digital to clear additional products as a derivatives clearing organization.</p>
Will SEC Go After Tether Next?
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission has gone all guns blazing against crypto recently, targeting some of the most prominent exchanges in Binance and Coinbase. With the SEC looking for a new target, could Tether be in its crosshairs next?</p>
Coinbase CEO Unfazed By SEC Lawsuit
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has revealed that he is unfazed by the SEC lawsuit. Instead, Armstrong has stated that a court battle will help establish much-needed clarity around crypto.</p>
Billionaire Mark Cuban Launches Scathing Attack On SEC
<p>Billionaire Mark Cuban has heavily criticized the SEC for what he calls a clear lack of support for companies trying to comply with securities regulations in the country.</p>
Robinhood Reviewing Crypto Offerings Following SEC Crackdown
<p>Robinhood is reportedly reviewing crypto offerings on its platform as the SEC cracks down on major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase.</p>
UK FCA Announces New Crypto Marketing Rules
<p>The UK Financial Conduct Authority has announced a new set of crypto marketing rules, which are set to take effect from the 8th of October.</p>
Did Gary Gensler Want To Join Binance?
<p>Binance lawyers have alleged that current SEC Chair Gary Gensler discussed the possibility of an informal advisor for the crypto exchange in 2019.</p>
UK Announces Ban On Airdrops And Free Promotional NFTs
<p>The Financial Conduct Authority has announced the prohibition of free promotional NFTs and crypto airdrops in a new set of stricter marketing rules announced earlier in the week.</p>
NFTs
Louis Vuitton Debuts New NFT Collection
<p>Luxury fashion house Louis Vuitton has announced the launch of a new NFT collection called Treasure Trunks, exclusively for its top customers.</p>
Web3
Ankr Launches Enterprise RPC Services On Azure
<p>Web3 developer hub Ankr has announced the official launch of Enterprise Remote Procedure Call on Microsoft&rsquo;s Azure Marketplace.</p>
Security
Elliptic To Integrate ChatGPT
<p>Crypto risk management firm Elliptic has revealed that it would be integrating ChatGPT for its risk management and intelligence-gathering operations.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Seeking More Pain - 12 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-seeking-more-pain-12-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-seeking-more-pain-12-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Eyeing More Pain:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 12 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained at elevated risk for more downside pain early in the Asian session as the pair remained highly volatile following recent prints below the 26000 figure.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid depreciation, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that recently intensified around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and below the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26623.11 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26327.29.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Eyeing More Pain:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 12 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained at elevated risk for more downside pain early in the Asian session as the pair remained highly volatile following recent prints below the 26000 figure.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid depreciation, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that recently intensified around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and below the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26623.11 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26327.29.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gensler Tries His Best but Fails to Kill the Crypto Industry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/gensler-tries-his-best-but-fails-to-kill-the-crypto-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:08:37 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/gensler-tries-his-best-but-fails-to-kill-the-crypto-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The regulatory action against the two biggest crypto exchanges has made it clear: the SEC, led by Chairman Gary Gensler, wants to end the crypto industry. The agency&rsquo;s scare tactics may succeed in the US, but it struggles with the overall market. </p>
<p>The US SEC made its position against crypto known this week when it launched severe regulatory action against Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange, and Coinbase, the largest crypto exchange by trade volume in the US. Leading the agency in its crusade is Gary Gensler, a man who has made his views of the industry no secret.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against the exchanges, the market was expected to react severely, and the prices would plunge. However, Bitcoin and the broader market held steady throughout the week.</p>
<p>However, Gensler&rsquo;s SEC made allegations in its suit against Binance, which labelled several popular cryptocurrencies unregistered securities. The SEC listed Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS).</p>
<p>The agency&rsquo;s naming of these tokens as securities did, however, cause panic in the market and spurred trading platform Robinhood to delist MATIC, SOL, and ADA from its platform come June 27.</p>
Alt-Market Reacts to Robinhood Delisting
<p>Although the market did not react as much as expected during the week, it did see a dramatic plunge on Saturday.</p>
<p>Undoubtedly fuelled by Robinhood&rsquo;s delisting announcement, the crypto alt market saw significant declines. ADA was trading down by as much as 25%, while SOL and MATIC also saw double-digit losses. Amid the dire market conditions, Singapore-based crypto exchange Crypto.com announced it would suspend its institutional exchange service for US customers.</p>
<p>Compared to the broader market, Bitcoin was only trading down only 5% to its lowest level since March and was trading hands at around $25,000.</p>
<p>The market appeared to recover ever so slightly by Sunday morning, but the &ldquo;bloodbath&rdquo; continues.</p>
Did Gary Gensler Offer His Services to Binance?
<p>A surprising report emerged this week amid the chaos when CNBC revealed that Gensler had a series of conversations with Binance officials and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. Binance lawyers allege that Gensler offered his services as an advisor to the exchange in 2019.</p>
<p>Although merely reports at the moment, the allegations undoubtedly damage Gensler and call into question his intentions as Chairman of the securities regulator.</p>
The Crypto Industry Will Prevail
<p>The SEC and all its might may continue to slap the industry with a barrage of claims, but it seems unlikely that it will manage to bring the industry down. The agency is certainly doing substantial damage to the US crypto industry, but the crypto market at large will not be taken down.</p>
<p>In light of the recent events in the crypto industry &ndash; recall the spectacular failures of FTX, we cannot live under the illusion that the industry can go on unregulated.</p>
<p>However, the US&rsquo;s approach to this is simply wrong and unproductive and achieves little bar driving crypto off US shores and into the hands of territories which welcome it with open arms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The regulatory action against the two biggest crypto exchanges has made it clear: the SEC, led by Chairman Gary Gensler, wants to end the crypto industry. The agency&rsquo;s scare tactics may succeed in the US, but it struggles with the overall market. </p>
<p>The US SEC made its position against crypto known this week when it launched severe regulatory action against Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange, and Coinbase, the largest crypto exchange by trade volume in the US. Leading the agency in its crusade is Gary Gensler, a man who has made his views of the industry no secret.</p>
<p>Following the SEC&rsquo;s lawsuits against the exchanges, the market was expected to react severely, and the prices would plunge. However, Bitcoin and the broader market held steady throughout the week.</p>
<p>However, Gensler&rsquo;s SEC made allegations in its suit against Binance, which labelled several popular cryptocurrencies unregistered securities. The SEC listed Polygon (MATIC), Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS).</p>
<p>The agency&rsquo;s naming of these tokens as securities did, however, cause panic in the market and spurred trading platform Robinhood to delist MATIC, SOL, and ADA from its platform come June 27.</p>
Alt-Market Reacts to Robinhood Delisting
<p>Although the market did not react as much as expected during the week, it did see a dramatic plunge on Saturday.</p>
<p>Undoubtedly fuelled by Robinhood&rsquo;s delisting announcement, the crypto alt market saw significant declines. ADA was trading down by as much as 25%, while SOL and MATIC also saw double-digit losses. Amid the dire market conditions, Singapore-based crypto exchange Crypto.com announced it would suspend its institutional exchange service for US customers.</p>
<p>Compared to the broader market, Bitcoin was only trading down only 5% to its lowest level since March and was trading hands at around $25,000.</p>
<p>The market appeared to recover ever so slightly by Sunday morning, but the &ldquo;bloodbath&rdquo; continues.</p>
Did Gary Gensler Offer His Services to Binance?
<p>A surprising report emerged this week amid the chaos when CNBC revealed that Gensler had a series of conversations with Binance officials and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. Binance lawyers allege that Gensler offered his services as an advisor to the exchange in 2019.</p>
<p>Although merely reports at the moment, the allegations undoubtedly damage Gensler and call into question his intentions as Chairman of the securities regulator.</p>
The Crypto Industry Will Prevail
<p>The SEC and all its might may continue to slap the industry with a barrage of claims, but it seems unlikely that it will manage to bring the industry down. The agency is certainly doing substantial damage to the US crypto industry, but the crypto market at large will not be taken down.</p>
<p>In light of the recent events in the crypto industry &ndash; recall the spectacular failures of FTX, we cannot live under the illusion that the industry can go on unregulated.</p>
<p>However, the US&rsquo;s approach to this is simply wrong and unproductive and achieves little bar driving crypto off US shores and into the hands of territories which welcome it with open arms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Sharply Lower to 25474 - 11 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-sharply-lower-to-25474-11-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-10-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-sharply-lower-to-25474-11-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Races Lower to 25474:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 11 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent depreciation early in the Asian session as the pair was pressured back below the 26000 figure, trading as low as the 25474.89 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid descent, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that emerged around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and below the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26617.83 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26315.77.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Races Lower to 25474:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 11 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent depreciation early in the Asian session as the pair was pressured back below the 26000 figure, trading as low as the 25474.89 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 26041.83 and 25720.64 areas during the rapid descent, downside price objectives related to technical selling pressure that emerged around the 27402.79 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Related downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; The ongoing move lower also included a test of the 25309.26 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and below the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26617.83 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26315.77.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto.com Shutters Its US Institutional Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cryptocom-shutters-its-us-institutional-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptocom-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptocom-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptocom-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 11:09:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cryptocom-shutters-its-us-institutional-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto.com announced that it would shut down its institutional exchange services customers in the United States in less than two weeks. </p>
<p>On Friday, Singapore-based crypto exchange Crypto.com announced that it would suspend its institutional exchange service for US customers. In a statement provided to media publication Blockworks, the exchange explained that demand is drying up due to the current market conditions in the US.</p>
<p>Although it did not specifically reference the lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, it was undoubtedly the overriding factor in the exchange&rsquo;s decision.</p>
<p>In a statement, Crypto.com said:</p>

<p>We recently made a business decision to suspend the institutional offering of the Crypto.com Exchange in the U.S. as of 11:59 pm EDT June 21, 2023, due to &ldquo;limited demand&rdquo; from institutions in the U.S. in the &ldquo;current market landscape.&rdquo; Impacted institutional users were given advance notice to support a smooth transition.</p>

<p>The exchange explained that the closure of the US services would not affect its retail trading app, including its crypto derivative product, UpDown Options, regulated by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The company further said it could reopen the platform in the future but did not provide more details.</p>
Crypto.com Receives Major Payment Institution Licence in Singapore
<p>The exchange started the month out well after receiving a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).</p>
<p>Securing this license means the exchange can offer DPT services to Singaporean customers.</p>
Crypto.com Arena Not Affected
<p>After the exchange announced shuttering its institutional services for US customers, speculation arose that it might affect the naming rights for Crypto.com Arena. The exchange entered into a naming rights agreement with AEG, the owner and operator of the arena formerly known as the Staples Center, in 2021, Forbes reports.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto.com announced that it would shut down its institutional exchange services customers in the United States in less than two weeks. </p>
<p>On Friday, Singapore-based crypto exchange Crypto.com announced that it would suspend its institutional exchange service for US customers. In a statement provided to media publication Blockworks, the exchange explained that demand is drying up due to the current market conditions in the US.</p>
<p>Although it did not specifically reference the lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, it was undoubtedly the overriding factor in the exchange&rsquo;s decision.</p>
<p>In a statement, Crypto.com said:</p>

<p>We recently made a business decision to suspend the institutional offering of the Crypto.com Exchange in the U.S. as of 11:59 pm EDT June 21, 2023, due to &ldquo;limited demand&rdquo; from institutions in the U.S. in the &ldquo;current market landscape.&rdquo; Impacted institutional users were given advance notice to support a smooth transition.</p>

<p>The exchange explained that the closure of the US services would not affect its retail trading app, including its crypto derivative product, UpDown Options, regulated by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). The company further said it could reopen the platform in the future but did not provide more details.</p>
Crypto.com Receives Major Payment Institution Licence in Singapore
<p>The exchange started the month out well after receiving a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).</p>
<p>Securing this license means the exchange can offer DPT services to Singaporean customers.</p>
Crypto.com Arena Not Affected
<p>After the exchange announced shuttering its institutional services for US customers, speculation arose that it might affect the naming rights for Crypto.com Arena. The exchange entered into a naming rights agreement with AEG, the owner and operator of the arena formerly known as the Staples Center, in 2021, Forbes reports.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Elon’s Dogecoin (DOGE) Losses Holders to Uwerx (WERX) – Here’s Why]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/elons-dogecoin-doge-losses-holders-to-uwerx-werx-heres-why</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-09-at-192906.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-09-at-192906.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-09-at-192906.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/elons-dogecoin-doge-losses-holders-to-uwerx-werx-heres-why</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk, the CEO of Twitter and Dogecoin (DOGE), is complicit in the rise to fame of the first meme coin cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Despite the crypto markets being hit by a renewed wave of meme coin speculation in recent weeks, more investors are dumping their Dogecoin (DOGE) bags to participate in other tokens like Uwerx, which have better use cases.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out why investors are taking this ruthless path to participate in the promising presale of Uwerx and recover their lost meme coin-laden portfolio.</p>
Dogecoin (Dogecoin): A Crypto Once Loved By All
<p>Initially developed as a joke by two software engineers, Dogecoin (DOGE) is the first ever meme coin created in 2013. </p>
<p>Elon Musk, nicknamed the Doge Father, has been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin (DOGE) and continues to tweet about the meme coin until many investors caught onto the revelation, sending the token&rsquo;s price jumping on many occasions.</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) cryptocurrency is currently the ninth largest cryptocurrency in the world, having a market capitalization of over $10 billion but has fallen off the good graces of the entire crypto community. Currently having a trading volume of $169.945, 370, and trading at $0.0734, less than 90% of his all-time high price of $0.7316. </p>
<p>In the recent wake of meme coin trading, even degen traders have shifted their attention off</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) to focus more on new meme coins like Pepe (PEPE) and Floki Inu(FLOKI), which are currently making all the waves in the meme coin world. Because of this, experts predict the price of Dogecoin (DOGE) to reach a bare minimum of $0.095 in the last quarter of 2023.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): A Token Set To Ride The Wave And Establish Itself As The New Market Leader
<p>Uwerx has been in every investor&rsquo;s mouth for completing their stage 1 and stage 2 presale in a record time of 17 days and 8 days, respectively.</p>
<p>Uwerx platform is treading the least but most rewarding path of utility by offering freelancers a chance to enjoy the web3 community-first ambiance. With 5,000 registered users on the platform, they plan to expand and transform the trillion-dollar freelance economy with their hard-to-beat offerings to freelancers and clients. </p>
<p>They are doing this by offering a wide range of benefits, like flagging a service fee of 1%, which is small compared to the 15% charged by popular freelance platforms like Upwork and Fiverr. Uwerkwill also provide more security and decentralization to the freelancers by allowing them to transact without needing a third party.</p>
<p>Not only is Uwerx focused on creating the best freelance platform there is, but they also plan on rewarding early adopters with a test airdrop of the WERX token after the end of its presale rounds on the 31st of July. After three successful presales, the WERX token sells for $0.041 per token in its stage 5 presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx contract has been certified by top auditing firms like SolidProof and InterFi Network, and its WERX token is currently listed on CoinSniper with pending listings on other platforms like Uniswap, CoinGecko, and CoinMarketCap.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Is Set To Break Into the Bull Market In Style
<p>Liquidity locking for a set period, renouncing contract ownership, reducing taxes to zero, and incentivizing holders are all markers for cryptos that plan on staying for the long term. These qualities will inevitably benefit Uwerx from the hyper-liquidity that will be deployed during the bull market.</p>
<p>Strategic positioning is one of the ways to make the most out of any crypto, starting at the presale phase. You can check out the Uwerx project and join in on the presale before the price goes parabolic with these links:</p>
<p>Join the Uwerx presale today and take advantage of the 15% presale bonus:</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s12">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elon Musk, the CEO of Twitter and Dogecoin (DOGE), is complicit in the rise to fame of the first meme coin cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Despite the crypto markets being hit by a renewed wave of meme coin speculation in recent weeks, more investors are dumping their Dogecoin (DOGE) bags to participate in other tokens like Uwerx, which have better use cases.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out why investors are taking this ruthless path to participate in the promising presale of Uwerx and recover their lost meme coin-laden portfolio.</p>
Dogecoin (Dogecoin): A Crypto Once Loved By All
<p>Initially developed as a joke by two software engineers, Dogecoin (DOGE) is the first ever meme coin created in 2013. </p>
<p>Elon Musk, nicknamed the Doge Father, has been a vocal supporter of Dogecoin (DOGE) and continues to tweet about the meme coin until many investors caught onto the revelation, sending the token&rsquo;s price jumping on many occasions.</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) cryptocurrency is currently the ninth largest cryptocurrency in the world, having a market capitalization of over $10 billion but has fallen off the good graces of the entire crypto community. Currently having a trading volume of $169.945, 370, and trading at $0.0734, less than 90% of his all-time high price of $0.7316. </p>
<p>In the recent wake of meme coin trading, even degen traders have shifted their attention off</p>
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) to focus more on new meme coins like Pepe (PEPE) and Floki Inu(FLOKI), which are currently making all the waves in the meme coin world. Because of this, experts predict the price of Dogecoin (DOGE) to reach a bare minimum of $0.095 in the last quarter of 2023.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): A Token Set To Ride The Wave And Establish Itself As The New Market Leader
<p>Uwerx has been in every investor&rsquo;s mouth for completing their stage 1 and stage 2 presale in a record time of 17 days and 8 days, respectively.</p>
<p>Uwerx platform is treading the least but most rewarding path of utility by offering freelancers a chance to enjoy the web3 community-first ambiance. With 5,000 registered users on the platform, they plan to expand and transform the trillion-dollar freelance economy with their hard-to-beat offerings to freelancers and clients. </p>
<p>They are doing this by offering a wide range of benefits, like flagging a service fee of 1%, which is small compared to the 15% charged by popular freelance platforms like Upwork and Fiverr. Uwerkwill also provide more security and decentralization to the freelancers by allowing them to transact without needing a third party.</p>
<p>Not only is Uwerx focused on creating the best freelance platform there is, but they also plan on rewarding early adopters with a test airdrop of the WERX token after the end of its presale rounds on the 31st of July. After three successful presales, the WERX token sells for $0.041 per token in its stage 5 presale.</p>
<p>Uwerx contract has been certified by top auditing firms like SolidProof and InterFi Network, and its WERX token is currently listed on CoinSniper with pending listings on other platforms like Uniswap, CoinGecko, and CoinMarketCap.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Is Set To Break Into the Bull Market In Style
<p>Liquidity locking for a set period, renouncing contract ownership, reducing taxes to zero, and incentivizing holders are all markers for cryptos that plan on staying for the long term. These qualities will inevitably benefit Uwerx from the hyper-liquidity that will be deployed during the bull market.</p>
<p>Strategic positioning is one of the ways to make the most out of any crypto, starting at the presale phase. You can check out the Uwerx project and join in on the presale before the price goes parabolic with these links:</p>
<p>Join the Uwerx presale today and take advantage of the 15% presale bonus:</p>
<p class="s12">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p class="s12">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Explore the Enigmatic Galaxy: Embark on an Immersive Journey in the IC1101 Metaverse]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/explore-the-enigmatic-galaxy-embark-on-an-immersive-journey-in-the-ic1101-metaverse</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-633.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-633.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-633.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/explore-the-enigmatic-galaxy-embark-on-an-immersive-journey-in-the-ic1101-metaverse</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>IC1101 is committed to providing a more immersive, fun, and autonomous experience than the current metaverse. IC1101, named after its astronomical designation, shines with infinite, mysterious light in the vast universe. As one of the largest known galaxies in the universe, IC1101 represents a huge, mysterious, and spectacular existence. It undoubtedly contains endless wonders and unknowns waiting for human exploration.</p>
<p>IC1101 is a mysterious galaxy, a new metaverse project name, and a super immersive multi-dimensional universe platform dedicated to providing a more immersive, fun, and autonomous experience than the current metaverse. Participants will be able to explore the mysterious qualities of IC1101 and discover endless possibilities within it.</p>
<p>Current metaverse projects often have limitations in terms of graphics, immersion, and participant decision-making power. IC1101 aims to solve these limitations and take the realism, participation, and activity of the metaverse world to a new level.</p>
<p>So, can it stand out in fierce competition and become a dark horse? Let us embark on the journey of IC1101 together, explore this mysterious galaxy, and find the answers.</p>
When Adventure Meets Creativity
<p>In the world of the metaverse, a fascinating worldview is particularly important: it not only determines the style of the project and the immersion of the players, but also opens up more imagination space for storytelling. As a galaxy full of wonders and fantasies, IC1101 has a unique and captivating worldview, bringing unprecedented experiences to participants.</p>
<p>The worldview of IC1101 is based on diversity and freedom. Eight major races converge in this galaxy, each with unique appearances and abilities. From appearance to cultural customs, from ideological concepts to social structures, the differences between races in IC1101 are rich and inclusive. In this galaxy, players will be able to explore the blending and mutual influence of diverse cultures, and feel the interaction and cooperation between different races.</p>
<p>IC1101 also provides players with great freedom and creativity. Players can choose their own role identity, create unique appearance and personality traits, and participate in various exciting activities and scenarios, such as driving spaceships to explore unknown planets in the galaxy, discovering hidden cosmic secrets; They can also join teams, collaborate to solve complex puzzles and tasks, and experience the fruits of cooperation and unity. At the same time, players can also trade in the economic market of IC1101, buying and selling various precious resources and items, and developing their own wealth and power.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Overall, IC1101 combines elements of science fiction, fantasy, and mystery. Players will find themselves in a colorful and mysterious interstellar world, where every exploration and adventure brings new surprises and challenges. But how will this worldview be realized through technology?</p>
Multi-platform support attracts different user groups.
<p>Overall, IC1101 is an immersive metaverse platform based on a multi-chain architecture that allows users from different public chains to easily connect. Through the introduction of token economics and NFTs, users can have their own digital assets and ownership, and can engage in social and game cooperation to complete tasks, satisfy their desires, and earn rewards.</p>
<p>IC1101's appeal is not just in its technological innovation and diverse universe construction, but more importantly, in its ability to attract different types of user groups.</p>
<p>Before introducing specific products and technologies, it is worth considering who will be interested in the metaverse. We can divide IC1101's audience into two categories, heavy gamers and casual gamers.</p>
<p>The former includes tech enthusiasts and gamers who have some technical expertise and equipment requirements, are interested in immersive virtual experiences, and pursue the ultimate experience; while the latter are more focused on commercial and social aspects, such as enterprises or projects interested in Web3 business models, and players who want to find more social opportunities and new friends in the virtual world.</p>
<p>Based on the needs of different user groups, IC1101 provides two products to meet their expectations: IC1101 World and IC1101 Space.</p>
IC1101 World: A more immersive metaverse world.
<p>IC1101 World is a more immersive metaverse world. In terms of technology and graphics, it is created using the Unreal Engine 5, with outstanding image quality that forms a strong contrast to most of the current metaverse projects made with the Unity engine, which tend to be low-poly in style.</p>
<p>In actual gameplay experience, we can see finely detailed graphics similar to those of AAA games, including finely detailed building details, dynamic blur during movement, and reflection of ripples on the water surface, all of which make players feel fully immersed in a virtual world.</p>
<p></p>
<p>In terms of scene design, IC1101 World provides more three-dimensional scenes, including different planets and buildings. Each planet has a unique theme and function, such as planets specifically designed for battles and planets for exhibitions and demonstrations. Different buildings also serve different purposes, such as Sony's music hall, which can be used for music playback and related artist activities.</p>
<p>In terms of scene design, IC1101 World offers more three-dimensional scenes, including different planets and buildings. Each planet has a unique theme and function, such as planets specifically designed for battles and planets for exhibitions and demonstrations. Different buildings also have different functions, such as Sony's music hall, which can be used for music playback and artist-related activities.</p>
<p>In addition, virtual assets have been mapped more realistically in the IC1101 World, and players can directly view and purchase NFTs in the mall, change outfits, and become a 3D image of the NFT, which also provides possibilities for more collaborative creation.</p>
IC1101 Space: Lower Threshold for Participation
<p>IC1101 World will bring better graphics and a more immersive world to players, but the cost is higher hardware requirements for accessing devices. A well-configured computer may be needed to smoothly enter the metaverse.</p>
<p>However, not everyone is a hardcore gamer or an extreme immersion seeker. For more casual players who want to experience the scenes and interactions of the metaverse, IC1101 provides another option: IC1101 Space.</p>
<p>IC1101 Space can be accessed through a simple browser login, presented in the form of a webpage, making it convenient and fast to use. Although the graphics may not be as detailed as the World version, they significantly lower the barrier to entry, making them particularly suitable for commercial and social users.</p>
<p>In IC1101 Space, players can take on their own roles and participate in online displays and interactions. Compared to traditional social media platforms, IC1101 Space provides richer ways of interaction. In the same scene, players can communicate and greet others, have deeper interactions with organizations, media, and partners they are interested in, bringing them closer together. Immersion is not the first choice for social demand orientation, as it is more important to allow more people to participate in the activities together. IC1101 has achieved this very well.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that the user data and scenes of the two versions, IC1101 World and IC1101 Space, are interoperable. This means that users can choose different login methods according to their own needs, but their behavior is visible in both versions, and together they influence the world of IC1101. This versioning method for different user groups can attract more users and provide better experiences for different types of participants. This is relatively rare in current metaverse projects, and many projects may not have considered this layered demand.</p>
<p>For hardcore players and explorers who are looking for ultimate graphics and immersion, IC1101 World provides a more immersive metaverse experience. For casual players who want to participate in metaverse social and business activities, IC1101 Space provides a lower threshold for participation. Whether for technology enthusiasts, gamers, business users, or social users, IC1101 can meet their needs and create new digital experiences and lifestyles for them.</p>
A sense of participation puts the galaxy within reach.
<p>The essence of social interaction is a sense of participation. People are the sum of social relationships, and in many metaverse projects, simple display and gathering are only a one-way and low-interaction social relationships, which cannot give players a strong sense of participation. Over time, players will feel empty and boring, and a rich and fulfilling virtual world seems out of reach.</p>
<p>Therefore, the metaverse also needs to be built around a sense of participation, so that users are willing, good at, and immersed in this virtual world, becoming "digital natives" in the metaverse.</p>
<p>In addition to excellent graphics and sensitive user segmentation, IC1101 is also working on a sense of participation.</p>
<p>Firstly, in terms of social aspects, in IC1101, users can enter with their own NFT digital avatars, and can also use these avatars within IC1101. This way, users can communicate with others in the virtual world through their digital avatars. Through functions such as lobby chat, private chat, friend teaming, community tasks/activities, live streaming, and social media sharing, users can establish emotional connections with others. In addition, users can also enhance friendships by sending friends gifts. These social functions not only allow users to display their digital avatars in IC1101, but also to establish real social relationships with others.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Next, let's delve into the gaming aspect. IC1101 is committed to creating interactive gaming spaces. In the world of IC1101, users can indulge in a wide variety of casual games, enticing more Web2 multi-users to migrate to the Web3 world. With diverse gaming experiences, IC1101 offers users more interactive and entertaining choices, allowing them to have a stronger sense of engagement within the game.</p>
<p>In addition, IC1101 provides a whole new shopping experience. Users can present and sell 2D NFTs purchased on other platforms in a 3D manner within IC1101. Furthermore, brand collaborations are able to bring users a shopping experience beyond reality. By partnering with brands, IC1101 has created a 3D NFT digital mall, offering users a completely new way of shopping and experiencing.</p>
<p>Finally, IC1101 also allows users to participate in scenario decision-making. Users can vote to decide the functions of buildings and scenes implemented in the metaverse world. This way, users can participate in the construction process of the metaverse, express their opinions and ideas, and further enhance their sense of participation in IC1101.</p>
Expert Team
<p>The project members of IC1101 are a group of creative industry experts with an average of 15 years of experience in their respective fields. The team members are located in North America and Asia, and have worked for globally renowned companies such as Dfinity, UBISOFT, Disney, Unity SF, and Konami. They have had long-standing partnerships with top global companies such as Blizzard, EA, Sony, and Amazon, and have participated in the development of many well-known products such as Hearthstone, World of Warcraft, Diablo, Harry Potter, New World, and The Last of Us.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The team members have a great passion for the Metaverse project and a deep understanding of it. They are familiar with the concept and development trends of the Metaverse, and are committed to creating an exciting and meaningful virtual experience for users.</p>
<p>The strength and partnerships of the IC1101 team have laid a solid foundation for the success of the project. Their professional knowledge and rich experience will ensure that IC1101 can provide the best technical solutions and continuously drive the development of the Metaverse. The team's goal is to create a realistic and engaging virtual world for users where everyone can experience unlimited possibilities and fun.</p>
SPACE X 3.0: Immerse Yourself in the Advanced Metaverse
<p>Even before its official launch, IC1101 offers a unique opportunity for an early experience that everyone has been eagerly waiting for.</p>
<p>On June 6th, starting at 10:00 AM, IC1101 is hosting a significant event called "SPACE X 3.0" Demo Day, providing a vital chance for those interested in the project. This event will showcase the latest developments of the IC1101 project and allow participants to have a firsthand experience of its remarkable products.</p>
<p>"SPACE X 3.0" Demo Day will take place in IC1101 Space. Participants will enter this metaverse in the form of digital avatars and engage in interactions with others. The event will offer a diverse range of experiences, including airdrops of tokens and real-time PvP competitions.</p>
<p>From the scenes of the event, it's apparent that the inaugural Demo Day has attracted thousands of visitors and garnered support from 30 VCs and 8 media outlets. This demonstrates the convenience, immersion, and engagement that IC1101 provides to its participants.</p>
<p>Beyond the event itself, we are also highly excited about the future of the IC1101 project. Through the showcase at Demo Day, IC1101 will unveil its enormous potential and prospects as a real metaverse to the world, bringing users more innovation and thrilling experiences.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IC1101 is committed to providing a more immersive, fun, and autonomous experience than the current metaverse. IC1101, named after its astronomical designation, shines with infinite, mysterious light in the vast universe. As one of the largest known galaxies in the universe, IC1101 represents a huge, mysterious, and spectacular existence. It undoubtedly contains endless wonders and unknowns waiting for human exploration.</p>
<p>IC1101 is a mysterious galaxy, a new metaverse project name, and a super immersive multi-dimensional universe platform dedicated to providing a more immersive, fun, and autonomous experience than the current metaverse. Participants will be able to explore the mysterious qualities of IC1101 and discover endless possibilities within it.</p>
<p>Current metaverse projects often have limitations in terms of graphics, immersion, and participant decision-making power. IC1101 aims to solve these limitations and take the realism, participation, and activity of the metaverse world to a new level.</p>
<p>So, can it stand out in fierce competition and become a dark horse? Let us embark on the journey of IC1101 together, explore this mysterious galaxy, and find the answers.</p>
When Adventure Meets Creativity
<p>In the world of the metaverse, a fascinating worldview is particularly important: it not only determines the style of the project and the immersion of the players, but also opens up more imagination space for storytelling. As a galaxy full of wonders and fantasies, IC1101 has a unique and captivating worldview, bringing unprecedented experiences to participants.</p>
<p>The worldview of IC1101 is based on diversity and freedom. Eight major races converge in this galaxy, each with unique appearances and abilities. From appearance to cultural customs, from ideological concepts to social structures, the differences between races in IC1101 are rich and inclusive. In this galaxy, players will be able to explore the blending and mutual influence of diverse cultures, and feel the interaction and cooperation between different races.</p>
<p>IC1101 also provides players with great freedom and creativity. Players can choose their own role identity, create unique appearance and personality traits, and participate in various exciting activities and scenarios, such as driving spaceships to explore unknown planets in the galaxy, discovering hidden cosmic secrets; They can also join teams, collaborate to solve complex puzzles and tasks, and experience the fruits of cooperation and unity. At the same time, players can also trade in the economic market of IC1101, buying and selling various precious resources and items, and developing their own wealth and power.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Overall, IC1101 combines elements of science fiction, fantasy, and mystery. Players will find themselves in a colorful and mysterious interstellar world, where every exploration and adventure brings new surprises and challenges. But how will this worldview be realized through technology?</p>
Multi-platform support attracts different user groups.
<p>Overall, IC1101 is an immersive metaverse platform based on a multi-chain architecture that allows users from different public chains to easily connect. Through the introduction of token economics and NFTs, users can have their own digital assets and ownership, and can engage in social and game cooperation to complete tasks, satisfy their desires, and earn rewards.</p>
<p>IC1101's appeal is not just in its technological innovation and diverse universe construction, but more importantly, in its ability to attract different types of user groups.</p>
<p>Before introducing specific products and technologies, it is worth considering who will be interested in the metaverse. We can divide IC1101's audience into two categories, heavy gamers and casual gamers.</p>
<p>The former includes tech enthusiasts and gamers who have some technical expertise and equipment requirements, are interested in immersive virtual experiences, and pursue the ultimate experience; while the latter are more focused on commercial and social aspects, such as enterprises or projects interested in Web3 business models, and players who want to find more social opportunities and new friends in the virtual world.</p>
<p>Based on the needs of different user groups, IC1101 provides two products to meet their expectations: IC1101 World and IC1101 Space.</p>
IC1101 World: A more immersive metaverse world.
<p>IC1101 World is a more immersive metaverse world. In terms of technology and graphics, it is created using the Unreal Engine 5, with outstanding image quality that forms a strong contrast to most of the current metaverse projects made with the Unity engine, which tend to be low-poly in style.</p>
<p>In actual gameplay experience, we can see finely detailed graphics similar to those of AAA games, including finely detailed building details, dynamic blur during movement, and reflection of ripples on the water surface, all of which make players feel fully immersed in a virtual world.</p>
<p></p>
<p>In terms of scene design, IC1101 World provides more three-dimensional scenes, including different planets and buildings. Each planet has a unique theme and function, such as planets specifically designed for battles and planets for exhibitions and demonstrations. Different buildings also serve different purposes, such as Sony's music hall, which can be used for music playback and related artist activities.</p>
<p>In terms of scene design, IC1101 World offers more three-dimensional scenes, including different planets and buildings. Each planet has a unique theme and function, such as planets specifically designed for battles and planets for exhibitions and demonstrations. Different buildings also have different functions, such as Sony's music hall, which can be used for music playback and artist-related activities.</p>
<p>In addition, virtual assets have been mapped more realistically in the IC1101 World, and players can directly view and purchase NFTs in the mall, change outfits, and become a 3D image of the NFT, which also provides possibilities for more collaborative creation.</p>
IC1101 Space: Lower Threshold for Participation
<p>IC1101 World will bring better graphics and a more immersive world to players, but the cost is higher hardware requirements for accessing devices. A well-configured computer may be needed to smoothly enter the metaverse.</p>
<p>However, not everyone is a hardcore gamer or an extreme immersion seeker. For more casual players who want to experience the scenes and interactions of the metaverse, IC1101 provides another option: IC1101 Space.</p>
<p>IC1101 Space can be accessed through a simple browser login, presented in the form of a webpage, making it convenient and fast to use. Although the graphics may not be as detailed as the World version, they significantly lower the barrier to entry, making them particularly suitable for commercial and social users.</p>
<p>In IC1101 Space, players can take on their own roles and participate in online displays and interactions. Compared to traditional social media platforms, IC1101 Space provides richer ways of interaction. In the same scene, players can communicate and greet others, have deeper interactions with organizations, media, and partners they are interested in, bringing them closer together. Immersion is not the first choice for social demand orientation, as it is more important to allow more people to participate in the activities together. IC1101 has achieved this very well.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that the user data and scenes of the two versions, IC1101 World and IC1101 Space, are interoperable. This means that users can choose different login methods according to their own needs, but their behavior is visible in both versions, and together they influence the world of IC1101. This versioning method for different user groups can attract more users and provide better experiences for different types of participants. This is relatively rare in current metaverse projects, and many projects may not have considered this layered demand.</p>
<p>For hardcore players and explorers who are looking for ultimate graphics and immersion, IC1101 World provides a more immersive metaverse experience. For casual players who want to participate in metaverse social and business activities, IC1101 Space provides a lower threshold for participation. Whether for technology enthusiasts, gamers, business users, or social users, IC1101 can meet their needs and create new digital experiences and lifestyles for them.</p>
A sense of participation puts the galaxy within reach.
<p>The essence of social interaction is a sense of participation. People are the sum of social relationships, and in many metaverse projects, simple display and gathering are only a one-way and low-interaction social relationships, which cannot give players a strong sense of participation. Over time, players will feel empty and boring, and a rich and fulfilling virtual world seems out of reach.</p>
<p>Therefore, the metaverse also needs to be built around a sense of participation, so that users are willing, good at, and immersed in this virtual world, becoming "digital natives" in the metaverse.</p>
<p>In addition to excellent graphics and sensitive user segmentation, IC1101 is also working on a sense of participation.</p>
<p>Firstly, in terms of social aspects, in IC1101, users can enter with their own NFT digital avatars, and can also use these avatars within IC1101. This way, users can communicate with others in the virtual world through their digital avatars. Through functions such as lobby chat, private chat, friend teaming, community tasks/activities, live streaming, and social media sharing, users can establish emotional connections with others. In addition, users can also enhance friendships by sending friends gifts. These social functions not only allow users to display their digital avatars in IC1101, but also to establish real social relationships with others.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Next, let's delve into the gaming aspect. IC1101 is committed to creating interactive gaming spaces. In the world of IC1101, users can indulge in a wide variety of casual games, enticing more Web2 multi-users to migrate to the Web3 world. With diverse gaming experiences, IC1101 offers users more interactive and entertaining choices, allowing them to have a stronger sense of engagement within the game.</p>
<p>In addition, IC1101 provides a whole new shopping experience. Users can present and sell 2D NFTs purchased on other platforms in a 3D manner within IC1101. Furthermore, brand collaborations are able to bring users a shopping experience beyond reality. By partnering with brands, IC1101 has created a 3D NFT digital mall, offering users a completely new way of shopping and experiencing.</p>
<p>Finally, IC1101 also allows users to participate in scenario decision-making. Users can vote to decide the functions of buildings and scenes implemented in the metaverse world. This way, users can participate in the construction process of the metaverse, express their opinions and ideas, and further enhance their sense of participation in IC1101.</p>
Expert Team
<p>The project members of IC1101 are a group of creative industry experts with an average of 15 years of experience in their respective fields. The team members are located in North America and Asia, and have worked for globally renowned companies such as Dfinity, UBISOFT, Disney, Unity SF, and Konami. They have had long-standing partnerships with top global companies such as Blizzard, EA, Sony, and Amazon, and have participated in the development of many well-known products such as Hearthstone, World of Warcraft, Diablo, Harry Potter, New World, and The Last of Us.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The team members have a great passion for the Metaverse project and a deep understanding of it. They are familiar with the concept and development trends of the Metaverse, and are committed to creating an exciting and meaningful virtual experience for users.</p>
<p>The strength and partnerships of the IC1101 team have laid a solid foundation for the success of the project. Their professional knowledge and rich experience will ensure that IC1101 can provide the best technical solutions and continuously drive the development of the Metaverse. The team's goal is to create a realistic and engaging virtual world for users where everyone can experience unlimited possibilities and fun.</p>
SPACE X 3.0: Immerse Yourself in the Advanced Metaverse
<p>Even before its official launch, IC1101 offers a unique opportunity for an early experience that everyone has been eagerly waiting for.</p>
<p>On June 6th, starting at 10:00 AM, IC1101 is hosting a significant event called "SPACE X 3.0" Demo Day, providing a vital chance for those interested in the project. This event will showcase the latest developments of the IC1101 project and allow participants to have a firsthand experience of its remarkable products.</p>
<p>"SPACE X 3.0" Demo Day will take place in IC1101 Space. Participants will enter this metaverse in the form of digital avatars and engage in interactions with others. The event will offer a diverse range of experiences, including airdrops of tokens and real-time PvP competitions.</p>
<p>From the scenes of the event, it's apparent that the inaugural Demo Day has attracted thousands of visitors and garnered support from 30 VCs and 8 media outlets. This demonstrates the convenience, immersion, and engagement that IC1101 provides to its participants.</p>
<p>Beyond the event itself, we are also highly excited about the future of the IC1101 project. Through the showcase at Demo Day, IC1101 will unveil its enormous potential and prospects as a real metaverse to the world, bringing users more innovation and thrilling experiences.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
