<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:57:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gemini Eyes UAE Expansion Amid US Uncertainty, Crypto.com Gets MPI License in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253325</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Gemini_UAE.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Gemini_UAE.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gemini is seeking a UAE licence to serve customers based in the Emirates.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Winklevoss-led crypto exchange Gemini announced it has started the process of acquiring a crypto license to serve customers based in the United Arab Emirates (UAE).</p>
<p>As part of its global expansion plans, Gemini revealed engaging with stakeholders throughout the region to learn more about local regulatory requirements and the needs of UAE crypto investors.</p>
<p>In other exchange-related news, Crypto.com said it had acquired a Major Payment Institution license for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).</p>
<h2>Gemini Doubles Down on UAE Presence</h2>
<p>The crypto exchange&#8217;s blog post <a href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-announces-plans-for-uae-crypto-license" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">cited</a> its 2022 Global State of Crypto Report, which found that over 35% of those surveyed in the UAE had purchased crypto, compared to only 20% of those in the US.</p>
<p>Almost 32% of non-owners in the UAE said they are likely to purchase digital assets in the next year. Meanwhile, 33% of crypto users in the UAE make in-person purchases with their tokens at brick-and-mortar retailers, compared to just 19% of owners globally.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our application is our first step towards providing customers in the UAE and beyond with a safe, secure, and easy-to-use platform to engage with crypto. Amazing awaits.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>While speaking with local media, Zawya, during their UAE visit, the co-founders <a href="https://www.zawya.com/en/special-coverage/the-future-of-cryptos/exclusive-winklevoss-twins-seek-uae-crypto-licence-after-hostility-lack-of-clarity-in-us-ujfg8b1a" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reiterated</a> their frustration over the regulatory climate in the US. Cameron Winklevoss touched upon the lack of clarity and consistency in the US about regulations regarding digital assets and added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It is actually very hostile to crypto companies. To keep building, innovating, is not going to be happening. There is a lot of headwinds. It is just hard to get things done in the US.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Exchanges Seek Global Expansion</h2>
<p>In recent months, Gemini <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to set up a new engineering hub in Gurgaon, India. It also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/geminis-non-us-derivatives-platform-goes-live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a non-US derivatives platform last month amidst regulatory headwinds back home. Several other crypto exchanges, including San Francisco-based Coinbase, have also broadened their user base elsewhere in response to the growing crackdown by US regulators.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com was <a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-obtains-major-payment-institution-licence-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">granted</a> a Major Payment Institution (MPI) license for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). The license authorizes Crypto.com to offer its DPT services to customers in the city-state.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/" rel="nofollow">Gemini Eyes UAE Expansion Amid US Uncertainty, Crypto.com Gets MPI License in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CleanSpark Scoops Up 12,500 Bitcoin Mining Machines for $40.5 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cleanspark-scoops-up-12500-bitcoin-mining-machines-for-40-5-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253481</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/mining-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/mining-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CleanSpark confirms another heavy investment into mining equipment, adding to nine figures worth of machines purchased this year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Sustainability-focused Bitcoin mining firm CleanSpark is expanding its ASIC fleet by 12,500 units after investing $40.5 million into new hardware. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The added equipment is projected to bring CleanSpark’s total hash rate to over 16 exahashes per second (EH/s). </span></p>
<h2>CleanSpark’s Mining Discount</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to a </span><a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/06/01/2680404/0/en/CleanSpark-Buys-12-500-Antminer-S19-XP-Bitcoin-Miners-for-40-5M.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">press release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from CleanSpark on Thursday, the firm’s newly purchased fleet of Antminer S19 XP machines worked out to a cost of $23 per terahash ($/TH). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Data from </span><a href="https://data.hashrateindex.com/asic-index-data" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Hashrate Index</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows this is slightly lower than the industry average of $23.27/TH for machines of similar efficiency. On this matter, CleanSpark said:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The Antminer S19 XP units have a power-efficiency rating of 21.5 joules per terahash (J/TH) and a bitcoin mining compute power (or hashrate) of 141 terahash per second (TH/s) each, for a combined total hash rate of 1.76 exahashes per second (EH/s).”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Costs for high-efficiency ASICs have consistently declined since June of last year, when Bitcoin’s freefall to under $20,000 made mining BTC far less profitable than during the bull market. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s return above $26,000 in March did little to break that trend, though this may be due to the increasing efficiency of ASIC machines over time. Indeed, though Bitcoin’s price remains down 61% from its all-time high, its </span><a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/bitcoin-hashrate.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">global hash rate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> continues to break records with minimal interruption.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After this purchase, Cleanspark’s total fleet would technically represent 4.7% of global hashrate combined. However, its new machines won’t go active right away, with 6000 expected to arrive from the manufacturer in June, and the remaining 6500 expected for August.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The company’s CEO, Zach Bradford, also suggested that the new fleet could replace existing, less efficient machines, rather than simply adding to them, depending on how the economics play out.</span></p>
<h2>CleanSpark’s Heavy Mining Investments</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CleanSpark has already revealed purchases for tens of thousands of machines across multiple announcements this year. This includes 20,000 Antminer S19j Pro+ units for $13.15/TH in February and 45,000 Antminer S19 XP units for $23/TH in </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cleanspark-boosts-mining-capacity-with-new-machinery-worth-145-million/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">April</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Only the first of those purchased has been paid off in full so far, with “significant progress” made on paying off the April buy. On the most recent investment, CleanSpark CEO Gary A. Vecchiarelli said the company has “already fully funded and paid for the first half of this purchase, or approximately 6,650 machines.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In late 2022, major North American mining firms including </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/core-scientific-to-send-20m-worth-of-mining-equipment-to-settle-payment-dispute/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Core Scientific</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Iris Energy struggled to pay down debt after taking out similar nine-figure loans to purchase new machines. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other firms like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-partners-with-foundry-to-launch-bitcoin-mining-investment-product/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and CleanSpark deliberately waited for the crypto bear market to set in before deploying major capital toward mining infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cleanspark-scoops-up-12500-bitcoin-mining-machines-for-40-5-million/" rel="nofollow">CleanSpark Scoops Up 12,500 Bitcoin Mining Machines for $40.5 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Meme Coin Wall Street Memes Presale Hits $2M: Could it be The Next Pepe?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-coin-wall-street-memes-presale-hits-2m-could-it-be-the-next-pepe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253443</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_presale_cover.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_presale_cover.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Meme coins continue to reign supreme in the market, with tokens like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu demonstrating the incredible power of retail traders. The latest to join this exciting market is Wall Street Memes (WSM) – a new community-driven token that has already amassed over $2 million through its presale. Given its early success, Wall [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins continue to reign supreme in the market, with tokens like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu demonstrating the incredible power of retail traders.</p>
<p>The latest to join this exciting market is <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> – a new community-driven token that has already amassed over $2 million through its presale.</p>
<p>Given its early success, Wall Street Memes is already being compared to the ultra-popular Pepe coin, which produced exponential returns for investors in mid-April.</p>
<h2>Early Presale Success As WSM Takes Flight</h2>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; presale only kicked off on May 26, yet investors have been coming in their droves to snag some WSM tokens while they&#8217;re being offered at a low price.</p>
<p>This presale is split into 30 stages, each with its own price point. By taking this approach, Wall Street Memes&#8217; team aims to reward those who show early faith in the project.</p>
<p>The response to the presale has been immense – with over $2.1 million in funding raised in only six days.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253446" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-1.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="291" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-1-300x145.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-1-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This means that Wall Street Memes is raking in an impressive $350,000 daily from presale investors.</p>
<p>The early success of the presale has also sparked rapid growth in the Wall Street Memes community, which is already over one million strong, thanks to the previous success of the Wall St Bulls NFT collection.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes’ official Telegram channel has seen a massive influx of new members over the past few days, while the project’s <a href="https://www.instagram.com/wallstbets/?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Instagram page</a> now boasts over 523,000 followers.</p>
<p>The exponential growth of the <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> community, coupled with the early success of the project’s presale phase, has led many in the investment community to speculate that WSM could be poised to replicate Pepe’s success.</p>
<h2>Colossal Community Propels Wall Street Memes Higher</h2>
<p>As mentioned above, Wall Street Memes benefits from a previously-established community spread across various social media channels, like Twitter and Instagram.</p>
<p>This community was inspired by the GameStop saga of 2021, where individual investors challenged the big dogs on Wall Street – and won.</p>
<p>Now, Wall Street Memes’ team aims to empower the community and reshape the world of finance using the WSM token.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253447" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="352" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-300x175.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Per the project’s whitepaper, the total supply of WSM tokens will be capped at two billion. Half of these tokens are reserved for presale investors, with the other half used for community rewards (e.g., airdrops) and CEX/DEX liquidity.</p>
<p>Through this tokenomics setup, Wall Street Memes’ team looks to ensure that the community holds all the power – and this is reinforced by the fact that there hasn’t been any private sale before the presale commenced.</p>
<p>Moreover, Wall Street Memes&#8217; team hasn&#8217;t reserved an allocation of WSM for themselves, demonstrating their long-term commitment to the project.</p>
<h2>Buzz Around WSM Reaches Fever Pitch After Influencer Backing</h2>
<p>Given the sheer scale of the <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> community, it’s no surprise that it has attracted attention from influential figures who recognize the power of meme-driven movements.</p>
<p>One notable example is Elon Musk, who has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1649784663924244482" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">interacted</a> with the Wall Street Memes community on Twitter several times.</p>
<p>The attention <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> has garnered from Musk, a figure commonly considered the epitome of meme culture, stands as a powerful testament to the community&#8217;s influence on social media.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253445" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-1.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="296" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-1-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-1-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Naturally, this has led to intense speculation among crypto analysts about where the WSM token could go once listed on popular CEXs and DEXs in Phase 2 of the project&#8217;s roadmap.</p>
<p>YouTuber Crypto Gains, who has over 106,000 subscribers, released a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rCA2jRX3cjY&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> where he hinted that WSM could perform really well if the momentum continues.</p>
<p>In addition, crypto influencer Jacob Bury <a href="https://twitter.com/BuryCrypto/status/1663928535206047745" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">tweeted</a> that WSM is “going to go wild” – and even speculated that the token could be listed on Binance in the future.</p>
<p>Ultimately, whether or not WSM will hit the heights forecast by Crypto Gains and Jacob Bury remains to be seen. However, one thing is for sure – the eyes of the crypto world are now firmly fixed on Wall Street Memes as it continues to make headway in the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-coin-wall-street-memes-presale-hits-2m-could-it-be-the-next-pepe/" rel="nofollow">New Meme Coin Wall Street Memes Presale Hits $2M: Could it be The Next Pepe?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Tests $0.5 Critical Resistance But Will the Rally Continue? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-explodes-above-0-5-heres-the-next-challenge-for-the-bulls-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253365</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price has shown bullish movement in recent weeks. However, there is a notable resistance level that needs to be overcome before a more sustained rally can be anticipated. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: XRP has displayed a consistent upward trend after being rejected from the 200-day moving average of around $0.4. Additionally, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price has shown bullish movement in recent weeks. However, there is a notable resistance level that needs to be overcome before a more sustained rally can be anticipated.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>XRP has displayed a consistent upward trend after being rejected from the 200-day moving average of around $0.4. Additionally, it has surpassed the 50-day moving average of around $0.45 and appears to be targeting the resistance zone at $0.6 in the short term.</p>
<p>A successful breakthrough of the $0.6 level would likely initiate a bullish phase, with the price potentially reaching as high as $0.9 in the mid-term. However, it is worth noting that the RSI has recently indicated an overbought condition, suggesting the possibility of a pullback or a period of consolidation in the upcoming days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253368" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253368" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253368 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0106231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-1-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253368" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price has successfully broken out of the significant descending channel after finding support near the 0.000016 SAT level. Furthermore, both the 50-day moving average, positioned around 0.000017 SAT, and the static resistance level at 0.000018 SAT have been surpassed.</p>
<p>The price is attempting to breach the 200-day moving average; however, the RSI&#8217;s overbought signal suggests the potential for a short-term correction. In such a scenario, both the 0.000018 SAT level and the 50-day moving average are likely to be retested, providing support to the market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253369" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253369" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253369 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0106232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-1-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253369" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-explodes-above-0-5-heres-the-next-challenge-for-the-bulls-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Tests $0.5 Critical Resistance But Will the Rally Continue? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Remains Uncertain But $2K Seems a Likely Target: Ethereum Price Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-remains-uncertain-but-2k-seems-a-likely-target-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253372</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum has been consolidating within a narrow price range, tightly bound by the upper limit of the descending flag pattern and the 100-day moving average. However, a breakout is imminent and will determine the subsequent direction of the cryptocurrency. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Examining the daily chart, Ethereum demonstrated a period of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has been consolidating within a narrow price range, tightly bound by the upper limit of the descending flag pattern and the 100-day moving average. However, a breakout is imminent and will determine the subsequent direction of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Examining the daily chart, Ethereum demonstrated a period of stable price action around the $1790 mark, near the 100-day moving average, before gaining support and embarking on an upward trajectory.</p>
<p>Despite an unsuccessful attempt to breach the flag&#8217;s upper boundary at $1.9K, resulting in a minor correction, Ethereum&#8217;s price remains confined within a limited range, approximately between the $1791 level of the 100-day moving average and the dynamic resistance offered by the flag&#8217;s upper trendline. A breakout from the flag pattern is likely to initiate another rally toward the $2K resistance zone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253373" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253373" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253373 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_0106231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253373" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>Taking a closer look at the 4-hour chart, three significant price regions present challenges for Ethereum buyers and sellers: the static resistance at $2K, the dynamic resistance from the mid-trendline of the ascending channel, and the dynamic support provided by the channel&#8217;s lower threshold.</p>
<p>Considering the ongoing price action, it might seem more likely that Ethereum will continue its upward trend, aiming to surpass the $2K resistance level. However, given the current market conditions and prevailing uncertainty among market participants, it is more probable that a consolidation phase will occur first between the $2K region and the lower boundary of the channel.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253374" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253374" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253374 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chat_0106232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETH-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253374" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-remains-uncertain-but-2k-seems-a-likely-target-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Remains Uncertain But $2K Seems a Likely Target: Ethereum Price Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FLEX Pumps 19% After OPNX Exchange Issues New Governance Token</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/flex-pumps-19-after-opnx-exchange-issues-new-governance-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253431</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/3AC_Coinflex.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/3AC_Coinflex.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FLEX holders will be able to convert their investments into OPNX’s new OX governance token at a fixed 1:100 rate.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">OPNX &#8211; the crypto bankruptcy claims exchange launched by Su </span>Zhu and Kyle Davies – released a whitepaper for its new ‘OX’ governance token on Wednesday.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Details around the coin’s tokenomics caused the price of FLEX – the platform’s existing native token – to spike on the day.</span></p>
<h2>OPNX, FLEX, and OX</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Following the </span><a href="https://twitter.com/OPNX_Official/status/1663999927452565507" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reveal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, FLEX trades for $1.14 at writing time, up 19% from $0.96 24 hours ago, and from $0.75 a week ago, according to CoinMarketCap.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By contrast, CoinGecko reflects a current price of just $1.09  for FLEX, which still represents a 7.9% daily bump and a clear indication of rising demand. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">FLEX will be convertible at a ratio of 1:100 for new OX tokens, which will provide fee discounts, staking opportunities, and governance rights at OPNX exchange. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Alternatively, If FLEX buyers choose to voluntarily lock up their OX for 3 months, they’ll earn 25% more tokens. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the exchange, OX will solve “major problems with traditional exchange token models.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Fixed discount models only incentivize short term holding for fees— while high minimum volume/holding bands are only accessible to whales &amp; require constant adjustment, causing confusion,” explained the firm. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By contrast, OX will use a “Stake To Trade For Free” rebate model allowing anybody that locks up OX tokens to trade freely on the platform. Specifically, users must lockup a proportion of the total OX supply that is greater than their total proportion of OPNX trading volume for fee-free trading.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The exchange will begin trading with a temporary bonus staking multiplier, letting users trade with a volume much greater than their relative stake size for free. “The earlier you are, the more you can capitalize on this bonus,” wrote the company. </span></p>
<h2>OPNX’s Disatorous Beginnings</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">OPNX was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/opnx-crypto-exchange-formed-by-3ac-founders-goes-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">opened</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to provide a liquid market for bankruptcy claims on numerous crypto companies that collapsed in 2022. Zhu and Davies themselves were behind the defunct crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), which imploded last June following Terra’s meltdown the previous month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The exchange’s existing FLEX tokens are a remnant of co-founder Mark Lamb’s former crypto exchange CoinFLEX, which froze withdrawals and filed for restructuring last year after a loan deal with </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/roger-vers-debt-part-of-the-reason-for-coinflexs-collapse-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Roger Ver</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> went south. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto exchange tokens as a concept came under fire in November during the collapse of crypto exchange FTX, which was in part spurred by the unraveling of its native FTT token. OPNX supports claims trading for FTX.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/flex-pumps-19-after-opnx-exchange-issues-new-governance-token/" rel="nofollow">FLEX Pumps 19% After OPNX Exchange Issues New Governance Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding Token Burns And Why They Are Becoming So Popular For Crypto Projects</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/understanding-token-burns-and-why-they-are-becoming-so-popular-for-crypto-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253388</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Token or cryptocurrency burning refers to a mechanism that permanently eliminates tokens from the circulating supply.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has boomed over the past decade, with many tokens boasting billion-dollar valuations.</p>
<p>With such exponential growth in the market, many would expect many of the thousands of tokens to fail or continually drop in value, but that rarely happens, especially amongst the<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> top 100 tokens</a>. The value of some of these tokens is controlled with the help of burning tokens.</p>
<p>Since the beginning  of crypto, many projects have adopted this mechanism to induce artificial scarcity of the tokens, consequently hiking the price. But this not-so-new concept is increasingly becoming popular as many crypto communities and users champion it.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the process of token burns differs from project to project, and it is important to fully understand how a project’s token burn will affect you and what it means. In this piece below, we dig deeper into what a cryptocurrency burn is, how it works, the history of token burns, and some practical examples of how previous token burns have been executed.</p>
<h2>What is a Token Burn?</h2>
<p>Token burns, or simply ‘burning,’ is a mechanism that crypto projects employ to permanently eliminate/destroy (burn) a number of tokens from the existing circulating token supply. This is typically done by sending the number of tokens to a burn address, which is a digital wallet that cannot be accessed by anybody as it has no private key. This reduces the number of tokens in circulation, locking them up for eternity and preventing anyone from accessing them, hence creating a ‘deflationary’ event.</p>
<p>The main reason for burning tokens is to boost the value of the remaining tokens. This follows the economic principle of supply/demand, whereby if there’s less supply of tokens in circulation when demand remains the same (or increases), it will cause scarcity of the asset; hence the asset commands a higher price.</p>
<p>Inversely, by increasing the number of tokens in circulation while demand remains the same, the asset’s price could witness a drop in value.</p>
<p>Burning tokens create scarcity, and in turn, the value of the asset could move upwards, and people trade it. Additionally, token burns also welcome new investors as they are viewed as a bullish indicator, again boosting demand.</p>
<p>Over the years, several projects, including Ethereum, Binance Coin (BNB), Shiba Inu, SWEAT Economy,  and hundreds of others, have employed this method to increase their value. While burning may be viewed as bullish, it always does not reflect on the price immediately, as some token burns are automated to happen regularly or are disclosed well in advance. This means the price will be effectively priced well before the token burn takes place.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253390" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="624" height="416" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<h2>The Importance of Token Burns</h2>
<p>As alluded to, token burns are an effective way for crypto projects to reduce the total supply of circulating tokens. Reducing the supply makes them more scarce and potentially valuable, which could create a positive feedback loop whereby prices spike, and more investors jump on the bandwagon, further increasing the demand.</p>
<p>Secondly, planned burn schedules, such as BNB quarterly burn, provide a more balanced ecosystem, in this case, for the BNB ecosystem. By burning crypto, the project reduces the advantages that early miners or investors have over new users of the token. As coins reduce, the blockchain network benefits investors equally, providing more value to every investor in the project.</p>
<p>Thirdly, burning tokens also increases the trust in developers and shows they are committed to the project. How? Reducing tokens shows that the developers are willing to reduce their token kitty and sacrifice their own supply (or the floating supply) for the greater benefit of investors, as explained above.</p>
<p>Finally, some projects apply a set schedule of burning the tokens, proof-of-burn (PoB), one of the consensus algorithms that ensure all participating nodes in the network validate the state of the blockchain.  PoB operates on the principle of miners and, at times, investors voting on burning these tokens. Once burnt, miners are granted the opportunity to mint the same proportion of tokens burnt.</p>
<p>One key example is the recent governance vote by SWEAT Economy that allowed investors and token holders to vote on either burning 100 million $SWEAT tokens or distributing them to existing token holders.</p>
<h2>Real-World Examples of Token burns</h2>
<p>As explained above, token burning is almost like crypto itself. In fact, some of the earliest and most successful projects have used token burning as part of their strategy. Below, we discuss some of the real-world examples of some of the most famous token burns in crypto history:</p>
<h3>‘Mistake’ Burning</h3>
<p>While it goes mostly unnoticed, mistake burns are one of the most popular ways tokens are burnt. For instance, Bitcoin is arguably the first and most famous example of these “mistake” burns. Whenever a user loses their private keys or sends the tokens to an inaccessible (invalid) wallet address, those BTC are effectively burned, as they will never be accessed forever. According to some estimates, over 4 million BTC have been effectively burned, accounting for 20% of the total supply.</p>
<h3>Buyback and burn (Binance Coin)</h3>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-bnb-burn-explained-how-much-is-burnt-and-when/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance coin (BNB) burn</a> schedule involves a buyback and burn mechanism whereby the project uses part of its revenue or profits to buy back tokens from the market and burn them. This increases the demand and reduces the supply, creating upward pressure on the price.</p>
<p>When BNB was launched in 2017, a commitment was made to remove 100 million BNB (half of its total supply) from circulation through a burning process. The latest burn (<a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/23rd-bnb-burn-2841286413235339089" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">23rd burn</a>) saw 2,020,132.25 BNB (~$676,744,304).</p>
<h3>Fee burn (Ethereum)</h3>
<p>As Ethereum <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-ethereum-shanghai-shapella-upgrade-everything-you-need-to-know/" data-wpel-link="internal">transitioned to its proof of stake (PoS)</a> consensus algorithm from proof of work (PoW), the community decided to burn part of the fees collected. The EIP-1559 update, introduced in August 2021, burns ether from the fees gathered from validating and verifying the network.</p>
<p>According to Beaconcha, 3252529.9 ETH (~$5,931,837,296.25) have been burned since August 2021, as of writing, reducing the number of ETH tokens in circulation. The designated <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x0000000000000000000000000000000000000000" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">burn address</a> is 0x0000000000000000000000000000000000000000 and does not have a private key, which means any tokens sent there are effectively destroyed.</p>
<h3>Governance burn (Sweat tokens)</h3>
<p>Governance in crypto has been a thing since the launch of decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs) back in 2015, giving token holders power over decisions on the progress of the platform. While some token burns are planned, platforms such as MakerDAO lets the community select whether to burn or not.</p>
<p>Of the available token burning mechanisms, governance vote token burns create the most trusted and interesting kind of token burns. Simply, the community votes on whether to burn tokens and how many tokens to burnt in a democratic way.</p>
<p>One of the interesting token burns through decentralized governance votes in recent times is the SWEAT token’s <a href="https://nearblocks.io/txns/8k3DYBX1S8ciYCa8v94vbr73pbki15bc31phNUo98EKG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April governance vote</a>. Unlike other burning schedules that vote on token burns exclusively, SWEAT introduced a token vs distribution governance vote, allowing the community to vote on whether to burn 100 million SWEAT tokens or distribute them to users with a 12-month growth jar by 25 April.</p>
<p>As expected, the community was divided when it came to choosing one of these two options. With 153,783 users participating in the vote, 91,481 users (59.487%) voted to distribute, while 62,302 users (40.513%) voted to burn tokens. In a first-of-its-kind vote, the 100 million SWEAT tokens were divided as the voters decided, with 59,541,465.013 SWEAT distributed and  40,549,975.987 $SWEAT burned.</p>
<blockquote><p>“It was cool to have the vote in-app and be transparent with the results. I’d like one on a contract next time to be sure,” another SWEAT voter shared.</p></blockquote>
<p>NFTb, an NFT protocol built on the BNB chain carried out its first <a href="https://nftb.io/governance/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">DAO-sanctioned token burn</a> in January,  allowing the community to choose how much of the NFTb the protocol will burn. The community had to select what portion of the total supply of tokens was to be burned, with choices including 5%, 15%, and 25%. The community selected o burn 25% of the tokens, which resulted in a 4X increase in price.</p>
<h3>Algorithmic stablecoin token burns (Terra stablecoin, UST)</h3>
<p>Finally, algorithmic stablecoins also conduct automatic token burns to control the supply of their tokens. For instance, if the demand for an algo token rises and the price loses its peg and goes above $1, the platform will automatically mint new tokens and flood them in the market until the price retracts to $1. Conversely, if the demand for a token falls and the price drops below $1, the platform will automatically buy back tokens and burn them until the price rises back to $1.</p>
<p>One of the most famous algo stablecoin burns is <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/qai/2022/09/20/what-really-happened-to-luna-crypto/?sh=12e63d464ff1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Terra’s UST token</a> which blew up in early 2022. To maintain the price stability of UST, the Terra Network used its native cryptocurrency, LUNA. If the price of UST went above $1, users could burn LUNA tokens to mint UST, increasing the supply and effectively bringing UST back to $1, and vice versa. However, once the price of LUNA collapsed in mid-2022, bringing UST down with it &#8211; losing investors over $60 billion.</p>
<h3>Meme coins burn (SHIBA INU)</h3>
<p>The growing interest in meme coins such as Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and Pepe in recent times has followed, with some of the projects selecting to burn their tokens to reduce their hyper-inflated supply. Late last month, Shiba Inu (the second-largest meme coin) announced it had completed its largest-ever daily token burn, with a record 41 Million SHIB tokens sent to the burn address in a day, on May 24th.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu has had an interesting <a href="https://www.shibburn.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">burn rate schedule</a> since the first burn when Vitalik Buterin, the founder of Ethereum, burned over 90% of SHIB tokens received from the creators of Shiba Inu. In May 2021, Vitalik decided to burn approximately 410 trillion SHIB tokens (or 40% of the total SHIB supply), marking one of the token&#8217;s greatest moments. Shiba Inu prices increased by nearly 40% after Vitalik burned the SHIB tokens.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-221477" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn.jpg" alt="Burn" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Burn-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Token burning is a powerful mechanism that can create value and utility for crypto tokens.</p>
<p>By reducing the supply and increasing the demand for the tokens, token burning can boost their price and scarcity. Nonetheless, there are potential risks to token burning, such as whales taking advantage of the token burn whereby they sell their tokens as soon the token price shoots up a bit, affecting the token&#8217;s value increase.</p>
<p>Additionally, some untrustworthy platforms may rug-pull their community, promising to burn tokens, but in reality, they send the tokens to an accessible wallet.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/understanding-token-burns-and-why-they-are-becoming-so-popular-for-crypto-projects/" rel="nofollow">Understanding Token Burns And Why They Are Becoming So Popular For Crypto Projects</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether (USDT) Market Cap Breaks May 2022 ATH Level of $83.2 Billion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-breaks-may-2022-ath-level-of-83-2-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253360</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Tether_ATH.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Tether_ATH.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While USDT continues to gain market dominance, other stablecoins like BUSD and USDC struggle to sustain their market share.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether (USDT), the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin, achieved a groundbreaking milestone by surpassing its previous all-time high market cap of $83.2 billion, a record set back in May 2022.</p>
<p>This remarkable feat further cements Tether&#8217;s unrivaled dominance in the rapidly expanding stablecoin market, which currently totals an astonishing $130 billion, with USDT&#8217;s market cap surpassing the combined value of its closest competitors.</p>
<h2>USDT Breaks 2022 Market Cap ATH</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-usdt-reaches-all-time-high-surpasses-previous-market-cap-high-of-832b/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> by Tether, the USDT stablecoin had an outstanding performance in Q1 2023 with a net profit of $1.48 billion.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Today&#8217;s numbers demonstrate that people want access to financial freedom, and when given that access, they will make use of it. Tether tokens offer a safe harbor for the unbanked and allow people in emerging markets to keep their buying power, even when their national currency is being devalued,&#8221; said Tether&#8217;s CTO Paolo Ardoino.</p></blockquote>
<p>The company has roughly 85% of its investments in cash, cash equivalents, and short-term deposits. Tether claims USDT has approximately 2.5 billion in excess reserves on top of the 100% minimum reserves and implements a 20% increase in token supply quarter over quarter.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Between our battle-tested resilience in the face of market volatility and our industry-leading transparency practices, Tether has proven that it can be trusted, and customers are responding in kind. We are eager to continue maintaining our laser focus on emerging markets and will not waver in our efforts to expand access to financial freedom globally,&#8221; Ardoino added.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Other Stablecoins Struggle</h2>
<p>USDT&#8217;s new feat comes as other stablecoins struggle to retain their market shares due to regulatory issues and unfavorable economic conditions.</p>
<p>While sharing the Tether update on Twitter, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), the CEO and founder of major crypto exchange Binance, <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1664188463950749696?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noted</a> that USDT saw significant growth after regulators capped Binance USD (BUSD).</p>
<p>Recall that the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-paxos-will-stop-minting-binance-usd-busd/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> stablecoin issuer Paxos to stop minting BUSD over alleged securities law violations in February. The stablecoin saw heavy outflows as investors reacted to the regulatory crackdown, and the asset lost its market cap of $23 billion. BUSD had a market cap of $5.1 billion at writing time, according to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/binance-usd/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>Besides BUSD, Circe-issued USD Coin (USDC), the second-largest stablecoin by market cap, also saw significant outflows in March as investors <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-usdc-outflows-surpassed-10b-since-svb-collapse-tether-dominance-rises/" data-wpel-link="internal">panicked</a> after roughly $3.3 billion of its reserves were stuck at the now-defunct Silicon Valley Bank (SVB).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-usdt-market-cap-breaks-may-2022-ath-level-of-83-2-billion/" rel="nofollow">Tether (USDT) Market Cap Breaks May 2022 ATH Level of $83.2 Billion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Devour and Alterverse Partner to Bring the First Web3 Food Ordering Marketplace to the Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/devour-and-alterverse-partner-to-bring-the-first-web3-food-ordering-marketplace-to-the-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253408</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DevourGO_in_Sky_City_1685562348d4O0CbJDeI.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/DevourGO_in_Sky_City_1685562348d4O0CbJDeI.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Phoenix, AZ, June 1st, 2023] Devour, a pioneering restaurant engagement technology company, is thrilled to announce its strategic partnership with AlterVerse, an innovative force in the gaming industry. The collaboration aims to revolutionize the restaurant and gaming experience by expanding DevourGO, Devour&#8217;s web3-enabled guest engagement platform, to the upcoming release of AlterVerse&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Phoenix, AZ, June 1st, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://devour.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Devour</a>, a pioneering restaurant engagement technology company, is thrilled to announce its strategic partnership with <a href="https://alterverse.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">AlterVerse</a>, an innovative force in the gaming industry. The collaboration aims to revolutionize the restaurant and gaming experience by expanding <a href="https://devourgo.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DevourGO</a>, Devour&#8217;s web3-enabled guest engagement platform, to the upcoming release of AlterVerse&#8217;s Sky City gaming Metaverse.</p>
<p>DevourGO has emerged as a prominent player in token-gating food ordering experiences. It is gaining swift recognition for its innovative approach, which allows users to unlock these experiences by utilizing their digital assets and the native token, DevourPAY ($DPAY), for payments and exclusive rewards on the platform. With this new partnership, DevourGO will extend its offering to include real-world food delivery orders coming from storefronts within AlterVerse’s stunning photorealistic metaverse, Sky City. The integration with AlterVerse will allow DevourGO to unlock a whole new level of immersive restaurant experiences for customers and restaurant brands.</p>
<p>The visionary AlterVerse team, backed by notable entities such as Binance Labs, Polygon Ventures, and Gate.io Labs, is actively building a vibrant global community of gaming enthusiasts. With Sky City, built on Unreal Engine 5, AlterVerse offers an extensive range of experiences that go beyond traditional gaming. Users can play countless games and challenges, design their own homes, engage in high-stakes competition, and shop at many restaurants and retail shops in the central hub. The metaverse is blockchain-driven, allowing users to create, own and sell in-game creations in support of its fun-first gaming mantra.</p>
<p>As part of this partnership, Devour will integrate its DevourGO order platform into Sky City, enabling users to seamlessly order food and beverages from participating restaurants within the virtual realm. As the partnership evolves, players will not only receive real-world food, but their avatars will gain valuable increases in their hunger and thirst meters, which players need to maintain in order to progress in the game. Because the Alterverse community is Global, players will be able to seamlessly order from restaurants local to their physical location.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to partner with Alterverse and expand the reach of DevourGO to the exciting world of AlterVerse&#8217;s Sky City metaverse,&#8221; said Shelly Rupel, CEO at Devour. &#8220;This collaboration represents a significant step forward in enhancing guest engagement for restaurant brands. By combining the immersive experiences of Alterverse with the convenience and efficiency of DevourGO, we are enabling restaurant guests to seamlessly order, dine, and engage in an entirely new way.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As the release of AlterVerse&#8217;s Sky City approaches, Devour and AlterVerse will work closely to ensure seamless integration of DevourGO with the metaverse. Restaurant brands will have the opportunity to leverage the combined power of Devour&#8217;s technology and AlterVerse&#8217;s immersive gaming environment to create unforgettable guest experiences and maximize their reach in the gaming community.</p>
<h2>About Devour</h2>
<p>Devour Inc is a next-gen restaurant engagement technology company dedicated to transforming the way restaurants connect with their guests. Their DevourGO platform utilizes web3 technology to provide community-focused delivery and pick-up ordering services for restaurant brands of all sizes, with on-premise ordering, reservations, and more digital guest engagement solutions coming soon. Included in the Devour ecosystem is DevourPAY $DPAY (https://devour.io/devourpay), the native utility token of the platform, and The Industry Pass (https://devour.io/theindustry) offering exclusive perks and benefits to its community members.</p>
<h2>About AlterVerse</h2>
<p>AlterVerse is a pioneering force in the gaming industry, creating a four-phase metaverse intricately built on Unreal Engine 5. Their upcoming Sky City gaming metaverse offers users the ability to play mini-games and adventures, fly a ‘Copter over the shrouded planet, race a Violator around the Sky City track, and monetize their in-game creations within an expansive, interconnected ecosystem. The metaverse is powered by blockchain technology, VR compatible, and provides players with opportunities for both immersive gameplay and financial reward.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This press release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/devour-and-alterverse-partner-to-bring-the-first-web3-food-ordering-marketplace-to-the-metaverse/" rel="nofollow">Devour and Alterverse Partner to Bring the First Web3 Food Ordering Marketplace to the Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>After Bitcoin&#8217;s First Monthly Decline of 2023, These Are the 3 Key Support Levels</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/after-bitcoins-first-monthly-decline-of-2023-these-are-the-3-key-support-levels/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253354</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Three levels around the $25,300 - $26,300 region is providing Bitcoin with robust support. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s network fundamentals have continued to explode this year. The price side of things, however, has been disappointing recently. With its stagnating since mid-March, concerns about possible downside targets stretching toward $20,000 have emerged.</p>
<p>Despite some encouraging signs in recent months, Bitcoin&#8217;s latest retreat dragged its price below $27,000.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Key Support Areas</h2>
<p>As the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency remained trapped in a narrow range below $30k, Glassnode observed that the spot price remains in close proximity to three significant pricing levels, &#8220;providing robust support around the $25,300 &#8211; $26,300 region.&#8221; The levels in question are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Short-Term Holder Cost-Basis: $26,000</li>
<li>Adjusted Realized Price: $25,300</li>
<li>200 WMA: $26,300</li>
</ul>
<p>According to Glassnode&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1664217187047940097" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">analysis</a>, sustained elevation above these crucial support areas can be deemed as a constructive sign. On the other hand, a drop in Bitcoin&#8217;s price beneath the key levels would infer a weakness in the trend.</p>
<p>The latest data surfaces after the crypto-analytic platform&#8217;s co-founder Negentropic <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-close-to-bullish-breakout-as-bottom-is-in-glassnode-co-founder/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">hinted</a> that the current tight-range consolidation could potentially be nearing an end, implying that BTC will soon hit its bottom and subsequently flip positive.</p>
<p>Moreover, the conviction among the existing BTC holders was found to be &#8220;remarkably high.&#8221; Such a trend can be counted as bullish, despite the crypto-asset&#8217;s slow growth this quarter. This is because such a trend potentially signifies that investors consider the current market condition to be an opportunity.</p>
<p>More recently, the exec <a href="https://twitter.com/Negentropic_/status/1664027740457009153" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a> that FOMC is likely to prove a major catalyst that will drive Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;More chop is expected until ~1 week before FOMC. Keep a close eye on open interest to see how the market is positioning (there is any positioning) going into June 14.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Transition Phase</h2>
<p>Bitcoin appears to have <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-22-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reached</a> a &#8220;transition,&#8221; which should set the stage for the next bull market top, according to Glassnode&#8217;s new research. The long-term investors of the premier crypto-asset are preparing for gains in the near term.</p>
<p>The company found that Bitcoin long-term holders (LTHs) &#8211;  those hodling BTC for at least 155 days &#8211; have started a transition toward a state of &#8220;equilibrium&#8221; before reaching full &#8220;euphoria,&#8221; which typically means that this cohort is preparing for the next BTC price cycle top.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-bitcoins-first-monthly-decline-of-2023-these-are-the-3-key-support-levels/" rel="nofollow">After Bitcoin&#8217;s First Monthly Decline of 2023, These Are the 3 Key Support Levels</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
