<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 23:52:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Multiple Binance Executives Resign Amid CZ&#8217;s Handling Of DOJ Probe: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-binance-executives-resign-amid-czs-handling-of-doj-probe-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259188</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance’s top brass appears to be leaving all at once, but its CEO claims that this is part of regular “turnover.”]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A slew of senior executives at Binance are reportedly fleeing en masse as the company grapples with a massive lawsuit from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and a Justice Department investigation into its CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ).</p>
<p>One executive – former Chief Strategy Officer Patrick Hillman – has already confirmed his departure.</p>
<h2>Chaos In Binance’s Ranks?</h2>
<p>A <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/06/binance-crisis-executives-quit-changpeng-zhao-justice-department/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> from Fortune on Thursday claimed that general counsel Han Ng and SVP for Compliance Steven Christie said they are leaving the company this week, alongside Hillman.</p>
<p>Their exit follows former IRS agent Matthew Price’s recent resignation, who served as Binance’s Global Head of Intelligence and Investigations. One person familiar with the matter told Fortune that the departures are a reaction to CZ’s response to the DOJ’s probe into himself and his exchange.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuit</a> against the firm last month, the SEC alleged that Binance had mishandled client assets between its international platform, U.S. platforms, and other Zhao-controlled firms, while also violating sanctions laws.</p>
<p>Binance has fought such claims made by both <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-refutes-sec-claims-about-mishandling-user-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">regulators</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-responds-to-reuters-claims-about-mixing-user-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal">media outlets</a> for years. One to counter such narratives has often been Patrick Hillman himself, who blasted Reuters in May for claiming that Binance was mixing client funds with its corporate treasury.</p>
<p>“It’s true that I am leaving Binance, but I’m doing so on good terms,” <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1677070523740884992" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> Hillman over Twitter on Thursday. The executive explained that his wife was soon to have their second child, thus he thought it was the “right time to step aside.”</p>
<p>“I continue to respect and support and am grateful for having had the incredible opportunity to work under his leadership,” he added.</p>
<p>Hillman also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mass-layoffs-at-binance-company-admits-to-reevaluating-roles/" data-wpel-link="internal">criticized</a> rumors about “mass layoffs” at Binance in June, claiming the company was not “rightsizing” but simply “reevaluating roles” as part of a regular “talent density audit.”</p>
<h2>CZ Responds</h2>
<p>As with many Binance rumors, CZ responded to reports about executive departures with the number ‘4’ – a Zhao-coined crypto slang term to ignore FUD (fear, uncertainty, and doubt) surrounding his exchange.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">4. More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the “news” are completely wrong.</p>
<p>As an organization that has grown from 30 to 8000 people in 6 years, from 0 to the world’s largest crypto exchange in less than 5 months…</p>
<p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1677092535871602691?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<blockquote><p>“Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the “news” are completely wrong,” he wrote to Twitter. “As markets and the global environment for crypto changes, as our organization evolves, and as personal situations change, there is turnover at every company.”</p></blockquote>
<p>CZ added that the executives did not resign within the same week. “They exaggerate everything,” he said.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multiple-binance-executives-resign-amid-czs-handling-of-doj-probe-report/" rel="nofollow">Multiple Binance Executives Resign Amid CZ&#8217;s Handling Of DOJ Probe: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gauntlet Accused of Sneaking in Previously Rejected Proposal to Adjust CRV LTV to Zero</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gauntlet-accused-of-sneaking-in-previously-rejected-proposal-to-adjust-crv-ltv-to-zero/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 23:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258877</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Curve_Loan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Curve_Loan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gauntlet will remove a proposal to set CRV LTV to zero from its lists of recommendations based on reactions from Aave DAO members.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Gauntlet, a decentralized finance (DeFi) risk management entity, seems to be facing some backlash on its latest proposal on the Aave governance forum after it was accused of fixing in elements of a previous one that was voted down by the community.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The proposal in question seeks to mitigate the risks regarding a loan tagged to Curve Finance founder Michael Egorov.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Egorov&#8217;s $64 Million Loan Draws Attention Again</h2>
<p dir="ltr">A member of the Aave community, Marc Zeller, <a href="https://governance.aave.com/t/arfc-gauntlet-risk-parameter-updates-for-ethereum-v3-arbitrum-v3-ethereum-v2-2023-06-26/13825/3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">opposed</a> one proposal from Gauntlet&#8217;s list of recommendations, which seeks to adjust CRV&#8217;s loan-to-value (LTV) on Aave version two (v2) to zero percent, claiming that the recommendation will cause more harm than good.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;Hello, we agree on all proposed changes but one: setting CRV LTV to zero. This will hurt more than help by removing the ability of CRV holders to increase their collateralization if needed by adding more collateral.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">According to Zeller, Gauntlet was attempting to sneak in the proposed change in its latest risk parameter update, which was already <a href="https://app.aave.com/governance/proposal/?proposalId=246" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">rejected</a> by the Aave community in a previous proposal.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In June, Gauntlet made two recommendations to the Aave governance forum, which were to freeze CRV collateral and adjust CRV LTV to zero on Aave v2. The entity put forth the proposals after accessing a wallet tagged to Curve founder Michael Egorov, which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-founder-repays-1-3m-usdt-of-aave-loan-to-reduce-liquidation-risk-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">borrowed</a> more than $60 million USDT and put up 288,000 CRV tokens as collateral.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Gauntlet, the proposal would prevent the wallet from accumulating more CRV tokens to reduce risk or make the wallet diversify its collateral. Based on <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0x7a16ff8270133f063aab6c9977183d9e72835428/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from the blockchain analytics platform Debank, the loan presently consists of over 281,000 CRV collateral worth more than $220 million to borrow $64 million in USDT, with a health rate of 1.83.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Gauntlet Responds</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Gauntlet, however, refuted Zeller&#8217;s claim while recognizing that the community was strongly against setting CRV LTV to zero. Subsequently, the entity said it would remove any recommendations about CRV in an updated snapshot.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;It looks like the temp check will fail, and we will take that as a definitive signal and continue to balance risk/reward with that in mind across v2. In addition, we will take this as a community preference to unbundle recommendations for assets that are considered sensitive for the community moving forward. In terms of next steps &#8211; we will remove the CRV recommendation and re-run the Snapshot vote without it.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gauntlet-accused-of-sneaking-in-previously-rejected-proposal-to-adjust-crv-ltv-to-zero/" rel="nofollow">Gauntlet Accused of Sneaking in Previously Rejected Proposal to Adjust CRV LTV to Zero</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex Returns Portion Of Assets Stolen From 2016 Hack</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitfinex-returns-portion-of-assets-stolen-from-2016-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 23:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259182</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitfinex_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitfinex_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Recovered assets will immediately be used to compensate Recovery Right Token (RRT) holders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Bitfinex has recovered some of the funds it lost after being hacked in August 2016.</p>
<p>The recovered assets will be used to compensate holders of the exchange’s Recovery Right Tokens (RRTs), which were issued to impacted creditors after the security breach.</p>
<h2>How Much Was Recovered?</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/media-releases/bitfinex-announces-return-of-seized-property-to-rrt-holders/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> by Bitfinex on Thursday, the United States Department of Homeland Security (DHS) has returned $312,219.71 in cash and 6.917 in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) accumulated from ongoing efforts to recover assets from the hack.</p>
<p>“We are extremely pleased to be able to reach another successful milestone in the recovery of assets stolen from Bitfinex in 2016,” said Paolo Ardoino, Chief Technology Officer of Bitfinex.</p>
<p>This month’s specific seizure was conducted by U.S. Customs and Border Protection and will be used to redeem RRT holders. There are 30 million RRT tokens in circulation redeemable for $1 each, meaning authorities still have much more to recover to compensate token holders.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the market price for such tokens surged from $0.7 to $0.9 on Thursday, before retracing to $0.75 at writing time, according to CoinGecko. Buyers of such tokens are effectively betting on Bitfinex’s successful ability to recover assets, in which case they are guaranteed to profit.</p>
<p>After compensating all RRT holders, Bitfinex will use up to 80% of the remaining recovered assets to reward holders of Bitfinex’s utility token, UNUS SED LEO.</p>
<p>“Bitfinex continues to work with relevant law enforcement agencies and through the judicial system to recover property stolen from the exchange during the security breach,” wrote the exchange.</p>
<h2>Bitfinex and the Largest Financial Seizure Ever</h2>
<p>The proceeds still pale in comparison to the 119,756 BTC lost at the time. Worth just north of $71 million at the time, that same stash is now valued at over $3.6 billion.</p>
<p>Thankfully, law enforcement arrested the couple suspected of being behind the hack last year after they attempted to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-60000-btc-worth-2-4b-stolen-in-the-2016-bitfinex-hack-just-moved/" data-wpel-link="internal">move funds</a> between blockchain addresses.</p>
<p>The DOJ recovered most of the associated funds as a result, making history’s l<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/justice-department-recovers-bitfinex-hack-funds-in-largest-ever-financial-seizure/" data-wpel-link="internal">argest-ever financial seizure</a>, and turning the U.S. government into the world’s largest single holder of BTC.</p>
<p>Rumors emerged in May that the government might be selling thousands of Bitcoin gleaned from both its Bitfinex and Silk Road seizures, but <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-fake-news-lead-to-bitcoins-recent-crash-cryptoquant-chips-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">on-chain data</a> proved such rumors false.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitfinex-returns-portion-of-assets-stolen-from-2016-hack/" rel="nofollow">Bitfinex Returns Portion Of Assets Stolen From 2016 Hack</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Withdraws ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8216;Browse With Bing&#8217; Feature Amid Copyright and Privacy Concerns</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/openai-withdraws-chatgpts-browse-with-bing-feature-amid-copyright-and-privacy-concerns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 22:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259009</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus is programmed to access the latest online information, which, reportedly, resulted in inadvertently accessing protected content. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OpenAI has disabled Browse With Bing, the internet surfing feature available to ChatGPT Plus users. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a tweet thread, OpenAI reasoned that the Browse feature can occasionally produce results in a manner that it doesn&#8217;t want it to.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Straying Into Protected Content  </span></h2>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We&#8217;ve learned that ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8220;Browse&#8221; beta can occasionally display content in ways we don&#8217;t want, e.g. if a user specifically asks for a URL&#8217;s full text, it may inadvertently fulfill this request. We are disabling Browse while we fix this—want to do right by content owners,&#8221; the ChatGPT maker <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1676072388436594688" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> in a tweet. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">News reports said the development follows revelations that the AI chatbot could circumvent paywall protections on websites and inadvertently produce results that are supposed to be available exclusively to qualified users. It was possible because </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ChatGPT Plus users can access a more powerful ChatGPT-4, which leverages up-to-date information online. The basic version of ChatGPT provides results based on information until September 2021. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides, ChatGPT Plus has access to Plugin Store and Browse with Bing, which has now been disabled. ChatGPT-4, with the help of some plugins, can breach protected areas of websites, which is both embarrassing and illegal. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Already in Legal Trouble </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OpenAI is already facing <a href="https://www.searchenginejournal.com/chatgpt-creator-faces-multiple-lawsuits-over-copyright-privacy-violations/490686/#close" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lawsuits</a> for copyright and privacy violations. One filed in the federal court in San Francisco alleges that the company copied text from books without consent, compensation, or credit to the entities holding the copyright. Another lawsuit charged the company with collecting people&#8217;s personal information online.  </span></p>
<p>However, ChatGPT itself has been a victim of data theft. A Group-IB report in June <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-chatgpt-accounts-leak-over-100000-credentials-leaked-according-to-cybersec-firm/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the personal data of about 100,000 ChatGPT users has been stolen and sold on the dark net.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ChatGPT Plus is a beta version of the chatbot, primarily meant to test and collect feedback. Recalling the Browse with Bing feature, OpenAI thanked the subscribers for helping it test the application. </span></p>
<h2>It’s Beta Version</h2>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Very grateful to the ChatGPT Plus subscribers who have been helping us test the browsing feature. This is why we started with a beta—have received extremely valuable feedback, learned a lot, &amp; will bring it back soon,&#8221; OpenAI <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1676072390273695744?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> in the tweet thread. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, some leaked documents disclosed that ChatGPT has been working to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-upgrade-may-bring-workspaces-file-uploading-and-enhanced-user-profile-features-to-chatgpt/" data-wpel-link="internal">offer</a> file uploading, enhanced profile, workspace, and organization management features.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openai-withdraws-chatgpts-browse-with-bing-feature-amid-copyright-and-privacy-concerns/" rel="nofollow">OpenAI Withdraws ChatGPT&#8217;s &#8216;Browse With Bing&#8217; Feature Amid Copyright and Privacy Concerns</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi&#8217;s Bankruptcy Plans Faces Stiff Opposition From FTX</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockfis-bankruptcy-plans-faces-stiff-opposition-from-ftx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258969</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/BlockFi_FTX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/BlockFi_FTX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BlockFi's newly proposed plan faces opposition from FTX.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no respite for BlockFi as the bankrupt crypto lender struggles to pay its creditors and customers.</p>
<p>BlockFi has brought forward several proposals since sliding into bankruptcy last year owing to the market turmoil. However, FTX&#8217;s latest legal <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/blockfi/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTU1MTY5Mw==&amp;id2=-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a> poses a hurdle for the now-defunct company as it accuses BlockFi of abusing the planning process.</p>
<ul>
<li>FTX said that the newly proposed plan attempts to avoid substantial claims against BlockFi.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Yet the BlockFi Debtors believe some bankruptcy wand can be waived to make the FTX Debtors’ claims disappear incident to their recently amended liquidating chapter 11 plan dated June 28, 2023 (the “Liquidating Plan”),4 and that they can do so without satisfying basic procedural fairness and due process requirements. This is abuse of the plan process.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>FTX also mentioned repayments and collateral with regards to a loan with its sister trading arm Alameda Research, in addition to $1 billion in collateral pledges made by Emergent Fidelity, a company established by former boss Sam Bankman-Fried to hold Robinhood shares.</li>
<li>The filing also asserted that BlockFi may have claims against FTX which the latter&#8217;s lawyers are expected to object to.</li>
<li>Besides FTX, Three Arrows Capital (3AC) has also opposed BlockFi&#8217;s bankruptcy plan and claims that the latter owes it more than $220 million.</li>
<li>The Singapore-based crypto hedge fund had earlier argued that it wasn’t provided the opportunity to challenge fraud allegations. Its liquidators are seeking to recover $1.3 billion from the founders.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfis-bankruptcy-plans-faces-stiff-opposition-from-ftx/" rel="nofollow">BlockFi&#8217;s Bankruptcy Plans Faces Stiff Opposition From FTX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Memecoin Sees Renewed Market Demand: Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-shib-memecoin-sees-renewed-market-demand-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258924</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/shibainu_downtrend_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SHIB has declined considerably this year and was up by a mere 5% over the past week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The memecoin resurgence appears to have faded, but that has not stopped the Shiba Inu token (SHIB) from stealing some of the limelight. On July 5th, SHIB was one of the tokens accounting for the highest transaction fees, which was indicative of a surge in activity around it.</p>
<p>Recent data suggest that the SHIB network has recorded significant growth. Another underlying trend that supports the bullish narrative is that the asset&#8217;s supply on exchanges is hovering close to the lowest level since 2022.</p>
<h2>Shiba Inu&#8217;s Market Buzz</h2>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1676822399575265283" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">analysis</a> conducted by Santiment, Shiba Inu (SHIB) saw a big rise in new daily addresses created on Wednesday. Despite the underwhelming price performance, the network consistently recorded over 2,500 per day in the past few weeks.</p>
<p>On further evaluation, the crypto analytic firm said the current focus on SHIB could be interpreted as a sign of market saturation or possible future decline. On the flip side, the trend could breathe new life into a previously &#8220;under-the-radar&#8221; token, as per Santiment.</p>
<p>It is also important to note that the daily active addresses for SHIB were lackluster before this surge in interest, which essentially demonstrates a &#8220;newfound&#8221; demand for the token.</p>
<h2>Shibarium Highlights</h2>
<p>The price of SHIB has heavily retraced this year. But the developments surrounding Shibarium updates have managed to catalyze small rallies for the memecoin. Recently, a new functionality was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-pumps-after-lead-developer-shares-shibarium-update-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> that will affect NFTs within the upcoming Shibarium &#8211; the metaverse and NFT-focused layer 2 blockchain expected to go live later this year.</p>
<p>According to the updates by developer Shytoshi Kusama, the upcoming blockchain will include blockchain gaming, &#8220;decentralized&#8221; entertainment, account abstraction, and international governance, among others.</p>
<p>In an attempt to push prices up, SHIB&#8217;s burn mechanism has been slowly reducing the token supply. But the price has not reacted notably to the burns so far. Hence, the launch of the project&#8217;s layer 2 is expected to increase its burn rate capacity to trillions each month.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/ShibaArchives/status/1675611600596656130" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Speculations</a> are rife in the SHIB community about Shibarium <a href="https://twitter.com/kukitorc151/status/1674751985700986882" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">boosting</a> the burn rate, even as the team behind the ecosystem has not divulged any information regarding the same.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-shib-memecoin-sees-renewed-market-demand-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Memecoin Sees Renewed Market Demand: Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale: The Trending Presale Opportunity in 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-the-trending-presale-opportunity-in-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 18:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259150</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-06_21-11-34.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/photo_2023-07-06_21-11-34.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Meme coins are a very hot topic in the cryptocurrency field, and some of them have been known for their explosive growth. One trending meme coin that’s currently going through its presale is Alex The Doge (ALEX), and some analysts seem to be optimistic about its potential for success. The unique features and strong foundation [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins are a very hot topic in the cryptocurrency field, and some of them have been known for their explosive growth.</p>
<p>One trending meme coin that’s currently going through its presale is <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Alex The Doge (ALEX)</a>, and some analysts seem to be optimistic about its potential for success. The unique features and strong foundation of ALEX have garnered attention and support from experts in the field. Their backing further amplifies the hype surrounding the presale.</p>
<p>Let’s unravel what causes the excitement surrounding ALEX and how you can be a part of the best presale of 2023.</p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;VISIT $ALEX PRESALE NOW&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</a></p>
<h2>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Momentum</h2>
<p>With over 15.7 Million tokens sold the Alex The Doge (ALEX) community is buzzing with excitement as the presale gains momentum. A dedicated decentralized exchange (DEX), MEME Swap, has been built on the <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Alex The Doge (ALEX)</a> platform, allowing community members to easily access ALEX and other gaming assets. Completing gaming challenges within the ecosystem offers the opportunity to earn other community-based tokens, such as SHIB and DOGE, as rewards.</p>
<p>The ALEX presale is an opportunity for early adopters and enthusiasts to get their hands on this token. With a maximum supply of only 1 billion ALEX, the presale offers a chance to secure your stake in the future of De-Fi and gaming. The presale is live now, and the excitement is growing among the crypto community.</p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;VISIT $ALEX PRESALE NOW&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</a></p>
<h2>How to Join the ALEX Presale &#8211; 3 Easy Steps</h2>
<p>Participating in the Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale is a straightforward process that can be completed in just three easy steps:</p>
<p>Visit ALEX Website: To join the presale, visit the Alex The Doge (ALEX) website and check out the button that allows to “Buy ALEX”. This will grant access to the payment stages and ensure a secure transaction.</p>
<p>Confirm Entry: Once the user selects “BUY ALEX” and enters the desired amount of ALEX tokens they wish to purchase, they can also proceed with the payment process. The initial presale price is 0.0084 USD per ALEX token.</p>
<p>Join Community: After completing the payment process, users can verify their account information to become a part of the ALEX community. This will grant them access to promotional bonuses and allow them to engage with fellow ALEX enthusiasts across various social media platforms.</p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;VISIT $ALEX PRESALE NOW&lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</a></p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>As the Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale continues to captivate the crypto community, the presale continues trending on. Offering unique features within the MiracleVerse, Alex The Doge (ALEX) is set to redefine the world of Play-To-Earn Gaming and Social-Fi.</p>
<p>For more information about Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale use the links down below:</p>
<ul>
<li>Website: <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://alexthedoge.live/</a></li>
<li>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://t.me/alexthedoge</a></li>
<li>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e</a></li>
<li><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-the-trending-presale-opportunity-in-2023/" rel="nofollow">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale: The Trending Presale Opportunity in 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will XRP Crash to $0.40? Bears Maintain Control (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-xrp-crash-to-0-40-bears-maintain-control-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259070</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price action has been choppy lately, especially against USD. Against BTC, though, things are looking interesting in the short term. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: Against USD, the price has been consolidating in a narrow range between $0.45 and $0.5. The 50-day moving average, currently around $0.5, is currently pushing the cryptocurrency [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price action has been choppy lately, especially against USD. Against BTC, though, things are looking interesting in the short term.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><strong>Edris</strong></a></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>Against USD, the price has been consolidating in a narrow range between $0.45 and $0.5. The 50-day moving average, currently around $0.5, is currently pushing the cryptocurrency lower. If XRP drops toward the $0.43 level, the 200-day moving average near that price is expected to provide strong support.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if XRP  breaks above the 50-day moving average, investors could be optimistic as the $0.6 resistance is likely to be tested.</p>
<p>This scenario could be ideal for Ripple as the market might enter a mid-term bullish phase after months of consolidation.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259075" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259075" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259075 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0607231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-6-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259075" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The market has been trending downward lately. The price has been on a free-fall since the breakdown of the 1,800 SAT level and the 200-day and 50-day moving averages earlier in June.</p>
<p>However, the key 1,500 SAT support zone is currently holding the XRP price from further drops. Additionally, the 50-day and 200-day moving averages printed a bullish crossover a few days back, increasing the probability of a rebound in the short term.</p>
<p>The RSI is also showing values close to the oversold area, boosting the chances of a bullish reversal in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>However, despite these positive signals from indicators, the price action remains bearish, and there is still a high probability of a bearish breakout below the 1,500 SAT level, which could lead to a subsequent crash toward the 1,300 SAT zone in a short period of time.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259074" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259074" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259074 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0607232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-6-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259074" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-xrp-crash-to-0-40-bears-maintain-control-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Will XRP Crash to $0.40? Bears Maintain Control (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s the Imminent Support to Watch as Bitcoin Tumbles Below $31K (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-imminent-support-to-watch-as-bitcoin-tumbles-below-31k-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259077</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin has been struggling to surpass the significant resistance region of $30K for some time now, despite an overall bullish outlook. Recent price movements have shown bearish signals that could potentially lead to a short-term reversal. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish rally has come to a halt upon reaching the crucial [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been struggling to surpass the significant resistance region of $30K for some time now, despite an overall bullish outlook. Recent price movements have shown bearish signals that could potentially lead to a short-term reversal.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s bullish rally has come to a halt upon reaching the crucial resistance region of $30K. This price range holds significant psychological resistance and has acted as a major barrier to the price for several months.</p>
<p>However, there are indications of a double-top bearish reversal pattern forming in conjunction with declining and weakening bullish momentum. This suggests the possibility of a reversal and a consolidation phase before the market determines its next direction.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that if the price is rejected at this critical resistance, a drop toward the dynamic support level of the 100-day moving average at $28K becomes highly likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259079" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259079" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259079 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0607231" width="2560" height="1324" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-768x397.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-1536x795.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-2048x1060.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259079" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>In the 4-hour timeframe, the diminished bullish momentum becomes more apparent as the price has been consolidating around the $30K mark for an extended period. Following a prolonged period of consolidation, a bearish double-top pattern has emerged, causing a slight decline as selling pressure outweighs demand.</p>
<p>However, it is important to wait for confirmation of the double-top pattern, which requires the price to fall below the neckline at $29.8K. If successful, Bitcoin&#8217;s next target would be the static support region at $27.5K.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it is worth mentioning that a clear bearish divergence is visible between the RSI indicator and the price, increasing the likelihood of a short-term downturn.</p>
<p>In summary, Bitcoin is currently facing significant resistance at the $30K level, accompanied by bearish signals and weakening bullish momentum. A reversal and consolidation phase may be in the cards, potentially leading to a short-term decline.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259078" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259078" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259078 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0607232" width="2560" height="1324" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-768x397.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-1536x795.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-2048x1060.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259078" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been on a strong bullish rally since the start of 2023, leading to profitable returns for many investors. The NUPL metric, illustrated on the chart, represents the disparity between market cap and realized cap divided by market cap. Essentially, this metric serves as an indicator of the proportion of investors who are in a profitable state.</p>
<p>Values above 0 indicate that investors are making profits, and a rising trend suggests an increasing number of investors entering the profitable zone. The recent upward movement in the NUPL metric, which reached its previous high from April, implies that more investors are now experiencing profitable returns. This serves as a significant indication of the prevailing bullish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>Consequently, if the metric surpasses its previous high simultaneously with further price appreciation, it would generate heightened buying pressure and establish an unequivocally bullish market condition.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259080" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259080" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259080 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_nupl_chart_0607231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Net-Unrealized-Profit_Loss-NUPL-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259080" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-imminent-support-to-watch-as-bitcoin-tumbles-below-31k-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s the Imminent Support to Watch as Bitcoin Tumbles Below $31K (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Fails at $2K But WIll Bulls Attempt Another Push? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-fails-at-2k-but-will-bulls-attempt-another-push-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259071</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After surpassing the 100-day moving average and retracing in the form of a pullback, Ethereum&#8217;s price initiated a rally that reached the resistance level of $2K. However, it has now temporarily paused, resulting in a consolidation phase around this crucial resistance. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Ethereum&#8217;s price successfully broke above the 100-day [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After surpassing the 100-day moving average and retracing in the form of a pullback, Ethereum&#8217;s price initiated a rally that reached the resistance level of $2K. However, it has now temporarily paused, resulting in a consolidation phase around this crucial resistance.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price successfully broke above the 100-day moving average and the upper trendline of the descending channel, subsequently retesting them during a pullback. This led to increased buying pressure and a significant price rise, reaching the critical resistance region of $2K.</p>
<p>However, due to the prevailing selling pressure around this vital level, the price faced rejection and began consolidating. Notably, the $2K zone aligns with a prior major swing in Ethereum&#8217;s worth, making it a formidable barrier.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259082" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259082" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259082 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_0607231" width="2560" height="1324" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-768x397.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-1536x795.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-2048x1060.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-DAily-2-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259082" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Analyzing the 4-hour timeframe, it becomes evident that the momentum of the rally has weakened, and the price has formed a bearish head and shoulders reversal pattern. This suggests a bearish outlook for the price in the short-term, potentially leading to minor rejections.</p>
<p>On the other hand, as a result of the recent price drop, Ethereum has reached an ascending trendline (indicated in green) and is on the verge of breaking below it. If the price falls below the trendline, which currently acts as support, a cascade toward the significant support zone of $1.7K becomes highly likely.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Ethereum&#8217;s price appears to be confined within a static range between the $2K resistance and the $1.7K support zones, undergoing consolidation for the mid-term perspective.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259081" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259081" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259081 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_0607232" width="2560" height="1324" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-768x397.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-1536x795.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-2048x1060.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259081" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingVIew</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">On-chain Analysis</span></p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has recently undergone a significant upward movement following a period of consolidation. This upward momentum is likely to attract the attention of investors and traders, especially those involved in the perpetual futures market who engage in speculative trading.</p>
<p>The Open Interest Metric, which measures the number of active futures positions, has shown a slight increase and reached its two-month high. This suggests that there could be higher market volatility due to a greater possibility of both long and short positions being liquidated.</p>
<p>As a result, it seems reasonable to anticipate a continued upward trend in the medium term, as the futures market has not yet reached an overheated state. However, it is important to consider that this potential uptrend may also coincide with increased volatility characterized by sudden and significant price fluctuations.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that unforeseen events could disrupt the current scenario and impact the market dynamics. Therefore, it is essential to monitor any developments that may influence Ethereum&#8217;s price movement and market sentiment.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259083" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259083" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259083 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_open_interest_chart_0607231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Open-Interest-All-Exchanges-All-Symbol-EMA-7-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259083" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-fails-at-2k-but-will-bulls-attempt-another-push-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Fails at $2K But WIll Bulls Attempt Another Push? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
