<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:37:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[DeFi platform Injective reveals $150 million ecosystem initiative]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/defi-platform-injective-reveals-150-million-ecosystem-initiative</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cos.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/defi-platform-injective-reveals-150-million-ecosystem-initiative</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>DeFi smart contracts blockchain platform Injective announces a $150 million ecosystem fund to promote building of interoperable infrastructure and DeFi on Cosmos.</p>
<p>The ecosystem fund announced by Injective a short time ago is designed to support developers who are building on the Cosmos Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fund is backed by a consortium of VC and Web3 companies, including Pantera Capital, Kraken Ventures, Jump Crypto, Kucoin Ventures, Delphi Labs, Flow Traders, Gate Labs and IDG Capital.</p>
<p>The members of the consortium will support projects that are building in some key areas of the Cosmos ecosystem, which include, interoperability, DeFi, trading, PoS infrastructure and scalability solutions.</p>
<p>Injective has been drawing eyes over time as it has become one of the most interoperable networks with access to Cosmos IBC enabled chains, as well as Ethereum.</p>
<p>It is a fully decentralised smart contracts platform with a focus on finance applications. Its plug and play modules can be used by developers to build protocols for exchanges, options, derivatives, and lending.</p>
<p>Eric Chen, co-founder and CEO of Injective Labs said:</p>

<p>"We're thrilled to see some of the largest names in the industry joining Injective's mission to create a more democratized financial system through decentralization. Developer activity on Injective is rapidly increasing with major projects and this new ecosystem fund will provide unmatched opportunities for new builders entering Web3 and the Cosmos ecosystem overall."</p>

<p>One of the first uses of the new ecosystem fund is the launch of an &ldquo;Injective Global Virtual Hackathon&rdquo;, which aims to encourage developers from across the world to learn how to build on Injective, but also to submit new proposals for funding.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DeFi smart contracts blockchain platform Injective announces a $150 million ecosystem fund to promote building of interoperable infrastructure and DeFi on Cosmos.</p>
<p>The ecosystem fund announced by Injective a short time ago is designed to support developers who are building on the Cosmos Network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fund is backed by a consortium of VC and Web3 companies, including Pantera Capital, Kraken Ventures, Jump Crypto, Kucoin Ventures, Delphi Labs, Flow Traders, Gate Labs and IDG Capital.</p>
<p>The members of the consortium will support projects that are building in some key areas of the Cosmos ecosystem, which include, interoperability, DeFi, trading, PoS infrastructure and scalability solutions.</p>
<p>Injective has been drawing eyes over time as it has become one of the most interoperable networks with access to Cosmos IBC enabled chains, as well as Ethereum.</p>
<p>It is a fully decentralised smart contracts platform with a focus on finance applications. Its plug and play modules can be used by developers to build protocols for exchanges, options, derivatives, and lending.</p>
<p>Eric Chen, co-founder and CEO of Injective Labs said:</p>

<p>"We're thrilled to see some of the largest names in the industry joining Injective's mission to create a more democratized financial system through decentralization. Developer activity on Injective is rapidly increasing with major projects and this new ecosystem fund will provide unmatched opportunities for new builders entering Web3 and the Cosmos ecosystem overall."</p>

<p>One of the first uses of the new ecosystem fund is the launch of an &ldquo;Injective Global Virtual Hackathon&rdquo;, which aims to encourage developers from across the world to learn how to build on Injective, but also to submit new proposals for funding.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Given at 23165 - 26 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-at-23165-26-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-25-january-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-at-23165-26-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Awaits Fresh Technical Sentiment:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 26 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 22326.24 area after encountering fresh selling pressure around the 23165.36 area, representing a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 23375.60 to 22298.15.&nbsp; The fresh 5-month high also represented a test of the 23300.64 area, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that strengthened around the 20333.33 area.&nbsp; BTC/USD recently appreciated to the 23375.60 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 22042.59 area during the recent appreciation, an upside price objective related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 and 17927.36 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 23544, 23808, 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 21711, 20682, 19850, 19019, 17989, and 17834 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22001.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22819.97.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Awaits Fresh Technical Sentiment:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 26 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) awaited fresh technical sentiment early in the Asian session as the pair came off to the 22326.24 area after encountering fresh selling pressure around the 23165.36 area, representing a test of the 78.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 23375.60 to 22298.15.&nbsp; The fresh 5-month high also represented a test of the 23300.64 area, an upside price objective related to buying pressure that strengthened around the 20333.33 area.&nbsp; BTC/USD recently appreciated to the 23375.60 area, its strongest print since August 2022.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 22042.59 area during the recent appreciation, an upside price objective related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 and 17927.36 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 16326.16 area include the 23544, 23808, 25455, 25774, 27609, and 28004 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to buying pressure around the 15460 area include the 23980, 24224, 26612, 26931, 29244, and 29639 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the recent move higher to multi-month highs, technical support levels and areas of potential buying pressure are around the 21711, 20682, 19850, 19019, 17989, and 17834 levels.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 21437, 20874, 20724, 20370, 20233, 20026, 19153, 18448, and 18253 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, technically significant areas include the 15900, 15512, 15313, 14500, 14364, 13369, 10727, 10432, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 22001.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 22819.97.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18390.99/ 16714.46/ 14500.15 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;23544.62/ 24224.60/ 25455.06 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Miner US Limited provide a reliable hash  USDT cloud mining]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/miner-us-limited-provide-a-reliable-hash-usdt-cloud-mining</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-161210.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/miner-us-limited-provide-a-reliable-hash-usdt-cloud-mining</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin was one of the most lucrative business opportunities available in the blockchain industry up until a few years ago. Currently, this is not the case. However, as more people entered the mining sector, the level of competition increased, which resulted in a decrease in profitability. Because the amount of computing power required to solve challenging cryptographic mathematical equations increases with the number of competitors, which results in a smaller profit margin for the business. </p>
<p>In addition, mining requires an initial investment of a significant amount of money, the installation of loud mining equipment in an area that has adequate ventilation, and a significant monthly investment in the cost of energy. Customers also have the option to adopt a mining service that is hosted in the cloud, which eliminates the complications and obstacles that were previously mentioned.</p>
<p>The first option that comes to mind is Miner US, which is widely regarded as one of the cloud mining industry's most effective and forward-thinking services while also preserving a reputation for exceptional ease of use. Customers can rent mining rigs from a service provider using cloud mining. After making the appropriate plan selection, paying the required fees, and getting started mining cryptocurrency, customers can start earning cryptocurrency. Take a look at this video to get a better understanding of Miner US Limited.</p>
<p>What is Miner US?</p>
<p>Miner US Limited has been successful in launching the Miner US platform, which enables investors to increase the transparency of the global financial, consumer, and internet infrastructure by leveraging digital assets and blockchains. This was accomplished through the use of blockchain technology. Miner US is a trustworthy platform that is well-known in the industry and regularly audited. Miner US possesses the legal authorization necessary to commence business operations, as well as the approval of the New York State Government. As a consequence of this, Miner US has been successful in convincing all of its users that it is a genuine and reliable platform, which has led to a significant increase in the size of its user base.</p>
<p>It is essential to pick a plan that satisfies the requirements of a high hash rate while remaining within a reasonable price range. The best part is that Miner US offers a variety of memberships, so potential miners from all walks of life are able to begin their path to success in the mining industry. This is the best thing that Miner US has to offer. Every plan, regardless of whether it lasts for 150 days or a lifetime, comes with a certain amount of mining power already included.</p>
<p>Why is Miner US the best option for you?</p>
<p>In case you were curious about the matter, the answer is "yes,&rdquo; moving your business to Miner US does come with a number of benefits, and here are a few of them:</p>
● Customers are required to spend several thousand dollars on an expensive setup that includes a miner, a cooling system, and a high-performance central processing unit when they construct a mining rig. This setup consists of the three components listed above. This configuration is made up of the following parts and pieces: Using Miner US is one way to avoid all of this, and getting started is simple and won't take too much time.
● Because everything can be done on a computer, there is no need to set aside space in the home or garage for a mining setup when using Miner US. This is because everything can be done on the computer. The procedure can be carried out in its entirety using a computer.
● Dashboard with simple navigation: The cloud dashboard provided by Miner US is uncluttered and straightforward, enabling customers to quickly validate the total income, offered hash rate, and monthly fee. This is made possible as a result of the accessibility of the dashboard.
● The mining of cryptocurrencies requires a significant amount of electricity, which leads to an increase in the amount of power that is consumed. This has a detrimental effect on the natural world if recyclable energy sources are not utilized instead. The mining of Bitcoin does not have a negative impact on the environment. Miner US has responded to the challenge by putting in place the mining rigs that are the most powerful and effective ones that are currently available. These systems have the ability to produce the highest output with the lowest possible amount of energy consumption.
● The platform is dedicated to providing a staff of conscientious specialists who are available to assist customers with their challenges and requirements twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week. One more advantage of using a cloud mining service is that the mining process with Miner US is the quickest.
<p>In the event that you have not already done so, sign up for Miner US right away so that you can witness firsthand the significant advances that it will bring to the field of cloud mining. The process is straightforward, and it shouldn't take too much time to get everything up and running properly.</p>
<p>How does Miner US referral rebate work?</p>
<p>When someone who is already a part of Miner US wants to invite a friend to join, they can do so by giving them an invitation code or a link to the site. In the "My Team" section of your account, you will be able to see your friend's profile once they have finished signing. Then they'll need to allocate more resources to acquire the necessary hash rate power. Only if the funds are spent on offline computer power are you eligible to take part in the commission dividend, which can be anywhere from 5% to 12% of the purchase price.</p>
<p>You can get more information about Miner US by going to the official website of the company and looking at the various pricing options that are listed on the website. Please visit the registration page if you are interested in becoming a member of Miner US. You should also make sure that you are following Miner US on all of its social groups and channels so that you can stay up to date with the most recent changes.</p>
<p class="s9">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram Channel | Telegram Group | Facebook Page | Twitter</p>
<p class="s9">Youtube Channel | White Paper | License &amp; Certificate</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mining bitcoin was one of the most lucrative business opportunities available in the blockchain industry up until a few years ago. Currently, this is not the case. However, as more people entered the mining sector, the level of competition increased, which resulted in a decrease in profitability. Because the amount of computing power required to solve challenging cryptographic mathematical equations increases with the number of competitors, which results in a smaller profit margin for the business. </p>
<p>In addition, mining requires an initial investment of a significant amount of money, the installation of loud mining equipment in an area that has adequate ventilation, and a significant monthly investment in the cost of energy. Customers also have the option to adopt a mining service that is hosted in the cloud, which eliminates the complications and obstacles that were previously mentioned.</p>
<p>The first option that comes to mind is Miner US, which is widely regarded as one of the cloud mining industry's most effective and forward-thinking services while also preserving a reputation for exceptional ease of use. Customers can rent mining rigs from a service provider using cloud mining. After making the appropriate plan selection, paying the required fees, and getting started mining cryptocurrency, customers can start earning cryptocurrency. Take a look at this video to get a better understanding of Miner US Limited.</p>
<p>What is Miner US?</p>
<p>Miner US Limited has been successful in launching the Miner US platform, which enables investors to increase the transparency of the global financial, consumer, and internet infrastructure by leveraging digital assets and blockchains. This was accomplished through the use of blockchain technology. Miner US is a trustworthy platform that is well-known in the industry and regularly audited. Miner US possesses the legal authorization necessary to commence business operations, as well as the approval of the New York State Government. As a consequence of this, Miner US has been successful in convincing all of its users that it is a genuine and reliable platform, which has led to a significant increase in the size of its user base.</p>
<p>It is essential to pick a plan that satisfies the requirements of a high hash rate while remaining within a reasonable price range. The best part is that Miner US offers a variety of memberships, so potential miners from all walks of life are able to begin their path to success in the mining industry. This is the best thing that Miner US has to offer. Every plan, regardless of whether it lasts for 150 days or a lifetime, comes with a certain amount of mining power already included.</p>
<p>Why is Miner US the best option for you?</p>
<p>In case you were curious about the matter, the answer is "yes,&rdquo; moving your business to Miner US does come with a number of benefits, and here are a few of them:</p>
● Customers are required to spend several thousand dollars on an expensive setup that includes a miner, a cooling system, and a high-performance central processing unit when they construct a mining rig. This setup consists of the three components listed above. This configuration is made up of the following parts and pieces: Using Miner US is one way to avoid all of this, and getting started is simple and won't take too much time.
● Because everything can be done on a computer, there is no need to set aside space in the home or garage for a mining setup when using Miner US. This is because everything can be done on the computer. The procedure can be carried out in its entirety using a computer.
● Dashboard with simple navigation: The cloud dashboard provided by Miner US is uncluttered and straightforward, enabling customers to quickly validate the total income, offered hash rate, and monthly fee. This is made possible as a result of the accessibility of the dashboard.
● The mining of cryptocurrencies requires a significant amount of electricity, which leads to an increase in the amount of power that is consumed. This has a detrimental effect on the natural world if recyclable energy sources are not utilized instead. The mining of Bitcoin does not have a negative impact on the environment. Miner US has responded to the challenge by putting in place the mining rigs that are the most powerful and effective ones that are currently available. These systems have the ability to produce the highest output with the lowest possible amount of energy consumption.
● The platform is dedicated to providing a staff of conscientious specialists who are available to assist customers with their challenges and requirements twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week. One more advantage of using a cloud mining service is that the mining process with Miner US is the quickest.
<p>In the event that you have not already done so, sign up for Miner US right away so that you can witness firsthand the significant advances that it will bring to the field of cloud mining. The process is straightforward, and it shouldn't take too much time to get everything up and running properly.</p>
<p>How does Miner US referral rebate work?</p>
<p>When someone who is already a part of Miner US wants to invite a friend to join, they can do so by giving them an invitation code or a link to the site. In the "My Team" section of your account, you will be able to see your friend's profile once they have finished signing. Then they'll need to allocate more resources to acquire the necessary hash rate power. Only if the funds are spent on offline computer power are you eligible to take part in the commission dividend, which can be anywhere from 5% to 12% of the purchase price.</p>
<p>You can get more information about Miner US by going to the official website of the company and looking at the various pricing options that are listed on the website. Please visit the registration page if you are interested in becoming a member of Miner US. You should also make sure that you are following Miner US on all of its social groups and channels so that you can stay up to date with the most recent changes.</p>
<p class="s9">Registration Link | Official Website | Telegram Channel | Telegram Group | Facebook Page | Twitter</p>
<p class="s9">Youtube Channel | White Paper | License &amp; Certificate</p>
<p class="s10">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Saudi Central Bank Continues Testing on its CBDC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/saudi-central-bank-continues-testing-on-its-cbdc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/saudi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/saudi-central-bank-continues-testing-on-its-cbdc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Saudi Arabia Central Bank (SAMA) announced that it is continuing its experiment with a central bank digital currency (CBDC). </p>
<p>SAMA announced in a press release earlier in the week that it is stepping up its research into a CBDC but has not said anything regarding its deployment. The bank&rsquo;s press release stated that it was working on a project that &ldquo;focuses on domestic wholesale CBDC use cases in collaboration with local banks and fintechs.&rdquo; The bank, however, reiterated that no conclusive decision had been reached to launch a CBDC:</p>

<p>SAMA stresses that although no decision has been made regarding the introduction of CBDC in the Kingdom, it continues to focus on exploring the benefits and potential risks of implementing CBDC, which will contribute to informed decision-making within SAMA and to CBDC explorations within the central banking community.</p>

<p>The Central Bank further stated that it tests the economic impact of implementing a CBDC and its market readiness and fast applications of CBDC-based payment solutions. SAMA said that it will continue testing the viability of a CBDC to achieve its Saudi Vision 2030 objectives but will consider &ldquo;policy, legal and regulatory considerations&rdquo; before it continues with the project.</p>
<p>The governor of SAMA, H.E. Fahad Almubarak, further stated that local banks and payment companies would be the foundation of the project and its implementation. He added that SAMA had approached local banks and fintechs, along with other market players and third-party consulting and technology providers, to comprehensively understand such a currency&rsquo;s functionality and test different design options.</p>
<p>The press release also added:</p>

<p>SAMA is set to continue with its research on CBDC while consulting with relative international bodies, local government entities, and the public. Additionally, SAMA will continue to experiment with CBDC solutions as an infrastructure enabler of innovation in financial services that has the potential to contribute to a more resilient payment ecosystem and accelerate digital transformation in the local financial sector.</p>

<p>SAMA successfully undertook a CBDC experiment in 2019 in collaboration with the Central Bank of the UAE to explore if distributed ledger technology, or blockchain, &ldquo;could contribute to seamless cross-border payments.&rdquo; The experiment was dubbed &ldquo;Projects Aber.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Saudi Arabia Central Bank (SAMA) announced that it is continuing its experiment with a central bank digital currency (CBDC). </p>
<p>SAMA announced in a press release earlier in the week that it is stepping up its research into a CBDC but has not said anything regarding its deployment. The bank&rsquo;s press release stated that it was working on a project that &ldquo;focuses on domestic wholesale CBDC use cases in collaboration with local banks and fintechs.&rdquo; The bank, however, reiterated that no conclusive decision had been reached to launch a CBDC:</p>

<p>SAMA stresses that although no decision has been made regarding the introduction of CBDC in the Kingdom, it continues to focus on exploring the benefits and potential risks of implementing CBDC, which will contribute to informed decision-making within SAMA and to CBDC explorations within the central banking community.</p>

<p>The Central Bank further stated that it tests the economic impact of implementing a CBDC and its market readiness and fast applications of CBDC-based payment solutions. SAMA said that it will continue testing the viability of a CBDC to achieve its Saudi Vision 2030 objectives but will consider &ldquo;policy, legal and regulatory considerations&rdquo; before it continues with the project.</p>
<p>The governor of SAMA, H.E. Fahad Almubarak, further stated that local banks and payment companies would be the foundation of the project and its implementation. He added that SAMA had approached local banks and fintechs, along with other market players and third-party consulting and technology providers, to comprehensively understand such a currency&rsquo;s functionality and test different design options.</p>
<p>The press release also added:</p>

<p>SAMA is set to continue with its research on CBDC while consulting with relative international bodies, local government entities, and the public. Additionally, SAMA will continue to experiment with CBDC solutions as an infrastructure enabler of innovation in financial services that has the potential to contribute to a more resilient payment ecosystem and accelerate digital transformation in the local financial sector.</p>

<p>SAMA successfully undertook a CBDC experiment in 2019 in collaboration with the Central Bank of the UAE to explore if distributed ledger technology, or blockchain, &ldquo;could contribute to seamless cross-border payments.&rdquo; The experiment was dubbed &ldquo;Projects Aber.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ZenGo Becomes The First Seedless Wallet on Polygon]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/zengo-becomes-the-first-seedless-wallet-on-polygon</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-231.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/zengo-becomes-the-first-seedless-wallet-on-polygon</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency wallets are the most straightforward option for users to engage in self-custody. However, the traditional approach of seed phrases and recovery seeds warrants improvements. ZenGo, a non-custodial Polygon wallet, offers a glimpse of what that future may look like.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seed Phrases May Be Phased Out
<p>Anyone who interfaced with a crypto wallet will have encountered a seed phrase or recovery seed. The string of words - often 12 or 24 words long - lets users restore their crypto wallet on a new device or within another software client. It is a big improvement over remembering the private key, a string of random letters and numbers. However, users still bear responsibility for handling their seed phrases correctly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, that is often where the issue begins. Writing down the seed phrase on a piece of paper isn't a good idea. Users often leave that paper out in the open, exposing their seed phrases to anyone who passes by it. It is a terrible security practice, although a very common one. Storing the data digitally - in a text document on an internet-connected device - is an even worse idea.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, it seems evident a new solution will be introduced eventually. Industry experts, like Udi Wertheimer, have publicly talked about how seed phrases need to go. He even deems it a "cop-out by wallet developers" and remains convinced builders can develop more secure solutions. More importantly, those new solutions should not result in less convenience.</p>
<p>The debate regarding seed phrases is pivotal for the crypto industry. Since the collapse of FTX, more people have moved funds off centralized exchanges. It is plausible to assume the funds moved to non-custodial wallets secured by recovery seeds. Unfortunately, most people will not conduct the correct security precautions to keep that sensitive data safe. As such, wallets without seed phrases may be the next frontier.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seedless Without Compromising Security
<p>On paper, it sounds straightforward to come up with a replacement for a seed phrase. However, it requires a security-oriented mindset to pull this off successfully. One wallet exploring the opportunity is ZenGo, a wallet for the Polygon ecosystem. It also supports ETH, BTC, and other assets. Rather than using a seed phrase, the wallet protects user funds through advanced biometrics and MPC cryptography.</p>
<p>Rather than using a private key, wallet users receive mathematical shares. One share resides on the user's phone or tablet, while the other is on ZenGo's servers. That ensures there is always a recovery option without having to worry about a single point of failure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The primary benefit of this approach is the ease of use when setting up the wallet while removing a single point of failure. Its non-seed phrase approach has proven successful, as no ZenGo wallet was breached since the company's launch in 2018.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to biometrics, there is also a native Web3 firewall dubbed ClearSign. It is designed to provide more insight into what users sign off on when engaging with decentralized applications and smart contracts. That should also help prevent the signing of dangerous and malicious transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency wallets are the most straightforward option for users to engage in self-custody. However, the traditional approach of seed phrases and recovery seeds warrants improvements. ZenGo, a non-custodial Polygon wallet, offers a glimpse of what that future may look like.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seed Phrases May Be Phased Out
<p>Anyone who interfaced with a crypto wallet will have encountered a seed phrase or recovery seed. The string of words - often 12 or 24 words long - lets users restore their crypto wallet on a new device or within another software client. It is a big improvement over remembering the private key, a string of random letters and numbers. However, users still bear responsibility for handling their seed phrases correctly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unfortunately, that is often where the issue begins. Writing down the seed phrase on a piece of paper isn't a good idea. Users often leave that paper out in the open, exposing their seed phrases to anyone who passes by it. It is a terrible security practice, although a very common one. Storing the data digitally - in a text document on an internet-connected device - is an even worse idea.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Therefore, it seems evident a new solution will be introduced eventually. Industry experts, like Udi Wertheimer, have publicly talked about how seed phrases need to go. He even deems it a "cop-out by wallet developers" and remains convinced builders can develop more secure solutions. More importantly, those new solutions should not result in less convenience.</p>
<p>The debate regarding seed phrases is pivotal for the crypto industry. Since the collapse of FTX, more people have moved funds off centralized exchanges. It is plausible to assume the funds moved to non-custodial wallets secured by recovery seeds. Unfortunately, most people will not conduct the correct security precautions to keep that sensitive data safe. As such, wallets without seed phrases may be the next frontier.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Seedless Without Compromising Security
<p>On paper, it sounds straightforward to come up with a replacement for a seed phrase. However, it requires a security-oriented mindset to pull this off successfully. One wallet exploring the opportunity is ZenGo, a wallet for the Polygon ecosystem. It also supports ETH, BTC, and other assets. Rather than using a seed phrase, the wallet protects user funds through advanced biometrics and MPC cryptography.</p>
<p>Rather than using a private key, wallet users receive mathematical shares. One share resides on the user's phone or tablet, while the other is on ZenGo's servers. That ensures there is always a recovery option without having to worry about a single point of failure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The primary benefit of this approach is the ease of use when setting up the wallet while removing a single point of failure. Its non-seed phrase approach has proven successful, as no ZenGo wallet was breached since the company's launch in 2018.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In addition to biometrics, there is also a native Web3 firewall dubbed ClearSign. It is designed to provide more insight into what users sign off on when engaging with decentralized applications and smart contracts. That should also help prevent the signing of dangerous and malicious transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[MarketAcross Named As European Blockchain Convention’s Web3 Lead Media Partner]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/marketacross-named-as-european-blockchain-conventions-web3-lead-media-partner</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/123456_16746500243gvImH6rhi.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/123456_16746500243gvImH6rhi.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/123456_16746500243gvImH6rhi.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/marketacross-named-as-european-blockchain-conventions-web3-lead-media-partner</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Tel Aviv, Israel, 25th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading blockchain marketing firm MarketAcross has joined the upcoming European Blockchain Convention (EBC) as its main global media partner. The convention, now in its eighth edition, is expected to welcome over 2,500 attendees to the Hyatt Regency in Barcelona between 15-17 February.</p>
<p>As part of the strategic partnership, the experienced blockchain PR and marketing firm will manage pre and post-event marketing efforts on behalf of the 2023 Convention, leveraging its vast network of thought leaders and speakers to raise the profile of the Barcelona event worldwide.</p>
<p>Thought to be the largest edition since the event launched in 2018, this year&rsquo;s in-person conference will inaugurate the EBC Blockchain Awards in recognition of the top 100 early-stage startups currently operating in Europe. The prize-giving follows a month of public voting, with ten finalists selected to pitch to a jury panel of investors during the three-day event.</p>
<p>This year&rsquo;s highly-anticipated EBC features over 200 high-profile industry figures including Bittrex CEO Oliver Linch, Aave founder Stani Kulechov, Solana co-founder Stephen Akridge, and Santander&rsquo;s Head of Crypto Coty de Monteverde. As in previous years, the conference will be held across two stages and welcome a diverse audience of blockchain developers and users, including those involved in DeFi, NFTs, Web3, and blockchain gaming.</p>
<p>New to this year&rsquo;s event will be an exhibition area consisting of stands for over 30 of the event&rsquo;s sponsors, providing attendees with a chance to get to know the companies. Out-of-hours networking opportunities will include a special networking event on 15 February and two parties with live music and drinks on 16 and 17 February.</p>
<p>As one of the industry&rsquo;s best-known PR companies, MarketAcross previously served as a web3 media partner of Benzinga&rsquo;s Future of Crypto conference in New York City. It will also be the official media partner for the upcoming 2023 Paris Blockchain Week in March.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled to join EBC as the main media partner, especially this year, as the speaker list will showcase a lot of exciting personas and projects. EBC is a veteran in the Europe crypto event scene and we are hyped to finally be there in person and make this year&rsquo;s event the best one yet.&rdquo; said Itai Elizur, COO &amp; Partner at MarketAcross.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Victoria Gago, Co-Founder of European Blockchain Convention added &ldquo;Since we launched in 2018 our mission has always been to help the blockchain community connect and thrive. We are very excited to partner up with the MarketAcross team. We are convinced that together we will have a bigger impact in the space."&nbsp;</p>
<p>About &nbsp;MarketAcross</p>
<p>MarketAcross is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain PR and marketing firm, providing a complete end-to-end marketing solution for blockchain companies around the world. MarketAcross has helped many of the industry&rsquo;s biggest exchanges and blockchain projects build their brand, among them Polkadot, Solana, Binance, Polygon, Crypto.com, Huobi, and eToro.</p>
<p>About European Blockchain Convention&nbsp;</p>
<p>Renowned by many as the most influential blockchain event in Europe, European Blockchain Convention is the annual meeting point for entrepreneurs, investors, developers, corporates, and global media in Europe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EBC was born in 2018 in Barcelona with the mission to inform, educate, and connect the global blockchain community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on tickets or to get involved, visit:&nbsp;</p>
<p>https://eblockchainconvention.com
&nbsp;</p>ContactItai Elizuritai@marketacross.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tel Aviv, Israel, 25th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading blockchain marketing firm MarketAcross has joined the upcoming European Blockchain Convention (EBC) as its main global media partner. The convention, now in its eighth edition, is expected to welcome over 2,500 attendees to the Hyatt Regency in Barcelona between 15-17 February.</p>
<p>As part of the strategic partnership, the experienced blockchain PR and marketing firm will manage pre and post-event marketing efforts on behalf of the 2023 Convention, leveraging its vast network of thought leaders and speakers to raise the profile of the Barcelona event worldwide.</p>
<p>Thought to be the largest edition since the event launched in 2018, this year&rsquo;s in-person conference will inaugurate the EBC Blockchain Awards in recognition of the top 100 early-stage startups currently operating in Europe. The prize-giving follows a month of public voting, with ten finalists selected to pitch to a jury panel of investors during the three-day event.</p>
<p>This year&rsquo;s highly-anticipated EBC features over 200 high-profile industry figures including Bittrex CEO Oliver Linch, Aave founder Stani Kulechov, Solana co-founder Stephen Akridge, and Santander&rsquo;s Head of Crypto Coty de Monteverde. As in previous years, the conference will be held across two stages and welcome a diverse audience of blockchain developers and users, including those involved in DeFi, NFTs, Web3, and blockchain gaming.</p>
<p>New to this year&rsquo;s event will be an exhibition area consisting of stands for over 30 of the event&rsquo;s sponsors, providing attendees with a chance to get to know the companies. Out-of-hours networking opportunities will include a special networking event on 15 February and two parties with live music and drinks on 16 and 17 February.</p>
<p>As one of the industry&rsquo;s best-known PR companies, MarketAcross previously served as a web3 media partner of Benzinga&rsquo;s Future of Crypto conference in New York City. It will also be the official media partner for the upcoming 2023 Paris Blockchain Week in March.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We are thrilled to join EBC as the main media partner, especially this year, as the speaker list will showcase a lot of exciting personas and projects. EBC is a veteran in the Europe crypto event scene and we are hyped to finally be there in person and make this year&rsquo;s event the best one yet.&rdquo; said Itai Elizur, COO &amp; Partner at MarketAcross.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Victoria Gago, Co-Founder of European Blockchain Convention added &ldquo;Since we launched in 2018 our mission has always been to help the blockchain community connect and thrive. We are very excited to partner up with the MarketAcross team. We are convinced that together we will have a bigger impact in the space."&nbsp;</p>
<p>About &nbsp;MarketAcross</p>
<p>MarketAcross is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain PR and marketing firm, providing a complete end-to-end marketing solution for blockchain companies around the world. MarketAcross has helped many of the industry&rsquo;s biggest exchanges and blockchain projects build their brand, among them Polkadot, Solana, Binance, Polygon, Crypto.com, Huobi, and eToro.</p>
<p>About European Blockchain Convention&nbsp;</p>
<p>Renowned by many as the most influential blockchain event in Europe, European Blockchain Convention is the annual meeting point for entrepreneurs, investors, developers, corporates, and global media in Europe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EBC was born in 2018 in Barcelona with the mission to inform, educate, and connect the global blockchain community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on tickets or to get involved, visit:&nbsp;</p>
<p>https://eblockchainconvention.com
&nbsp;</p>ContactItai Elizuritai@marketacross.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Market Analysts Say These Crypto Projects Will Thrive in 2023: Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), Flow (FLOW) and Polygon (MATIC)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/market-analysts-say-these-crypto-projects-will-thrive-in-2023-orbeon-protocol-orbn-flow-flow-and-polygon-matic</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-141314.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-141314.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-25-at-141314.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/market-analysts-say-these-crypto-projects-will-thrive-in-2023-orbeon-protocol-orbn-flow-flow-and-polygon-matic</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">The bear market of 2022, which carried over in 2023, has put the crypto industry in a predicament. With no clear idea as to when the market will stabilize, crypto investors are looking for projects that can guarantee them high returns in the future. Market analysts predict that Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), Flow (FLOW), and Polygon (MATIC) are three such projects that have the potential to emerge successful from the crypto winter.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN): Shaping the Future of Crowdfunding</p>
<p class="s6">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is designed to shape the venture capital industry. Following a unique crowdfunding concept, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is created by keeping the best interests of businesses and investors in mind. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) helps investors find new startups that can return good investments in the long run. </p>
<p class="s6">At the same time, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) empowers new businesses to connect the right communities and raise sufficient funds at lower costs. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) uses an NFTs-as-service (NFTaaS) feature, allowing anyone to invest in promising startups for as low as $1. When a business needs to launch a funding round, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) mints and fractionalizes an NFT for the business, which represents the trader's investment in the company.</p>
<p class="s10">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) presents investors a marketplace of vetted businesses to choose from, saving them from losing funds to deceptive projects. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) uses a &lsquo;Fill or Kill&rsquo; mechanism in its smart contract, which guarantees that investors will get their money back if a startup doesn&rsquo;t raise the required amount. </p>
<p class="s10">ORBN is the native token powering Orbeon Protocol&rsquo;s ecosystem, which had an initial price of $0.004. ORBN is currently trading at $0.06, and market analysts predict that its value will increase by 6000% by the end of its presale stage, due to the unique business model that benefits investors and new businesses.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Flow (FLOW) Value Steadily on the Rise</p>
<p class="s6">The Flow (FLOW) blockchain provides fast, low-cost transactions on the blockchain network. Flow (FLOW) also supports the creation of smart contracts. Flow (FLOW) blockchain is used to design games, NFT collectibles, and digital assets to be used across applications. </p>
<p class="s6">FLOW is the native currency that powers the Flow blockchain. FLOW has shown an increase in its value by 37.47% in the past week. The current price of Flow (FLOW) is $1.07, which is 97.68% below its all time high of $46.16. </p>
<p class="s6">Many NFT-crypto projects like Flow (FLOW) took a back seat as an aftermath of the bear market in 2022. However, 2023 presents a new opportunity for the Flow (FLOW) crypto project to take off again.</p>
<p class="s9">Polygon (MATIC) May Rise in 2023</p>
<p class="s6">Polygon (MATIC) is a protocol and framework for building Ethereum-compatible blockchain networks. Polygon (MATIC) is a Layer-2 solution, enabling the Ethereum network to scale and improve its functionality. Polygon (MATIC) protocol uses side chains for faster, and cheaper Ethereum transactions. MATIC is the native currency of the Polygon framework. </p>
<p class="s6">Though Polygon was in a downward spiral in 2022, the price of MATIC has risen by 17.58% in the past week. The current price of Polygon (MATIC) is $1.01, which is 65.46% below its all time high of $2.92. Polygon (MATIC) is often referred to as &ldquo;Ethereum&rsquo;s internet of blockchains.&rdquo; Since Polygon (MATIC) provides good throughput and low gas expenses, market analysts predict that its value has the potential to rise in 2023.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s14">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">The bear market of 2022, which carried over in 2023, has put the crypto industry in a predicament. With no clear idea as to when the market will stabilize, crypto investors are looking for projects that can guarantee them high returns in the future. Market analysts predict that Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), Flow (FLOW), and Polygon (MATIC) are three such projects that have the potential to emerge successful from the crypto winter.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN): Shaping the Future of Crowdfunding</p>
<p class="s6">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is designed to shape the venture capital industry. Following a unique crowdfunding concept, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is created by keeping the best interests of businesses and investors in mind. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) helps investors find new startups that can return good investments in the long run. </p>
<p class="s6">At the same time, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) empowers new businesses to connect the right communities and raise sufficient funds at lower costs. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) uses an NFTs-as-service (NFTaaS) feature, allowing anyone to invest in promising startups for as low as $1. When a business needs to launch a funding round, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) mints and fractionalizes an NFT for the business, which represents the trader's investment in the company.</p>
<p class="s10">Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) presents investors a marketplace of vetted businesses to choose from, saving them from losing funds to deceptive projects. Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) uses a &lsquo;Fill or Kill&rsquo; mechanism in its smart contract, which guarantees that investors will get their money back if a startup doesn&rsquo;t raise the required amount. </p>
<p class="s10">ORBN is the native token powering Orbeon Protocol&rsquo;s ecosystem, which had an initial price of $0.004. ORBN is currently trading at $0.06, and market analysts predict that its value will increase by 6000% by the end of its presale stage, due to the unique business model that benefits investors and new businesses.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Flow (FLOW) Value Steadily on the Rise</p>
<p class="s6">The Flow (FLOW) blockchain provides fast, low-cost transactions on the blockchain network. Flow (FLOW) also supports the creation of smart contracts. Flow (FLOW) blockchain is used to design games, NFT collectibles, and digital assets to be used across applications. </p>
<p class="s6">FLOW is the native currency that powers the Flow blockchain. FLOW has shown an increase in its value by 37.47% in the past week. The current price of Flow (FLOW) is $1.07, which is 97.68% below its all time high of $46.16. </p>
<p class="s6">Many NFT-crypto projects like Flow (FLOW) took a back seat as an aftermath of the bear market in 2022. However, 2023 presents a new opportunity for the Flow (FLOW) crypto project to take off again.</p>
<p class="s9">Polygon (MATIC) May Rise in 2023</p>
<p class="s6">Polygon (MATIC) is a protocol and framework for building Ethereum-compatible blockchain networks. Polygon (MATIC) is a Layer-2 solution, enabling the Ethereum network to scale and improve its functionality. Polygon (MATIC) protocol uses side chains for faster, and cheaper Ethereum transactions. MATIC is the native currency of the Polygon framework. </p>
<p class="s6">Though Polygon was in a downward spiral in 2022, the price of MATIC has risen by 17.58% in the past week. The current price of Polygon (MATIC) is $1.01, which is 65.46% below its all time high of $2.92. Polygon (MATIC) is often referred to as &ldquo;Ethereum&rsquo;s internet of blockchains.&rdquo; Since Polygon (MATIC) provides good throughput and low gas expenses, market analysts predict that its value has the potential to rise in 2023.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p class="s14">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[North Korean crypto hacking group adapts its attacks]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/north-korean-crypto-hacking-group-adapts-its-attacks</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/nk.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/nk.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/nk.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/north-korean-crypto-hacking-group-adapts-its-attacks</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>North Korean hacking group TA444 is primarily targeting crypto, but security researchers say that it is launching phishing attacks aimed at other targets.</p>
<p>According to analysis by CoinGecko, crypto hacks and exploits reached $2.8 billion in 2022, which is the second largest amount stolen since the infamous Silk Road hack of 2012.</p>
<p>Hackers are adapting and upping their game in order to take advantage of a nascent cryptocurrency industry that is still learning as it progresses. Hacking groups out of North Korea are taking a large part of the pie in this respect, and one group in particular, TA444, is adapting and shifting focus.</p>
<p>In an article on the security oriented website Data Breach Today, it was reported that researchers had been tracking the North Korean hacking group TA444, which in one month almost doubled the amount of spam that it sent over the 11 months previously.</p>
<p>TA444 is yet another identified hacking group to join the ranks of others which include: APT38, Bluenoroff, BlackAlicanto, Stardust Chollima and Copernicium group.</p>
<p>Researchers at Proofpoint say that the recent activity from TA444 could possibly be evidence that the group is &ldquo;targeting away from major cryptocurrency and financial institutions&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The language used in attacks by TA444 have so far been in English, Spanish, Polish, and Japanese. Phishing emails are said to be &ldquo;well-crafted&rdquo; and have &ldquo;lure content&rdquo; in the form of high paying job opportunities, and salary adjustments.</p>
<p>The Data Breach Today article specifies the types of payloads that the spam emails deliver:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The phishing emails deliver payloads available in two file formats - an obfuscated LNK file and a chain beginning with documents using remote templates. TA444 continues to use both methods but also now uses other file types like MSI Installer files, virtual hard drive, ISO to bypass Windows Mark of the Web, and compiled HTML.&rdquo;</p>

<p>With TA444 managing to hack more than $1 billion in 2022, an improvement on the 2021 total of around $400 million, this fast-learning and adaptive group is likely to have a good amount of security resources devoted to countering its operations.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>North Korean hacking group TA444 is primarily targeting crypto, but security researchers say that it is launching phishing attacks aimed at other targets.</p>
<p>According to analysis by CoinGecko, crypto hacks and exploits reached $2.8 billion in 2022, which is the second largest amount stolen since the infamous Silk Road hack of 2012.</p>
<p>Hackers are adapting and upping their game in order to take advantage of a nascent cryptocurrency industry that is still learning as it progresses. Hacking groups out of North Korea are taking a large part of the pie in this respect, and one group in particular, TA444, is adapting and shifting focus.</p>
<p>In an article on the security oriented website Data Breach Today, it was reported that researchers had been tracking the North Korean hacking group TA444, which in one month almost doubled the amount of spam that it sent over the 11 months previously.</p>
<p>TA444 is yet another identified hacking group to join the ranks of others which include: APT38, Bluenoroff, BlackAlicanto, Stardust Chollima and Copernicium group.</p>
<p>Researchers at Proofpoint say that the recent activity from TA444 could possibly be evidence that the group is &ldquo;targeting away from major cryptocurrency and financial institutions&rdquo;.</p>
<p>The language used in attacks by TA444 have so far been in English, Spanish, Polish, and Japanese. Phishing emails are said to be &ldquo;well-crafted&rdquo; and have &ldquo;lure content&rdquo; in the form of high paying job opportunities, and salary adjustments.</p>
<p>The Data Breach Today article specifies the types of payloads that the spam emails deliver:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The phishing emails deliver payloads available in two file formats - an obfuscated LNK file and a chain beginning with documents using remote templates. TA444 continues to use both methods but also now uses other file types like MSI Installer files, virtual hard drive, ISO to bypass Windows Mark of the Web, and compiled HTML.&rdquo;</p>

<p>With TA444 managing to hack more than $1 billion in 2022, an improvement on the 2021 total of around $400 million, this fast-learning and adaptive group is likely to have a good amount of security resources devoted to countering its operations.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Asset Management Practices Are Changing for the Better]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-asset-management-practices-are-changing-for-the-better</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-512.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-512.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-512.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-asset-management-practices-are-changing-for-the-better</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Source: Depositphotos</p>
<p>Over the past year or so, the crypto market has been ravaged by a slew of insolvencies, resulting in a major loss of investor confidence in the space. A prime example of this has been FTX, the world&rsquo;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange at one point by daily trade volume. During its heyday, the platform was valued at approx. $32 trillion, holding massive sums of investor money, both in storage and as part of its various investment vehicles and offerings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, after it came to light that the exchange had been misusing customer funds by indulging in shady deals as well as investing large sums of these assets illegally, it abruptly halted customer withdrawals, resulting in widespread market panic and turmoil. What&rsquo;s more is that similar moves were also witnessed in relation to a number of other high-profile platforms, including crypto lender Celsius, Voyager, Vauld, amongst others.</p>
<p>As a result of these developments, more and more digital asset investors have started to realize the importance of having high-quality recovery mechanisms in place so that in case there is ever a situation where they feel they need to withdraw their assets, they are able to do so without any interruptions or third party interference.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Transparency is the need of the hour.
<p>As the market continues to reel in from the effects of the ongoing crypto contagion, it is important for digital asset exchanges to have mechanisms in place that can allow users to utilize their funds as they see fit, regardless of the prevailing market environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this regard, Dexalot, a dual-chain, non-custodial central order book decentralized exchange (DEX) powered by Avalanche&rsquo;s subnet technology, comes with a built-in asset balance snapshot (ABS) feature that helps establish an immutable snapshot proof of its users&rsquo; held balances. To elaborate, the module makes it extremely simple for users to verify their holdings by periodically recording relevant data into Dexalot&rsquo;s native subnet framework (using an information structure called referred to as a &lsquo;Merkle Tree&rsquo;).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moreover, the ABS module is completely independent in its functionality and can work even when the Dexalot subnet is unavailable for use, thereby maximizing fund security and individual privacy. Lastly, it bears mentioning that ABS makes it possible to recover the state of one&rsquo;s assets on the Avalanche mainnet C-chain should any situation unforeseen situation arise.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In other words, Dexalot&rsquo;s novel feature set not only helps provide transparency in relation to any digital currencies interacting with its interface but also affords users the ability to confirm assets independently. Lastly, it allows for the immutable time series data of asset balances for analysis, if need be.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The market is evolving rapidly.
<p>In recent months, a growing number of cryptocurrency exchanges have continued to establish systems &mdash; such as the increasingly popular proof of reserve (PoR) audit trail&mdash; that allow users to verify a company&rsquo;s held assets and overall liabilities. And while this may help investors and clients to breathe easy, albeit somewhat, they tend to give extremely limited insights into a firm&rsquo;s true financial status.</p>
<p>To this point, recently, a growing number of digital trading platforms have hired third-party entities to conduct an inspection of their funds so as to prove that their businesses are solvent while also being in possession of enough assets to cover any liabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, since most cryptocurrency trading platforms are privately owned/held, their owners are not obligated to submit detailed financial records with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) or even get them verified/audited by an independent agency. Therefore, more can be done to help ensure the safety of customer funds.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The road ahead
<p>As a growing forum of crypto investors continues to demand more clarity and transparency from companies operating within this rapidly evolving realm, it stands to reason that more and more mainstream crypto entities will have to adopt accountability frameworks (such as Dexalot&rsquo;s ABS feature) that can allow users to gain a better overview of their assets in the near to mid term. Therefore, it will be interesting to see how this burgeoning tech paradigm continues to evolve from here on out.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Source: Depositphotos</p>
<p>Over the past year or so, the crypto market has been ravaged by a slew of insolvencies, resulting in a major loss of investor confidence in the space. A prime example of this has been FTX, the world&rsquo;s second-largest cryptocurrency exchange at one point by daily trade volume. During its heyday, the platform was valued at approx. $32 trillion, holding massive sums of investor money, both in storage and as part of its various investment vehicles and offerings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, after it came to light that the exchange had been misusing customer funds by indulging in shady deals as well as investing large sums of these assets illegally, it abruptly halted customer withdrawals, resulting in widespread market panic and turmoil. What&rsquo;s more is that similar moves were also witnessed in relation to a number of other high-profile platforms, including crypto lender Celsius, Voyager, Vauld, amongst others.</p>
<p>As a result of these developments, more and more digital asset investors have started to realize the importance of having high-quality recovery mechanisms in place so that in case there is ever a situation where they feel they need to withdraw their assets, they are able to do so without any interruptions or third party interference.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Transparency is the need of the hour.
<p>As the market continues to reel in from the effects of the ongoing crypto contagion, it is important for digital asset exchanges to have mechanisms in place that can allow users to utilize their funds as they see fit, regardless of the prevailing market environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this regard, Dexalot, a dual-chain, non-custodial central order book decentralized exchange (DEX) powered by Avalanche&rsquo;s subnet technology, comes with a built-in asset balance snapshot (ABS) feature that helps establish an immutable snapshot proof of its users&rsquo; held balances. To elaborate, the module makes it extremely simple for users to verify their holdings by periodically recording relevant data into Dexalot&rsquo;s native subnet framework (using an information structure called referred to as a &lsquo;Merkle Tree&rsquo;).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Moreover, the ABS module is completely independent in its functionality and can work even when the Dexalot subnet is unavailable for use, thereby maximizing fund security and individual privacy. Lastly, it bears mentioning that ABS makes it possible to recover the state of one&rsquo;s assets on the Avalanche mainnet C-chain should any situation unforeseen situation arise.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In other words, Dexalot&rsquo;s novel feature set not only helps provide transparency in relation to any digital currencies interacting with its interface but also affords users the ability to confirm assets independently. Lastly, it allows for the immutable time series data of asset balances for analysis, if need be.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The market is evolving rapidly.
<p>In recent months, a growing number of cryptocurrency exchanges have continued to establish systems &mdash; such as the increasingly popular proof of reserve (PoR) audit trail&mdash; that allow users to verify a company&rsquo;s held assets and overall liabilities. And while this may help investors and clients to breathe easy, albeit somewhat, they tend to give extremely limited insights into a firm&rsquo;s true financial status.</p>
<p>To this point, recently, a growing number of digital trading platforms have hired third-party entities to conduct an inspection of their funds so as to prove that their businesses are solvent while also being in possession of enough assets to cover any liabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, since most cryptocurrency trading platforms are privately owned/held, their owners are not obligated to submit detailed financial records with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) or even get them verified/audited by an independent agency. Therefore, more can be done to help ensure the safety of customer funds.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The road ahead
<p>As a growing forum of crypto investors continues to demand more clarity and transparency from companies operating within this rapidly evolving realm, it stands to reason that more and more mainstream crypto entities will have to adopt accountability frameworks (such as Dexalot&rsquo;s ABS feature) that can allow users to gain a better overview of their assets in the near to mid term. Therefore, it will be interesting to see how this burgeoning tech paradigm continues to evolve from here on out.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[$105M Payday For Coinbase’s Chief Product Officer]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/105m-payday-for-coinbase-chief-product-officer</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/105m-payday-for-coinbase-chief-product-officer</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Surojit Chatterjee will be cashing out a portion of his Coinbase stocks on his final day for a whopping $105 million exit package.&nbsp;</p>
Million Dollar Payout After Subpar Performance
<p>Crypto executives are no strangers to high benefits and severance packages. With his final day at Coinbase inching closer, former chief product officer Surojit Chatterjee is making news for the size of his payday package. Chatterjee, who will be selling off a portion of his stock holdings, will rake in a whopping $105 million after logging out on his last day at Coinbase on February 3. Furthermore, he will also retain an additional 249,315 shares of COIN stock, which is presently valued at $49.42 per share. Ever since this information spread, crypto Twitter has been abuzz over the size of his payday amount, especially in the context of Coinbase's subpar performance (the unsuccessful NFT initiative) during his tenure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter user "Autism Capital" wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A reminder that a mid project manager got paid $115 MILLION DOLLARS to launch the worst most embarrassing NFT grift attempt for Coinbase with a total of 7 active daily users and transaction volume less than your daily gas fees.&rdquo;</p>

Severance Package Includes Benefits
<p>Chatterjee had migrated to the San Fransisco-based company from Google back in February 2020, just on the eve of the Covid-19 pandemic. His annual starting salary was a million dollars, which brings up his total earnings from the company till his last day to around $115 million. As per his separation agreement, Chatterjee will receive severance benefits, which include a lump sum amount and health insurance coverage for ten months. Furthermore, he will continue to be employed in an advisory capacity for the rest of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Chatterjee had commented on the matter via a LinkedIn post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m looking forward to continuing to contribute in my role as an advisor to Brian and the exec team and to continuing the hard but critical work of creating more economic freedom and building a better internet for everyone.&rdquo;</p>

Chatterjee&rsquo;s Claim To Wealth
<p>It is to be noted that Chatterjee initially had a five-year contract with the company, which was cut short by his resignation due to personal issues. As per the original agreement, he would have earned $646 million at the end of the five-year term. Also, another important factor at play here was the turbulence in the crypto market and the rise and fall of crypto valuation. 2021 was Chatterjee&rsquo;s first year at Coinbase, which was also marked by the ballooning interest in crypto from people stuck in lockdown during the pandemic. The value of COIN stock skyrocketed to an all-time high of $342, making him and everybody who held COIN stock fabulously wealthy. The valuation dropped quite significantly the next year, bringing down the net valuation of Chatterjee and other high-level executives. However, the initial pandemic boost and the exorbitant package agreement still ensured that Chatterjee left with a sizeable chunk of cash.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Surojit Chatterjee will be cashing out a portion of his Coinbase stocks on his final day for a whopping $105 million exit package.&nbsp;</p>
Million Dollar Payout After Subpar Performance
<p>Crypto executives are no strangers to high benefits and severance packages. With his final day at Coinbase inching closer, former chief product officer Surojit Chatterjee is making news for the size of his payday package. Chatterjee, who will be selling off a portion of his stock holdings, will rake in a whopping $105 million after logging out on his last day at Coinbase on February 3. Furthermore, he will also retain an additional 249,315 shares of COIN stock, which is presently valued at $49.42 per share. Ever since this information spread, crypto Twitter has been abuzz over the size of his payday amount, especially in the context of Coinbase's subpar performance (the unsuccessful NFT initiative) during his tenure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter user "Autism Capital" wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A reminder that a mid project manager got paid $115 MILLION DOLLARS to launch the worst most embarrassing NFT grift attempt for Coinbase with a total of 7 active daily users and transaction volume less than your daily gas fees.&rdquo;</p>

Severance Package Includes Benefits
<p>Chatterjee had migrated to the San Fransisco-based company from Google back in February 2020, just on the eve of the Covid-19 pandemic. His annual starting salary was a million dollars, which brings up his total earnings from the company till his last day to around $115 million. As per his separation agreement, Chatterjee will receive severance benefits, which include a lump sum amount and health insurance coverage for ten months. Furthermore, he will continue to be employed in an advisory capacity for the rest of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Chatterjee had commented on the matter via a LinkedIn post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m looking forward to continuing to contribute in my role as an advisor to Brian and the exec team and to continuing the hard but critical work of creating more economic freedom and building a better internet for everyone.&rdquo;</p>

Chatterjee&rsquo;s Claim To Wealth
<p>It is to be noted that Chatterjee initially had a five-year contract with the company, which was cut short by his resignation due to personal issues. As per the original agreement, he would have earned $646 million at the end of the five-year term. Also, another important factor at play here was the turbulence in the crypto market and the rise and fall of crypto valuation. 2021 was Chatterjee&rsquo;s first year at Coinbase, which was also marked by the ballooning interest in crypto from people stuck in lockdown during the pandemic. The value of COIN stock skyrocketed to an all-time high of $342, making him and everybody who held COIN stock fabulously wealthy. The valuation dropped quite significantly the next year, bringing down the net valuation of Chatterjee and other high-level executives. However, the initial pandemic boost and the exorbitant package agreement still ensured that Chatterjee left with a sizeable chunk of cash.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US Senator says well-regulated crypto benefits financial system]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-senator-says-well-regulated-crypto-benefits-financial-system</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/fin-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/fin-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/fin-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-senator-says-well-regulated-crypto-benefits-financial-system</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Republican Senator Richie Torres stated that crypto can be good for his South Bronx community, but that it needs a comprehensive regulatory framework.</p>
Crypto can provide a superior payments system
<p>Senator Torres is a member of the House Financial Services Committee, and he is pro regulation for the cryptocurrency industry. In an interview on Tuesday for the City &amp; State New York political platform, he said that his community had been failed by the traditional financial system.</p>
<p>He is a believer in blockchain and crypto, and has the view that this combination of technologies &ldquo;has the potential to create a new layer of the internet&rdquo;, and also to &ldquo;create a better, cheaper, and faster payments system."</p>
FTX doesn&rsquo;t represent crypto
<p>When asked what he thought of the FTX collapse he replied that Sam Bankman-Fried was no more representative of the crypto sector than Bernie Madoff was of the conventional finance sector.</p>
<p>He just thought that the affair brought more urgency for regulation that would &ldquo;make crypto safe for consumers and investors&rdquo;. In spite of his support for crypto, he acknowledged that the space was currently dangerously deregulated.</p>
Regulation is needed
<p>His idea for regulation includes obliging exchanges and stablecoin issuers to prove that their assets are liquid enough to cover all their liabilities. He was of the view that exchanges should never have a hedge fund (FTX/Alameda), and vice versa. He said he was worried about Tether because its reserves backing fell short of 100%.</p>
<p>Although the Senator is very supportive of crypto technology generally, he doesn&rsquo;t think it can succeed without comprehensive regulations. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am skeptical that the crypto industry can succeed without a comprehensive regulatory framework at the federal level. I think if there is a regulatory framework that distinguishes the best actors from the worst actors, then the industry has a fighting chance of succeeding.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Republican Senator Richie Torres stated that crypto can be good for his South Bronx community, but that it needs a comprehensive regulatory framework.</p>
Crypto can provide a superior payments system
<p>Senator Torres is a member of the House Financial Services Committee, and he is pro regulation for the cryptocurrency industry. In an interview on Tuesday for the City &amp; State New York political platform, he said that his community had been failed by the traditional financial system.</p>
<p>He is a believer in blockchain and crypto, and has the view that this combination of technologies &ldquo;has the potential to create a new layer of the internet&rdquo;, and also to &ldquo;create a better, cheaper, and faster payments system."</p>
FTX doesn&rsquo;t represent crypto
<p>When asked what he thought of the FTX collapse he replied that Sam Bankman-Fried was no more representative of the crypto sector than Bernie Madoff was of the conventional finance sector.</p>
<p>He just thought that the affair brought more urgency for regulation that would &ldquo;make crypto safe for consumers and investors&rdquo;. In spite of his support for crypto, he acknowledged that the space was currently dangerously deregulated.</p>
Regulation is needed
<p>His idea for regulation includes obliging exchanges and stablecoin issuers to prove that their assets are liquid enough to cover all their liabilities. He was of the view that exchanges should never have a hedge fund (FTX/Alameda), and vice versa. He said he was worried about Tether because its reserves backing fell short of 100%.</p>
<p>Although the Senator is very supportive of crypto technology generally, he doesn&rsquo;t think it can succeed without comprehensive regulations. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I am skeptical that the crypto industry can succeed without a comprehensive regulatory framework at the federal level. I think if there is a regulatory framework that distinguishes the best actors from the worst actors, then the industry has a fighting chance of succeeding.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Mixed-Up Customer Funds With B-Token Collateral]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-mixed-up-customer-funds-with-the-b-token-collateral</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/binance-mixed-up-customer-funds-with-the-b-token-collateral</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Binance crypto exchange has mistakenly stored customer funds in the same wallet used to store collateral for its Binance-pegged tokens.&nbsp;</p>
PoR Reveals Funds Mix-Up
<p>According to a report published by Bloomberg on Tuesday, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange, Binance had mistakenly kept collateral for some of the crypto assets it issues in the same wallet as customer funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Binance spokesperson commented on the matter, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Collateral assets have previously been moved into this wallet in error and referenced accordingly on the B-Token Proof of Collateral page. Binance is aware of this mistake and is in the process of transferring these assets to dedicated collateral wallets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The crypto exchange released a proof-of-reserve on Monday, which revealed that there were 94 Binance-peg tokens, also referred to as B-Tokens, half of which were stored in a cold wallet called Binance 8, are supposed to be backed following a 1:1 ratio. However, upon investigation, it was revealed that the wallet contained more tokens than required for the number of B-Tokens issued, indicating that the collateral was mixed up with customer tokens.&nbsp;</p>
Is Binance&rsquo;s Reserves Undercollateralized?&nbsp;
<p>There has been increasing scrutiny on crypto exchanges and their reserves ever since the FTX debacle unveiled fund sharing between the exchange and its associated hedge fund, Alameda Research. As a result, other crypto platforms have rushed to show the status of their funds through proof-of-reserve reports. Binance itself had shown that its customer reserves of Bitcoin were overcollateralized through one such report.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The spokesperson clarified further,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"To be clear, Binance holds all of its clients&rsquo; assets in segregated accounts, which are identified separately from any accounts used to hold assets belonging to Binance. Binance does not invest or otherwise deploy user assets without consent under the terms of specific products."</p>

<p>However, earlier this month reports emerged of under-collateralization of the BNB Smart Chain-based stablecoin, BUSD, on at least three occasions. The company has since then released information about how it manages the backing of its tokens. However, the recent reports of the mix-up between customer funds and the B-tokens reveal some holes in the management.&nbsp;</p>
Binance In The News
<p>With FTX declaring bankruptcy and the 2022 bear market barely behind us, all eyes are on Binance for even the smallest faux pas. Most recently, Signature Bank, a partner of Binance, has advised that it will no longer support SWIFT transfers of under $100,000 for the exchange&rsquo;s users. The exchange has also been implicated by United States authorities in its money laundering case against Bitzlato.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, things are not all looking down for the exchange. The platform has successfully registered itself as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) in Poland and has recently launched&nbsp; Binance Mirror, an off-exchange settlement solution for its institutional investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Binance crypto exchange has mistakenly stored customer funds in the same wallet used to store collateral for its Binance-pegged tokens.&nbsp;</p>
PoR Reveals Funds Mix-Up
<p>According to a report published by Bloomberg on Tuesday, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange, Binance had mistakenly kept collateral for some of the crypto assets it issues in the same wallet as customer funds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Binance spokesperson commented on the matter, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Collateral assets have previously been moved into this wallet in error and referenced accordingly on the B-Token Proof of Collateral page. Binance is aware of this mistake and is in the process of transferring these assets to dedicated collateral wallets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The crypto exchange released a proof-of-reserve on Monday, which revealed that there were 94 Binance-peg tokens, also referred to as B-Tokens, half of which were stored in a cold wallet called Binance 8, are supposed to be backed following a 1:1 ratio. However, upon investigation, it was revealed that the wallet contained more tokens than required for the number of B-Tokens issued, indicating that the collateral was mixed up with customer tokens.&nbsp;</p>
Is Binance&rsquo;s Reserves Undercollateralized?&nbsp;
<p>There has been increasing scrutiny on crypto exchanges and their reserves ever since the FTX debacle unveiled fund sharing between the exchange and its associated hedge fund, Alameda Research. As a result, other crypto platforms have rushed to show the status of their funds through proof-of-reserve reports. Binance itself had shown that its customer reserves of Bitcoin were overcollateralized through one such report.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The spokesperson clarified further,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"To be clear, Binance holds all of its clients&rsquo; assets in segregated accounts, which are identified separately from any accounts used to hold assets belonging to Binance. Binance does not invest or otherwise deploy user assets without consent under the terms of specific products."</p>

<p>However, earlier this month reports emerged of under-collateralization of the BNB Smart Chain-based stablecoin, BUSD, on at least three occasions. The company has since then released information about how it manages the backing of its tokens. However, the recent reports of the mix-up between customer funds and the B-tokens reveal some holes in the management.&nbsp;</p>
Binance In The News
<p>With FTX declaring bankruptcy and the 2022 bear market barely behind us, all eyes are on Binance for even the smallest faux pas. Most recently, Signature Bank, a partner of Binance, has advised that it will no longer support SWIFT transfers of under $100,000 for the exchange&rsquo;s users. The exchange has also been implicated by United States authorities in its money laundering case against Bitzlato.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, things are not all looking down for the exchange. The platform has successfully registered itself as a Virtual Asset Service Provider (VASP) in Poland and has recently launched&nbsp; Binance Mirror, an off-exchange settlement solution for its institutional investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Winter Cripples Gemini, Crypto Daily TV 25/1/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-winter-cripples-gemini-crypto-daily-tv-25-1-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-gemini.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-gemini.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-gemini.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-winter-cripples-gemini-crypto-daily-tv-25-1-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>North Korean hackers behind Horizon Bridge theft</p>
<p>A pair of North Korean hacker groups were behind the June theft of $100 million in crypto assets from Horizon Bridge, the Federal Bureau of Investigation said. Lazarus Group and APT38, both associated with North Korea, are responsible for the attack in June, the agency concluded.</p>
<p>Gemini becomes the latest victim of crypto winter</p>
<p>Gemini has revealed cutting 10 percent of its staff, citing macroeconomic factors as its primary pain point, in its third round of job cuts in under a year. The crypto exchange had 1000 employees as of November 2022, suggesting around 100 people lost their positions. It had previously laid off 7 percent of its staff in July 2022, after dismissing 10 percent a month earlier.</p>
<p>Cit&eacute; Gestion becomes first private bank to tokenize its own shares</p>
<p>Cit&eacute; Gestion, an independent Swiss private bank founded in 2009, is using Taurus technology to tokenize its own shares as the bank delves deeper into blockchain technology. The move will be the first by a private bank to issue shares as ledger-based securities under Swiss law, the company said.</p>
BTC/USD made a minor downwards correction of 0.1%.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair corrected downwards in the last session, falling 0.1%. According to the RSI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 22217.3333 and resistance at 23515.3333.</p>
<p>The RSI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 1.8% in the last session. The CCI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1568.7967 and resistance at 1672.5767.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 1.5% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 1.5% in the last session. The CCI indicates an overbought market. Support is at 0.3854 and resistance at 0.4518.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 2.2% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dropped 2.2% in the last session after rising as much as 1.4% during the session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 84.71 and resistance at 95.561.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Coincident Index</p>
<p>The Coincident Index released by the Cabinet Office is a single summary statistic that tracks the current state of the Japanese economy. Japan's Coincident Index will be released at 05:00 GMT, Germany's IFO &ndash; Business Climate at 09:00 GMT, the UK's PPI Core Output at 07:00 GMT.</p>
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Business Climate</p>
<p>The IFO Business Climate index is regarded as an early indicator of current conditions and business expectations. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the economic situation.</p>
<p>UK PPI Core Output</p>
<p>The Producer Prices Index (PPI) Core Output is a price index of producer prices and excludes volatile items such as food and energy.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered as a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market. The US MBA Mortgage Applications will be released at 12:00 GMT, the UK's Producer Price Index at 07:00 GMT, Australia's Consumer Price Index at 00:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Producer Price Index</p>
<p>The Producer Price Index measures the average changes in prices in primary markets by producers of commodities in all states of processing.</p>
<p>AU Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>North Korean hackers behind Horizon Bridge theft</p>
<p>A pair of North Korean hacker groups were behind the June theft of $100 million in crypto assets from Horizon Bridge, the Federal Bureau of Investigation said. Lazarus Group and APT38, both associated with North Korea, are responsible for the attack in June, the agency concluded.</p>
<p>Gemini becomes the latest victim of crypto winter</p>
<p>Gemini has revealed cutting 10 percent of its staff, citing macroeconomic factors as its primary pain point, in its third round of job cuts in under a year. The crypto exchange had 1000 employees as of November 2022, suggesting around 100 people lost their positions. It had previously laid off 7 percent of its staff in July 2022, after dismissing 10 percent a month earlier.</p>
<p>Cit&eacute; Gestion becomes first private bank to tokenize its own shares</p>
<p>Cit&eacute; Gestion, an independent Swiss private bank founded in 2009, is using Taurus technology to tokenize its own shares as the bank delves deeper into blockchain technology. The move will be the first by a private bank to issue shares as ledger-based securities under Swiss law, the company said.</p>
BTC/USD made a minor downwards correction of 0.1%.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair corrected downwards in the last session, falling 0.1%. According to the RSI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 22217.3333 and resistance at 23515.3333.</p>
<p>The RSI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 1.8% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 1.8% in the last session. The CCI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1568.7967 and resistance at 1672.5767.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 1.5% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 1.5% in the last session. The CCI indicates an overbought market. Support is at 0.3854 and resistance at 0.4518.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 2.2% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair dropped 2.2% in the last session after rising as much as 1.4% during the session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 84.71 and resistance at 95.561.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>JP Coincident Index</p>
<p>The Coincident Index released by the Cabinet Office is a single summary statistic that tracks the current state of the Japanese economy. Japan's Coincident Index will be released at 05:00 GMT, Germany's IFO &ndash; Business Climate at 09:00 GMT, the UK's PPI Core Output at 07:00 GMT.</p>
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Business Climate</p>
<p>The IFO Business Climate index is regarded as an early indicator of current conditions and business expectations. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the economic situation.</p>
<p>UK PPI Core Output</p>
<p>The Producer Prices Index (PPI) Core Output is a price index of producer prices and excludes volatile items such as food and energy.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered as a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market. The US MBA Mortgage Applications will be released at 12:00 GMT, the UK's Producer Price Index at 07:00 GMT, Australia's Consumer Price Index at 00:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Producer Price Index</p>
<p>The Producer Price Index measures the average changes in prices in primary markets by producers of commodities in all states of processing.</p>
<p>AU Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wormhole Bridge's Threat Actor Moves $155m Through DEX]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/wormhole-bridges-threat-actor-moves-155m-through-dex</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wormhole-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wormhole-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wormhole-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/wormhole-bridges-threat-actor-moves-155m-through-dex</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In what appears to be the third largest hack in recent DeFi history, news of fund movement in relation to the historical Wormhole hack once again sparks a certain degree of fear, uncertainty, an doubt in the DeFi industry.Roughly a year ago, CryptoDaily reported how $323 million was siphoned off of Wormhole, a cross-chain protocol bridging the Solana and Ethereum ecosystems. According to CryptoDaily's previous coverage, the attack was carried out using a &lsquo;re-entrancy&rsquo; bug, which allowed the yet unidentified threat actors to freely withdraw funds from the protocol.In terms of methodology, the re-entrancy exploit is similar to one that has been identified as a vulnerability in Uniswap's Universal Router, a process that's been explained in detail by Dedaub. The attack left Wormhole's protocol open to scrutiny, with more concerns on the future stability of the protocol thrown for the project's developers and community.According to data extracted from Etherscan, the funds from the previous year's attack have been moved, with transaction data indicating some $155 million worth of Ethereum (95,630 $ETH) being transferred through OpenOcean, a decentralized exchange. Blockchain security auditing firm CertiK provided an initial alert on the matter:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">#CertiKSkynetAlert 🚨We are seeing address ​​0x629e&hellip; Wormhole Network Exploiter swap 95,630 Ether (~$155M) to stETH Stay safe! pic.twitter.com/ZR6zxlRuKX</p>
&mdash; CertiK Alert (@CertiKAlert) January 23, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>However, at the time of writing, the wallet address itself has not been confirmed nor identified as belonging to the threat actor behind the Wormhole hack. The funds were later converted into assets pegged against Ethereum such as stETH (from Lido Finance) and wstETH (resulting wrapped token), which are rebased tokens that are integrated with other DeFi platforms such as Curve and Yearn. The protocol's development team has attempted to communicate with the threat actor through an embedded message, offering a bug bounty worth $10 million if the funds are returned safely.</p>
<p>This recent development caused a minor price impact on stETH, with the asset depegging to 0.9962 within the day of discovery (January 23rd), while quickly recovering to a minimal price variation as the price cycle closed off.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In what appears to be the third largest hack in recent DeFi history, news of fund movement in relation to the historical Wormhole hack once again sparks a certain degree of fear, uncertainty, an doubt in the DeFi industry.Roughly a year ago, CryptoDaily reported how $323 million was siphoned off of Wormhole, a cross-chain protocol bridging the Solana and Ethereum ecosystems. According to CryptoDaily's previous coverage, the attack was carried out using a &lsquo;re-entrancy&rsquo; bug, which allowed the yet unidentified threat actors to freely withdraw funds from the protocol.In terms of methodology, the re-entrancy exploit is similar to one that has been identified as a vulnerability in Uniswap's Universal Router, a process that's been explained in detail by Dedaub. The attack left Wormhole's protocol open to scrutiny, with more concerns on the future stability of the protocol thrown for the project's developers and community.According to data extracted from Etherscan, the funds from the previous year's attack have been moved, with transaction data indicating some $155 million worth of Ethereum (95,630 $ETH) being transferred through OpenOcean, a decentralized exchange. Blockchain security auditing firm CertiK provided an initial alert on the matter:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">#CertiKSkynetAlert 🚨We are seeing address ​​0x629e&hellip; Wormhole Network Exploiter swap 95,630 Ether (~$155M) to stETH Stay safe! pic.twitter.com/ZR6zxlRuKX</p>
&mdash; CertiK Alert (@CertiKAlert) January 23, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>However, at the time of writing, the wallet address itself has not been confirmed nor identified as belonging to the threat actor behind the Wormhole hack. The funds were later converted into assets pegged against Ethereum such as stETH (from Lido Finance) and wstETH (resulting wrapped token), which are rebased tokens that are integrated with other DeFi platforms such as Curve and Yearn. The protocol's development team has attempted to communicate with the threat actor through an embedded message, offering a bug bounty worth $10 million if the funds are returned safely.</p>
<p>This recent development caused a minor price impact on stETH, with the asset depegging to 0.9962 within the day of discovery (January 23rd), while quickly recovering to a minimal price variation as the price cycle closed off.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Aave Community Voting On Proposal To Deploy v3 On Ethereum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/aave-community-voting-on-proposal-to-deploy-v3-on-ethereum</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/aave-community-voting-on-proposal-to-deploy-v3-on-ethereum</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized lending and borrowing protocol Aave is in the midst of a vote to deploy its third iteration, v3, on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>The voting is scheduled to end on the 25th of January, 2023, and so far, all participating token holders have voted to activate v3 on Ethereum.</p>
The Ongoing Governance Vote
<p>Aave, the non-custodial, decentralized lending and borrowing protocol, is currently voting on a proposal to execute its third iteration, v3, on the Ethereum blockchain. The vote is seen as critical within the decentralized finance (DeFi) community, which hopes to benefit from v3 and its focus on capital efficiency and risk management. The governance vote, which is currently ongoing, has seen all participants vote in favor of activating Aave&rsquo;s third iteration on the Ethereum blockchain. The protocol has called the v3 the most significant upgrade to Aave since its launch.</p>
<p>The voting is scheduled to end on the 25th of January, 2023, at 18:58 UTC. If the proposal is passed, it will be deployed on the 27th of January, 2023.</p>
Several New Improvements
<p>Ethereum is the Aave Protocol&rsquo;s first and largest market for borrowing and lending crypto capital on-chain. The protocol has rolled out v3 on other chains such as Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism, and Avalanche. v3 aims to improve capital efficiency, risk management, and user experience on Ethereum. The protocol is the largest lender in the DeFi ecosystem, with around $3.78 billion in Total Value Locked (TVL), according to DeFiLlama.</p>
<p>The move is being seen as significant by others in Ethereum&rsquo;s DeFi ecosystem, which depend on Aave for liquidity. Pseudo Anonymous spokesperson for the Lido Protocol, Kethfinex, stated that Aave v3 on Ethereum will help improve the borrowing and lending markets for Lido&rsquo;s staked ETH and called it a big step forward.</p>
New Features
<p>v3 will also bring new features such as eMode (efficiency mode) to Ethereum. However, this will initially be introduced in a limited manner. For the time being, Aave&rsquo;s v3 market on Ethereum will feature wBTC, wETH, wstETH, USDC, DAI, LINK, and AAVE. However, a key feature on v3, Isolation mode, will not be instantly enabled for assets when v3 launches. Isolation mode allows users to borrow a newly listed and risky asset up to a particular debt ceiling. Furthermore, v3 interest rate models also vary from v2, with the difference primarily due to stablecoin rates.</p>
<p>The author of the proposal, Bored Ghost Developing Labs, stated that the initial interest rates on v3 &ldquo;will follow those present on v2 Ethereum assets and other existing instances of v3.&rdquo;</p>
A Steady Decline In Numbers
<p>According to data sourced from DeFiLlama, Aave v2 ranks as the 5th largest protocol when it comes to Total Value Locked, behind other protocols such as Lido, MakerDAO, Curve, and WBTC. Aave v3 is operational on six chains, and its TVL currently stands at $525.96 million, meaning most of the Aave ecosystem activity takes place on v2 on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>However, user activity has seen a steady decline in the number of daily new users, according to Dune Analytics, which notes a 96% drop in daily new unique users. This drop can be attributed to the steady decline in incentives offered by the protocol. Some of the incentives offered by the protocol include interest rate discounts, reduced withdrawal fees, and earning additional interest on assets. The drop has also resulted in a decrease in the daily revenue generated by Aave.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized lending and borrowing protocol Aave is in the midst of a vote to deploy its third iteration, v3, on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p>The voting is scheduled to end on the 25th of January, 2023, and so far, all participating token holders have voted to activate v3 on Ethereum.</p>
The Ongoing Governance Vote
<p>Aave, the non-custodial, decentralized lending and borrowing protocol, is currently voting on a proposal to execute its third iteration, v3, on the Ethereum blockchain. The vote is seen as critical within the decentralized finance (DeFi) community, which hopes to benefit from v3 and its focus on capital efficiency and risk management. The governance vote, which is currently ongoing, has seen all participants vote in favor of activating Aave&rsquo;s third iteration on the Ethereum blockchain. The protocol has called the v3 the most significant upgrade to Aave since its launch.</p>
<p>The voting is scheduled to end on the 25th of January, 2023, at 18:58 UTC. If the proposal is passed, it will be deployed on the 27th of January, 2023.</p>
Several New Improvements
<p>Ethereum is the Aave Protocol&rsquo;s first and largest market for borrowing and lending crypto capital on-chain. The protocol has rolled out v3 on other chains such as Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism, and Avalanche. v3 aims to improve capital efficiency, risk management, and user experience on Ethereum. The protocol is the largest lender in the DeFi ecosystem, with around $3.78 billion in Total Value Locked (TVL), according to DeFiLlama.</p>
<p>The move is being seen as significant by others in Ethereum&rsquo;s DeFi ecosystem, which depend on Aave for liquidity. Pseudo Anonymous spokesperson for the Lido Protocol, Kethfinex, stated that Aave v3 on Ethereum will help improve the borrowing and lending markets for Lido&rsquo;s staked ETH and called it a big step forward.</p>
New Features
<p>v3 will also bring new features such as eMode (efficiency mode) to Ethereum. However, this will initially be introduced in a limited manner. For the time being, Aave&rsquo;s v3 market on Ethereum will feature wBTC, wETH, wstETH, USDC, DAI, LINK, and AAVE. However, a key feature on v3, Isolation mode, will not be instantly enabled for assets when v3 launches. Isolation mode allows users to borrow a newly listed and risky asset up to a particular debt ceiling. Furthermore, v3 interest rate models also vary from v2, with the difference primarily due to stablecoin rates.</p>
<p>The author of the proposal, Bored Ghost Developing Labs, stated that the initial interest rates on v3 &ldquo;will follow those present on v2 Ethereum assets and other existing instances of v3.&rdquo;</p>
A Steady Decline In Numbers
<p>According to data sourced from DeFiLlama, Aave v2 ranks as the 5th largest protocol when it comes to Total Value Locked, behind other protocols such as Lido, MakerDAO, Curve, and WBTC. Aave v3 is operational on six chains, and its TVL currently stands at $525.96 million, meaning most of the Aave ecosystem activity takes place on v2 on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>However, user activity has seen a steady decline in the number of daily new users, according to Dune Analytics, which notes a 96% drop in daily new unique users. This drop can be attributed to the steady decline in incentives offered by the protocol. Some of the incentives offered by the protocol include interest rate discounts, reduced withdrawal fees, and earning additional interest on assets. The drop has also resulted in a decrease in the daily revenue generated by Aave.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[China's "Instagram" chooses Conflux Network for permissionless blockchain integration]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/chinas-instagram-chooses-conflux-network-for-permissionless-blockchain-integration</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-25_06-52-58_1674622414BiBvhYoROl.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-25_06-52-58_1674622414BiBvhYoROl.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-01-25_06-52-58_1674622414BiBvhYoROl.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/chinas-instagram-chooses-conflux-network-for-permissionless-blockchain-integration</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Toronto, Canada, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Little Red Book, (XiaohongShu), the Chinese version of Instagram integrates Conflux Network as permissionless blockchain allowing users to showcase NFTs minted on Conflux on their profile page in the digital collection section called &lsquo;R-Space&rsquo;.</p>
<p>The platform has more than 200 million active monthly users and this integration brings NFTs a step closer to mass adoption, where people are actively using Web3 technology on a daily basis within a Web2 system. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Little Red Book has previous alliances with blockchains and NFTs but never a permissionless network.&nbsp;</p>
Ming Wu, CTO of Conflux said &ldquo;large internet industry players in China have initiated efforts embracing the Web3 transition. Conflux is becoming the major bridge connecting the two worlds and taking a leadership role to expand Web3 technology into traditional industry scenarios.&rdquo;
<p>From a regulation perspective, having such a large-scale company integrate a permissionless blockchain further solidifies China&rsquo;s pro-NFT position and suggests we can expect an increase in local companies considering blockchain technology integration with existing Web2 companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The first Conflux NFT supported by Little Red Book is from the Mimic Shhans community, which has a large Chinese community base, and owners of the original NFT can go through a predefined process to receive the Conflux NFT that can be shown on their Little Red Book profile page.</p>
<p>To see full images please see the Dropbox link: &nbsp;https://www.dropbox.com/sh/s2i440p5hf2s2aw/AAC-JfdxXApMResEpMSqCjDEa?dl=0</p>
<p>About Conflux
Conflux is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols. Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. In the region, Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p>
<p>To learn more about Conflux, visit confluxnetwork.org</p>ContactMelissa TireyShift6 Studiosconflux@shift6studios.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Toronto, Canada, 24th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Little Red Book, (XiaohongShu), the Chinese version of Instagram integrates Conflux Network as permissionless blockchain allowing users to showcase NFTs minted on Conflux on their profile page in the digital collection section called &lsquo;R-Space&rsquo;.</p>
<p>The platform has more than 200 million active monthly users and this integration brings NFTs a step closer to mass adoption, where people are actively using Web3 technology on a daily basis within a Web2 system. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Little Red Book has previous alliances with blockchains and NFTs but never a permissionless network.&nbsp;</p>
Ming Wu, CTO of Conflux said &ldquo;large internet industry players in China have initiated efforts embracing the Web3 transition. Conflux is becoming the major bridge connecting the two worlds and taking a leadership role to expand Web3 technology into traditional industry scenarios.&rdquo;
<p>From a regulation perspective, having such a large-scale company integrate a permissionless blockchain further solidifies China&rsquo;s pro-NFT position and suggests we can expect an increase in local companies considering blockchain technology integration with existing Web2 companies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The first Conflux NFT supported by Little Red Book is from the Mimic Shhans community, which has a large Chinese community base, and owners of the original NFT can go through a predefined process to receive the Conflux NFT that can be shown on their Little Red Book profile page.</p>
<p>To see full images please see the Dropbox link: &nbsp;https://www.dropbox.com/sh/s2i440p5hf2s2aw/AAC-JfdxXApMResEpMSqCjDEa?dl=0</p>
<p>About Conflux
Conflux is a permissionless Layer 1 blockchain connecting decentralized economies across borders and protocols. Recently migrated to hybrid PoW/PoS consensus, Conflux provides a fast, secure, and scalable blockchain environment with zero congestion, low fees, and improved network security.</p>
<p>As the only regulatory-compliant public blockchain in China, Conflux provides a unique advantage for projects building and expanding into Asia. In the region, Conflux has collaborated with global brands and government entities on blockchain and metaverse initiatives, including the city of Shanghai, McDonald&rsquo;s China, and Oreo.</p>
<p>To learn more about Conflux, visit confluxnetwork.org</p>ContactMelissa TireyShift6 Studiosconflux@shift6studios.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Proposes “Recovery Corporation” to Repay Creditors]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-proposes-recovery-corporation-to-repay-creditors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/celsius-proposes-recovery-corporation-to-repay-creditors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The legal team of the bankrupt cryptocurrency lending firm Celsius Network LLC announced on Tuesday that the company is working on reinventing itself as a new, publicly traded &ldquo;recovery corporation,&rdquo; adding that it may issue a token to repay its creditors. </p>
<p>According to reports by Bloomberg and some additional information provided by CoinDesk, Celsius&rsquo;s legal team said that the crypto lender had devised a new plan to reinvent itself as a new, publicly traded &ldquo;recovery corporation&rdquo; to exit bankruptcy proceedings. The firm&rsquo;s new strategy, which, as it stands, has not yet received approval from the U.S. Trustee&rsquo;s Office, would issue a token called the Asset Share Token (AST) to its creditors with locked assets above a certain threshold that reflects the value of their assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Twitter user that often provides updates on the case, CelsiusFacts, has also claimed to have discovered details about the restructuring plan:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">BREAKING NEWS - #CelsiusNetwork is looking at having a stratefied recovery smaller holders bellow 5k might get all assets to leave.- Larger holders will get a debt token that seems to represent all the value, so you can sell if you dont believe in the company or recovery.</p>
&mdash; CelsiusFactsNumbers (@CelsiusFacts) January 24, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The legal team added that holders of the AST token would be able to hold their tokens which would entitle them to dividends over time, or they may sell them on the open cryptocurrency market. As for the rest, and the majority of Celsius&rsquo;s customers, estimated to be between 60% to 70%, they would receive a once-off distribution in liquid cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Ross Kwastaniet, a lawyer for Kirkland &amp; Ellis, the law firm representing the bankrupt lender, said:</p>

<p>[The distribution] would be at a discount. We&rsquo;re not envisioning a full recovery, but it&rsquo;s a meaningful recovery, Your Honor. Adding, &ldquo;It would be a one-time distribution in liquid crypto &ndash; call it bitcoin, ethereum, or stablecoins. Something that has, you know, readily tradable, readily ascertainable market value to everybody who has claims below a certain threshold.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The legal team has not disclosed the threshold amount for receiving a pay-out, with Kwastaniet adding that the firm was still in discussions over the dollar amount of the threshold.</p>
&ldquo;Recovery Corporation&rdquo; Being Pursued After Receiving No Attractive Bids for Assets
<p>Kwastaniet informed the court that Celsius chose to establish a &ldquo;recovery corporation&rdquo; after it received no worthwhile bids for its assets:</p>

<p>The bids we&rsquo;ve received for discrete assets and for the transfer of customer accounts have not been compelling.</p>

<p>He further stated:</p>

<p>The debtors can&rsquo;t just simply distribute their assets and move on, so to speak, because the bidding process has revealed that this would require us to sell many illiquid assets at what we believe are fire-sale prices. So, given that, the debtors are focused on placing their assets into a new [company] that would hold those assets and manage them over time to maximize value as markets improve.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The legal team of the bankrupt cryptocurrency lending firm Celsius Network LLC announced on Tuesday that the company is working on reinventing itself as a new, publicly traded &ldquo;recovery corporation,&rdquo; adding that it may issue a token to repay its creditors. </p>
<p>According to reports by Bloomberg and some additional information provided by CoinDesk, Celsius&rsquo;s legal team said that the crypto lender had devised a new plan to reinvent itself as a new, publicly traded &ldquo;recovery corporation&rdquo; to exit bankruptcy proceedings. The firm&rsquo;s new strategy, which, as it stands, has not yet received approval from the U.S. Trustee&rsquo;s Office, would issue a token called the Asset Share Token (AST) to its creditors with locked assets above a certain threshold that reflects the value of their assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Twitter user that often provides updates on the case, CelsiusFacts, has also claimed to have discovered details about the restructuring plan:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">BREAKING NEWS - #CelsiusNetwork is looking at having a stratefied recovery smaller holders bellow 5k might get all assets to leave.- Larger holders will get a debt token that seems to represent all the value, so you can sell if you dont believe in the company or recovery.</p>
&mdash; CelsiusFactsNumbers (@CelsiusFacts) January 24, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The legal team added that holders of the AST token would be able to hold their tokens which would entitle them to dividends over time, or they may sell them on the open cryptocurrency market. As for the rest, and the majority of Celsius&rsquo;s customers, estimated to be between 60% to 70%, they would receive a once-off distribution in liquid cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Ross Kwastaniet, a lawyer for Kirkland &amp; Ellis, the law firm representing the bankrupt lender, said:</p>

<p>[The distribution] would be at a discount. We&rsquo;re not envisioning a full recovery, but it&rsquo;s a meaningful recovery, Your Honor. Adding, &ldquo;It would be a one-time distribution in liquid crypto &ndash; call it bitcoin, ethereum, or stablecoins. Something that has, you know, readily tradable, readily ascertainable market value to everybody who has claims below a certain threshold.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The legal team has not disclosed the threshold amount for receiving a pay-out, with Kwastaniet adding that the firm was still in discussions over the dollar amount of the threshold.</p>
&ldquo;Recovery Corporation&rdquo; Being Pursued After Receiving No Attractive Bids for Assets
<p>Kwastaniet informed the court that Celsius chose to establish a &ldquo;recovery corporation&rdquo; after it received no worthwhile bids for its assets:</p>

<p>The bids we&rsquo;ve received for discrete assets and for the transfer of customer accounts have not been compelling.</p>

<p>He further stated:</p>

<p>The debtors can&rsquo;t just simply distribute their assets and move on, so to speak, because the bidding process has revealed that this would require us to sell many illiquid assets at what we believe are fire-sale prices. So, given that, the debtors are focused on placing their assets into a new [company] that would hold those assets and manage them over time to maximize value as markets improve.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Dusk Network launches Citadel: Zero-Knowledge KYC solution]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/dusk-network-launches-citadel-zero-knowledge-kyc-solution</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-15.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-15.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-15.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/dusk-network-launches-citadel-zero-knowledge-kyc-solution</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[Research submitted and first use cases in development
<p>Fintech scale-up Dusk Network presents Citadel, a zero-knowledge proof KYC solution where users and institutions are in control of sharing permissions and personal information. The framework can be used for all claim-based KYC requests and puts users in total control of what information they are sharing and with whom while being completely compliant and private at the same time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After months of research and submitting the official paper to arXiv, Citadel finally launches. It is one of the first decentralized Know Your Customer (KYC) solutions focusing on the financial ecosystem, that invites institutions to use the technology for cost-reducing compliance. As the user is in charge of his own data, it isn&rsquo;t necessary to do KYC with service providers that have already been used prior. Or for example, multiple KYC processes for the trade of one asset.&nbsp;</p>

&nbsp;
How does Citadel work
<p>Dusk Network is the first to integrate zero-knowledge technology KYC in a Layer-1 (L1) blockchain. It is a key feature of Dusk Network itself to implement it in its privacy-preserving protocol. Using the Citadel framework, an entity that is able to handle private information - for example, the company Dusk who is compliant with all necessary regulations and is allowed to handle private information, or a company that is verified to do KYC on behalf of institutions - can provide a list of requirements for their KYC verification. The user who needs to provide the KYC verification is able to provide the necessary information, share how long their information can be stored and can withdraw access to their data. The company will authenticate the data, which will be privately stored in the Dusk blockchain. To simplify: it is using non-fungible token (NFT) technology, where instead of an art piece, a license is created.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
&nbsp;

Use case
<p>If you open a bank account, you need to go through a KYC verification procedure and share personal information with your bank. If you then decide to do stock trading, you'll need to open an account with a brokerage service, where you will also have to do KYC/Anti-Money Laundering (AML). You will either have to share the same information with them, or your bank will provide it to them. If you buy a house and get a mortgage, you will also have to offer a lot of KYC/AML/personal information. All these players will keep your information and store it, which both has a big impact on your privacy and puts you at risk of data leakage.</p>
<p>Instead, if you use Citadel, you would store your data with one party who is only able to store and verify data, and other services can opt to accept the licenses and use that as KYC/AML proof. This significantly reduces risk and privacy exposure. In a fully on-chain world, you can buy regulated assets simply by providing a license that you're in compliance with the requirements of the trading platform. You can borrow money from a lending service by providing a license that meets their KYC and AML requirements. You can loan out money and get yield, simply by providing the license. No need to share personal information with the three parties. For safety measures, a quarterly confirmation of the correctness of all the provided data in the license, could help data stay up to date.</p>
Cost-reducing compliance
<p>Banks and financial institutions are often complaining that new regulations like the Travel Rule* and other Anti-Money Laundering measures are costly operations, costs that are also charged to the customer. The processes to meet the requirements are tedious, time-consuming and involve many unnecessary parties, making the process even more challenging. Citadel as a SSI protocol can provide the basis for a KYC service that could eliminate the need for financial institutions to do KYC/AML themselves and/or with third parties. It can significantly reduce the cost for gathering, protecting and renewing client information. A KYC provider built on Citadel will speed up processes and information is always up to date, real-time accessible and privacy-preserving. With Citadel, the client will be fully in charge of their own details, without unnecessary information duplication and a reduced risk of information leakage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Next to digital identity verification like in the use case above, Citadel can be used for privacy-preserving transactions and global compliance and much more.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[Research submitted and first use cases in development
<p>Fintech scale-up Dusk Network presents Citadel, a zero-knowledge proof KYC solution where users and institutions are in control of sharing permissions and personal information. The framework can be used for all claim-based KYC requests and puts users in total control of what information they are sharing and with whom while being completely compliant and private at the same time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After months of research and submitting the official paper to arXiv, Citadel finally launches. It is one of the first decentralized Know Your Customer (KYC) solutions focusing on the financial ecosystem, that invites institutions to use the technology for cost-reducing compliance. As the user is in charge of his own data, it isn&rsquo;t necessary to do KYC with service providers that have already been used prior. Or for example, multiple KYC processes for the trade of one asset.&nbsp;</p>

&nbsp;
How does Citadel work
<p>Dusk Network is the first to integrate zero-knowledge technology KYC in a Layer-1 (L1) blockchain. It is a key feature of Dusk Network itself to implement it in its privacy-preserving protocol. Using the Citadel framework, an entity that is able to handle private information - for example, the company Dusk who is compliant with all necessary regulations and is allowed to handle private information, or a company that is verified to do KYC on behalf of institutions - can provide a list of requirements for their KYC verification. The user who needs to provide the KYC verification is able to provide the necessary information, share how long their information can be stored and can withdraw access to their data. The company will authenticate the data, which will be privately stored in the Dusk blockchain. To simplify: it is using non-fungible token (NFT) technology, where instead of an art piece, a license is created.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
&nbsp;

Use case
<p>If you open a bank account, you need to go through a KYC verification procedure and share personal information with your bank. If you then decide to do stock trading, you'll need to open an account with a brokerage service, where you will also have to do KYC/Anti-Money Laundering (AML). You will either have to share the same information with them, or your bank will provide it to them. If you buy a house and get a mortgage, you will also have to offer a lot of KYC/AML/personal information. All these players will keep your information and store it, which both has a big impact on your privacy and puts you at risk of data leakage.</p>
<p>Instead, if you use Citadel, you would store your data with one party who is only able to store and verify data, and other services can opt to accept the licenses and use that as KYC/AML proof. This significantly reduces risk and privacy exposure. In a fully on-chain world, you can buy regulated assets simply by providing a license that you're in compliance with the requirements of the trading platform. You can borrow money from a lending service by providing a license that meets their KYC and AML requirements. You can loan out money and get yield, simply by providing the license. No need to share personal information with the three parties. For safety measures, a quarterly confirmation of the correctness of all the provided data in the license, could help data stay up to date.</p>
Cost-reducing compliance
<p>Banks and financial institutions are often complaining that new regulations like the Travel Rule* and other Anti-Money Laundering measures are costly operations, costs that are also charged to the customer. The processes to meet the requirements are tedious, time-consuming and involve many unnecessary parties, making the process even more challenging. Citadel as a SSI protocol can provide the basis for a KYC service that could eliminate the need for financial institutions to do KYC/AML themselves and/or with third parties. It can significantly reduce the cost for gathering, protecting and renewing client information. A KYC provider built on Citadel will speed up processes and information is always up to date, real-time accessible and privacy-preserving. With Citadel, the client will be fully in charge of their own details, without unnecessary information duplication and a reduced risk of information leakage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Next to digital identity verification like in the use case above, Citadel can be used for privacy-preserving transactions and global compliance and much more.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[EU Lawmakers Back More Stringent Rules for Banks Holding Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/eu-lawmakers-back-more-stringent-rules-for-banks-holding-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 06:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/eu-lawmakers-back-more-stringent-rules-for-banks-holding-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers in the European Union (EU) voted on and approved on Tuesday a draft law that would see banks in the bloc holding cryptocurrencies follow more stringent measures. </p>
EU Lawmakers Back Draft Law
<p>EU lawmakers on Tuesday voted to back a draft law to implement the final stage of post-financial global bank capital rules. According to reports by Reuters, the draft law added &ldquo;prohibitive&rdquo; requirements to cover risks from crypto assets. The so-called &ldquo;prohibitive&rdquo; measures would require banks to hold a punitive amount of capital to cover more than 100% of any loss from cryptocurrency companies and is in line with Basel III capital rules and is set to take effect from January 2025.</p>
<p>Previous reports indicated that one of the amendments up for a vote would require banks to set a risk-weighting of 1,250% to all capital with crypto exposure, meaning that banks could cover 100% of any potential losses.</p>
<p>The approval of this draft law is just an interim measure pending further and more comprehensive EU legislation in line with recommendations from global banking regulators. Markus Ferber, a member of the European Parliament, said that banks would have to hold a euro of their capital for every euro they hold in crypto assets. The regulator argues that since cryptocurrency is such a &ldquo;high-risk investment,&rdquo; it has become necessary to implement such a measure. Ferber added:</p>

<p>Such prohibitive capital requirements will help prevent instability in the crypto world from spilling over into the financial system.</p>

<p>The United States, Britain, and other countries are reportedly taking similar steps against the backdrop of integrating such a &ldquo;high-risk investment&rdquo; into the financial sector.</p>
<p>The Association for Financial Market in Europe (AFME), an industry body, however, noted that the draft law, as it stands, contains no definition of &ldquo;crypto assets&rdquo; and may well end up being applied to tokenized securities also. Reuters reports that EU states have already approved their versions of the draft law, negotiations between member states are set to take place, and a few amendments are expected.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers in the European Union (EU) voted on and approved on Tuesday a draft law that would see banks in the bloc holding cryptocurrencies follow more stringent measures. </p>
EU Lawmakers Back Draft Law
<p>EU lawmakers on Tuesday voted to back a draft law to implement the final stage of post-financial global bank capital rules. According to reports by Reuters, the draft law added &ldquo;prohibitive&rdquo; requirements to cover risks from crypto assets. The so-called &ldquo;prohibitive&rdquo; measures would require banks to hold a punitive amount of capital to cover more than 100% of any loss from cryptocurrency companies and is in line with Basel III capital rules and is set to take effect from January 2025.</p>
<p>Previous reports indicated that one of the amendments up for a vote would require banks to set a risk-weighting of 1,250% to all capital with crypto exposure, meaning that banks could cover 100% of any potential losses.</p>
<p>The approval of this draft law is just an interim measure pending further and more comprehensive EU legislation in line with recommendations from global banking regulators. Markus Ferber, a member of the European Parliament, said that banks would have to hold a euro of their capital for every euro they hold in crypto assets. The regulator argues that since cryptocurrency is such a &ldquo;high-risk investment,&rdquo; it has become necessary to implement such a measure. Ferber added:</p>

<p>Such prohibitive capital requirements will help prevent instability in the crypto world from spilling over into the financial system.</p>

<p>The United States, Britain, and other countries are reportedly taking similar steps against the backdrop of integrating such a &ldquo;high-risk investment&rdquo; into the financial sector.</p>
<p>The Association for Financial Market in Europe (AFME), an industry body, however, noted that the draft law, as it stands, contains no definition of &ldquo;crypto assets&rdquo; and may well end up being applied to tokenized securities also. Reuters reports that EU states have already approved their versions of the draft law, negotiations between member states are set to take place, and a few amendments are expected.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC’s Hester Peirce gives her lessons for the crypto industry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/sec-hester-pierce-gives-her-lessons-for-the-crypto-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hes.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hes.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hes.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/sec-hester-pierce-gives-her-lessons-for-the-crypto-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a conference speech last Friday, Commissioner Peirce gave a speech in which she recommended that the crypto industry take onboard the lessons learnt so far.</p>
<p>Commissioner Hester Peirce spoke at the Digital Assets at Duke Conference in Washington recently, and she had much advice for those who were building out the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
Lessons for crypto
<p>The main lesson she wanted to impart was to say that crypto shouldn&rsquo;t wait for the regulators to sort it out. Instead, people who promoted the industry would do better to &ldquo;root out harmful practices and encourage good behaviour&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Even as a regulating commissioner, Hester Peirce advised that regulatory solutions were more likely to be &ldquo;inflexible&rdquo;, and that they shouldn&rsquo;t be used as a first resort. She believed rather that voluntarily imposed solutions could be far more effective given that those imposing them understood their industry far better than the regulator.</p>
<p>Her second piece of advice was to remember the actual point of crypto, which wasn&rsquo;t trying to drive up prices or lending tokens to others to trade with. She said that the point was to solve various problems, and mentioned some of the multitude of use cases such as:</p>

<p>&ldquo;smart contracts, payments, provenance, identity, recordkeeping, data storage, prediction markets, tokenization of assets, and borderless human collaboration.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Thirdly, she suggested that each blockchain, crypto asset, or project should be taken on its own merits, and talking about it as just crypto obscured the important differences.</p>
<p>Fourth, she recommended that all new protocols be tested very carefully before release into public use, given that &ldquo;disastrous consequences&rdquo; could otherwise ensue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Fifth, the commissioner advised that people be extremely careful when dealing with any centralised crypto entities, and should take the same precautions as with any non-crypto company. By the same token, she suggested that crypto companies be careful to keep the trust that was invested in them by the public.</p>
<p>Sixth, Pierce laid out a list of lessons from traditional finance that were applicable to crypto. Doing due diligence on counterparties and the level of risk they would expose an investor to was highlighted as very important.</p>
An honest summation of the SEC
<p>While agreeing with Gary Gensler, chairman of the SEC on several important issues confronting the agency, one incredibly refreshing part of Commissioner Peirce&rsquo;s speech was her extremely candid summation of other issues that concern the SEC. She stated her view that the SEC interpretation of the Howey test was &ldquo;askew&rdquo;, and said the following on the SEC&rsquo;s general approach to crypto:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tell people to come down to the office to talk to us about their projects, plug the information they give us into our proprietary security-identifying algorithms, and then send the people home with a court date. Hardly a reasonable way forward, and one that results in what one lawyer has dubbed &ldquo;regulation by anxiety.&rdquo; Operating in such an opaque environment is very stressful for law-abiding people.&rdquo;</p>

A counter-voice in the SEC
<p>It cannot be argued that Commissioner Pierce&rsquo;s views on crypto are very refreshing. She has always let it be known that she would retain her independent thought and therefore she is an excellent foil to Gary Gensler, the chairman of the SEC.</p>
<p>Given the importance of crypto, and the likelihood that solutions for many issues in many areas of industry can be found here, it is a relief that someone of Hester Peirce&rsquo;s neutrality and good sense can be found in the regulatory space.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a conference speech last Friday, Commissioner Peirce gave a speech in which she recommended that the crypto industry take onboard the lessons learnt so far.</p>
<p>Commissioner Hester Peirce spoke at the Digital Assets at Duke Conference in Washington recently, and she had much advice for those who were building out the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
Lessons for crypto
<p>The main lesson she wanted to impart was to say that crypto shouldn&rsquo;t wait for the regulators to sort it out. Instead, people who promoted the industry would do better to &ldquo;root out harmful practices and encourage good behaviour&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Even as a regulating commissioner, Hester Peirce advised that regulatory solutions were more likely to be &ldquo;inflexible&rdquo;, and that they shouldn&rsquo;t be used as a first resort. She believed rather that voluntarily imposed solutions could be far more effective given that those imposing them understood their industry far better than the regulator.</p>
<p>Her second piece of advice was to remember the actual point of crypto, which wasn&rsquo;t trying to drive up prices or lending tokens to others to trade with. She said that the point was to solve various problems, and mentioned some of the multitude of use cases such as:</p>

<p>&ldquo;smart contracts, payments, provenance, identity, recordkeeping, data storage, prediction markets, tokenization of assets, and borderless human collaboration.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Thirdly, she suggested that each blockchain, crypto asset, or project should be taken on its own merits, and talking about it as just crypto obscured the important differences.</p>
<p>Fourth, she recommended that all new protocols be tested very carefully before release into public use, given that &ldquo;disastrous consequences&rdquo; could otherwise ensue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Fifth, the commissioner advised that people be extremely careful when dealing with any centralised crypto entities, and should take the same precautions as with any non-crypto company. By the same token, she suggested that crypto companies be careful to keep the trust that was invested in them by the public.</p>
<p>Sixth, Pierce laid out a list of lessons from traditional finance that were applicable to crypto. Doing due diligence on counterparties and the level of risk they would expose an investor to was highlighted as very important.</p>
An honest summation of the SEC
<p>While agreeing with Gary Gensler, chairman of the SEC on several important issues confronting the agency, one incredibly refreshing part of Commissioner Peirce&rsquo;s speech was her extremely candid summation of other issues that concern the SEC. She stated her view that the SEC interpretation of the Howey test was &ldquo;askew&rdquo;, and said the following on the SEC&rsquo;s general approach to crypto:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tell people to come down to the office to talk to us about their projects, plug the information they give us into our proprietary security-identifying algorithms, and then send the people home with a court date. Hardly a reasonable way forward, and one that results in what one lawyer has dubbed &ldquo;regulation by anxiety.&rdquo; Operating in such an opaque environment is very stressful for law-abiding people.&rdquo;</p>

A counter-voice in the SEC
<p>It cannot be argued that Commissioner Pierce&rsquo;s views on crypto are very refreshing. She has always let it be known that she would retain her independent thought and therefore she is an excellent foil to Gary Gensler, the chairman of the SEC.</p>
<p>Given the importance of crypto, and the likelihood that solutions for many issues in many areas of industry can be found here, it is a relief that someone of Hester Peirce&rsquo;s neutrality and good sense can be found in the regulatory space.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
