<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>What is PISS Coin And Why Is It Ranked in The Most Trending Cryptocurrency Tokens on DEXTools</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm</link><description>PISS coin, a unique cryptocurrency token, has captured attention as one of the most trending tokens on DEXTools.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this update, we delve into the intriguing world of PISS Coin, exploring its features, purpose, and the factors that have contributed to its rising popularity.  &lt;br /&gt;
Discover why PISS Coin has emerged as a notable player in the cryptocurrency market and the potential impact it may have on the evolving landscape of digital currencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm"&gt;Read More: What is PISS Coin And Why Is It Ranked in The Most Trending Cryptocurrency Tokens on DEXTools&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114475/276465/fwd8wjcxsaa-dzb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="66836"/></item><item><title>$SLUTS, $WAGMI, $LFG Join the Shitcoin List After Andrew Tate Tweet – 5 Best Meme Cryptos to Buy Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm</link><description>The crypto space has been inundated with many new meme coin projects launched in a short period.  &lt;br /&gt;
Some of these meme tokens went on to record huge gains, while others dumped after fifteen minutes of fame. &lt;br /&gt;
One such project that has enjoyed brief stardom is $SLUTS. The digital asset was launched on the back of a viral tweet by social media influencer Andrew Tate. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm"&gt;Read More: $SLUTS, $WAGMI, $LFG Join the Shitcoin List After Andrew Tate Tweet – 5 Best Meme Cryptos to Buy Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114474/276462/meme-coins.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="907000"/></item><item><title>SEC, Ripple Seeking One-Week Extension on Unsealing Hinman Documents</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission and Ripple have requested a one-week extension on unsealing the internal deliberations following a speech by former director William Hinman. &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, both the SEC and Ripple reportedly filed a request seeking to extend the deadline for the filing of multiple exhibits including the Hinman documents....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC, Ripple Seeking One-Week Extension on Unsealing Hinman Documents&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>SEC</category><category>Ripple</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114455/276425/9d2156dd21.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120035"/></item><item><title>AI Meme Crypto Presale AiDoge Hits $10 Million Raised - Now 70% Sold Out</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm</link><description>New AI powered meme generation tool AiDoge.com has now passed the $10 million mark in its ongoing presale, now over 70% complete. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin project, which introduces crypto’s first meme-to-earn model, has been generating a buzz in the crypto space. It is raking in funds at a brisk pace, having raised $10,136,059 at the time of writing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Meme Crypto Presale AiDoge Hits $10 Million Raised - Now 70% Sold Out&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114469/276451/aidoge-presale-progress.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="610051"/></item><item><title>The Political Memes Creating Generational Wealth - Wojak, Pepe, Copium, Chad Meme Coins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm</link><description>Meme coins have historically been seen as a way to generate interest in the crypto space and as a form of light-hearted humor as well as an investment vehicle, if a volatile one. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a number of them in 2023 are also delving into the political landscape, and helping many early buyers get rich in the process....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm"&gt;Read More: The Political Memes Creating Generational Wealth - Wojak, Pepe, Copium, Chad Meme Coins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114468/276450/meme-coins.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="875663"/></item><item><title>PSYOP Token Price Explodes 1,000% But Is It A Crypto Scam? - Best Meme Coins to Invest In Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm</link><description>The hot news in the cryptocurrency market today is the explosive rise of PSYOP token, with its price soaring by over 1,000%, and the coin ranked in the top trending assets on DEXTools. &lt;br /&gt;
However, despite its positive price action there have been questions posed about the legitimacy of the new crypto project....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm"&gt;Read More: PSYOP Token Price Explodes 1,000% But Is It A Crypto Scam? - Best Meme Coins to Invest In Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114451/276426/listing.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="38532"/></item><item><title>Controversial Recoveries, Promising Partnerships, Regulation Gambling and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Controversial Recoveries, Promising Partnerships, Regulation Gambling and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114340/276255/fwqatnhakautuc7.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="70363"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Holds At $26,800 – Is $30,000 the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin price continues to captivate investors as it holds steady at $26,800.  &lt;br /&gt;
With this stability, market analysts and enthusiasts are now wondering if $30,000 will be the next target for BTC.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this Bitcoin price prediction, we will explore the factors and predictions surrounding the Bitcoin price and delve into the possibilities of reaching this significant milestone....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Holds At $26,800 – Is $30,000 the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114445/276419/20-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="529326"/></item><item><title>Mantle: BitDAO token will be Mantle after BIP-21 Vote</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm</link><description>BitDAO's native token BIT is set to rebrand to Mantle after the community voted in favor of a proposal seeking to optimize the token ahead of the launch of a new layer-2 mainnet. &lt;br /&gt;
The measure was approved by a majority vote as part of the BIP-21 proposal, which sought to unify the BitDAO ecosystem under a “One brand, One token” principle....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm"&gt;Read More: Mantle: BitDAO token will be Mantle after BIP-21 Vote&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>BitDAO</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Token</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114444/276412/bitdao-meta-image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="331341"/></item><item><title>Ripple Adds Nielsen CFO to Its Board of Directors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm</link><description>Ripple is bringing on the chief financial officer of market researcher Nielsen to its board of directors, the crypto firm announced on Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
Warren Jenson was added to the board and was also appointed as Ripple’s chair of the audit committee, overseeing the auditing process of Ripple’s operations, according to a press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple Adds Nielsen CFO to Its Board of Directors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Career</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114439/276406/screen-shot-2023-05-19-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="761798"/></item><item><title>South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</link><description>South Korea’s Justice Ministry has hit out at claims that Minister Han Dong-hoon “refused to disclose information” about whether or not he owns crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Newsis, the ministry claimed that “the cryptoasset holding status of public officials who work with cryptoasset [regulation]” is “checked regularly.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Politics</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114373/276294/adobestock-555291710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="304195"/></item><item><title>Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</link><description>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. made campaign promises on Friday advocating for bitcoin users, adding that he plans to accept campaign donations in bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable,” Kennedy said at the Bitcoin 2023 Conference in Miami. &lt;br /&gt;
Kennedy, who is the nephew of former President John F. Kennedy and the son of Robert F. Kennedy, announced his run for US president last month. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Presidential campaign</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114436/276402/screen-shot-2023-05-03-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="570501"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</link><description>The battle between Bitcoin and the $27,000 mark continues, with the cryptocurrency struggling to make headway in the face of mounting economic challenges. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a ray of hope is beginning to break through the macroeconomic clouds as Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell suggests a possible abatement in rate increases.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the face of mounting cryptocurrency market uncertainty, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>BGB</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>RNDR</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>INJ</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Render Token</category><category>Injective</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114440/276407/19-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="338633"/></item><item><title>NFT Influencer Ben.eth Rakes in $7 Million in PSYOP Meme Coin Presale – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Pseudonymous NFT collector turned celebrity meme coin creator Ben.eth has raked in a huge more than $7 million in ETH sales in the past seven days via a presale of his next memecoin called $PSYOP. &lt;br /&gt;
Investors were eager to get in on Ben.eth’s latest meme coin project in wake of the success of his first meme coin launch called $BEN....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: NFT Influencer Ben.eth Rakes in $7 Million in PSYOP Meme Coin Presale – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ben.eth</category><category>PSYOP</category><category>Presale</category><category>ETH</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114438/276403/ben-eth.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="355940"/></item><item><title>Bankrupt Crypto Firm Celsius May Receive Second Chance from Wall Street</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm</link><description>The now-bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network may get a second chance with the help of Wall Street investment giants. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Wall Street Journal article from Thursday, two groups of investment heavyweights are currently engaged in a bidding war for what remains of Celsius, close to a year after the lender filed for bankruptcy in New York....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankrupt Crypto Firm Celsius May Receive Second Chance from Wall Street&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114395/276330/celsius-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="124729"/></item><item><title>Global Payments Giant Visa Experiments with Ethereum's Goerli Testnet – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Global payments giant Visa has used Ethereum's Goerli testnet to try out transaction-free payments with the help of account abstraction.  &lt;br /&gt;
On-chain data shows that Visa used a smart contract called Paymaster, allowing the company to take advantage of account abstraction to perform complex tasks on behalf of accounts and manage transaction costs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Global Payments Giant Visa Experiments with Ethereum's Goerli Testnet – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Visa</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Smart Contract</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114377/276302/19ec1be016-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="56740"/></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Introduce ‘First Bipartisan Bill’ Blocking a CBDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm</link><description>US lawmakers from both sides of the aisle introduced a bill this week to block the Federal Reserve from issuing a central bank digital currency.  &lt;br /&gt;
Republican Rep. French Hill of Arkansas and Democratic Rep. Jake Auchincloss of Massachusetts introduced the bill this week, dubbed the Power of the Mint Act.  &lt;br /&gt;
Hill said it was the first bipartisan bill in Congress to block the central bank from issuing a CBDC, on the House floor this week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: US Lawmakers Introduce ‘First Bipartisan Bill’ Blocking a CBDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Legislation</category><category>French Hill</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114430/276384/us-capitol-g6d9c63c16-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="104371"/></item><item><title>US CFTC Chair Rostin Behnam Says DeFi Crypto Exchanges Can Be Regulated – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and other aspects of the decentralized finance (DeFi) world can be regulated in the US, even though it is “just code,” according to Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) chair Rostin Behnam....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: US CFTC Chair Rostin Behnam Says DeFi Crypto Exchanges Can Be Regulated – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CFTC</category><category>SEC</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114429/276383/rostin-behnam.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1187381"/></item><item><title>President Biden’s Crypto Mining Tax “Isn’t Going To Happen,” Sen. Lummis Says</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm</link><description>US Sen. Cynthia Lummis is not a fan of President Biden’s proposed 30 percent tax on cryptocurrency miners.  &lt;br /&gt;
“That isn't going to happen,” the Wyoming Republican and crypto enthusiast, said on Friday at Bitcoin 2023 Conference in Miami.  &lt;br /&gt;
There are environmental benefits including “not venting gases into the atmosphere as well as stabilizing grids,” Lummis said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm"&gt;Read More: President Biden’s Crypto Mining Tax “Isn’t Going To Happen,” Sen. Lummis Says&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Cynthia Lummis</category><category>President Joe Biden</category><category>Mining</category><category>Taxes</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114423/276382/cl-official-portrait-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="720776"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction Following Fed Chair Powell's Speech – Is the Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>Fed Chair Powell's recent speech has sparked significant interest and speculation within the financial community.  &lt;br /&gt;
As one of the most influential figures in the global economy, Powell's remarks carry substantial weight and have the potential to impact various sectors, including the cryptocurrency market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors are analyzing his statements for insights into the future direction of monetary policy and its potential effects on Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction Following Fed Chair Powell's Speech – Is the Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114419/276378/19-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481296"/></item></channel></rss>
