<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 04:12:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Privacy Landscape of Remote Working]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/navigating-the-privacy-landscape-of-remote-working</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/remote.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/remote.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/remote.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:25:25 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/navigating-the-privacy-landscape-of-remote-working</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>For millions of businesses and their employees globally, remote work is the &lsquo;new normal&rsquo;. Over the last three years, the migration to this working style has revealed numerous benefits on both sides, such as happier and more productive workforces, as well as employees who enjoy greater flexibility and the death of the commute. Unfortunately, it&rsquo;s not all rosy. The transition to remote work has created untold challenges for the cybersecurity industry, IT departments, and distributed teams, particularly regarding private and secure communications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With so much work now being done from home, co-working spaces, temporary accommodation, and caf&eacute;s, the line between personal and professional life has become increasingly blurred. With the same devices often being used for all digital work and leisure activities, it leaves individuals vulnerable to potential privacy breaches. The privacy landscape has evolved and mutated, with newer and uglier threats. Now, it is undeniably more important than ever to prioritize individual sovereignty when maintaining privacy in order to mitigate the potential risks, such as cyberattacks, data breaches, and spying (employee surveillance) that are associated with remote work.</p>
<p>One of the most significant video communication breaches in recent times was the Zoom security incident in 2020. The incident involved unauthorized access to Zoom meetings and the stealing of user credentials. Another notable breach was the Microsoft Teams breach in 2021, where hackers could gain access to user accounts via a single sign-on (SSO) system.</p>
Insight &amp; Guidance on Personal Privacy for Remote Workers
<p>Maintaining privacy and security while working remotely, whether in your own country or abroad as a Digital Nomad (as they are commonly referred to), requires a great deal of awareness and practical strategies to combat malicious digital entities. You need to think about three things: your data, your communications, and your activities. These are the three most poignant areas that leave you exposed, especially in a remote work environment where you are theoretically changing wi-fi networks more frequently (if using caf&eacute;s, temporary accommodation, and co-working spaces).&nbsp;</p>
<p>So, how can you effectively navigate the privacy landscape? It all starts with self-awareness and understanding the privacy risks and potential threats. Once you understand the risks, you&rsquo;re more likely to take actions to protect yourself, such as the use of end-to-end encryption tools. Apps such as Telegram or Signal for messaging, Relayz for video calls, and ProtonMail for emails are all leveraging end-to-end encryption to protect their users.</p>
<p>With the right knowledge and tools in place, you should next consider some of the low-hanging fruit for personal privacy and protection, such as strong passwords and two-factor authentication. These, typically used in tandem, can stop unwanted or unauthorized access to your accounts. You&rsquo;ll want to secure your home network too, keep any hardware or software up to date, make the password impossible to guess, and, depending on the nature of your work and activities, make use of a Virtual Private Network (VPN) too. If you are constantly on the move as a nomadic remote worker, you might want to look at portable hardware for guaranteeing a secure internet connection, instead of trusting potentially harmful and compromised public wi-fi networks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The final piece of guidance seems like common sense, but in fact, it&rsquo;s the way that people most frequently get hacked or have their privacy compromised. Be cautious about what you share online. Personal details, your home address, bank account information, your passport or ID cards - they can all be used against you. Oversharing is one of the most common ways for your accounts and privacy to be compromised. Your social media accounts are a treasure trove of information.&nbsp;</p>
Ultimate Borderless Communications
<p>Remote workers, many of whom have the liberty to travel as they work, come to realize that they need borderless solutions with end-to-end encryption. This is especially true for video communications, due to the way in which video is now commonly used by distributed teams to keep in touch regarding work and projects. Video calls have become particularly vulnerable to privacy breaches, with the major comms providers simply not doing enough to guarantee user safety. Fortunately, Relayz uses end-to-end encryption to prioritize privacy, security, and user experience in its communications solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Relayz is a decentralized communication platform designed for the Web3 era, offering hyper-secure and privacy-preserving video conferencing for the masses. Built on blockchain technology, Relayz delivers quantum-resistant end-to-end encryption and industry-leading HD video quality, all wrapped up in a user-friendly interface. Relayz was created by a team of industry experts and developers who recognized the shortcomings of traditional video communication products and developed a blockchain-based rival technology that overcomes them.</p>
<p>For remote workers and digital nomads, Relayz appears to provide the privacy, security, and convenience needed for confident and confidential communications. Conversations and data are protected from potential privacy breaches, while user experience and interface are constantly being optimized for maximum usability. The video communications market has a new major player.</p>
Don&rsquo;t Panic, Simply Prioritize Privacy Solutions
<p>In an increasingly digital world, privacy and security are paramount, especially for the growing number of remote workers and digital nomads. By understanding the risks, utilizing best practices, and leveraging technology solutions like Relayz, it's possible to safeguard personal information and protect sensitive data from prying eyes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Whether you're communicating with colleagues or conducting business on the go, secure end-to-end encrypted video calls, secure wi-fi networks, and strong passwords should be a fundamental part of your work toolkit. So, the question remains: are you doing enough to protect your privacy as a remote worker? As the world of work continues to evolve, it's up to each individual to take responsibility for their own privacy and security, to ensure they can work confidently and securely, no matter where they are.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For millions of businesses and their employees globally, remote work is the &lsquo;new normal&rsquo;. Over the last three years, the migration to this working style has revealed numerous benefits on both sides, such as happier and more productive workforces, as well as employees who enjoy greater flexibility and the death of the commute. Unfortunately, it&rsquo;s not all rosy. The transition to remote work has created untold challenges for the cybersecurity industry, IT departments, and distributed teams, particularly regarding private and secure communications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With so much work now being done from home, co-working spaces, temporary accommodation, and caf&eacute;s, the line between personal and professional life has become increasingly blurred. With the same devices often being used for all digital work and leisure activities, it leaves individuals vulnerable to potential privacy breaches. The privacy landscape has evolved and mutated, with newer and uglier threats. Now, it is undeniably more important than ever to prioritize individual sovereignty when maintaining privacy in order to mitigate the potential risks, such as cyberattacks, data breaches, and spying (employee surveillance) that are associated with remote work.</p>
<p>One of the most significant video communication breaches in recent times was the Zoom security incident in 2020. The incident involved unauthorized access to Zoom meetings and the stealing of user credentials. Another notable breach was the Microsoft Teams breach in 2021, where hackers could gain access to user accounts via a single sign-on (SSO) system.</p>
Insight &amp; Guidance on Personal Privacy for Remote Workers
<p>Maintaining privacy and security while working remotely, whether in your own country or abroad as a Digital Nomad (as they are commonly referred to), requires a great deal of awareness and practical strategies to combat malicious digital entities. You need to think about three things: your data, your communications, and your activities. These are the three most poignant areas that leave you exposed, especially in a remote work environment where you are theoretically changing wi-fi networks more frequently (if using caf&eacute;s, temporary accommodation, and co-working spaces).&nbsp;</p>
<p>So, how can you effectively navigate the privacy landscape? It all starts with self-awareness and understanding the privacy risks and potential threats. Once you understand the risks, you&rsquo;re more likely to take actions to protect yourself, such as the use of end-to-end encryption tools. Apps such as Telegram or Signal for messaging, Relayz for video calls, and ProtonMail for emails are all leveraging end-to-end encryption to protect their users.</p>
<p>With the right knowledge and tools in place, you should next consider some of the low-hanging fruit for personal privacy and protection, such as strong passwords and two-factor authentication. These, typically used in tandem, can stop unwanted or unauthorized access to your accounts. You&rsquo;ll want to secure your home network too, keep any hardware or software up to date, make the password impossible to guess, and, depending on the nature of your work and activities, make use of a Virtual Private Network (VPN) too. If you are constantly on the move as a nomadic remote worker, you might want to look at portable hardware for guaranteeing a secure internet connection, instead of trusting potentially harmful and compromised public wi-fi networks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The final piece of guidance seems like common sense, but in fact, it&rsquo;s the way that people most frequently get hacked or have their privacy compromised. Be cautious about what you share online. Personal details, your home address, bank account information, your passport or ID cards - they can all be used against you. Oversharing is one of the most common ways for your accounts and privacy to be compromised. Your social media accounts are a treasure trove of information.&nbsp;</p>
Ultimate Borderless Communications
<p>Remote workers, many of whom have the liberty to travel as they work, come to realize that they need borderless solutions with end-to-end encryption. This is especially true for video communications, due to the way in which video is now commonly used by distributed teams to keep in touch regarding work and projects. Video calls have become particularly vulnerable to privacy breaches, with the major comms providers simply not doing enough to guarantee user safety. Fortunately, Relayz uses end-to-end encryption to prioritize privacy, security, and user experience in its communications solution.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Relayz is a decentralized communication platform designed for the Web3 era, offering hyper-secure and privacy-preserving video conferencing for the masses. Built on blockchain technology, Relayz delivers quantum-resistant end-to-end encryption and industry-leading HD video quality, all wrapped up in a user-friendly interface. Relayz was created by a team of industry experts and developers who recognized the shortcomings of traditional video communication products and developed a blockchain-based rival technology that overcomes them.</p>
<p>For remote workers and digital nomads, Relayz appears to provide the privacy, security, and convenience needed for confident and confidential communications. Conversations and data are protected from potential privacy breaches, while user experience and interface are constantly being optimized for maximum usability. The video communications market has a new major player.</p>
Don&rsquo;t Panic, Simply Prioritize Privacy Solutions
<p>In an increasingly digital world, privacy and security are paramount, especially for the growing number of remote workers and digital nomads. By understanding the risks, utilizing best practices, and leveraging technology solutions like Relayz, it's possible to safeguard personal information and protect sensitive data from prying eyes.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Whether you're communicating with colleagues or conducting business on the go, secure end-to-end encrypted video calls, secure wi-fi networks, and strong passwords should be a fundamental part of your work toolkit. So, the question remains: are you doing enough to protect your privacy as a remote worker? As the world of work continues to evolve, it's up to each individual to take responsibility for their own privacy and security, to ensure they can work confidently and securely, no matter where they are.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[How Banksters Is Redefining Fantasy Trading with Blockchain and NFT Integration]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/how-banksters-is-redefining-fantasy-trading-with-blockchain-and-nft-integration</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-164245.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-164245.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-164245.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/how-banksters-is-redefining-fantasy-trading-with-blockchain-and-nft-integration</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>NFT gaming is no longer just a niche concept in the world of blockchain gaming. As more and more games incorporate NFT assets and mechanics, it's become an established part of the blockchain gaming landscape. Players are starting to see the value in owning unique digital assets that can be used both inside and outside of games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Banksters, currently in their open beta, is a new blockchain-based mobile game that is set to revolutionize the world of trading and gaming. The game's unique concept combines NFTs with fantasy trading to create an innovative experience that is both entertaining and educational. A survey of NFT game developers conducted by Game Marketing Genie found that the most popular genre of NFT games is currently trading card games. While this isn&rsquo;t directly correlated with Banksters, there are undoubtedly trading and collectible game elements in the game, reaffirming that when Banksters fully launches, the interest in the game will soar to even further heights.</p>
<p>Banksters is a PvP (Player versus player) game that explores the world of fantasy trading, where players predict the market flow, influence it, and earn rewards. The game uses &lsquo;Banksters&rsquo; - Digital avatars as playable characters, with unique sets of abilities to influence gameplay depending on its class. Players can choose their avatar with special powers to impact market rates, customize it, mine in-game currency, and use it as an entry fee to win Investment runs. Players can also challenge friends and other players to know who the best Bankster is.</p>
<p>The Importance of Learning about Trading Strategies and Market Trends</p>
<p>Banksters is an ideal game for those interested in learning about trading strategies and market trends. Players can learn about technical analysis, market psychology, and risk management, all while having fun in a virtual environment. Banksters' educational aspect makes it a unique gaming experience, and players can transfer the knowledge they gain from the game to real-life trading scenarios, almost like a gamified twin of usual trading.</p>
<p>Banksters provides players with real-time market data, and players have to predict how the market will move and strategize accordingly. This feature provides an immersive experience that simulates real-world market conditions. By competing with other players, players can test their skills, learn new strategies, and hone their trading skills.</p>
<p>In the world of blockchain-based games, the value of the gaming ecosystem is too often tied solely to the fluctuation of token prices. When token prices are up, interest in the game increases, but any decline in price leads to a mass exodus of players. This model is unsustainable and has been likened to a Ponzi scheme by industry experts who see it as relying on a constant flow of new entrants to sustain itself.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this model tends to attract players who are solely focused on earning tokens rather than engaging with the game itself. As a result, the gaming sector experiences a mass exodus during bear markets in crypto.</p>
<p>Banksters prioritizes innovation and community over token price, and promises to bring new and exciting capabilities to NFT gaming. By transcending beyond the questionable models employed by existing blockchain games, Banksters aims to create a sustainable and engaging gaming ecosystem.</p>
<p>Differentiating from the competition</p>
<p>The game's avatars are BANKSTERS - digital avatars with unique sets of abilities that influence gameplay depending on their class. Players can choose their avatar and customize it with special powers to impact market rates. These powers give players an edge over their opponents, allowing them to earn rewards and climb the ranks.</p>
<p>Banksters is a game that requires strategy, skill, and knowledge of market trends. Players have to predict how the market will move, strategize accordingly, and use their avatar's unique powers to influence the market in their favor. By competing with other players, players can test their skills, learn new strategies, and hone their trading skills.</p>
<p>One of the most innovative aspects of Banksters is how it separates the game's value from the price of its native token. This means that players can enjoy the game and its rewards without being overly concerned about token fluctuations. Whether the token goes up or down, players can still win by mastering the game's mechanics and making smart trading decisions. This makes Banksters a unique and refreshing addition to the world of blockchain gaming, where many games are tied closely to cryptocurrency prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By prioritizing the user experience and offering a game that's both fun and educational, Banksters is helping to push the evolution of the metaverse forward, bringing more players into the world of fantasy trading and NFT gaming.</p>
<p>About Banksters:</p>
<p>Banksters is an NFT-based Play &amp; Earn game about crypto, mining, and investments, making it one of the few projects that attract different areas of interest from the crypto world, especially the trading audience. Users are now able to influence the outcome of their investments, even when the market goes in an undesirable direction.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NFT gaming is no longer just a niche concept in the world of blockchain gaming. As more and more games incorporate NFT assets and mechanics, it's become an established part of the blockchain gaming landscape. Players are starting to see the value in owning unique digital assets that can be used both inside and outside of games.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Banksters, currently in their open beta, is a new blockchain-based mobile game that is set to revolutionize the world of trading and gaming. The game's unique concept combines NFTs with fantasy trading to create an innovative experience that is both entertaining and educational. A survey of NFT game developers conducted by Game Marketing Genie found that the most popular genre of NFT games is currently trading card games. While this isn&rsquo;t directly correlated with Banksters, there are undoubtedly trading and collectible game elements in the game, reaffirming that when Banksters fully launches, the interest in the game will soar to even further heights.</p>
<p>Banksters is a PvP (Player versus player) game that explores the world of fantasy trading, where players predict the market flow, influence it, and earn rewards. The game uses &lsquo;Banksters&rsquo; - Digital avatars as playable characters, with unique sets of abilities to influence gameplay depending on its class. Players can choose their avatar with special powers to impact market rates, customize it, mine in-game currency, and use it as an entry fee to win Investment runs. Players can also challenge friends and other players to know who the best Bankster is.</p>
<p>The Importance of Learning about Trading Strategies and Market Trends</p>
<p>Banksters is an ideal game for those interested in learning about trading strategies and market trends. Players can learn about technical analysis, market psychology, and risk management, all while having fun in a virtual environment. Banksters' educational aspect makes it a unique gaming experience, and players can transfer the knowledge they gain from the game to real-life trading scenarios, almost like a gamified twin of usual trading.</p>
<p>Banksters provides players with real-time market data, and players have to predict how the market will move and strategize accordingly. This feature provides an immersive experience that simulates real-world market conditions. By competing with other players, players can test their skills, learn new strategies, and hone their trading skills.</p>
<p>In the world of blockchain-based games, the value of the gaming ecosystem is too often tied solely to the fluctuation of token prices. When token prices are up, interest in the game increases, but any decline in price leads to a mass exodus of players. This model is unsustainable and has been likened to a Ponzi scheme by industry experts who see it as relying on a constant flow of new entrants to sustain itself.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this model tends to attract players who are solely focused on earning tokens rather than engaging with the game itself. As a result, the gaming sector experiences a mass exodus during bear markets in crypto.</p>
<p>Banksters prioritizes innovation and community over token price, and promises to bring new and exciting capabilities to NFT gaming. By transcending beyond the questionable models employed by existing blockchain games, Banksters aims to create a sustainable and engaging gaming ecosystem.</p>
<p>Differentiating from the competition</p>
<p>The game's avatars are BANKSTERS - digital avatars with unique sets of abilities that influence gameplay depending on their class. Players can choose their avatar and customize it with special powers to impact market rates. These powers give players an edge over their opponents, allowing them to earn rewards and climb the ranks.</p>
<p>Banksters is a game that requires strategy, skill, and knowledge of market trends. Players have to predict how the market will move, strategize accordingly, and use their avatar's unique powers to influence the market in their favor. By competing with other players, players can test their skills, learn new strategies, and hone their trading skills.</p>
<p>One of the most innovative aspects of Banksters is how it separates the game's value from the price of its native token. This means that players can enjoy the game and its rewards without being overly concerned about token fluctuations. Whether the token goes up or down, players can still win by mastering the game's mechanics and making smart trading decisions. This makes Banksters a unique and refreshing addition to the world of blockchain gaming, where many games are tied closely to cryptocurrency prices.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By prioritizing the user experience and offering a game that's both fun and educational, Banksters is helping to push the evolution of the metaverse forward, bringing more players into the world of fantasy trading and NFT gaming.</p>
<p>About Banksters:</p>
<p>Banksters is an NFT-based Play &amp; Earn game about crypto, mining, and investments, making it one of the few projects that attract different areas of interest from the crypto world, especially the trading audience. Users are now able to influence the outcome of their investments, even when the market goes in an undesirable direction.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Internet Computer (ICP) and Aptos (APT) Decrease in Value While Sparklo (SPRK) Presale Gains Momentum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/internet-computer-icp-and-aptos-apt-decrease-in-value-while-sparklo-sprk-presale-gains-momentum</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-162411.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-162411.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-162411.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/internet-computer-icp-and-aptos-apt-decrease-in-value-while-sparklo-sprk-presale-gains-momentum</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Investors and traders are consistently on the lookout for new blockchain-based projects that can provide them with significant returns. They are also aware of the value surrounding the process of diversifying a portfolio.</p>
<p class="s5">With the recent decrease and downward trend surrounding the Internet Computer (ICP) and Aptos (APT) cryptocurrencies, they have moved towards presale-stage projects like Sparklo that can provide significant returns. Today, we will be going over each one of these cryptocurrencies to see how far they can climb in regard to value.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) To Revolutionize Investments in Gold, Silver, and Platinum</p>
<p class="s5">Sparklo will be an innovative platform for alternative investments that will enable anyone an opportunity to make investments in, and trade fractionalized non-fungible tokens (NFTs), all of which are backed by silver, gold, and platinum.</p>
<p class="s5">The Sparklo platform will also work with jewelry stores to help them bring their products to market and also enable investors to get benefits such as first access to new products as well as t discounts.</p>
<p class="s5">When it comes to its security, it has been audited by the InterFi Network. Sparklo will also have its liquidity locked for 100 years.</p>
<p class="s5">As for the presale stage, the SPRK token trades at $0.017. Analysts predict that its value can climb 40x in the upcoming months, and as such, investors and traders will want to get in on the project early to get the most significant gains.</p>
<p class="s9">Internet Computer (ICP) Down 6.8% in The Last 24 Hours</p>
<p class="s5">DFINITY made an announcement that smart contracts on top of Bitcoin are made possible on Internet computers (ICP). Through the usage of ckBTC, coding BTC is simple, according to the team.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, DFINITY also announced that a decentralized, permissionless governance system known as the NNS also runs on Internet computers (ICP).</p>
<p class="s5">Despite both of these developments, as of May 2, 2023, the Internet Computer (ICP) cryptocurrency trades at $5.68. </p>
<p class="s5">In the last 30 days, Internet Computer (ICP) saw an increase in value by 9%. However, in the last 24 hours, its value has begun to decline, as Internet Computer (ICP) decreased by 6.8%.</p>
<p class="s9">Aptos (APT) Sees Decrease of 11.9%</p>
<p class="s5">Aptos (APT) also made waves within the WEb3 space, where they announced Laptops Labs and that the Aptos Foundation will support and develop the network and ecosystem, while Labs will develop the tooling and products on the blockchain.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, Aptos (APT) also partnered with Mastercard and will create an on-chain identity and verification framework with a variety of applications in regard to payments, remittances, ticketing, and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p class="s5">When we go over the value of the Aptos (APT) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $9.91. In the last 30 days, the Aptos (APT) cryptocurrency saw a decrease in its value by 11.9%.</p>
<p class="s5">In the last 24 hours, it began to see an additional decrease of 2.2%, and this has left investors worried about the future of Aptos (APT).</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Investors and traders are consistently on the lookout for new blockchain-based projects that can provide them with significant returns. They are also aware of the value surrounding the process of diversifying a portfolio.</p>
<p class="s5">With the recent decrease and downward trend surrounding the Internet Computer (ICP) and Aptos (APT) cryptocurrencies, they have moved towards presale-stage projects like Sparklo that can provide significant returns. Today, we will be going over each one of these cryptocurrencies to see how far they can climb in regard to value.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPARKLO TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) To Revolutionize Investments in Gold, Silver, and Platinum</p>
<p class="s5">Sparklo will be an innovative platform for alternative investments that will enable anyone an opportunity to make investments in, and trade fractionalized non-fungible tokens (NFTs), all of which are backed by silver, gold, and platinum.</p>
<p class="s5">The Sparklo platform will also work with jewelry stores to help them bring their products to market and also enable investors to get benefits such as first access to new products as well as t discounts.</p>
<p class="s5">When it comes to its security, it has been audited by the InterFi Network. Sparklo will also have its liquidity locked for 100 years.</p>
<p class="s5">As for the presale stage, the SPRK token trades at $0.017. Analysts predict that its value can climb 40x in the upcoming months, and as such, investors and traders will want to get in on the project early to get the most significant gains.</p>
<p class="s9">Internet Computer (ICP) Down 6.8% in The Last 24 Hours</p>
<p class="s5">DFINITY made an announcement that smart contracts on top of Bitcoin are made possible on Internet computers (ICP). Through the usage of ckBTC, coding BTC is simple, according to the team.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, DFINITY also announced that a decentralized, permissionless governance system known as the NNS also runs on Internet computers (ICP).</p>
<p class="s5">Despite both of these developments, as of May 2, 2023, the Internet Computer (ICP) cryptocurrency trades at $5.68. </p>
<p class="s5">In the last 30 days, Internet Computer (ICP) saw an increase in value by 9%. However, in the last 24 hours, its value has begun to decline, as Internet Computer (ICP) decreased by 6.8%.</p>
<p class="s9">Aptos (APT) Sees Decrease of 11.9%</p>
<p class="s5">Aptos (APT) also made waves within the WEb3 space, where they announced Laptops Labs and that the Aptos Foundation will support and develop the network and ecosystem, while Labs will develop the tooling and products on the blockchain.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, Aptos (APT) also partnered with Mastercard and will create an on-chain identity and verification framework with a variety of applications in regard to payments, remittances, ticketing, and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p class="s5">When we go over the value of the Aptos (APT) cryptocurrency, on May 2, 2023, it traded at $9.91. In the last 30 days, the Aptos (APT) cryptocurrency saw a decrease in its value by 11.9%.</p>
<p class="s5">In the last 24 hours, it began to see an additional decrease of 2.2%, and this has left investors worried about the future of Aptos (APT).</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s12">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s12">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Toncoin (TON), Conflux (CFX), and Tradecurve (TCRV) Are Set to Reward Investors Massively in 2023.]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/toncoin-ton-conflux-cfx-and-tradecurve-tcrv-are-set-to-reward-investors-massively-in-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-163529.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-163529.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-163529.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/toncoin-ton-conflux-cfx-and-tradecurve-tcrv-are-set-to-reward-investors-massively-in-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Investors seeking massive returns in 2023 should consider Toncoin (TON), Conflux (CFX), and Tradecurve (TCRV). Specifically, Tradecurve (TCRV), a new hybrid exchange token, is set to reward investors with 50x gains.</p>
<p class="s5">Summary </p>
● Toncoin gains the backing of popular hardware wallet SafePal
● Conflux scales up with Zk technologies
● Tradecurve introduces a challenger trading platform
<p class="s10">Toncoin gains the backing of popular hardware wallet SafePal</p>
<p class="s5">Toncoin is a decentralised layer-1 blockchain that provides its customers with fast, transparent, and secure payment services, facilitating transactions with minimal fees and third-party applications. While the general crypto market was on a steady decline last year, $TON had a different story as the year wrapped up.</p>
<p class="s5">Capital.com reports that Telegram-backed cryptocurrency Toncoin (TON) rallied significantly as the number of wallet holders was on a steady increase in December 2022. Earlier, Toncoin made headlines as popular hardware wallet SafePal announced it would be the first wallet to support the coin. The announcement led to a surge in the token&rsquo;s price by around 8%.</p>
<p class="s5">Following data on Changelly, $TON has been in a good upward trend for the last 7 days, increasing by 13.5%.</p>
<p class="s10">Tradecurve introduces a challenger trading platform</p>
<p class="s5">Tradecurve is a new platform that allows users to trade a variety of financial assets from one account. It aims to give users the best trading experience while allowing them to enjoy DeFiprivacy.</p>
<p class="s5">Users on Tradecurve do not need to complete KYC. Once they sign up with email and deposit any crypto of their choice, they can explore other financial markets like stocks, forex, and commodities. Also, they enjoy high leverage, algorithmic trading, access to a decentralisedwallet, excellent customer support, exclusive deposit bonuses and level-up perks. Additionally, they don&rsquo;t have to bother about prevailing problems in regular exchanges like high fees, lack of transparency, limited asset class, regulatory issues, etc. This is because Tradecurve allows users to trade crypto and financial markets all from one account. And as a permissionless exchange, users can connect their wallets, deposit crypto and trade 24/7 non-stop. Furthermore, holders of the $TCRV token enjoy a discount on trading fees, staking rewards, and more. Interested investors can purchase the token from the ongoing presale and expect 50x gains as predicted by experts.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s12">Conflux scales up with Zk technologies</p>
<p class="s5">Conflux is a public layer-1 blockchain designed to power dApps, e-commerce, and Web 3.0 infrastructure by being more scalable, decentralised, and secure than existing protocols. Recently, Conflux announced a new zero-knowledge (ZK) strategy in partnership with Accseal, a company that specializes in building ZK-accelerating chips.</p>
<p class="s5">This partnership aims to seek out the most advanced ZK technologies and solutions that can be integrated into the Conflux ecosystem. Also, the project will leverage this development to ramp up scalability.</p>
<p class="s5">Already, Conflux boasts a thriving NFT ecosystem, with over 150 enterprises minting and selling NFTs on the network. Now with ZK solutions, the number of NFTs will continue to grow exponentially and positively impact the token&rsquo;s price. Conflux (CFX) is trading at $0.296 as of press time.</p>
<p class="s14">Find out more about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale here:</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s14">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Investors seeking massive returns in 2023 should consider Toncoin (TON), Conflux (CFX), and Tradecurve (TCRV). Specifically, Tradecurve (TCRV), a new hybrid exchange token, is set to reward investors with 50x gains.</p>
<p class="s5">Summary </p>
● Toncoin gains the backing of popular hardware wallet SafePal
● Conflux scales up with Zk technologies
● Tradecurve introduces a challenger trading platform
<p class="s10">Toncoin gains the backing of popular hardware wallet SafePal</p>
<p class="s5">Toncoin is a decentralised layer-1 blockchain that provides its customers with fast, transparent, and secure payment services, facilitating transactions with minimal fees and third-party applications. While the general crypto market was on a steady decline last year, $TON had a different story as the year wrapped up.</p>
<p class="s5">Capital.com reports that Telegram-backed cryptocurrency Toncoin (TON) rallied significantly as the number of wallet holders was on a steady increase in December 2022. Earlier, Toncoin made headlines as popular hardware wallet SafePal announced it would be the first wallet to support the coin. The announcement led to a surge in the token&rsquo;s price by around 8%.</p>
<p class="s5">Following data on Changelly, $TON has been in a good upward trend for the last 7 days, increasing by 13.5%.</p>
<p class="s10">Tradecurve introduces a challenger trading platform</p>
<p class="s5">Tradecurve is a new platform that allows users to trade a variety of financial assets from one account. It aims to give users the best trading experience while allowing them to enjoy DeFiprivacy.</p>
<p class="s5">Users on Tradecurve do not need to complete KYC. Once they sign up with email and deposit any crypto of their choice, they can explore other financial markets like stocks, forex, and commodities. Also, they enjoy high leverage, algorithmic trading, access to a decentralisedwallet, excellent customer support, exclusive deposit bonuses and level-up perks. Additionally, they don&rsquo;t have to bother about prevailing problems in regular exchanges like high fees, lack of transparency, limited asset class, regulatory issues, etc. This is because Tradecurve allows users to trade crypto and financial markets all from one account. And as a permissionless exchange, users can connect their wallets, deposit crypto and trade 24/7 non-stop. Furthermore, holders of the $TCRV token enjoy a discount on trading fees, staking rewards, and more. Interested investors can purchase the token from the ongoing presale and expect 50x gains as predicted by experts.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s12">Conflux scales up with Zk technologies</p>
<p class="s5">Conflux is a public layer-1 blockchain designed to power dApps, e-commerce, and Web 3.0 infrastructure by being more scalable, decentralised, and secure than existing protocols. Recently, Conflux announced a new zero-knowledge (ZK) strategy in partnership with Accseal, a company that specializes in building ZK-accelerating chips.</p>
<p class="s5">This partnership aims to seek out the most advanced ZK technologies and solutions that can be integrated into the Conflux ecosystem. Also, the project will leverage this development to ramp up scalability.</p>
<p class="s5">Already, Conflux boasts a thriving NFT ecosystem, with over 150 enterprises minting and selling NFTs on the network. Now with ZK solutions, the number of NFTs will continue to grow exponentially and positively impact the token&rsquo;s price. Conflux (CFX) is trading at $0.296 as of press time.</p>
<p class="s14">Find out more about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale here:</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s14">Presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s14">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p class="s14">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Injective (INJ), Kava (KAVA) Shows Bearish Market Movement As Yachtify (YCHT) Keeps Surging Higher]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/injective-inj-kava-kava-shows-bearish-market-movement-as-yachtify-ycht-keeps-surging-higher</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161023.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161023.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161023.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/injective-inj-kava-kava-shows-bearish-market-movement-as-yachtify-ycht-keeps-surging-higher</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Many cryptocurrencies have lost value during the bear season, such as Injective (INJ) and Kava (KAVA). Investors are looking for potential new technologies to invest in for the upcoming bull run because the price of current outdated coins is declining. </p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify has a lot of development potential and might very well end up being a blue-chip cryptocurrency. </p>
<p class="s5">Injective (INJ) High Withdrawal Fee Despite Bearish Run</p>
<p class="s5">The launch of the WazirX INR market for Injective (INJ) demonstrates the exchange's dedication to growing its offerings and giving customers a variety of trading options. The action is a big step toward satisfying the changing needs of the Indian crypto community and is a response to the rising demand for INR trading pairs.</p>
<p class="s5">Users could withdraw Injective (INJ) a few days after the listing, according to a recent blog post from WazirX, ensuring easy access to their money. The Indian exchange firm recently declared that it has stopped providing services of the Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) marketplace, despite the positive news of the Indian Rupee's listing on the platform. </p>
<p class="s5">TheNewsCrypto media reports that the WazirX exchange charges a 30.43 USDT withdrawal fee for withdrawals of at least 60.80 USDT. In spite of this knowledge, Injective (INJ) has traded poorly during the last 24 hours. The price of the digital coin Injective (INJ) has dropped by 2.41%, and Injective (INJ) is now trading at $7.43; $7.38 acts as a support level, and $7.96 acts as a resistance level.</p>
<p class="s5">Market Structure Shows Kava (KAVA) Price Analysis</p>
<p class="s5">At the time of writing, Kava (KAVA) is ranked 99th on CoinMarketCap. The forecast for the price of Kava (KAVA) in 2023 is described below with a daily time period. </p>
<p class="s5">Horizontal channel patterns, commonly referred to as sideways trends, were put down by Kava (KAVA). The horizontal channel typically develops during a period of price consolidation. In this pattern, the price action is contained between the horizontally parallel upper trendline, which links the highs, and the lower trendline, which connects the lows.</p>
<p class="s5">As the buying and selling points are consolidating, a horizontal channel is frequently regarded as one of the effective patterns for timing the market.</p>
<p class="s5">The cost of kava (KAVA) was $0.7931 at the time of analysis. The price of Kava (KAVA) may rise to the resistance levels of $0.847 and $0.954 if the pattern trend persists. The price of Kava (KAVA) may drop to support $0.754 if the trend changes.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Yachtify Revolutionizing Yacht Industry through Digital Finance</p>
<p class="s5">With its fractional private boat ownership model, Yachtify Protocol offers investors a special chance to participate in a maritime sector with numerous revenue sources that is recession-proof. By doing this, we let crypto users access the wealthy and powerful's private yacht market.</p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify is conducting a presale that is in Stage One and costs $0.1 right now. For as long as they have the tokens, presale investors can profit from a portion of the platform fees. In more tangible terms, they can profit from their ownership by renting out the yacht they own. Investors can feel secure knowing that the liquidity will be permanently locked and that the Yachtify network has completed an InterFi network KYC.</p>
<p>Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://yachtify.market/</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market/login</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Many cryptocurrencies have lost value during the bear season, such as Injective (INJ) and Kava (KAVA). Investors are looking for potential new technologies to invest in for the upcoming bull run because the price of current outdated coins is declining. </p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify has a lot of development potential and might very well end up being a blue-chip cryptocurrency. </p>
<p class="s5">Injective (INJ) High Withdrawal Fee Despite Bearish Run</p>
<p class="s5">The launch of the WazirX INR market for Injective (INJ) demonstrates the exchange's dedication to growing its offerings and giving customers a variety of trading options. The action is a big step toward satisfying the changing needs of the Indian crypto community and is a response to the rising demand for INR trading pairs.</p>
<p class="s5">Users could withdraw Injective (INJ) a few days after the listing, according to a recent blog post from WazirX, ensuring easy access to their money. The Indian exchange firm recently declared that it has stopped providing services of the Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT) marketplace, despite the positive news of the Indian Rupee's listing on the platform. </p>
<p class="s5">TheNewsCrypto media reports that the WazirX exchange charges a 30.43 USDT withdrawal fee for withdrawals of at least 60.80 USDT. In spite of this knowledge, Injective (INJ) has traded poorly during the last 24 hours. The price of the digital coin Injective (INJ) has dropped by 2.41%, and Injective (INJ) is now trading at $7.43; $7.38 acts as a support level, and $7.96 acts as a resistance level.</p>
<p class="s5">Market Structure Shows Kava (KAVA) Price Analysis</p>
<p class="s5">At the time of writing, Kava (KAVA) is ranked 99th on CoinMarketCap. The forecast for the price of Kava (KAVA) in 2023 is described below with a daily time period. </p>
<p class="s5">Horizontal channel patterns, commonly referred to as sideways trends, were put down by Kava (KAVA). The horizontal channel typically develops during a period of price consolidation. In this pattern, the price action is contained between the horizontally parallel upper trendline, which links the highs, and the lower trendline, which connects the lows.</p>
<p class="s5">As the buying and selling points are consolidating, a horizontal channel is frequently regarded as one of the effective patterns for timing the market.</p>
<p class="s5">The cost of kava (KAVA) was $0.7931 at the time of analysis. The price of Kava (KAVA) may rise to the resistance levels of $0.847 and $0.954 if the pattern trend persists. The price of Kava (KAVA) may drop to support $0.754 if the trend changes.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Yachtify Revolutionizing Yacht Industry through Digital Finance</p>
<p class="s5">With its fractional private boat ownership model, Yachtify Protocol offers investors a special chance to participate in a maritime sector with numerous revenue sources that is recession-proof. By doing this, we let crypto users access the wealthy and powerful's private yacht market.</p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify is conducting a presale that is in Stage One and costs $0.1 right now. For as long as they have the tokens, presale investors can profit from a portion of the platform fees. In more tangible terms, they can profit from their ownership by renting out the yacht they own. Investors can feel secure knowing that the liquidity will be permanently locked and that the Yachtify network has completed an InterFi network KYC.</p>
<p>Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://yachtify.market/</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market/login</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Price Prediction for Synthetix Network (SNX) Token, Liquity (LTQY), and Uwerx (WERX): These Cryptos Are Expected to Deliver Significant Gains This Year]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/price-prediction-for-synthetix-network-snx-token-liquity-ltqy-and-uwerx-werx-these-cryptos-are-expected-to-deliver-significant-gains-this-year</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161833.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161833.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-161833.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/price-prediction-for-synthetix-network-snx-token-liquity-ltqy-and-uwerx-werx-these-cryptos-are-expected-to-deliver-significant-gains-this-year</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) is a decentralized crypto project that rose to popularity with its non-blockchain assets. Liquity (LTQY) is another innovative project based on Ethereum that enables users to draw loans. Uwerx is an upcoming project that intends to revolutionize the freelance industry and provide numerous benefits to freelancers and investors. </p>
<p class="s6">The price prediction for Synthetix Network (SNX), Liquity (LTQY), and Uwerx is expected to be positive this year. Read on to know more about the expected gains of these three projects in 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) Price Surges With Its Robust Liquidity</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) provides deep liquidity and low fees. Its popularity is due to its role as a backend for multiple projects built on Ethereum and Optimism. Synthetix Network (SNX) focuses on widening the crypto space by including non-blockchain assets, which results in easy access to a robust financial market. </p>
<p class="s6">The current price of Synthetix Network (SNX) is $2.37, and its 24-hour trading volume is $31,427,115. Analysts predict a positive price momentum for Synthetix Network (SNX). The token is expected to increase to $4.13 by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) to Outperform Other Cryptos With Its Unique Features</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx will focus on the freelance industry, aiming to bring about better rewards for freelancers and substantial returns for investors. The freelance industry is undergoing rapid growth due to the increasing shift of businesses toward the gig economy. As per a Forbes report, 20% of companies stated that they will increase their dependence on freelancers in 2021, with an additional 60% stating their dependence was consistent with the previous year. </p>
<p class="s6">While the freelance sector is burgeoning, it also faces many problems like lack of trust, overt control by middlemen, transactional hurdles, expensive fees, and more. Uwerx is expected to overcome the obstacles faced by the industry with its decentralized blockchain technology. Being built on the Polygon network, it grabs attention with its unique characteristics, such as:</p>
● Incentivization that will serve as motivation and increase engagement for freelancers
● Integrated collaboration tools for efficient work processes
● Personalized matching that will help freelancers find the right projects
● Transparent pricing that would ensure increased trust and an equitable marketplace
● An inbuilt conflict resolution system
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) Shows Positive Price Prediction</p>
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) is a decentralized crypto platform that focuses on enabling efficient loan processing. Built on the Ethereum network, the Liquity (LTQY) platform allows Ether holders to draw loans in LQTY form. Loan issuance fees and redemption are algorithmically adjusted. </p>
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) is now available at the price of $1.47 and has a 24-hour trading volume of $10,197,324. Price prediction for Liquity (LTQY) indicates a positive uptrend in 2023, and the price is expected to increase to a maximum value of $3.49 by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) Price Prediction</p>
<p class="s6">The current price of the Uwerx token is $0.012 and is expected to increase as the ongoing presale progresses. Once the presale ends, the liquidity will be locked and remain so for 25 years.</p>
<p class="s6">As a project with real-world value and tangible users, Uwerx could solve many of the issues that plague the freelance market. Its full audit approval by InterFi Network and Solidproofcompanies is an encouraging sign to prospective investors. Additionally, an announcement was made by the team that they gave up the ownership of smart contracts once taxes were reduced to zero.</p>
<p class="s6">We believe Uwerx can likely become a future blue-chip crypto used by millions worldwide. Analysts expect its price to increase to $1.20 by Q3/Q4 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Grabs the Attention of Whales</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) and Liquity (LTQY) have good price predictions, but the future outlook for Uwerx is excellent. Uwerx presale is in progress, and the huge response for the presale indicates the popularity and inherent value of the project. As experienced investors know, early projects with high growth potential, like Uwerx, can provide substantial gains. The various advantages and growth potential of Uwerx make it an ideal investment choice. </p>
<p class="s6">With its immense growth potential, its current price of $0.012 will increase as the presale progresses. Now is the best time to grab this crypto before it explodes in value. Visit the links below to know more about the Uwerx presale. </p>
<p class="s14">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s14">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) is a decentralized crypto project that rose to popularity with its non-blockchain assets. Liquity (LTQY) is another innovative project based on Ethereum that enables users to draw loans. Uwerx is an upcoming project that intends to revolutionize the freelance industry and provide numerous benefits to freelancers and investors. </p>
<p class="s6">The price prediction for Synthetix Network (SNX), Liquity (LTQY), and Uwerx is expected to be positive this year. Read on to know more about the expected gains of these three projects in 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) Price Surges With Its Robust Liquidity</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) provides deep liquidity and low fees. Its popularity is due to its role as a backend for multiple projects built on Ethereum and Optimism. Synthetix Network (SNX) focuses on widening the crypto space by including non-blockchain assets, which results in easy access to a robust financial market. </p>
<p class="s6">The current price of Synthetix Network (SNX) is $2.37, and its 24-hour trading volume is $31,427,115. Analysts predict a positive price momentum for Synthetix Network (SNX). The token is expected to increase to $4.13 by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) to Outperform Other Cryptos With Its Unique Features</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx will focus on the freelance industry, aiming to bring about better rewards for freelancers and substantial returns for investors. The freelance industry is undergoing rapid growth due to the increasing shift of businesses toward the gig economy. As per a Forbes report, 20% of companies stated that they will increase their dependence on freelancers in 2021, with an additional 60% stating their dependence was consistent with the previous year. </p>
<p class="s6">While the freelance sector is burgeoning, it also faces many problems like lack of trust, overt control by middlemen, transactional hurdles, expensive fees, and more. Uwerx is expected to overcome the obstacles faced by the industry with its decentralized blockchain technology. Being built on the Polygon network, it grabs attention with its unique characteristics, such as:</p>
● Incentivization that will serve as motivation and increase engagement for freelancers
● Integrated collaboration tools for efficient work processes
● Personalized matching that will help freelancers find the right projects
● Transparent pricing that would ensure increased trust and an equitable marketplace
● An inbuilt conflict resolution system
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) Shows Positive Price Prediction</p>
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) is a decentralized crypto platform that focuses on enabling efficient loan processing. Built on the Ethereum network, the Liquity (LTQY) platform allows Ether holders to draw loans in LQTY form. Loan issuance fees and redemption are algorithmically adjusted. </p>
<p class="s6">Liquity (LTQY) is now available at the price of $1.47 and has a 24-hour trading volume of $10,197,324. Price prediction for Liquity (LTQY) indicates a positive uptrend in 2023, and the price is expected to increase to a maximum value of $3.49 by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) Price Prediction</p>
<p class="s6">The current price of the Uwerx token is $0.012 and is expected to increase as the ongoing presale progresses. Once the presale ends, the liquidity will be locked and remain so for 25 years.</p>
<p class="s6">As a project with real-world value and tangible users, Uwerx could solve many of the issues that plague the freelance market. Its full audit approval by InterFi Network and Solidproofcompanies is an encouraging sign to prospective investors. Additionally, an announcement was made by the team that they gave up the ownership of smart contracts once taxes were reduced to zero.</p>
<p class="s6">We believe Uwerx can likely become a future blue-chip crypto used by millions worldwide. Analysts expect its price to increase to $1.20 by Q3/Q4 2023.</p>
<p class="s6">Uwerx (WERX) Presale Grabs the Attention of Whales</p>
<p class="s6">Synthetix Network (SNX) and Liquity (LTQY) have good price predictions, but the future outlook for Uwerx is excellent. Uwerx presale is in progress, and the huge response for the presale indicates the popularity and inherent value of the project. As experienced investors know, early projects with high growth potential, like Uwerx, can provide substantial gains. The various advantages and growth potential of Uwerx make it an ideal investment choice. </p>
<p class="s6">With its immense growth potential, its current price of $0.012 will increase as the presale progresses. Now is the best time to grab this crypto before it explodes in value. Visit the links below to know more about the Uwerx presale. </p>
<p class="s14">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s14">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s14">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s14">Website: https://www.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Reach 27605 - 9 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-reach-27605-9-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-reach-27605-9-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Reach 27605:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to experience strong negative momentum early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 28000 figure after Stops were elected below the 28059.16 level, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 29850 and 29466.76 levels.&nbsp; Traders pushed BTC/USD as low as the 27605.23 area during the depreciation, representing a test of a previous upside price objective associated with buying pressure that strengthened around the 27194.51 area.&nbsp; Significant buying and selling activity recently took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to buying pressure that increased around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishlly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28924.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28933.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Reach 27605:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to experience strong negative momentum early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 28000 figure after Stops were elected below the 28059.16 level, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 29850 and 29466.76 levels.&nbsp; Traders pushed BTC/USD as low as the 27605.23 area during the depreciation, representing a test of a previous upside price objective associated with buying pressure that strengthened around the 27194.51 area.&nbsp; Significant buying and selling activity recently took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to buying pressure that increased around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishlly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28924.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28933.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ethereum Attracts Crypto Whales With 8 Billion Trading Volume, Are Baby Doge Coin And Collateral Going To Surge Next?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ethereum-attracts-crypto-whales-with-8-billion-trading-volume-are-baby-doge-coin-and-collateral-going-to-surge-next</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-155532.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-155532.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-08-at-155532.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ethereum-attracts-crypto-whales-with-8-billion-trading-volume-are-baby-doge-coin-and-collateral-going-to-surge-next</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Since its Shanghai Upgrade Ethereum (ETH) has been in the spotlight worldwide. Ethereum (ETH) staking is on the rise, and its value continues to increase while other mainstream projects struggle. With bullish price predictions for May, investors are now asking if Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) and Collateral Network (COLT) will be the next best investments 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For COLT Presale Here&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Collateral Network Seeks To Revolutionize Crowdlending </p>
<p class="s6">Collateral Network (COLT) is believed to be the next high return presale of 2023. After price increases of 40% and an additional 26% rise predicted in May, the number of investors buying Collateral Network (COLT) tokens has exploded as each looks to maximize their potential returns. </p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Collateral Network&rsquo;s unique platform offers an alternative to traditional asset lending methods, using DeFi technology to help individuals unlock liquidity from their assets. </p>
<p class="s6">The challenger lender platform is designed for high value assets such as supercars, watches, yachts and diamonds, each of which is brought on-chain as an NFT, before being fractionalized and promoted to the Collateral Network (COLT) community. </p>
<p class="s6">Each NFT can be purchased in fractions, with investors lending small percentages of a loan until its fully funded. By lending money, investors can generate a passive income via a fixed interest rate, which is paid out until the loan is paid back. Should a borrower default on their loan however, their asset will be sold at a private auction to Collateral Network (COLT) token holders who purchased during the project's presale. </p>
<p class="s6">With the potential to revolutionize crowdlending, market experts have big expectations for Collateral Network (COLT), predicting it will rise to $0.35 over the next six months. Many speculate that additional price increases could also occur once COLT tokens are listed on major exchanges. </p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Ethereum Hits $1.9 Going Into May</p>
<p class="s6">Just five days into the month, Ethereum&rsquo;s (ETH) value has increased by 0.53%, taking the price of Ethereum (ETH) to $1,917.11. Its recent upgrade has triggered a huge increase in Ethereum (ETH) trading and staking activity, with more investors staking Ethereum (ETH) than ever. </p>
<p class="s6">In the final two weeks of April, investors staked 100,000 Ethereum (ETH), which equaled more than the whole of March. This monumental achievement has helped investors regain confidence in Ethereum (ETH) and has attracted many new investors in the process. </p>
<p class="s6">With additional Ethereum (ETH) price increases predicted, Ethereum (ETH) has attracted a number of crypto whales, causing its daily trading volume to pass $8 billion. </p>
<p class="s12">Can Baby Doge Coin Recover After Recent Price Dips?</p>
<p class="s6">With memecoin trading surging over the past week, Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) is expected to become one of the best investments over the next few months. However, not all investors are confident after Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) decreased in value by 15.12% during the first week of May. </p>
<p class="s6">Nonetheless, Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) has continued to grow in regards to both trading volume and number of holders. In the last thirty days, the number of unique wallets holding Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) has increased by almost 1000, and daily trading volume was up by 62.76% on the 5th of May. As the number of investors buying Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) continues to rise, analysts anticipate a price increase in the next two weeks. </p>
<p class="s6">One Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) is currently selling for $0.000000002535 at the time of writing, which is seen as a huge bargain to investors looking to profit on future Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) price surges. </p>
<p class="s13">Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/</p>
<p class="s13">Presale: https://app.collateralnetwork.io/register</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Since its Shanghai Upgrade Ethereum (ETH) has been in the spotlight worldwide. Ethereum (ETH) staking is on the rise, and its value continues to increase while other mainstream projects struggle. With bullish price predictions for May, investors are now asking if Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) and Collateral Network (COLT) will be the next best investments 2023. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For COLT Presale Here&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s9">Collateral Network Seeks To Revolutionize Crowdlending </p>
<p class="s6">Collateral Network (COLT) is believed to be the next high return presale of 2023. After price increases of 40% and an additional 26% rise predicted in May, the number of investors buying Collateral Network (COLT) tokens has exploded as each looks to maximize their potential returns. </p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Collateral Network&rsquo;s unique platform offers an alternative to traditional asset lending methods, using DeFi technology to help individuals unlock liquidity from their assets. </p>
<p class="s6">The challenger lender platform is designed for high value assets such as supercars, watches, yachts and diamonds, each of which is brought on-chain as an NFT, before being fractionalized and promoted to the Collateral Network (COLT) community. </p>
<p class="s6">Each NFT can be purchased in fractions, with investors lending small percentages of a loan until its fully funded. By lending money, investors can generate a passive income via a fixed interest rate, which is paid out until the loan is paid back. Should a borrower default on their loan however, their asset will be sold at a private auction to Collateral Network (COLT) token holders who purchased during the project's presale. </p>
<p class="s6">With the potential to revolutionize crowdlending, market experts have big expectations for Collateral Network (COLT), predicting it will rise to $0.35 over the next six months. Many speculate that additional price increases could also occur once COLT tokens are listed on major exchanges. </p>
<p></p>
<p class="s9">Ethereum Hits $1.9 Going Into May</p>
<p class="s6">Just five days into the month, Ethereum&rsquo;s (ETH) value has increased by 0.53%, taking the price of Ethereum (ETH) to $1,917.11. Its recent upgrade has triggered a huge increase in Ethereum (ETH) trading and staking activity, with more investors staking Ethereum (ETH) than ever. </p>
<p class="s6">In the final two weeks of April, investors staked 100,000 Ethereum (ETH), which equaled more than the whole of March. This monumental achievement has helped investors regain confidence in Ethereum (ETH) and has attracted many new investors in the process. </p>
<p class="s6">With additional Ethereum (ETH) price increases predicted, Ethereum (ETH) has attracted a number of crypto whales, causing its daily trading volume to pass $8 billion. </p>
<p class="s12">Can Baby Doge Coin Recover After Recent Price Dips?</p>
<p class="s6">With memecoin trading surging over the past week, Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) is expected to become one of the best investments over the next few months. However, not all investors are confident after Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) decreased in value by 15.12% during the first week of May. </p>
<p class="s6">Nonetheless, Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) has continued to grow in regards to both trading volume and number of holders. In the last thirty days, the number of unique wallets holding Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) has increased by almost 1000, and daily trading volume was up by 62.76% on the 5th of May. As the number of investors buying Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) continues to rise, analysts anticipate a price increase in the next two weeks. </p>
<p class="s6">One Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) is currently selling for $0.000000002535 at the time of writing, which is seen as a huge bargain to investors looking to profit on future Baby Doge Coin (BabyDoge) price surges. </p>
<p class="s13">Find out more about the Collateral Network presale here:</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://www.collateralnetwork.io/</p>
<p class="s13">Presale: https://app.collateralnetwork.io/register</p>
<p class="s13">Telegram: https://t.me/collateralnwk</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Collateralnwk</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Argentina bans crypto payment apps while Bolivia sells gold for dollars]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/argentina-bans-crypto-payment-apps-while-bolivia-sells-gold-for-dollars</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arg-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arg-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/arg-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:45:26 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/argentina-bans-crypto-payment-apps-while-bolivia-sells-gold-for-dollars</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Argentine government is obliged by the IMF to force crypto out of the reach of its citizens, while Bolivia takes the decision to sell half its gold reserves for US dollars.</p>
Argentina restricts crypto
<p>The banking industry and its world financial agencies such as the IMF are using their power and hold over desperate nations to impel them to force their citizens away from Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Central Bank of the Argentine Republic (BCRA) issued a statement recently that prohibits any crypto app from issuing payments in crypto, or carrying out operations that have anything to do with crypto transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It does say however that this does not apply to a crypto app that is regulated and that is also authorised by the central bank, but there are no details on how easy or difficult that process would be.</p>
<p>The reason for this move is the loan condition that was imposed on Argentina by the International Monetary Fund, which stipulated that the Argentine government must do more to restrict its citizens from engaging with cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>With an inflation rate of more than 100% the financial environment for citizens in Argentina is awful. For them to be told that they cannot make or accept payments in crypto through apps is a way of keeping them corralled inside a broken fiat banking system.</p>
<p>It can only be imagined how things might improve for the average citizen if they were to put a percentage of their wealth into Bitcoin. Their purchasing power with fiat currency can only go down, whereas Bitcoin is arguably about to start its bull run in earnest over the next few months.</p>
Bolivia sells its gold
<p>Bolivia is another very poor country in Latin America that is struggling to avoid a full economic crisis. According to Reuters, the country recently passed a law that enabled it to monetise its gold reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Bolivian government plans to buy mined gold from mining cooperatives in the country, and use this to trade on the international market. However, this will likely end up reducing the country&rsquo;s gold reserves and just result in Bolivia postponing the eventual crisis.</p>
El Salvador on the up
<p>Meanwhile, there is one success story in Latin America, namely El Salvador. Fitch credit rating agency upgraded the small country&rsquo;s credit rating from CC, to CCC+, given that it had paid off its global bond write-downs and the danger of default appeared to have receded.</p>
<p>It seems that a country that has adopted Bitcoin as legal tender is doing very well on it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>President Bukele tweeted that his country&rsquo;s expected budget surplus for 2024 could lead to yet another ratings upgrade. All this in spite of the IMF threatening the country over future loans and predicting that the country would fall into financial instability over its Bitcoin adoption.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Argentine government is obliged by the IMF to force crypto out of the reach of its citizens, while Bolivia takes the decision to sell half its gold reserves for US dollars.</p>
Argentina restricts crypto
<p>The banking industry and its world financial agencies such as the IMF are using their power and hold over desperate nations to impel them to force their citizens away from Bitcoin and cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Central Bank of the Argentine Republic (BCRA) issued a statement recently that prohibits any crypto app from issuing payments in crypto, or carrying out operations that have anything to do with crypto transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It does say however that this does not apply to a crypto app that is regulated and that is also authorised by the central bank, but there are no details on how easy or difficult that process would be.</p>
<p>The reason for this move is the loan condition that was imposed on Argentina by the International Monetary Fund, which stipulated that the Argentine government must do more to restrict its citizens from engaging with cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>With an inflation rate of more than 100% the financial environment for citizens in Argentina is awful. For them to be told that they cannot make or accept payments in crypto through apps is a way of keeping them corralled inside a broken fiat banking system.</p>
<p>It can only be imagined how things might improve for the average citizen if they were to put a percentage of their wealth into Bitcoin. Their purchasing power with fiat currency can only go down, whereas Bitcoin is arguably about to start its bull run in earnest over the next few months.</p>
Bolivia sells its gold
<p>Bolivia is another very poor country in Latin America that is struggling to avoid a full economic crisis. According to Reuters, the country recently passed a law that enabled it to monetise its gold reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Bolivian government plans to buy mined gold from mining cooperatives in the country, and use this to trade on the international market. However, this will likely end up reducing the country&rsquo;s gold reserves and just result in Bolivia postponing the eventual crisis.</p>
El Salvador on the up
<p>Meanwhile, there is one success story in Latin America, namely El Salvador. Fitch credit rating agency upgraded the small country&rsquo;s credit rating from CC, to CCC+, given that it had paid off its global bond write-downs and the danger of default appeared to have receded.</p>
<p>It seems that a country that has adopted Bitcoin as legal tender is doing very well on it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>President Bukele tweeted that his country&rsquo;s expected budget surplus for 2024 could lead to yet another ratings upgrade. All this in spite of the IMF threatening the country over future loans and predicting that the country would fall into financial instability over its Bitcoin adoption.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud Launches Cloudverse on Avalanche]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/alibaba-cloud-launches-cloudverse-on-avalanche</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/alibaba-x-avalanche-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/alibaba-x-avalanche-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/alibaba-x-avalanche-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/alibaba-cloud-launches-cloudverse-on-avalanche</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Alibaba Cloud, the cloud division of Chinese tech giant Alibaba, has announced that it is building a metaverse launchpad on the Avalanche blockchain called Cloudverse.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launchpad is designed to provide an end-to-end platform for companies to customize and maintain their metaverse spaces in an attempt to find innovative ways to engage with customers. Avalanche will supply the technology to construct the metaverse spaces, while Alibaba Cloud will contribute computing and storage resources. The partnership is Alibaba's second collaboration with a blockchain network in less than a month, following its agreement with Mysten Labs, developer of the Sui Layer 1 blockchain, to provide node services for validators on the network's testnet.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Through Cloudverse, builders will have access to various support systems, including interactive functions, continued operations, meta-economics, and events. Each metaverse space is expected to be ready within a month of the initial outreach. The platform's subnets allow operators to customize the blockchain according to specific requirements.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alibaba Cloud and Avalanche are hoping to build out and accelerate the development of metaverse ecosystems by combining their expertise, thereby creating new opportunities for users, developers, and businesses. The deployment of a secure and scalable metaverse infrastructure through blockchain technology could lead to more decentralized, secure, and interoperable metaverse platforms, unlocking new possibilities for the future of virtual reality.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The CEO and founder of Ava Labs, Emin G&uuml;n Sirer, claims that through Cloudverse, anyone could create a metaverse at any time. It takes only 15 minutes to spin up and set the chain, and builders can establish the turnkey and wallet in just a few hours. The technology has been designed to be simple and user-friendly, with all available tools being open source.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Avalanche operates one of the crypto industry's most robust smart contract platforms, offering infinite scalability and rapid transaction finalization. It employs a unique consensus protocol, Subnet infrastructure, and HyperSDK toolkit to enable businesses to effortlessly develop powerful, tailor-made blockchain solutions. Avalanche is an eco-friendly blockchain designed to cater to both Web3 developers and businesses, allowing them to build anything they want, however they want.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">MUA DAO, on the other hand, is a metaverse middleware infrastructure that offers a one-stop solution to empower enterprises and businesses in creating, operating, and managing digital assets compatible with multiple metaverse platforms. It does this through unified interfaces in the "MUAverse." MUA's proprietary MUAverse includes an AI-powered interactive engine that supports the rapid development and upscaling of universal engineering conditions across multiple metaverse platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The collaboration between Alibaba Cloud, Avalanche, and MUA DAO aims to provide an easy-to-use, high-performance, and cost-effective metaverse solution through Cloudverse. This launchpad enables businesses to create, customize, and maintain their metaverse spaces on the Avalanche blockchain. By leveraging Avalanche's high-performance smart contract platform and Alibaba Cloud's infrastructure offerings, businesses can develop secure and scalable metaverse environments, unlocking new opportunities for growth and innovation in the virtual world.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Alibaba Cloud, the cloud division of Chinese tech giant Alibaba, has announced that it is building a metaverse launchpad on the Avalanche blockchain called Cloudverse.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launchpad is designed to provide an end-to-end platform for companies to customize and maintain their metaverse spaces in an attempt to find innovative ways to engage with customers. Avalanche will supply the technology to construct the metaverse spaces, while Alibaba Cloud will contribute computing and storage resources. The partnership is Alibaba's second collaboration with a blockchain network in less than a month, following its agreement with Mysten Labs, developer of the Sui Layer 1 blockchain, to provide node services for validators on the network's testnet.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Through Cloudverse, builders will have access to various support systems, including interactive functions, continued operations, meta-economics, and events. Each metaverse space is expected to be ready within a month of the initial outreach. The platform's subnets allow operators to customize the blockchain according to specific requirements.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alibaba Cloud and Avalanche are hoping to build out and accelerate the development of metaverse ecosystems by combining their expertise, thereby creating new opportunities for users, developers, and businesses. The deployment of a secure and scalable metaverse infrastructure through blockchain technology could lead to more decentralized, secure, and interoperable metaverse platforms, unlocking new possibilities for the future of virtual reality.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The CEO and founder of Ava Labs, Emin G&uuml;n Sirer, claims that through Cloudverse, anyone could create a metaverse at any time. It takes only 15 minutes to spin up and set the chain, and builders can establish the turnkey and wallet in just a few hours. The technology has been designed to be simple and user-friendly, with all available tools being open source.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Avalanche operates one of the crypto industry's most robust smart contract platforms, offering infinite scalability and rapid transaction finalization. It employs a unique consensus protocol, Subnet infrastructure, and HyperSDK toolkit to enable businesses to effortlessly develop powerful, tailor-made blockchain solutions. Avalanche is an eco-friendly blockchain designed to cater to both Web3 developers and businesses, allowing them to build anything they want, however they want.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">MUA DAO, on the other hand, is a metaverse middleware infrastructure that offers a one-stop solution to empower enterprises and businesses in creating, operating, and managing digital assets compatible with multiple metaverse platforms. It does this through unified interfaces in the "MUAverse." MUA's proprietary MUAverse includes an AI-powered interactive engine that supports the rapid development and upscaling of universal engineering conditions across multiple metaverse platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The collaboration between Alibaba Cloud, Avalanche, and MUA DAO aims to provide an easy-to-use, high-performance, and cost-effective metaverse solution through Cloudverse. This launchpad enables businesses to create, customize, and maintain their metaverse spaces on the Avalanche blockchain. By leveraging Avalanche's high-performance smart contract platform and Alibaba Cloud's infrastructure offerings, businesses can develop secure and scalable metaverse environments, unlocking new opportunities for growth and innovation in the virtual world.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Halts Bitcoin Transactions Twice, Moves $4.4b in $BTC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-halts-bitcoin-transactions-twice-moves-4-point-4b-in-btc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-btc-issues-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-btc-issues-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-btc-issues-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-halts-bitcoin-transactions-twice-moves-4-point-4b-in-btc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance has had to pause Bitcoin ($BTC) withdrawals twice in a span of 12 hours this Sunday May 7. The exchange has moved a some $4.4 billion worth of Bitcoin (188,000 BTC) between its hot and cold wallets over the weekend. The move took place while the exchange halted BTC withdrawals twice due to network congestion as well as a large volume of pending transactions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The exchange has since resumed Bitcoin withdrawals and made adjustments to its fees to prevent future occurrences. Reports indicate that Binance is working on enabling BTC Lightning Network withdrawals to help mitigate such issues in the future.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to official information from Binance, the first pause occurred at about 8pm BST. In a tweet, the exchange explained the pause was due to &ldquo;congestion issues&rdquo; which was then promptly resolved about an hour-and-a-half later. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Six hours later, the exchange paused Bitcoin withdrawals for a second time, this time citing a &ldquo;large volume of pending transactions.&rdquo; They further explained that &ldquo;our set fees did not anticipate the recent surge in $BTC network gas fees.&rdquo; About two hours later, withdrawals were resumed and as of writing, there seem to be no more hiccups in the exchange&rsquo;s operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The temporary halt of BTC withdrawals can be partly attributed to the increasing adoption of Ordinal inscriptions, which function similarly to NFTs on the Bitcoin network. These inscriptions have contributed to a surge in transaction fees and a significant increase in the daily number of Bitcoin transactions. On April 30, the number of daily Bitcoin transactions reached a new all-time high of over 568,300, surpassing the previous peak during the 2017 bull run by nearly 78,000 transactions. This increase was also likely influenced by JPMorgan Chase's acquisition of First Republic.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's 24-hour trading volume has reached over $7.6 billion, according to blockchain analytics from CoinMarketCap, a figure which is which is more than eight times the volume of the next-largest crypto exchange, Coinbase. As a result of the weekend's events and the broader market conditions, Bitcoin's price has dropped by 3.4% over the past 24 hours, currently trading at $27,913.64.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The recent events surrounding Binance and the Bitcoin network highlight the challenges faced by major cryptocurrency exchanges in handling large volumes of transactions and maintaining smooth operations. Binance's decision to halt BTC withdrawals temporarily drew attention to the network's congestion and increased fees, prompting concerns among users and traders.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, Binance has taken steps to address these issues by adjusting its fees and exploring the implementation of BTC Lightning Network withdrawals. The Lightning Network is a layer-2 solution that allows for faster and cheaper transactions by creating off-chain payment channels, which can help alleviate network congestion and reduce fees.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Exchanges like Binance will need to adapt and innovate to maintain their competitive edge and ensure a more seamless trading experience for their users. Implementing solutions like the Lightning Network and adjusting fees in response to market conditions are key to this.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance has had to pause Bitcoin ($BTC) withdrawals twice in a span of 12 hours this Sunday May 7. The exchange has moved a some $4.4 billion worth of Bitcoin (188,000 BTC) between its hot and cold wallets over the weekend. The move took place while the exchange halted BTC withdrawals twice due to network congestion as well as a large volume of pending transactions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The exchange has since resumed Bitcoin withdrawals and made adjustments to its fees to prevent future occurrences. Reports indicate that Binance is working on enabling BTC Lightning Network withdrawals to help mitigate such issues in the future.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to official information from Binance, the first pause occurred at about 8pm BST. In a tweet, the exchange explained the pause was due to &ldquo;congestion issues&rdquo; which was then promptly resolved about an hour-and-a-half later. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Six hours later, the exchange paused Bitcoin withdrawals for a second time, this time citing a &ldquo;large volume of pending transactions.&rdquo; They further explained that &ldquo;our set fees did not anticipate the recent surge in $BTC network gas fees.&rdquo; About two hours later, withdrawals were resumed and as of writing, there seem to be no more hiccups in the exchange&rsquo;s operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The temporary halt of BTC withdrawals can be partly attributed to the increasing adoption of Ordinal inscriptions, which function similarly to NFTs on the Bitcoin network. These inscriptions have contributed to a surge in transaction fees and a significant increase in the daily number of Bitcoin transactions. On April 30, the number of daily Bitcoin transactions reached a new all-time high of over 568,300, surpassing the previous peak during the 2017 bull run by nearly 78,000 transactions. This increase was also likely influenced by JPMorgan Chase's acquisition of First Republic.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's 24-hour trading volume has reached over $7.6 billion, according to blockchain analytics from CoinMarketCap, a figure which is which is more than eight times the volume of the next-largest crypto exchange, Coinbase. As a result of the weekend's events and the broader market conditions, Bitcoin's price has dropped by 3.4% over the past 24 hours, currently trading at $27,913.64.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The recent events surrounding Binance and the Bitcoin network highlight the challenges faced by major cryptocurrency exchanges in handling large volumes of transactions and maintaining smooth operations. Binance's decision to halt BTC withdrawals temporarily drew attention to the network's congestion and increased fees, prompting concerns among users and traders.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, Binance has taken steps to address these issues by adjusting its fees and exploring the implementation of BTC Lightning Network withdrawals. The Lightning Network is a layer-2 solution that allows for faster and cheaper transactions by creating off-chain payment channels, which can help alleviate network congestion and reduce fees.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Exchanges like Binance will need to adapt and innovate to maintain their competitive edge and ensure a more seamless trading experience for their users. Implementing solutions like the Lightning Network and adjusting fees in response to market conditions are key to this.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[TUSD readies operation plan for international transition]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tusd-readies-operation-plan-for-international-transition</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_1683533207aWUKNNzxlO.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_1683533207aWUKNNzxlO.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Untitled_design_1683533207aWUKNNzxlO.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:00:38 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tusd-readies-operation-plan-for-international-transition</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>TrueUSD (TUSD), a leading stablecoin provider, announced its intention to implement a plan for the international transition of its management services, reflecting an emerging industry trend of international expansion. Since its inception in 2018, TUSD has led industry innovation in the stablecoin sector with a strong emphasis on client due diligence and regulatory compliance while growing its reserve portfolios in collaboration with a diversified network of financial institutions and fiduciaries. TrueUSD has proven to be one of the most trusted stablecoins during recent market volatility and disruption to the US banking sector.</p><p>The expansion and transition of TrueUSD&rsquo;s operations was part of the intention around its acquisition in 2020 and conditions are now appropriate to begin this next phase of portfolio review, consolidation and growth. While TrueUSD remains committed to serving all members of its global community, this announcement signifies TUSD&rsquo;s effort to further align itself with the development of the stablecoin sector against continued disruptions to the banking system and ongoing regulatory uncertainty.</p><p>About TrueUSD</p><p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is the first digital asset with live on-chain attestations by independent third-party institutions and is backed 1:1 with USD. So far, it has been listed on more than 100 trading platforms such as Binance and Huobi, and is live on 10+ mainstream public chains including Ethereum, TRON, Avalanche, BNB Chain, Fantom, and Polygon. TrueUSD is attested in real-time by The Network Firm LLP, an independent, industry-specialized accounting firm in the U.S., to ensure the 1:1 ratio of its USD reserve to the circulating token supply and the 100% collateral rate. With the integration of Chainlink PoR, TrueUSD becomes the first USD-Backed stablecoin to secure minting and further ensure transparency and reliability. Users can access the relevant data via the official website tusd.io at any time. TUSD was granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the Commonwealth of Dominica on October 7th 2022.</p><p>Website | Twitter | Medium | Discord | Telegram | YouTube | Instagram</p><p></p>ContactCristian Ngpr@trueusd.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 8th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>TrueUSD (TUSD), a leading stablecoin provider, announced its intention to implement a plan for the international transition of its management services, reflecting an emerging industry trend of international expansion. Since its inception in 2018, TUSD has led industry innovation in the stablecoin sector with a strong emphasis on client due diligence and regulatory compliance while growing its reserve portfolios in collaboration with a diversified network of financial institutions and fiduciaries. TrueUSD has proven to be one of the most trusted stablecoins during recent market volatility and disruption to the US banking sector.</p><p>The expansion and transition of TrueUSD&rsquo;s operations was part of the intention around its acquisition in 2020 and conditions are now appropriate to begin this next phase of portfolio review, consolidation and growth. While TrueUSD remains committed to serving all members of its global community, this announcement signifies TUSD&rsquo;s effort to further align itself with the development of the stablecoin sector against continued disruptions to the banking system and ongoing regulatory uncertainty.</p><p>About TrueUSD</p><p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is the first digital asset with live on-chain attestations by independent third-party institutions and is backed 1:1 with USD. So far, it has been listed on more than 100 trading platforms such as Binance and Huobi, and is live on 10+ mainstream public chains including Ethereum, TRON, Avalanche, BNB Chain, Fantom, and Polygon. TrueUSD is attested in real-time by The Network Firm LLP, an independent, industry-specialized accounting firm in the U.S., to ensure the 1:1 ratio of its USD reserve to the circulating token supply and the 100% collateral rate. With the integration of Chainlink PoR, TrueUSD becomes the first USD-Backed stablecoin to secure minting and further ensure transparency and reliability. Users can access the relevant data via the official website tusd.io at any time. TUSD was granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the Commonwealth of Dominica on October 7th 2022.</p><p>Website | Twitter | Medium | Discord | Telegram | YouTube | Instagram</p><p></p>ContactCristian Ngpr@trueusd.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The Sandbox Joins Affyn To Push Metaverse Interoperability ]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-sandbox-joins-affyn-to-push-metaverse-interoperability</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-46.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-46.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-46.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-sandbox-joins-affyn-to-push-metaverse-interoperability</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Popular metaverse platform, The Sandbox, forms a partnership with Singapore-based Web 3 game development firm, Affyn to create an immersive and more interoperable open metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Announced Monday, The Sandbox, a leading decentralized gaming virtual world, has entered into a partnership with Singapore-based games and metaverse developer, Affyn, to enhance the metaverse experiences for both their players. The partnership aims to extend the interoperable metaverse experiences, offering a first-of-its-kind community-focused, interoperable and open metaverse, connecting creators and collaborators across the globe. The partnership aims to create sustainable Web 3 gaming ecosystems and metaverses, converging the physical and virtual worlds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the meeting between the two entities, Lucaz Lee, Ceo and co-founder of Affyn showed excitement about the partnership, promising users and enthusiasts a &ldquo;more immersive and interactive experience&rdquo; following the partnership.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our shared belief and vision of an open metaverse is the driving force behind this collaboration,&rdquo; Lee said. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re confident it will provide gamers, collaborators and virtual world enthusiasts with an even more immersive and interactive experience.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to a joint statement release, the collaboration aims to bring interoperability within the metaverse and blockchain gaming. The two companies are currently working together to explore interoperability within the open metaverse, allowing for a seamless experience for all communities. As the metaverse community grows, this partnership will allow gamers, creators and collaborators to easily interact across the Sandbox and Affyn metaverse communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, the collaboration also aims to educate creators and newcomers in the field, helping them better understand the metaverse and giving them a better opportunity to grow their communities in the metaverse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Sandbox has always been a strong advocate of interoperability and decentralisation,&rdquo; George Wong, Head of Singapore Sandbox said. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to see more platforms embracing interoperability as a choice rather than working in independent silos and we hope that this brings forth more creative opportunities and exciting use cases to collaboratively grow the metaverse experience.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Since its launch, The Sandbox has witnessed massive user adoption rates, mainly pushed through its collaboration with A-list stars and global brands. The Web 3 virtual gaming firm has collaborated with over 400 partners including Warner Music Group, Ubisoft, Tony Hawk, Gucci Vault, The Walking Dead, Invincible, Snoop Dogg, Adidas, Deadmau5, Steve Aoki, SM Entertainment, Atari, etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With Sandbox offering players a platform to create and design their own adventures, the partnership with Affyn will allow players to continuously share stories in the metaverse, bringing together characters and heroes from both virtual worlds into one immersive metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The partnership is set to be unveiled in the upcoming Affyn&rsquo;s keynote event, Evolution, on May 10 2023, revealing new features of its virtual game and a new game set to launch later this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Popular metaverse platform, The Sandbox, forms a partnership with Singapore-based Web 3 game development firm, Affyn to create an immersive and more interoperable open metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Announced Monday, The Sandbox, a leading decentralized gaming virtual world, has entered into a partnership with Singapore-based games and metaverse developer, Affyn, to enhance the metaverse experiences for both their players. The partnership aims to extend the interoperable metaverse experiences, offering a first-of-its-kind community-focused, interoperable and open metaverse, connecting creators and collaborators across the globe. The partnership aims to create sustainable Web 3 gaming ecosystems and metaverses, converging the physical and virtual worlds.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following the meeting between the two entities, Lucaz Lee, Ceo and co-founder of Affyn showed excitement about the partnership, promising users and enthusiasts a &ldquo;more immersive and interactive experience&rdquo; following the partnership.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Our shared belief and vision of an open metaverse is the driving force behind this collaboration,&rdquo; Lee said. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re confident it will provide gamers, collaborators and virtual world enthusiasts with an even more immersive and interactive experience.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to a joint statement release, the collaboration aims to bring interoperability within the metaverse and blockchain gaming. The two companies are currently working together to explore interoperability within the open metaverse, allowing for a seamless experience for all communities. As the metaverse community grows, this partnership will allow gamers, creators and collaborators to easily interact across the Sandbox and Affyn metaverse communities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, the collaboration also aims to educate creators and newcomers in the field, helping them better understand the metaverse and giving them a better opportunity to grow their communities in the metaverse.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Sandbox has always been a strong advocate of interoperability and decentralisation,&rdquo; George Wong, Head of Singapore Sandbox said. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re excited to see more platforms embracing interoperability as a choice rather than working in independent silos and we hope that this brings forth more creative opportunities and exciting use cases to collaboratively grow the metaverse experience.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Since its launch, The Sandbox has witnessed massive user adoption rates, mainly pushed through its collaboration with A-list stars and global brands. The Web 3 virtual gaming firm has collaborated with over 400 partners including Warner Music Group, Ubisoft, Tony Hawk, Gucci Vault, The Walking Dead, Invincible, Snoop Dogg, Adidas, Deadmau5, Steve Aoki, SM Entertainment, Atari, etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With Sandbox offering players a platform to create and design their own adventures, the partnership with Affyn will allow players to continuously share stories in the metaverse, bringing together characters and heroes from both virtual worlds into one immersive metaverse.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The partnership is set to be unveiled in the upcoming Affyn&rsquo;s keynote event, Evolution, on May 10 2023, revealing new features of its virtual game and a new game set to launch later this year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Fracton Protocol Leads the Charge for Blue-chip NFT Adoption]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/fracton-protocol-leads-the-charge-for-blue-chip-nft-adoption</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-563.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-563.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-563.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/fracton-protocol-leads-the-charge-for-blue-chip-nft-adoption</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<ul>
<li>Fracton Protocol supports 26 top collections with its innovative fractionalization approach.</li>
<li>Cutting-edge NFT infrastructure of Fracton Protocol prioritizes user experience &amp; combat rug pulls.</li>
<li>Fracton Protocol achieves remarkable milestones in under ten months.</li>
</ul>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Fracton Protocol, a new non-fungible tokens (NFTs) player, has become the top holder in seven renowned NFT collections, including Doodles, Mfers, Valhalla, Genuine Undead, Renga, Fluf, and ENS 10k club. This remarkable feat is especially noteworthy considering the current bearish NFT market that has impacted several NFT projects and protocols.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Fracton Protocol has reportedly achieved significant milestones in under ten months, including a total value locked (TVL) of over 7,000 ETH. By securing its position as the top holder in multiple blue-chip NFT collections, Fracton Protocol reaffirms its status as a leading player in the quest for mass NFT adoption.</p>
<p>Fracton protocol`s success can be credited to its strategic partnership with KuCoin, one of the largest crypto exchanges globally. By integrating with KuCoin, the project has effectively expanded its NFT holder base and cemented the significance of this cutting-edge protocol.</p>
<p>Chido, the Global Head of Community at Fracton Protocol, says;</p>

<p>&nbsp;We are incredibly honored to become the top holder in these prestigious NFT collections. It highlights Fracton Protocol's commitment to supporting valuable digital assets and our influential role in the NFT ecosystem&nbsp;</p>

<p>Fracton Protocol's approach to fractionalization and CEX integration has reportedly served as an effective strategy for expanding the NFT holder base and further establishing the importance of this innovative protocol. The project focuses on creating new opportunities for new users to invest in high-quality NFTs while minimizing the risks associated with rug pulls and other threats.</p>
<p>According to the team, Fracton Protocol is a cutting-edge NFT infrastructure that focuses on fractionalization and places user experience at the forefront to combat rug pulls and encourage broader access to NFT ownership and trading. Its hiNFTs feature simplifies the onboarding experience for crypto enthusiasts and those new to NFTs, bridging the gap and offering secure, affordable access to top-tier collections while significantly minimizing rug pull risks for newcomers in the market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td valign="top">
<ul>
<li>Fracton Protocol supports 26 top collections with its innovative fractionalization approach.</li>
<li>Cutting-edge NFT infrastructure of Fracton Protocol prioritizes user experience &amp; combat rug pulls.</li>
<li>Fracton Protocol achieves remarkable milestones in under ten months.</li>
</ul>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>Fracton Protocol, a new non-fungible tokens (NFTs) player, has become the top holder in seven renowned NFT collections, including Doodles, Mfers, Valhalla, Genuine Undead, Renga, Fluf, and ENS 10k club. This remarkable feat is especially noteworthy considering the current bearish NFT market that has impacted several NFT projects and protocols.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Fracton Protocol has reportedly achieved significant milestones in under ten months, including a total value locked (TVL) of over 7,000 ETH. By securing its position as the top holder in multiple blue-chip NFT collections, Fracton Protocol reaffirms its status as a leading player in the quest for mass NFT adoption.</p>
<p>Fracton protocol`s success can be credited to its strategic partnership with KuCoin, one of the largest crypto exchanges globally. By integrating with KuCoin, the project has effectively expanded its NFT holder base and cemented the significance of this cutting-edge protocol.</p>
<p>Chido, the Global Head of Community at Fracton Protocol, says;</p>

<p>&nbsp;We are incredibly honored to become the top holder in these prestigious NFT collections. It highlights Fracton Protocol's commitment to supporting valuable digital assets and our influential role in the NFT ecosystem&nbsp;</p>

<p>Fracton Protocol's approach to fractionalization and CEX integration has reportedly served as an effective strategy for expanding the NFT holder base and further establishing the importance of this innovative protocol. The project focuses on creating new opportunities for new users to invest in high-quality NFTs while minimizing the risks associated with rug pulls and other threats.</p>
<p>According to the team, Fracton Protocol is a cutting-edge NFT infrastructure that focuses on fractionalization and places user experience at the forefront to combat rug pulls and encourage broader access to NFT ownership and trading. Its hiNFTs feature simplifies the onboarding experience for crypto enthusiasts and those new to NFTs, bridging the gap and offering secure, affordable access to top-tier collections while significantly minimizing rug pull risks for newcomers in the market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Does today’s bitcoin price even matter?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/does-todays-bitcoin-price-even-matter</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-43.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-43.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-43.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 11:56:45 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/does-todays-bitcoin-price-even-matter</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is having a period of down price action. With a likely much looser Fed policy coming in the next few months Bitcoin can be a strong play.</p>
Take some profits?
<p>Many inexperienced investors into Bitcoin over the last few months might be glancing nervously at the charts and wondering if now is the time to sell and take those profits.</p>
<p>While taking profits is always a good idea, nervousness over where Bitcoin is going next probably isn&rsquo;t necessary. $26,500 could be a next target for the king of the cryptocurrencies, or even $25,000. Both are the next strong areas of support and a correction down to either of these would be considered very healthy.</p>
Bitcoin or banks?
<p>However, in the grand scheme of things Bitcoin is arguably the asset to hold, at least for the next couple of years or so. The banks are underwater currently, and it is only the Federal Reserve saying that it will backstop any of the &ldquo;too big to fail&rdquo; banks that allows the banks to survive, albeit at the huge cost of reduced purchasing power of the individual.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is not the case for the smaller banks, and therefore some of these could fail over the coming months, and with the bigger banks being encouraged by the Fed to gobble them up, the process of bank monopolisation continues.</p>
<p>Holding your currency in the bank can consequently be a risk, although a bigger risk might be the low interest rates offered by the banks, which wouldn&rsquo;t allow investors to protect their wealth when the high rate of inflation is taken into account.</p>
Alternatives
<p>Some analysts have suggested that investors put their currency into shorter term treasuries with the thinking that this doesn&rsquo;t lock the investor in for a long time, and also pays a reasonable interest that is safer.</p>
<p>Gold and silver are two hedges that have something in common with Bitcoin in that they are all &lsquo;sound money&rsquo;. Sound money is defined as holding its value over time, a medium of exchange, and highly divisible.</p>
<p>Those embedded in the banking industry would argue that Bitcoin is not a stable value, and given its nascence, this has some truth. It can still see some large swings in value against the US dollar.</p>
<p>However, over time, Bitcoin follows cycles that bring it higher every time, unlike fiat currencies like the dollar that only lose value because they are based on debt and need to be constantly printed into existence, futher debasing the currency.</p>
Education is key
<p>Bitcoin is currently just under $28,000. Many analysts agree that it has started its bull run. It can go lower, but the lower it goes the more it will be bought up by those who have the intelligence to understand what it is.</p>
<p>The genie is out of the bottle and Bitcoin can not be crushed or erased by governments. It is the money of the people and as such it behoves all people who care about financial freedom to educate themselves on how they can protect themselves from what is to come.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is having a period of down price action. With a likely much looser Fed policy coming in the next few months Bitcoin can be a strong play.</p>
Take some profits?
<p>Many inexperienced investors into Bitcoin over the last few months might be glancing nervously at the charts and wondering if now is the time to sell and take those profits.</p>
<p>While taking profits is always a good idea, nervousness over where Bitcoin is going next probably isn&rsquo;t necessary. $26,500 could be a next target for the king of the cryptocurrencies, or even $25,000. Both are the next strong areas of support and a correction down to either of these would be considered very healthy.</p>
Bitcoin or banks?
<p>However, in the grand scheme of things Bitcoin is arguably the asset to hold, at least for the next couple of years or so. The banks are underwater currently, and it is only the Federal Reserve saying that it will backstop any of the &ldquo;too big to fail&rdquo; banks that allows the banks to survive, albeit at the huge cost of reduced purchasing power of the individual.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is not the case for the smaller banks, and therefore some of these could fail over the coming months, and with the bigger banks being encouraged by the Fed to gobble them up, the process of bank monopolisation continues.</p>
<p>Holding your currency in the bank can consequently be a risk, although a bigger risk might be the low interest rates offered by the banks, which wouldn&rsquo;t allow investors to protect their wealth when the high rate of inflation is taken into account.</p>
Alternatives
<p>Some analysts have suggested that investors put their currency into shorter term treasuries with the thinking that this doesn&rsquo;t lock the investor in for a long time, and also pays a reasonable interest that is safer.</p>
<p>Gold and silver are two hedges that have something in common with Bitcoin in that they are all &lsquo;sound money&rsquo;. Sound money is defined as holding its value over time, a medium of exchange, and highly divisible.</p>
<p>Those embedded in the banking industry would argue that Bitcoin is not a stable value, and given its nascence, this has some truth. It can still see some large swings in value against the US dollar.</p>
<p>However, over time, Bitcoin follows cycles that bring it higher every time, unlike fiat currencies like the dollar that only lose value because they are based on debt and need to be constantly printed into existence, futher debasing the currency.</p>
Education is key
<p>Bitcoin is currently just under $28,000. Many analysts agree that it has started its bull run. It can go lower, but the lower it goes the more it will be bought up by those who have the intelligence to understand what it is.</p>
<p>The genie is out of the bottle and Bitcoin can not be crushed or erased by governments. It is the money of the people and as such it behoves all people who care about financial freedom to educate themselves on how they can protect themselves from what is to come.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Are There Investment Opportunities In The Web3 Travel Industry? ]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/are-there-investment-opportunities-in-the-web3-travel-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-45.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-45.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-1-45.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 09:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/are-there-investment-opportunities-in-the-web3-travel-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Source: Depositphotos</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Web3 concept&mdash;including the technology, the community, and the use cases&mdash;has caused a significant amount of disruption in ways that our society needs most.&nbsp; It has shaken off many of the assumptions we&rsquo;ve had about contracts, about who controls a company, and about how we can make investments.&nbsp; And it really does take a combination of technology, community, applied to a good use case to work.&nbsp; We&rsquo;ve seen strong Web3 disruptions in finance, gaming, and collectables.&nbsp; However, one of the strongest disruptions caused by Web3 is a change in how we look at investing.&nbsp; Once there were limited options in how to invest, with stocks/bonds, real estate, art, etc. being the main choices.&nbsp; However, Web3 can use smart contracts, DAOs, and real assets to provide new opportunities that transcend borders or budgets.&nbsp; Let&rsquo;s look into the details of&nbsp; this model and explore as an example the travel industry, which is working to create an entire investment ecosystem.&nbsp; In particular, we will look at the Arakis model to see how Web3 is disrupting the travel industry.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The Web3 Investment Model:&nbsp; Smart Contracts, Real Assets, Tokenized Value
<p>The Web3 investment model has three key components:&nbsp; smart contracts, real assets, and tokenized value.&nbsp; The smart contract lays out the agreement between the asset holder and the investor.&nbsp; As certain activities occur, as an asset rises or drops in value, the smart contract will automatically take pre-determined actions that were agreed to by both parties.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unlike token speculation, this model is driven by real-world, often physical assets.&nbsp; These can be assets that are expected to rise in value, like famous paintings; or they can be assets expected to earn revenue, such as a house that is rented out.&nbsp; In any case, there is a generally understood value for these assets.&nbsp; Finally, the investment made is represented by tokenized value.&nbsp; This is the expected long term value of the asset, whether it is an expected rise in value when it is sold, or an expected lifetime revenue amount.&nbsp; There is always some risk in any investment, and the Web3 model is no different.&nbsp; However, there are real assets behind the investment.</p>
<p>So what makes the Web3 investment model so different from the standard investments we have today?&nbsp; One key difference with the Web3 model is availability and access.&nbsp; If you have a significant amount of money to invest, then congratulations.&nbsp; For the vast majority of people, however, it is extremely difficult to raise enough funds to invest in businesses, buy artwork, or trade on financial markets.&nbsp; This is a shame, because a little money from a lot of people quickly becomes a lot of funding.&nbsp; The Web3 investment model breaks down what is required to participate in an investment.&nbsp; People of all walks of life can find a Web3 investment model they like, set up a wallet, and spend a small amount of money to join.&nbsp; In many cases, this means either buying a token and staking, or more recently, buying an NFT that represents the investment (usually a physical asset) and that interacts with the smart contract.&nbsp; In this way, the NFT will operate according to the rules of the smart contract.&nbsp; Even if the investment is small, it can still generate return for the investor.</p>
<p>One last question:&nbsp; Why is the investment represented as an NFT?&nbsp; This may actually be the most disruptive part of all.&nbsp; As an NFT, the investment becomes a prepackaged and independent item.&nbsp; In other words, it is not permanently tied to the investor, or even the platform where the NFT was purchased.&nbsp; This means that the NFT as an investment is untethered and can be sold to other users using an NFT marketplace.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Example: Arakis
<p>The travel platform Arakis offers an example of this phenomenon in action.&nbsp; The platform is working to partner with members of the travel industry across the board.&nbsp; As new partnerships are developed, the platform will issue specific NFTs, called Revenue Sharing Tokens (RST), that represent the travel partners' specific assets.&nbsp; For example, an RST is launched by Arakis for the Hilton in London so that when a user buys one, a predetermined percentage of booking fees will go to the RST holders, when the booking is made through the Arakis platform.&nbsp; As rooms continue to be booked, token holders will continue to gain a part of the revenue sharing.&nbsp; If the RST costs a small amount, the revenue sharing may be small (and depends on if the asset is making revenue to be shared).&nbsp; However, it is an investment providing a return and is available to a much, much wider audience.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The big questions are, how far do we see the potential for the RST in the travel industry?&nbsp; And what type of travel businesses (hotels, airlines, car rentals, tours, etc.) will likely use RSTs the most?</p>
<p>Arakis founder Semil Vithani weighed in with his thoughts:</p>
<p>&ldquo;The RST is the revolution in travel profitability, with its main use case creating a revenue sharing model out of any productive asset in the travel industry.&nbsp; This benefits both travelers and companies, maximizing earnings from every booking and putting profits back in the hands of travelers.&nbsp; Arakis will start implementing the RST with hotel bookings, as this is the most straightforward application.&nbsp; After that however, we aim to convert airline routes, tour packages, and many more travel activities into RSTs.&rdquo;</p>
<p>This is the transformative nature of the Web3 investment model at work.&nbsp; And with a population of potential investors this wide, the amount of investment capital worldwide is unbelievable.&nbsp; Think about the travel industry and how the Arakis use case could expand.&nbsp; NFTs (as RSTs) could be minted for any travel related asset that can generate revenue:&nbsp; hotels, tours, restaurants, rental cars, airline tickets&hellip; the list goes on.&nbsp; Feasibly, any of these could decide to issue RSTs at a price and proportion that will attract investors and micro-investors worldwide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Looking Ahead
<p>When you look at the concept of investing in this new light, it becomes clear that we will look back at this time period as the beginning of the Web3 Investment Model revolution, where people of all financial means and geographic location were given the chance to invest and earn returns.&nbsp; Unlike TradFi and traditional business investment, there are nearly zero limitations.&nbsp; Potential investors can study the smart contract to find a fair opportunity, and use the power of reputation and satisfied customers to find the right platform to partner with.&nbsp; And unlike normal investments, users have control of their investment-as-NFT, being able to collect revenue sharing or even sell their NFT on a marketplace of their choice.&nbsp; The travel industry is one of the first to begin this journey, but it won&rsquo;t be long before other industries adopt this disruptive way to level the playing field for the masses, while giving industries an untapped way to raise capital.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Source: Depositphotos</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Web3 concept&mdash;including the technology, the community, and the use cases&mdash;has caused a significant amount of disruption in ways that our society needs most.&nbsp; It has shaken off many of the assumptions we&rsquo;ve had about contracts, about who controls a company, and about how we can make investments.&nbsp; And it really does take a combination of technology, community, applied to a good use case to work.&nbsp; We&rsquo;ve seen strong Web3 disruptions in finance, gaming, and collectables.&nbsp; However, one of the strongest disruptions caused by Web3 is a change in how we look at investing.&nbsp; Once there were limited options in how to invest, with stocks/bonds, real estate, art, etc. being the main choices.&nbsp; However, Web3 can use smart contracts, DAOs, and real assets to provide new opportunities that transcend borders or budgets.&nbsp; Let&rsquo;s look into the details of&nbsp; this model and explore as an example the travel industry, which is working to create an entire investment ecosystem.&nbsp; In particular, we will look at the Arakis model to see how Web3 is disrupting the travel industry.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
The Web3 Investment Model:&nbsp; Smart Contracts, Real Assets, Tokenized Value
<p>The Web3 investment model has three key components:&nbsp; smart contracts, real assets, and tokenized value.&nbsp; The smart contract lays out the agreement between the asset holder and the investor.&nbsp; As certain activities occur, as an asset rises or drops in value, the smart contract will automatically take pre-determined actions that were agreed to by both parties.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Unlike token speculation, this model is driven by real-world, often physical assets.&nbsp; These can be assets that are expected to rise in value, like famous paintings; or they can be assets expected to earn revenue, such as a house that is rented out.&nbsp; In any case, there is a generally understood value for these assets.&nbsp; Finally, the investment made is represented by tokenized value.&nbsp; This is the expected long term value of the asset, whether it is an expected rise in value when it is sold, or an expected lifetime revenue amount.&nbsp; There is always some risk in any investment, and the Web3 model is no different.&nbsp; However, there are real assets behind the investment.</p>
<p>So what makes the Web3 investment model so different from the standard investments we have today?&nbsp; One key difference with the Web3 model is availability and access.&nbsp; If you have a significant amount of money to invest, then congratulations.&nbsp; For the vast majority of people, however, it is extremely difficult to raise enough funds to invest in businesses, buy artwork, or trade on financial markets.&nbsp; This is a shame, because a little money from a lot of people quickly becomes a lot of funding.&nbsp; The Web3 investment model breaks down what is required to participate in an investment.&nbsp; People of all walks of life can find a Web3 investment model they like, set up a wallet, and spend a small amount of money to join.&nbsp; In many cases, this means either buying a token and staking, or more recently, buying an NFT that represents the investment (usually a physical asset) and that interacts with the smart contract.&nbsp; In this way, the NFT will operate according to the rules of the smart contract.&nbsp; Even if the investment is small, it can still generate return for the investor.</p>
<p>One last question:&nbsp; Why is the investment represented as an NFT?&nbsp; This may actually be the most disruptive part of all.&nbsp; As an NFT, the investment becomes a prepackaged and independent item.&nbsp; In other words, it is not permanently tied to the investor, or even the platform where the NFT was purchased.&nbsp; This means that the NFT as an investment is untethered and can be sold to other users using an NFT marketplace.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Example: Arakis
<p>The travel platform Arakis offers an example of this phenomenon in action.&nbsp; The platform is working to partner with members of the travel industry across the board.&nbsp; As new partnerships are developed, the platform will issue specific NFTs, called Revenue Sharing Tokens (RST), that represent the travel partners' specific assets.&nbsp; For example, an RST is launched by Arakis for the Hilton in London so that when a user buys one, a predetermined percentage of booking fees will go to the RST holders, when the booking is made through the Arakis platform.&nbsp; As rooms continue to be booked, token holders will continue to gain a part of the revenue sharing.&nbsp; If the RST costs a small amount, the revenue sharing may be small (and depends on if the asset is making revenue to be shared).&nbsp; However, it is an investment providing a return and is available to a much, much wider audience.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The big questions are, how far do we see the potential for the RST in the travel industry?&nbsp; And what type of travel businesses (hotels, airlines, car rentals, tours, etc.) will likely use RSTs the most?</p>
<p>Arakis founder Semil Vithani weighed in with his thoughts:</p>
<p>&ldquo;The RST is the revolution in travel profitability, with its main use case creating a revenue sharing model out of any productive asset in the travel industry.&nbsp; This benefits both travelers and companies, maximizing earnings from every booking and putting profits back in the hands of travelers.&nbsp; Arakis will start implementing the RST with hotel bookings, as this is the most straightforward application.&nbsp; After that however, we aim to convert airline routes, tour packages, and many more travel activities into RSTs.&rdquo;</p>
<p>This is the transformative nature of the Web3 investment model at work.&nbsp; And with a population of potential investors this wide, the amount of investment capital worldwide is unbelievable.&nbsp; Think about the travel industry and how the Arakis use case could expand.&nbsp; NFTs (as RSTs) could be minted for any travel related asset that can generate revenue:&nbsp; hotels, tours, restaurants, rental cars, airline tickets&hellip; the list goes on.&nbsp; Feasibly, any of these could decide to issue RSTs at a price and proportion that will attract investors and micro-investors worldwide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Looking Ahead
<p>When you look at the concept of investing in this new light, it becomes clear that we will look back at this time period as the beginning of the Web3 Investment Model revolution, where people of all financial means and geographic location were given the chance to invest and earn returns.&nbsp; Unlike TradFi and traditional business investment, there are nearly zero limitations.&nbsp; Potential investors can study the smart contract to find a fair opportunity, and use the power of reputation and satisfied customers to find the right platform to partner with.&nbsp; And unlike normal investments, users have control of their investment-as-NFT, being able to collect revenue sharing or even sell their NFT on a marketplace of their choice.&nbsp; The travel industry is one of the first to begin this journey, but it won&rsquo;t be long before other industries adopt this disruptive way to level the playing field for the masses, while giving industries an untapped way to raise capital.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC Fees Reach Multi-Year Highs, Crypto Daily TV 8/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-fees-reach-a-multi-year-highs-crypto-daily-tv-8-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-fees.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-fees.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-fees.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-fees-reach-a-multi-year-highs-crypto-daily-tv-8-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Memecoin hype drives Bitcoin transaction fees to multi-year highs</p>
<p>Bitcoin transaction fees surged in early May, reaching their highest point over the past two years, according to data from Crypto Fees. On May 3, the total amount of fees paid on the Bitcoin blockchain reached $3.5 million, jumping about 400% from late April.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stripe tackles 'cold start problem' </p>
<p>Crypto-friendly payment company Stripe has launched a fiat-to-crypto onramp service to help Web3 companies tackle the issue of their customers not having &ldquo;crypto in their wallets to carry out transactions.</p>
<p>Binance closes BTC withdrawals.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance closed Bitcoin withdrawals on May 7 due to an alleged overflow of transactions on the Bitcoin network.&nbsp; Bitcoin mempool was clogged with over 400,000 transactions waiting to be processed at the time.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 27632.3333 and resistance is at 30474.3333.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded 1.0% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.0% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1780.851 and resistance is at 2070.731.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
The last session saw XRP fall 0.4% against USD.
<p>The last session saw the Ripple fall 0.4% against the Dollar. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4425 and resistance is at 0.4766.</p>
<p>The ROC gives a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 76.271 and resistance is at 92.731.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>FI Trade Balance</p>
<p>The Trade Balance is the total difference between exports and imports of goods and services. A positive value shows a trade surplus, while a negative value represents a trade deficit. Finland's Trade Balance will be released at 06:00 GMT, Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI at 00:30 GMT, and Germany's Industrial Production at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions.</p>
<p>DE Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of industrial production.</p>
<p>UK BRC Like-For-Like Retail Sales</p>
<p>The British Retail Consortium Like-For-Like Retail Sales measure changes in the actual value of retail sales from participating companies with invaluable management information on a regular and reliable basis. The UK's BRC Like-For-Like Retail Sales will be released at 23:01 GMT, Japan's Overall Household Spending at 23:30 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Overall Household Spending</p>
<p>The Overall Household Spending is an indicator that measures the total expenditures of households. The level of spending can be used as an indicator of consumer optimism.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Memecoin hype drives Bitcoin transaction fees to multi-year highs</p>
<p>Bitcoin transaction fees surged in early May, reaching their highest point over the past two years, according to data from Crypto Fees. On May 3, the total amount of fees paid on the Bitcoin blockchain reached $3.5 million, jumping about 400% from late April.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stripe tackles 'cold start problem' </p>
<p>Crypto-friendly payment company Stripe has launched a fiat-to-crypto onramp service to help Web3 companies tackle the issue of their customers not having &ldquo;crypto in their wallets to carry out transactions.</p>
<p>Binance closes BTC withdrawals.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance closed Bitcoin withdrawals on May 7 due to an alleged overflow of transactions on the Bitcoin network.&nbsp; Bitcoin mempool was clogged with over 400,000 transactions waiting to be processed at the time.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 27632.3333 and resistance is at 30474.3333.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD exploded 1.0% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.0% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1780.851 and resistance is at 2070.731.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
The last session saw XRP fall 0.4% against USD.
<p>The last session saw the Ripple fall 0.4% against the Dollar. The ROC is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4425 and resistance is at 0.4766.</p>
<p>The ROC gives a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.4% in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 76.271 and resistance is at 92.731.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>FI Trade Balance</p>
<p>The Trade Balance is the total difference between exports and imports of goods and services. A positive value shows a trade surplus, while a negative value represents a trade deficit. Finland's Trade Balance will be released at 06:00 GMT, Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI at 00:30 GMT, and Germany's Industrial Production at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions.</p>
<p>DE Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of industrial production.</p>
<p>UK BRC Like-For-Like Retail Sales</p>
<p>The British Retail Consortium Like-For-Like Retail Sales measure changes in the actual value of retail sales from participating companies with invaluable management information on a regular and reliable basis. The UK's BRC Like-For-Like Retail Sales will be released at 23:01 GMT, Japan's Overall Household Spending at 23:30 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Overall Household Spending</p>
<p>The Overall Household Spending is an indicator that measures the total expenditures of households. The level of spending can be used as an indicator of consumer optimism.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[China’s Supreme Court Approves Use Of Crypto To Settle Debts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/chinas-supreme-court-approves-use-of-crypto-to-settle-debts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-crypto.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-crypto.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/china-crypto.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 08:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/chinas-supreme-court-approves-use-of-crypto-to-settle-debts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>China&rsquo;s Supreme Court has, in recently issued guidelines, ruled that virtual currencies can be used to settle a debt, provided that both parties agree to it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The ruling shows that despite China&rsquo;s blanket ban on cryptocurrencies, the regulation of its crypto sector is continuously evolving.&nbsp;</p>
China&rsquo;s Supreme Court Ruling&nbsp;
<p>According to the ruling, parties interacting with one another can use cryptocurrencies to settle debts that arise from labor service, mutual exchange, and other basic human interactions. However, the use of cryptocurrencies would be considered legal only if both parties agreed to it. In this particular scenario, the court ruled that cryptocurrencies have network virtual properties. However, it also stressed that such an approach would be valid only if there were no other valid reasons against it. The court, in its ruling, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If it is agreed between the parties that a small amount of virtual currency shall be used to compensate the debts arising from mutual exchange, labor service, and other basic relations, if there are no other invalid causes, the people&rsquo;s court shall recognize the contract as valid.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, the court clarified that if one party transfers cryptocurrency to another and the receiving party cannot fulfill their responsibility towards the deal, then the court would determine compensation. This compensation would be determined based on the property&rsquo;s actual value that the receiving party accepts at the time of the contract signing.&nbsp;</p>
China&rsquo;s Stand On Crypto&nbsp;
<p>China&rsquo;s stance regarding cryptocurrencies has been a little confusing for investors and users lately. While there is a blanket ban on cryptocurrencies in force, there is some flexibility in the interpretation and enforcement of rules. The Supreme Court ruling shows that the regulation of China&rsquo;s digital asset space is continuing to evolve and is a positive development.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In 2022, the Beijing Number One Intermediate People&rsquo;s Court ruled that citizens could still trade cryptocurrencies as virtual assets. However, they could not use them as currency. The ruling allowed investors to explore and use the potential of cryptocurrencies despite the blanket ban. Provided they have access to the correct guidance and understanding of the legal framework, investors could make informed decisions and take advantage of cryptocurrencies. As a result, it remains unclear if the Chinese government recognizes the legal status of cryptocurrencies following the supreme court ruling.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In one ruling dealing with the instance of an outstanding loan case, the Beijing Number One Intermediate People&rsquo;s Court ruled that crypto could be considered as a property of an individual, just like data. The court added that the virtual asset fails to meet the standards of a currency and falls under the bracket of personal property.&nbsp;</p>
Investor Interest Surging&nbsp;
<p>Despite the blanket ban on crypto in China, investor interest in digital assets has gone through the roof recently. According to a report published in 2022, China was ranked in the top ten countries in the global crypto adoption index. China has also hinted that it acknowledges the growing interest in cryptocurrencies. One report revealed that the country had implemented a 20% income tax on profits made by Bitcoin miners and individual cryptocurrency investors. This shows that while the legal status of cryptocurrencies is yet to be determined, China has noted the growing investor interest in them. However, investors must ensure they are up to date with the ever-evolving guidelines around crypto in China.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>China&rsquo;s Supreme Court has, in recently issued guidelines, ruled that virtual currencies can be used to settle a debt, provided that both parties agree to it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The ruling shows that despite China&rsquo;s blanket ban on cryptocurrencies, the regulation of its crypto sector is continuously evolving.&nbsp;</p>
China&rsquo;s Supreme Court Ruling&nbsp;
<p>According to the ruling, parties interacting with one another can use cryptocurrencies to settle debts that arise from labor service, mutual exchange, and other basic human interactions. However, the use of cryptocurrencies would be considered legal only if both parties agreed to it. In this particular scenario, the court ruled that cryptocurrencies have network virtual properties. However, it also stressed that such an approach would be valid only if there were no other valid reasons against it. The court, in its ruling, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If it is agreed between the parties that a small amount of virtual currency shall be used to compensate the debts arising from mutual exchange, labor service, and other basic relations, if there are no other invalid causes, the people&rsquo;s court shall recognize the contract as valid.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, the court clarified that if one party transfers cryptocurrency to another and the receiving party cannot fulfill their responsibility towards the deal, then the court would determine compensation. This compensation would be determined based on the property&rsquo;s actual value that the receiving party accepts at the time of the contract signing.&nbsp;</p>
China&rsquo;s Stand On Crypto&nbsp;
<p>China&rsquo;s stance regarding cryptocurrencies has been a little confusing for investors and users lately. While there is a blanket ban on cryptocurrencies in force, there is some flexibility in the interpretation and enforcement of rules. The Supreme Court ruling shows that the regulation of China&rsquo;s digital asset space is continuing to evolve and is a positive development.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In 2022, the Beijing Number One Intermediate People&rsquo;s Court ruled that citizens could still trade cryptocurrencies as virtual assets. However, they could not use them as currency. The ruling allowed investors to explore and use the potential of cryptocurrencies despite the blanket ban. Provided they have access to the correct guidance and understanding of the legal framework, investors could make informed decisions and take advantage of cryptocurrencies. As a result, it remains unclear if the Chinese government recognizes the legal status of cryptocurrencies following the supreme court ruling.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In one ruling dealing with the instance of an outstanding loan case, the Beijing Number One Intermediate People&rsquo;s Court ruled that crypto could be considered as a property of an individual, just like data. The court added that the virtual asset fails to meet the standards of a currency and falls under the bracket of personal property.&nbsp;</p>
Investor Interest Surging&nbsp;
<p>Despite the blanket ban on crypto in China, investor interest in digital assets has gone through the roof recently. According to a report published in 2022, China was ranked in the top ten countries in the global crypto adoption index. China has also hinted that it acknowledges the growing interest in cryptocurrencies. One report revealed that the country had implemented a 20% income tax on profits made by Bitcoin miners and individual cryptocurrency investors. This shows that while the legal status of cryptocurrencies is yet to be determined, China has noted the growing investor interest in them. However, investors must ensure they are up to date with the ever-evolving guidelines around crypto in China.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  28394 Buying Pressure - 8 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-28394-buying-pressure-8-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 23:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-28394-buying-pressure-8-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Trades Above 29686:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought to add to recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair traded as high as the 29033.95 level after buying pressure emerged around the 28742.27 area, a test of an upside price objective related to demand that strengthened around the 28122 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;During the recent depreciation, bears pushed BTC/USD as low as the 28394 area after Stops were elected below the 28481.31 level, a related previous upside price objective.&nbsp; &nbsp;Significant buying and selling activity also took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to the same buying pressure that expanded around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishlly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28924.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28933.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Trades Above 29686:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) sought to add to recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair traded as high as the 29033.95 level after buying pressure emerged around the 28742.27 area, a test of an upside price objective related to demand that strengthened around the 28122 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;During the recent depreciation, bears pushed BTC/USD as low as the 28394 area after Stops were elected below the 28481.31 level, a related previous upside price objective.&nbsp; &nbsp;Significant buying and selling activity also took place around the 29298.31 area during the depreciation, an upside price objective linked to the same buying pressure that expanded around the 28122 area.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Above the market, upside price objectives relate to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishlly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28924.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28933.63.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;26533.04/ 25604.51/ 25094.62 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[$KING, Solana's Answer To Ethereum's $PEPE, Lists on BitMart Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/king-solanas-answer-to-ethereums-pepe-lists-on-bitmart-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Fvim6WOXwAE9x___1683480100Tc1HRyERb6.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Fvim6WOXwAE9x___1683480100Tc1HRyERb6.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Fvim6WOXwAE9x___1683480100Tc1HRyERb6.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 19:04:47 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/king-solanas-answer-to-ethereums-pepe-lists-on-bitmart-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, May 7th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>$KING coin, the revolutionary memecoin on the Solana blockchain, has recently achieved a significant milestone by securing a listing on the prestigious BitMart exchange. This listing not only increases the accessibility and visibility of $KING within the global crypto market but also provides a platform for its rapidly growing community to trade and invest with ease, bringing the famous Solana coin one step closer to becoming the &ldquo;$KING of Memecoins&rdquo;.</p><p>The listing is a huge milestone for $KING and great news for all crypto traders, as it enables every person on earth to buy and hold the $KING token now through the CEX (&ldquo;Centralized Exchange&rdquo;), a luxury that was limited exclusively to Solana blockchain users until now. BitMart, a top global cryptocurrency exchange, offers a secure and advanced trading environment, enabling users to seamlessly buy, sell, and trade $KING tokens. The listing follows the meteoric success of $KING since its launch, where it quickly claimed the #3 spot as the most popular token across all blockchains within just 24 hours. The project has attracted over 8,000 unique wallet holders and generated a trading volume exceeding $18M in its first day alone.</p><p></p><p>To celebrate this momentous achievement, $KING is launching an exclusive international community campaign, giving away a staggering 10,000,000 $KING tokens as part of a viral marketing initiative. Every participant in the campaign will receive a portion of the prize pool, reinforcing $KING's commitment to fostering a strong, sustainable community and rewarding its supporters.</p>GonzoSOL, the founder of DucksVegas and creator of $KING, shared his excitement about the campaign: "Our listing on BitMart is a significant milestone, and we want to celebrate it with our community. This campaign enables us to give back to our supporters while simultaneously raising awareness about $KING and its unique value proposition within the Solana ecosystem."<p>$KING is designed to attract new users and cultivate a vibrant, sustainable community by employing a redistributive reward system and continually expanding its offerings. The project, which was launched in tandem with King Charles III's coronation, has garnered significant attention due to its innovative approach, strategic alignment of narratives, and the renouncement of its smart contract, exemplifying transparency and trust.</p><p></p><p>For more information on the $KING token, its BitMart listing, and details on how to participate in the exclusive international community campaign, visit the $KING Coin Official Website and follow $KING on Twitter.</p><p>About $KING</p><p>$KING is a memecoin on the Solana blockchain, designed to onboard new users and foster a sustainable, thriving community. Launched to coincide with King Charles III's coronation, $KING aspires to become the premier memecoin within the Solana ecosystem. Created by GonzoSOL, founder of DucksVegas, the project utilizes a redistributive reward system and is committed to the ongoing expansion of its offerings for the benefit of its community members. Notably, the $KING smart contract has been renounced, showcasing the project's dedication to transparency and trust. The $KING roadmap encompasses a special coronation celebration, centralized exchange listings, and holder rewards for active community participation. Strategically aligning with various narratives and catalysts, $KING has rapidly gained attention, becoming the #3 most popular token across all blockchains within 24 hours of launch. With an impressive trading volume of over $18 million and more than 8,000 unique wallet holders on its first day, $KING will significantly impact the Solana ecosystem and the broader crypto market.</p><p>For more information visit $KING: Website | Twitter | Telegram </p>ContactCMOXavier NukajamKing Coin Financekingsolanacoin@gmail.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, May 7th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>$KING coin, the revolutionary memecoin on the Solana blockchain, has recently achieved a significant milestone by securing a listing on the prestigious BitMart exchange. This listing not only increases the accessibility and visibility of $KING within the global crypto market but also provides a platform for its rapidly growing community to trade and invest with ease, bringing the famous Solana coin one step closer to becoming the &ldquo;$KING of Memecoins&rdquo;.</p><p>The listing is a huge milestone for $KING and great news for all crypto traders, as it enables every person on earth to buy and hold the $KING token now through the CEX (&ldquo;Centralized Exchange&rdquo;), a luxury that was limited exclusively to Solana blockchain users until now. BitMart, a top global cryptocurrency exchange, offers a secure and advanced trading environment, enabling users to seamlessly buy, sell, and trade $KING tokens. The listing follows the meteoric success of $KING since its launch, where it quickly claimed the #3 spot as the most popular token across all blockchains within just 24 hours. The project has attracted over 8,000 unique wallet holders and generated a trading volume exceeding $18M in its first day alone.</p><p></p><p>To celebrate this momentous achievement, $KING is launching an exclusive international community campaign, giving away a staggering 10,000,000 $KING tokens as part of a viral marketing initiative. Every participant in the campaign will receive a portion of the prize pool, reinforcing $KING's commitment to fostering a strong, sustainable community and rewarding its supporters.</p>GonzoSOL, the founder of DucksVegas and creator of $KING, shared his excitement about the campaign: "Our listing on BitMart is a significant milestone, and we want to celebrate it with our community. This campaign enables us to give back to our supporters while simultaneously raising awareness about $KING and its unique value proposition within the Solana ecosystem."<p>$KING is designed to attract new users and cultivate a vibrant, sustainable community by employing a redistributive reward system and continually expanding its offerings. The project, which was launched in tandem with King Charles III's coronation, has garnered significant attention due to its innovative approach, strategic alignment of narratives, and the renouncement of its smart contract, exemplifying transparency and trust.</p><p></p><p>For more information on the $KING token, its BitMart listing, and details on how to participate in the exclusive international community campaign, visit the $KING Coin Official Website and follow $KING on Twitter.</p><p>About $KING</p><p>$KING is a memecoin on the Solana blockchain, designed to onboard new users and foster a sustainable, thriving community. Launched to coincide with King Charles III's coronation, $KING aspires to become the premier memecoin within the Solana ecosystem. Created by GonzoSOL, founder of DucksVegas, the project utilizes a redistributive reward system and is committed to the ongoing expansion of its offerings for the benefit of its community members. Notably, the $KING smart contract has been renounced, showcasing the project's dedication to transparency and trust. The $KING roadmap encompasses a special coronation celebration, centralized exchange listings, and holder rewards for active community participation. Strategically aligning with various narratives and catalysts, $KING has rapidly gained attention, becoming the #3 most popular token across all blockchains within 24 hours of launch. With an impressive trading volume of over $18 million and more than 8,000 unique wallet holders on its first day, $KING will significantly impact the Solana ecosystem and the broader crypto market.</p><p>For more information visit $KING: Website | Twitter | Telegram </p>ContactCMOXavier NukajamKing Coin Financekingsolanacoin@gmail.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
