<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>EU Draft Law Focused on Privacy in Using a Digital Euro Offline: CoinDesk</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-draft-law-focused-privacy-using-digital-euro-offline-coindesk.htm</link><description>A proposed digital euro would have to be usable offline from day one to safeguard privacy, according to a draft law obtained by CoinDesk.  &lt;br /&gt;
“The digital euro shall be available for both online and offline digital euro payment transactions as of the first issuance of the digital euro,” according to the draft text viewed by CoinDesk. The level of privacy for offline, face-to-face use should be “comparable” to withdrawing banknotes at an ATM, Coindesk reported....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-draft-law-focused-privacy-using-digital-euro-offline-coindesk.htm"&gt;Read More: EU Draft Law Focused on Privacy in Using a Digital Euro Offline: CoinDesk&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>European Commission</category><category>CBDC</category><category>European Union</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-draft-law-focused-privacy-using-digital-euro-offline-coindesk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117070/313299/adobestock-210414987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="161638"/></item><item><title>Ukraine Wants to Tax Crypto Gains at 18% from 2024</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraine-wants-tax-crypto-gains-at-18-from-2024.htm</link><description>Ukrainian regulators are prepared to start taxing crypto gains at 18% from 2024, with lawmakers set to vote on proposals this fall. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Forbes Ukraine, the National Commission for Securities and the Stock Market is set to unveil a draft law, which will be set before lawmakers at the next parliamentary session. &lt;br /&gt;
The market regulator’s proposals include creating a flat-rate 18% tax on “income” from crypto “investments,” but military servicepeople will only need to pay 1.5%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraine-wants-tax-crypto-gains-at-18-from-2024.htm"&gt;Read More: Ukraine Wants to Tax Crypto Gains at 18% from 2024&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ukraine</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ukraine-wants-tax-crypto-gains-at-18-from-2024.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116952/313048/adobestock-217810103.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="588011"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Analytics Firm Chainalysis Urges Crypto Firms to Start MiCA Preparations Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-chainalysis-urges-crypto-firms-start-mica-preparations-now.htm</link><description>The past week saw the forthcoming Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation formally published in the EU's official journal, marking a significant milestone for regulation in the crypto space. &lt;br /&gt;
Consequently, Chainalysis’ head of policy for Europe has urged cryptocurrency companies to start preparing for it as soon as possible....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-chainalysis-urges-crypto-firms-start-mica-preparations-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Analytics Firm Chainalysis Urges Crypto Firms to Start MiCA Preparations Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-chainalysis-urges-crypto-firms-start-mica-preparations-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117067/313308/adobestock-420516439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="773480"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 15 June – Trust Wallet, Uniswap, Casper</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-june-trust-wallet-uniswap-casper.htm</link><description>A slight deviation in Tether's (USDT) stablecoin earlier today has caught the attention of cryptocurrency traders. &lt;br /&gt;
The move occurred within Curve's 3Pool decentralized finance ecosystem, which holds significant liquidity and three primary stablecoins: USDT, USDC, and DAI. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-june-trust-wallet-uniswap-casper.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 15 June – Trust Wallet, Uniswap, Casper&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>WSM</category><category>TWT</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>UNI</category><category>YPRED</category><category>CSPR</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Trust Wallet Token</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Casper Network</category><category>Casper</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Crypto Gaming</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Rpg</category><category>Role Playing Games</category><category>Artifical Intelligence</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Crypto Project</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-june-trust-wallet-uniswap-casper.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117072/313304/best-crypto-15j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="341922"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Fed Chair Powell Says May Be a 'Couple of Years' Before Rates Can Be Cut – Will BTC Crash to $20,000 Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fed-chair-powell-says-may-couple-of-years-before-rates-can-cut-will-btc-crash-20000-soon.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin continues its volatile journey, the latest statement from Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell has sparked concerns among investors. &lt;br /&gt;
Powell's remarks suggesting that it may be a "couple of years" before interest rates can be cut have left many questioning the future trajectory of Bitcoin's price.  &lt;br /&gt;
With this uncertainty looming, there are growing speculations about a potential crash that could drive Bitcoin's value down to $20,000. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fed-chair-powell-says-may-couple-of-years-before-rates-can-cut-will-btc-crash-20000-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Fed Chair Powell Says May Be a 'Couple of Years' Before Rates Can Be Cut – Will BTC Crash to $20,000 Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fed-chair-powell-says-may-couple-of-years-before-rates-can-cut-will-btc-crash-20000-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117073/313303/15-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="483466"/></item><item><title>Binance Seeks to Deregister Cyprus Entity Amid Upcoming EU MiCA Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-deregister-cyprus-entity-amid-upcoming-eu-mica-rules.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, is seeking to delist itself from the register of authorized crypto asset service providers (CASPs) in Cyprus in order to focus its efforts on complying with the EU’s Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-deregister-cyprus-entity-amid-upcoming-eu-mica-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Seeks to Deregister Cyprus Entity Amid Upcoming EU MiCA Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>EU</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-deregister-cyprus-entity-amid-upcoming-eu-mica-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117038/313259/binance-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="81659"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Becomes Best Performing Coin of the Day Despite Crypto Market Crash – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-becomes-best-performing-coin-of-day-despite-crypto-market-crash-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) has demonstrated remarkable resilience in the face of the recent cryptocurrency market crash.  &lt;br /&gt;
After bouncing off above the support level of 0.00009044, LUNC has managed to climb back up and is currently trading at $0.00009534.  &lt;br /&gt;
This impressive recovery has captured the attention of investors, who are now keen to understand the factors driving LUNC's upward momentum....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-becomes-best-performing-coin-of-day-despite-crypto-market-crash-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Becomes Best Performing Coin of the Day Despite Crypto Market Crash – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-becomes-best-performing-coin-of-day-despite-crypto-market-crash-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117064/313298/lunc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="108070"/></item><item><title>HSBC, Standard Chartered, and Bank of China Pressured by Hong Kong to Embrace Crypto Exchanges – Next Crypto Hub?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hsbc-standard-chartered-bank-of-china-pressured-by-hong-kong-embrace-crypto-exchanges-next-crypto-hub.htm</link><description>Hong Kong’s banking regulator has reportedly exerted pressure on banks including HSBC, Standard Chartered, and Bank of China to engage with crypto clients. &lt;br /&gt;
During a meeting last month, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) questioned why the banks had not accepted crypto exchanges as clients, The Financial Times reported, citing people familiar with the matter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hsbc-standard-chartered-bank-of-china-pressured-by-hong-kong-embrace-crypto-exchanges-next-crypto-hub.htm"&gt;Read More: HSBC, Standard Chartered, and Bank of China Pressured by Hong Kong to Embrace Crypto Exchanges – Next Crypto Hub?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>HSBC</category><category>Bank of China</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hsbc-standard-chartered-bank-of-china-pressured-by-hong-kong-embrace-crypto-exchanges-next-crypto-hub.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117049/313276/adobestock-f11photo-1-med.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="233215"/></item><item><title>CoinEx Has To Refund Thousands as Part of Settlement With New York Attorney General Letitia James</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinex-refund-thousands-as-part-of-settlement-with-new-york-attorney-general-letitia-james.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency firm CoinEx will have to refund thousands of New York investors more than $1.7 million and pay penalties to the state as a result of settlement with New York Attorney General Letitia James.  &lt;br /&gt;
CoinEx is also banned from operating in the state, according to a statement on Thursday from James’ office. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinex-refund-thousands-as-part-of-settlement-with-new-york-attorney-general-letitia-james.htm"&gt;Read More: CoinEx Has To Refund Thousands as Part of Settlement With New York Attorney General Letitia James&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Letitia James</category><category>New York</category><category>New York Attorney General</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinex-refund-thousands-as-part-of-settlement-with-new-york-attorney-general-letitia-james.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117054/313280/adobestock-126216157.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="620404"/></item><item><title>“Bitcoin Mayor” Francis Suarez of Miami Throws in His Republican Bid for Presidency</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mayor-francis-suarez-of-miami-throws-his-republican-bid-for-presidency.htm</link><description>The pro-bitcoin mayor of Miami Francis Suarez is running for US president. &lt;br /&gt;
Suarez announced his run on Thursday morning on Twitter. &lt;br /&gt;
“My Dad taught me that you get to choose your battles, and I am choosing the biggest one of my life. I'm running for President,” he tweeted.  &lt;br /&gt;
Suarez joins other Republicans in an increasingly crowded field, including Donald Trump, Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and Sen. Tim Scott. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mayor-francis-suarez-of-miami-throws-his-republican-bid-for-presidency.htm"&gt;Read More: “Bitcoin Mayor” Francis Suarez of Miami Throws in His Republican Bid for Presidency&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Francis Suarez</category><category>Donald Trump</category><category>Tim Scott</category><category>Ron DeSantis</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mayor-francis-suarez-of-miami-throws-his-republican-bid-for-presidency.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117051/313279/screen-shot-2023-06-15-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="799152"/></item><item><title>Former SEC Chair Clayton Says 'Vast Majority' of Crypto Tokens are Securities – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chair-clayton-says-vast-majority-of-crypto-tokens-are-securities-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Jay Clayton – former chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – expressed a view of the crypto market on Wednesday that largely mirrors that of his current successor, Gary Gensler. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chair-clayton-says-vast-majority-of-crypto-tokens-are-securities-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Former SEC Chair Clayton Says 'Vast Majority' of Crypto Tokens are Securities – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chair-clayton-says-vast-majority-of-crypto-tokens-are-securities-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117050/313277/adobestock-302242411-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="126345"/></item><item><title>‘If You’re Selling BTC for Something, Sell it for Gold Instead of USD’, Says Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/if-youre-selling-btc-for-something-sell-it-for-gold-instead-of-usd-says-tether-cto-paolo-ardoino.htm</link><description>In an insightful conversation with Cryptonews, Paolo Ardoino, the CTO of both Tether and Bitfinex, shed light on crucial topics relating to the crypto world. &lt;br /&gt;
The dialogue navigated the volatile waters of inflation, the allure of gold as a tangible asset, and the growing fascination with digital gold – Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
Ardoino also explained Tether's novel approach toward global transactions and the role of their unique digital gold model.Let's dive in....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/if-youre-selling-btc-for-something-sell-it-for-gold-instead-of-usd-says-tether-cto-paolo-ardoino.htm"&gt;Read More: ‘If You’re Selling BTC for Something, Sell it for Gold Instead of USD’, Says Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><category>Gold</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Inflation</category><category>Coronavirus</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Turkey</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Asia</category><category>China</category><category>India</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Security</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/if-youre-selling-btc-for-something-sell-it-for-gold-instead-of-usd-says-tether-cto-paolo-ardoino.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116388/312282/paolo-ardoino-source-cnbc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="449854"/></item><item><title>BlackRock Close to Filing an Application for a Bitcoin ETF: CoinDesk</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-close-filing-an-application-for-bitcoin-etf-coindesk.htm</link><description>The world’s largest asset manager is close to filing an application for a bitcoin exchange-traded fund, according to CoinDesk.  &lt;br /&gt;
BlackRock will use Coinbase (COIN) Custody for the ETF as well as Coinbase’s spot market data for pricing, a source told CoinDesk.  &lt;br /&gt;
It is not clear if the ETF will be one based on the spot or futures market — Blackrock did not respond to a request for comment from cryptonews. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-close-filing-an-application-for-bitcoin-etf-coindesk.htm"&gt;Read More: BlackRock Close to Filing an Application for a Bitcoin ETF: CoinDesk&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Etf Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-close-filing-an-application-for-bitcoin-etf-coindesk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117035/313255/adobestock-389547752-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="495065"/></item><item><title>Twitter Founder Jack Dorsey Backs Bitcoin Nonprofit Brink with $5 Million Investment – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/twitter-founder-jack-dorsey-backs-bitcoin-nonprofit-brink-with-5-million-investment-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>Twitter founder Jack Dorsey has decided to commit $5 million to Bitcoin non-profit Brink, providing the organization with funds to finance its support for independent BTC developers.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a tweet, Brink expressed gratitude to the entrepreneur for the funds. The non-profit clarified that these funds would be distributed in five separate payments, each amounting to $1 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/twitter-founder-jack-dorsey-backs-bitcoin-nonprofit-brink-with-5-million-investment-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Twitter Founder Jack Dorsey Backs Bitcoin Nonprofit Brink with $5 Million Investment – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Dorsey</category><category>Brink</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/twitter-founder-jack-dorsey-backs-bitcoin-nonprofit-brink-with-5-million-investment-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117031/313250/image0-50.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185294"/></item><item><title>SEC Crackdown on Crypto: Harsh Realization or Necessary Clarity?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-crackdown-crypto-harsh-realization-or-necessary-clarity.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency industry has been under huge pressure since the price of Bitcoin plunged from its all-time high of $69,000 in late 2021.  &lt;br /&gt;
A string of alleged frauds, financial contagions, and security breaches, along with the collapse of some high-profile trading and lending platforms, has led to the loss of around $2 trillion in value across the digital asset market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-crackdown-crypto-harsh-realization-or-necessary-clarity.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Crackdown on Crypto: Harsh Realization or Necessary Clarity?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-crackdown-crypto-harsh-realization-or-necessary-clarity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117019/313221/adobestock-521876474-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="375020"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as Market Sell-Off Sends ETH Below $1,800 Level – Where is the Next ETH Support?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-market-sell-off-sends-eth-below-1800-level-where-is-the-next-eth-support.htm</link><description>The price of Ethereum (ETH) has dropped by 6.5% in the past 24 hours, with its fall to $1,637 coming as the cryptocurrency market continues to suffer losses amid regulatory uncertainty. &lt;br /&gt;
ETH is now down by 11% in the past week, although it does remain up by 52% in the last 12 months, with the coin having recovered relatively well since the start of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-market-sell-off-sends-eth-below-1800-level-where-is-the-next-eth-support.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as Market Sell-Off Sends ETH Below $1,800 Level – Where is the Next ETH Support?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-market-sell-off-sends-eth-below-1800-level-where-is-the-next-eth-support.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117012/313224/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1410792"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin-Based Strike Debuts Lightning Network Cross-Border Payments in Mexico – Crypto Adoption on the Rise</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-based-strike-debuts-lightning-network-cross-border-payments-in-mexico-crypto-adoption-on-the-rise.htm</link><description>Bitcoin payments firm Strike has extended the reach of its cross-border payments service to Mexico, as the company aims to leverage the country’s expansive remittances market. &lt;br /&gt;
As of June 14, 2023, the company has introduced its 'Send Globally' service to the third-largest country in Latin America. The service allows users to send funds internationally, providing a convenient solution for cross-border transactions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-based-strike-debuts-lightning-network-cross-border-payments-in-mexico-crypto-adoption-on-the-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin-Based Strike Debuts Lightning Network Cross-Border Payments in Mexico – Crypto Adoption on the Rise&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Lightning Network</category><category>Binance</category><category>U.S. Dollar</category><category>Layer-2</category><category>Layer-2 scaling solution</category><category>Layer Protocol</category><category>Mexico</category><category>Argentina</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-based-strike-debuts-lightning-network-cross-border-payments-in-mexico-crypto-adoption-on-the-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117011/313196/btc-l.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="422310"/></item><item><title>Five Reasons Why Long-term Holders Are Dumping Dogecoin for Doge Rush</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/five-reasons-why-long-term-holders-are-dumping-dogecoin-for-doge-rush.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The text below is a press release that is not part of Cryptonews.com editorial content. &lt;br /&gt;
The Doge Rush presale is moving ahead at a meteoric pace as investors hoard $DR tokens at a discount in anticipation of a wild bull run later this year. Interestingly, a significant share of the presale participants includes long-term DOGE and SHIB holders who are leaving the high-cap meme coins for better returns. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/five-reasons-why-long-term-holders-are-dumping-dogecoin-for-doge-rush.htm"&gt;Read More: Five Reasons Why Long-term Holders Are Dumping Dogecoin for Doge Rush&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/five-reasons-why-long-term-holders-are-dumping-dogecoin-for-doge-rush.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117013/313190/image1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="289531"/></item><item><title>Crypto Broker FPG Suspends Services After $15 Million Cyberattack</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-broker-fpg-suspends-services-after-15-million-cyber-attack.htm</link><description>Floating Point Group (FPG), a crypto prime brokerage, has suspended all withdrawals, deposits and trading on its platform after suffering from a $15 million cyberattack over the weekend. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm said in a Twitter thread on Wednesday that although it had managed to limit the overall impact of the attack, operations were still being suspended “out of an abundance of caution.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-broker-fpg-suspends-services-after-15-million-cyber-attack.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Broker FPG Suspends Services After $15 Million Cyberattack&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-broker-fpg-suspends-services-after-15-million-cyber-attack.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117010/313185/suspension-of-service.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="208507"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as $100 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying SHIB at This Level?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib-at-level.htm</link><description>The Shiba Inu price has dropped by 4% in the past 24 hours, falling to $0.00000656 as the cryptocurrency market continues to weather the storm caused by the SEC's recent actions against Binance and Coinbase. &lt;br /&gt;
SHIB's current price means it has declined by 17% in the past week and by 25% in the last 30 days, with the meme token also down by 19% since the beginning of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib-at-level.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as $100 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying SHIB at This Level?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-100-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib-at-level.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117004/313183/shiba-inu-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1195418"/></item></channel></rss>
