<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Binance Forced to Stop Providing Crypto Services in Belgium by Financial Regulator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-forced-stop-providing-crypto-services-belgium-by-financial-regulator.htm</link><description>Source: AdobeStock / prima91 &lt;br /&gt;
The financial regulator in Belgium, the Financial Services and Markets Authority (FSMA) had forced the cryptocurrency exchange Binance to halt its services in the country alleging that the exchange has violated the law by serving Belgian customers from countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-forced-stop-providing-crypto-services-belgium-by-financial-regulator.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Forced to Stop Providing Crypto Services in Belgium by Financial Regulator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-forced-stop-providing-crypto-services-belgium-by-financial-regulator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117843/314526/binance.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="86909"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Cash Price Prediction as $1.2 Billion Pushes BCH Up 75% in a Week – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-12-billion-pushes-bch-up-75-week-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Bitcoin Cash (BCH) has witnessed an extraordinary price surge, soaring by 75% in a mere week. This notable ascent has been accompanied by a substantial inflow of $1.2 billion in trading volume.  &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin Cash's recent remarkable upward trend can largely be attributed to its listing on the EDX exchange.  &lt;br /&gt;
EDX is a trading platform supported by prominent financial institutions such as Fidelity, Schwab, and Citadel. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-12-billion-pushes-bch-up-75-week-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Cash Price Prediction as $1.2 Billion Pushes BCH Up 75% in a Week – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cash-price-prediction-as-12-billion-pushes-bch-up-75-week-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117844/314543/bch.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="321245"/></item><item><title>Wall Street Memes Surges Past $10 Million as Investors Rush to Buy the Latest Meme Coin Before It Lists on Exchanges - How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-surges-past-10-million-as-investors-rush-to-buy-the-latest-meme-coin-before-it-lists-on-exchanges-how-to-buy-early.htm</link><description>The innovative meme coin, Wall Street Memes ($WSM), has achieved an impressive milestone by surging beyond the $10 million mark in presale investment. &lt;br /&gt;
This burgeoning cryptocurrency is rapidly gaining popularity among early-stage investors, positioning itself as the next king of meme coins.  &lt;br /&gt;
Meme coins have played a crucial role in the recent resurgence of the cryptocurrency market. The paradigm shift began with the Pepe-the-frog meme coin project and has since spilled over....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-surges-past-10-million-as-investors-rush-to-buy-the-latest-meme-coin-before-it-lists-on-exchanges-how-to-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Wall Street Memes Surges Past $10 Million as Investors Rush to Buy the Latest Meme Coin Before It Lists on Exchanges - How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-surges-past-10-million-as-investors-rush-to-buy-the-latest-meme-coin-before-it-lists-on-exchanges-how-to-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117850/314539/wall-street-meme-price.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="523238"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Gains Victory in Supreme Court Over Arbitration Lawsuit – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-gains-victory-supreme-court-over-arbitration-lawsuit-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The US Supreme Court has ruled in favor of Coinbase, backing its request to halt customer lawsuits while it pursues appeals aimed at moving the disputes out of courts and into private arbitration.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, five of the nine Justices voted in support of Coinbase's request, overturning a lower court's ruling involving a user who sued after a scammer stole money from his account....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-gains-victory-supreme-court-over-arbitration-lawsuit-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Gains Victory in Supreme Court Over Arbitration Lawsuit – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>US Supreme Court</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-gains-victory-supreme-court-over-arbitration-lawsuit-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117847/314531/adobestock-286664985-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="152203"/></item><item><title>Prison Time, Scam Entity, ETF Attempts, Mini FBI and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/prison-time-scam-entity-etf-attempts-mini-fbi-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/prison-time-scam-entity-etf-attempts-mini-fbi-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Prison Time, Scam Entity, ETF Attempts, Mini FBI and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/prison-time-scam-entity-etf-attempts-mini-fbi-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117780/314443/markets-crypto-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="362757"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Makes New Yearly High – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-makes-new-yearly-high-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has experienced a remarkable surge, surpassing the 31,000 mark, signaling a bullish momentum in the cryptocurrency market.  &lt;br /&gt;
The recent price movement has defied expectations, as Bitcoin failed to complete a retracement to the 23.6% Fibonacci level.  &lt;br /&gt;
This upward trend has been fueled by growing optimism and positive sentiment in the crypto market, particularly driven by the recent news of a Bitcoin ETF. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-makes-new-yearly-high-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Makes New Yearly High – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-makes-new-yearly-high-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117832/314520/24-5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="527912"/></item><item><title>JPMorgan Enables Euro-Denominated Blockchain Payments through JPM Coin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-enables-euro-denominated-blockchain-payments-through-jpm-coin.htm</link><description>JPMorgan has expanded its JPM Coin blockchain payment service to include euro-denominated transactions for corporate clients.  &lt;br /&gt;
The platform, launched in 2019 for dollar payments, allows wholesale payments clients to transfer dollars or euros between JPMorgan accounts around the world, or make payments to other customers of the bank using blockchain technology instead of traditional payment methods. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-enables-euro-denominated-blockchain-payments-through-jpm-coin.htm"&gt;Read More: JPMorgan Enables Euro-Denominated Blockchain Payments through JPM Coin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Tokenization</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-enables-euro-denominated-blockchain-payments-through-jpm-coin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117835/314512/adobestock-monticellllo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="247160"/></item><item><title>Experts: This Is Why Russia Is Becoming a ‘Crypto Mining Hotspot’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/experts-why-russia-becoming-crypto-mining-hotspot.htm</link><description>Experts have explained why Russia is reportedly becoming a crypto mining hotspot, as the nation claims its crypto mining hashrate is second only to that of the USA. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Finam, Nikita Zuborev, a Senior Analyst at the domestic crypto platform BestChange, said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/experts-why-russia-becoming-crypto-mining-hotspot.htm"&gt;Read More: Experts: This Is Why Russia Is Becoming a ‘Crypto Mining Hotspot’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Crypto Mining</category><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/experts-why-russia-becoming-crypto-mining-hotspot.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117765/314356/rus-2306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="463890"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Traditional Finance Giants Citadel, Fidelity and Schwab Enter Crypto – Can BTC Hit $1 Million?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-traditional-finance-giants-citadel-fidelity-schwab-enter-crypto-can-btc-hit-1-million.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, faces an intriguing future as major players from the traditional finance sector, including Citadel, Fidelity, and Charles Schwab, officially enter the crypto space.  &lt;br /&gt;
Despite regulatory challenges and previous setbacks in the industry, the participation of established institutions demonstrates sustained long-term institutional interest in cryptocurrencies. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-traditional-finance-giants-citadel-fidelity-schwab-enter-crypto-can-btc-hit-1-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Traditional Finance Giants Citadel, Fidelity and Schwab Enter Crypto – Can BTC Hit $1 Million?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-traditional-finance-giants-citadel-fidelity-schwab-enter-crypto-can-btc-hit-1-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117800/314472/23-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="484680"/></item><item><title>Santander, Crédit Agricole Asset Servicing Arm Acquires French Crypto Custody License – Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/santander-credit-agricole-asset-servicing-arm-acquires-french-crypto-custody-license-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>CACEIS Bank, the combined asset servicing arm of the major European banks Crédit Agricole and Santander, has acquired a French crypto custody license, according to the website of France’s financial regulator. &lt;br /&gt;
The license, which was granted by France’s Financial Markets Authority (AMF) on June 20, means that CACEIS Bank is now registered as a digital asset service provider for the service of “digital asset custody” only....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/santander-credit-agricole-asset-servicing-arm-acquires-french-crypto-custody-license-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Santander, Crédit Agricole Asset Servicing Arm Acquires French Crypto Custody License – Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>France</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/santander-credit-agricole-asset-servicing-arm-acquires-french-crypto-custody-license-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117818/314489/paris.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="195603"/></item><item><title>BlackRock Executive Stresses Importance of Knowing Counterparties in DeFi for Institutional Engagement</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-executive-stresses-importance-of-knowing-counterparties-defi-for-institutional-engagement.htm</link><description>It is critical for financial institutions to know who they are trading with when using decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols, asset management giant BlackRock’s head of strategic partnerships, Joseph Chalom, has said. &lt;br /&gt;
"The first issue is, who am I trading with? [...] We go to jail, if we don't know who we're trading with," Chalom told the audience during the State of Crypto Summit hosted by Coinbase and the Financial Times on Thursday in New York....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-executive-stresses-importance-of-knowing-counterparties-defi-for-institutional-engagement.htm"&gt;Read More: BlackRock Executive Stresses Importance of Knowing Counterparties in DeFi for Institutional Engagement&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blackrock-executive-stresses-importance-of-knowing-counterparties-defi-for-institutional-engagement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117802/314444/blackrock-building.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="221477"/></item><item><title>Fentanyl Ingredients Sold for Crypto by Chinese Labs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fentanyl-ingredients-sold-for-crypto-by-chinese-labs.htm</link><description>Chinese chemical producers are accepting cryptocurrency as payment for fentanyl ingredients they sell to drug organizations worldwide. &lt;br /&gt;
Researchers at crypto analytics platform Elliptic have found over 90 Chinese chemical companies that sold fentanyl precursor chemicals and advertised their products on the open web, 90% of which offered to accept payment in cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Tether (USDT)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fentanyl-ingredients-sold-for-crypto-by-chinese-labs.htm"&gt;Read More: Fentanyl Ingredients Sold for Crypto by Chinese Labs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Fentanyl</category><category>Drugs</category><category>Elliptic</category><category>Crypto Payment</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fentanyl-ingredients-sold-for-crypto-by-chinese-labs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117816/314485/apothecary-g82be9182e-192.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="100755"/></item><item><title>Deal Cancelled: BitGo Pulls Out of Prime Trust Acquisition and Users Report Withdrawal Issues</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/deal-cancelled-bitgo-pulls-out-of-prime-trust-acquisition-users-report-withdrawal-issues.htm</link><description>BitGo, the American crypto custodian platform, has made the decision to cancel the acquisition of Prime Trust.  &lt;br /&gt;
Following this announcement, Prime Trust has taken measures to suspend withdrawals. &lt;br /&gt;
The cancellation of the deal comes just two weeks after BitGo signed a non-binding letter of intent to acquire Prime Trust. &lt;br /&gt;
The intended acquisition of Prime Trust by BitGo was expected to provide financial support to Prime Trust, which has been facing bankruptcy challenges....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/deal-cancelled-bitgo-pulls-out-of-prime-trust-acquisition-users-report-withdrawal-issues.htm"&gt;Read More: Deal Cancelled: BitGo Pulls Out of Prime Trust Acquisition and Users Report Withdrawal Issues&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>BitGo</category><category>Prime Trust</category><category>TUSD</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/deal-cancelled-bitgo-pulls-out-of-prime-trust-acquisition-users-report-withdrawal-issues.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117767/314366/bitgo-prime-trust-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="90415"/></item><item><title>Mastercard's 'Engage' Programme Enters Crypto Card Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercards-engage-programme-enters-crypto-card-market.htm</link><description>The world’s second-largest payment-processing company, Mastercard, has announced that it is expanding its Engage program to help scale crypto and blockchain technology.  &lt;br /&gt;
As per a press release, Mastercard is expanding its Engage program to allow a number of crypto firms to leverage the credit card giant’s global network. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercards-engage-programme-enters-crypto-card-market.htm"&gt;Read More: Mastercard's 'Engage' Programme Enters Crypto Card Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>mastercard</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mastercards-engage-programme-enters-crypto-card-market.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117784/314395/mastercard.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="290475"/></item><item><title>Artificial Intelligence and Cryptocurrencies: Regulatory Frenemies in the Making</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/artificial-intelligence-cryptocurrencies-regulatory-frenemies-making.htm</link><description>Both at the forefront of technological innovation of investor interest, crypto and artificial intelligence (AI) are forming something of a love-hate relationship. Aaron Brown – former head of financial market research at AQR Capital Management – argued in a recent opinion piece that both industries represent competing areas of venture capital interest, as well as dueling sources of fear for regulators. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/artificial-intelligence-cryptocurrencies-regulatory-frenemies-making.htm"&gt;Read More: Artificial Intelligence and Cryptocurrencies: Regulatory Frenemies in the Making&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/artificial-intelligence-cryptocurrencies-regulatory-frenemies-making.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117814/314484/adobestock-323829966.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="63766"/></item><item><title>Arbitrum Price Prediction as $200 Million Trading Volume Shoots ARB Up 9% – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-price-prediction-as-200-million-trading-volume-shoots-arb-up-9-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>Arbitrum (ARB) coin, the leading Layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum, has been experiencing a surge in popularity and investor interest.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the past week, its value has significantly increased from $0.9411 to $1.1691, with a current settling point around $1.1250.  &lt;br /&gt;
One contributing factor to Arbitrum's success is the introduction of Arbitrum Orbit, a revolutionary tool that empowers Layer 3 networks and brings new possibilities to the ecosystem. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-price-prediction-as-200-million-trading-volume-shoots-arb-up-9-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Arbitrum Price Prediction as $200 Million Trading Volume Shoots ARB Up 9% – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-price-prediction-as-200-million-trading-volume-shoots-arb-up-9-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117809/314478/arb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="199994"/></item><item><title>Binance Brazil Executive Called to Testify in Congress Amid Regulatory Crackdown</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-brazil-executive-called-testify-congress-amid-regulatory-crackdown.htm</link><description>Amidst a global regulatory crackdown on Binance, the director of Binance Brazil, Guilherme Haddad, has been summoned to testify before the Brazilian parliament.  &lt;br /&gt;
Alfredo Gaspar, a member of the Brazilian Chamber of Deputies, initiated the summons.  &lt;br /&gt;
Haddad is expected to provide testimony as part of the ongoing investigation conducted by the Parliamentary Commission of Inquiry (CPI), which is examining allegations of pyramid schemes in the country....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-brazil-executive-called-testify-congress-amid-regulatory-crackdown.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Brazil Executive Called to Testify in Congress Amid Regulatory Crackdown&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-brazil-executive-called-testify-congress-amid-regulatory-crackdown.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117774/314488/adobestock-484307506-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="222759"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: JPMorgan Deploys JPM Coin for Euro-Denominated Payments, Casa Rolls out Support for Ethereum Storage, US SEC Grants BlockFi Temporary Relief From Settling a $30M Penalty, Gemini Staking Pro Expands to the UK</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-deploys-jpm-coin-for-euro-denominated-payments-casa-rolls-out-support-for-ethereum-storage-us-sec-grants-blockfi-temporary-relief-from-settling-a-30m-penalty-gemini-staking-pro-expands-to-the-uk.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-deploys-jpm-coin-for-euro-denominated-payments-casa-rolls-out-support-for-ethereum-storage-us-sec-grants-blockfi-temporary-relief-from-settling-a-30m-penalty-gemini-staking-pro-expands-to-the-uk.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: JPMorgan Deploys JPM Coin for Euro-Denominated Payments, Casa Rolls out Support for Ethereum Storage, US SEC Grants BlockFi Temporary Relief From Settling a $30M Penalty, Gemini Staking Pro Expands to the UK&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Banking</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>Euro</category><category>Siemens</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Legal</category><category>BlockFi</category><category>SEC</category><category>Gemini</category><category>UK</category><category>Staking</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Crypto.com</category><category>Spain</category><category>Middle East</category><category>Africa</category><category>Investment</category><category>Casa</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-jpmorgan-deploys-jpm-coin-for-euro-denominated-payments-casa-rolls-out-support-for-ethereum-storage-us-sec-grants-blockfi-temporary-relief-from-settling-a-30m-penalty-gemini-staking-pro-expands-to-the-uk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117779/314413/adobestock-dragos-asaftei-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="499012"/></item><item><title>Daniela Barbosa, Executive Director of Hyperledger Foundation, on Asset Tokenization, Enterprise Blockchain Use Cases, and CBDCs | Ep. 241</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/daniela-barbosa-executive-director-of-hyperledger-foundation-asset-tokenization-enterprise-blockchain-use-cases-cbdcs-ep-241.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Daniela Barbosa, Executive Director of Hyperledger Foundation, talks about Hyperledger Foundation’s history and the role it plays within the blockchain ecosystem, the growing enterprise and institutional adoption of blockchain technology, and government adoption of CBDCs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/daniela-barbosa-executive-director-of-hyperledger-foundation-asset-tokenization-enterprise-blockchain-use-cases-cbdcs-ep-241.htm"&gt;Read More: Daniela Barbosa, Executive Director of Hyperledger Foundation, on Asset Tokenization, Enterprise Blockchain Use Cases, and CBDCs | Ep. 241&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/daniela-barbosa-executive-director-of-hyperledger-foundation-asset-tokenization-enterprise-blockchain-use-cases-cbdcs-ep-241.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117775/314376/daniela-barbosa-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120571"/></item><item><title>Crypto Community Divided over BlackRock's Recent Bitcoin ETF Application</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-community-divided-over-blackrocks-recent-bitcoin-etf-application.htm</link><description>Asset management giant BlackRock's recent application to launch a Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) has stirred a debate within the crypto community, with mixed reactions and concerns about the involvement of traditional financial giants in the industry. &lt;br /&gt;
The world's largest asset manager's move to enter the crypto space is seen by many as a significant validation for the industry, especially after a turbulent period of bankruptcies and scandals....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-community-divided-over-blackrocks-recent-bitcoin-etf-application.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Community Divided over BlackRock's Recent Bitcoin ETF Application&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>Blackrock</category><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-community-divided-over-blackrocks-recent-bitcoin-etf-application.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117793/314417/bitcoin-etf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="118863"/></item></channel></rss>
