<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Rodeo Finance Exploited For $888,000 In Another DeFi Hack on Arbitrum Network</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm</link><description>Arbitrum Network-based Rodeo Finance lost 472 ether ($888,000) in a DeFi exploit today. &lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain security firm PeckShield revealed that the Rodeo Finance hacker transferred the stolen funds from Arbitrum to Ethereum. &lt;br /&gt;
Further analysis revealed that the attacker exchanged the stolen tokens for various other assets before converting them back to ether. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm"&gt;Read More: Rodeo Finance Exploited For $888,000 In Another DeFi Hack on Arbitrum Network&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119292/317267/crypto-hack-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="116999"/></item><item><title>Former SEC Chairman Highlights Conditions for Bitcoin ETF Approval</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm</link><description>Former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairman Jay Clayton has said that a spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded fund (ETF) is likely to get approved if it can be shown that the Bitcoin spot market offers the same “efficacy” as the futures market. &lt;br /&gt;
“If they’re [applicants] right—that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market—it would be hard to resist approving a Bitcoin ETF,” Clayton said in an interview with CNBC on Monday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Former SEC Chairman Highlights Conditions for Bitcoin ETF Approval&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Jay Clayton</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119299/317266/jay-clayton.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="610480"/></item><item><title>Apple vs. Zapple Pay: Bitcoin Tipping on Damus App Challenges App Store Policies</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm</link><description>In June, Apple (AAPL) threatened to remove the Bitcoin-friendly social media app, Damus from its App Store, which led to the rise of Zapple Pay. The reason behind this threat is Damus' feature that allows users to tip each other with bitcoin (BTC) on the app, which Apple considers equivalent to selling digital media. &lt;br /&gt;
Damus operates on the Nostr protocol, a decentralized social media platform popular among Bitcoiners due to its support for Lightning Network payments. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm"&gt;Read More: Apple vs. Zapple Pay: Bitcoin Tipping on Damus App Challenges App Store Policies&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Apple</category><category>Apple app store</category><category>Jack Dorsey</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119294/317263/screenshot-2023-07-11-123343.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="65646"/></item><item><title>Crypto and Stablecoins Are Not Money, Says Bank of England Governor in Favor of 'Enhanced Digital Money'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm</link><description>Andrew Bailey, Governor of the Bank of England (BoE), has reiterated his stance against cryptocurrencies, during his recent speech at the Mansion House in London. &lt;br /&gt;
Bailey, who has previously voiced his concerns about the speculative nature of digital currencies, said Monday that Bitcoins have “no intrinsic value and are highly volatile.” He also noted that cryptos like Bitcoin (BTC) are “best treated as extremely speculative investments.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto and Stablecoins Are Not Money, Says Bank of England Governor in Favor of 'Enhanced Digital Money'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119285/317249/adobestock-94685515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="604663"/></item><item><title>Crypto Phishing Attack: Gutter Cat Gang Twitter Account Compromised, NFTs Worth $750K Stolen</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-phishing-attack-gutter-cat-gang-twitter-account-compromised-nfts-worth-750k-stolen.htm</link><description>The crypto industry has seen yet another hacking attack that resulted in a theft of a massive amount of money.  &lt;br /&gt;
The hacker or hackers targeted the official Twitter account of Gutter Cat Gang — a popular NFT collection on the Ethereum network.  &lt;br /&gt;
The hack of the account belonging to the project’s co-founder resulted in a loss estimated somewhere between $750,000 and $900,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-phishing-attack-gutter-cat-gang-twitter-account-compromised-nfts-worth-750k-stolen.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Phishing Attack: Gutter Cat Gang Twitter Account Compromised, NFTs Worth $750K Stolen&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-phishing-attack-gutter-cat-gang-twitter-account-compromised-nfts-worth-750k-stolen.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119288/317252/crypto-phishing-attack.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1715153"/></item><item><title>Crypto Sleuth Claims YouTuber 'Blue' Used NFT Drainer Tech to Carry Out $1.5 Million Scam</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuth-claims-youtuber-blue-used-nft-drainer-tech-carry-out-15-million-scam.htm</link><description>Crypto sleuth ZachXBT has alleged YouTuber known as Blue or Jack used NFT drainer tech Monkey and other similar services to steal $1.5 million. &lt;br /&gt;
ZachXBT’s investigation revealed that the YouTuber was involved in multiple crypto scams and stole millions of dollars. &lt;br /&gt;
Before turning to crypto scams in 2021, the YouTuber amassed a following of more than 122,000 subscribers by uploading gaming and trolling videos....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuth-claims-youtuber-blue-used-nft-drainer-tech-carry-out-15-million-scam.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Sleuth Claims YouTuber 'Blue' Used NFT Drainer Tech to Carry Out $1.5 Million Scam&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Crypto Scam</category><category>ZachXBT</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-sleuth-claims-youtuber-blue-used-nft-drainer-tech-carry-out-15-million-scam.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119284/317250/cryptoscam.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="154465"/></item><item><title>BTC2.0 Surges 7,000% as the Meme Token Goes Viral But Crypto Whales are Stacking This Lesser Known Coin Instead – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-surges-7000-as-meme-token-goes-viral-but-crypto-whales-are-stacking-lesser-known-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>BTC2.0 has surged by a massive 7,000% in the past 24 hours, with the new meme token reaching $0.1478 as it goes viral and attracts exchange listings. &lt;br /&gt;
BTC2.0 is the latest in a long – and seemingly endless – line of new meme tokens that have emerged this year to promise gains during the ongoing bear market, following in the footsteps of PEPE, SPONGE and also a wave of '2.0' coins that have piggybacked on the successes of earlier tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-surges-7000-as-meme-token-goes-viral-but-crypto-whales-are-stacking-lesser-known-coin-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: BTC2.0 Surges 7,000% as the Meme Token Goes Viral But Crypto Whales are Stacking This Lesser Known Coin Instead – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-surges-7000-as-meme-token-goes-viral-but-crypto-whales-are-stacking-lesser-known-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119282/317247/btc2-0-surges-7000-as-the.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="540783"/></item><item><title>Stepn Creator Plans to Give Away $430,000+ in Crypto to Generate Buzz for New Video Game</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/stepn-creator-plans-give-away-430000-crypto-generate-buzz-for-new-video-game.htm</link><description>Find Satoshi Lab, the team behind blockchain-powered fitness app STEPN revealed its first Web3 video game dubbed 'Gas Hero'. And it claims to give away $431,400 in a contest promoting it. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Find Satoshi Lab, this is a Web3 social game that will invite users to collect Gas Hero non-fungible tokens (NFTs).  &lt;br /&gt;
It is built around the concept of Battle and Earn, as well as on strategy and decentralized elements such as community voting....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/stepn-creator-plans-give-away-430000-crypto-generate-buzz-for-new-video-game.htm"&gt;Read More: Stepn Creator Plans to Give Away $430,000+ in Crypto to Generate Buzz for New Video Game&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Gaming</category><category>STEPN</category><category>Web3</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/stepn-creator-plans-give-away-430000-crypto-generate-buzz-for-new-video-game.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119266/317240/screenshot-2023-07-11-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="963945"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin is Going to Zero as PEPE Price Falls 20% in a Week and Thug Life Token Just Raised Almost $1 Million With Less Than 7 Days Left</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-going-zero-as-pepe-price-falls-20-week-thug-life-token-just-raised-almost-1-million-with-less-than-7-days-left.htm</link><description>The price of Pepe Coin (PEPE) has risen by 4% in the past 24 hours, although its move to $0.00000152 today still means that it's down by nearly 20% in the past week. &lt;br /&gt;
And while PEPE is actually up by 60% in the last 30 days, it remains down by 64% since hitting an all-time high of $0.00000431 in early May....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-going-zero-as-pepe-price-falls-20-week-thug-life-token-just-raised-almost-1-million-with-less-than-7-days-left.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin is Going to Zero as PEPE Price Falls 20% in a Week and Thug Life Token Just Raised Almost $1 Million With Less Than 7 Days Left&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-going-zero-as-pepe-price-falls-20-week-thug-life-token-just-raised-almost-1-million-with-less-than-7-days-left.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119276/317242/pepe-coin-is-going-to-zer.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1284642"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Up 1.5% as Market Focus Shifts to June CPI and PPI Readings</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is trading at $30,492 in today's market, marking an over 1% rise on Tuesday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency market continues to draw attention as Gary Gensler, the chair of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), faces criticism from a Ripple attorney, who refers to him as a "bad faith regulator" following the SEC's acceptance of Grayscale's Bitcoin Futures Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Up 1.5% as Market Focus Shifts to June CPI and PPI Readings&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-up-15-as-market-focus-shifts-to-june-cpi-and-ppi-readings.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119259/317203/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1662397"/></item><item><title>Litecoin's Strong Performance Before 'Halvening' Fuels Optimism for Bitcoin Rally</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) investors are closely watching the performance of Litecoin (LTC), another proof-of-work token, as the flagship cryptocurrency gears up for its upcoming "halvening" event.  &lt;br /&gt;
The term "halvening" refers to the protocol-backed reduction in rewards for miners who successfully solve puzzles and add blocks to proof-of-work tokens like Litecoin and Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin's Strong Performance Before 'Halvening' Fuels Optimism for Bitcoin Rally&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>Litecoin price</category><category>Halving</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoins-strong-performance-before-halvening-fuels-optimism-for-bitcoin-rally.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119277/317236/ltc-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="201632"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Builds Strong Support at $1,800 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</link><description>The Ethereum price has risen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, with its move to $1,881 coming as the wider cryptocurrency market also sees a modest gain today. &lt;br /&gt;
ETH is now down by 3.5% in the past week but up by 7% in the last 30 days, with the altcoin holding firmly above the $1,800 support level in the face of recent market-wide losses....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as ETH Builds Strong Support at $1,800 Level – When is the Next Leg Up?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-eth-builds-strong-support-at-1800-level-when-next-leg-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119271/317228/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1375174"/></item><item><title>Dubai Virtual Assets Regulator Imposes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Exchange BitOasis</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm</link><description>Dubai-based cryptocurrency exchange BitOasis, which received a minimum viable product (MVP) operational license from the UAE’s crypto regulator in April, is now facing enforcement actions from the authority. &lt;br /&gt;
Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) issued a market alert on July 10, indicating that BitOasis’ conditional MVP license has been suspended as the firm failed to meet mandated conditions set forth by the regulator....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm"&gt;Read More: Dubai Virtual Assets Regulator Imposes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Exchange BitOasis&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-virtual-assets-regulator-imposes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-exchange-bitoasis.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119269/317219/buildings-1839726-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="188449"/></item><item><title>South Korean Pop Star Says He Lost ‘$77,000’ on Crypto Investment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm</link><description>Seo Chul-goo (aka Xitsuh), a South Korean pop star, rapper, and TV personality, says he “lost” up to $77,000 on bad crypto investments.  &lt;br /&gt;
The star and his fiancee Lee Young-joo appeared on the E Channel TV talk show “Love of a Lifetime” (literal translation), where he discussed his precarious financial situation.  &lt;br /&gt;
TVDaily quoted Lee as saying,...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Pop Star Says He Lost ‘$77,000’ on Crypto Investment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Celebrities</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-pop-star-say-he-lost-77000-crypto-investment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119224/317130/eer1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="559283"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Police to Auction Assets Seized from Suspected Crypto Fraudsters</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm</link><description>Police in Brazil have announced plans to auction off assets seized from Trust Investing, a suspected crypto-themed financial pyramid operator. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Portal do Bitcoin, a Federal Court in Campo Grande granted the authorities the right to auction off “seven luxury cars,” including armored vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;
The assets are valued at just under $288,000 and comprise BMWs, a Land Rover, and Porsches, as well as trucks and other cars....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Police to Auction Assets Seized from Suspected Crypto Fraudsters&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Fraud</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-auction-assets-seized-from-suspected-crypto-fraudsters.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119095/316920/adobestock-193294139.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="535660"/></item><item><title>DeFi Platform Arcadia Finance Falls Victim to $455K Hack on Ethereum and Optimism</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm</link><description>Arcadia Finance has joined the growing list of DeFi protocols to lose funds in hack exploitation. The hackers leveraged a code vulnerability to siphon about $455,000 from the protocol’s Ethereum and Optimism vaults. &lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain sleuth PeckShield alerted about Arcadia’s exploitation in a July 9 tweet. In the tweet, PeckShield also highlighted the cause of the attack....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm"&gt;Read More: DeFi Platform Arcadia Finance Falls Victim to $455K Hack on Ethereum and Optimism&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defi-platform-arcadia-finance-falls-victim-455k-hack-ethereum-optimism.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119240/317175/computer-g1b843fd86-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="176673"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Co-founder Faces Legal Proceedings: Trial Preparations Underway</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm</link><description>Source: UDC / YouTube &lt;br /&gt;
Legal proceedings have been initiated against Shin Hyun-Seong, also known as Daniel Shin, concerning charges concerning alleged illicit profits from the sale of Terra (LUNA) tokens. &lt;br /&gt;
The co-founder of Terraform Labs, Daniel Shin, was indicted in South Korea on April 25 in connection with the collapse of Terra and Luna cryptocurrencies. Shin, along with co-founder Do Kwon, established Terraform Labs in 2018. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Co-founder Faces Legal Proceedings: Trial Preparations Underway&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Terra</category><category>Terra Luna</category><category>Terra Classic (LUNC)</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-faces-legal-proceedings-trial-preparations-underway.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119239/317185/screenshot-2023-07-11-010312.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="220288"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 10, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Woonen (WOOO) &lt;br /&gt;
BinanceRemoved Trading Pairs:POWR/BUSDQKC/BUSDSC/BUSDSTEEM/BUSD...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 10, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119210/317075/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Wobbles at $30,000 Support – Is a Larger Sell Off on the Way?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price is currently teetering around the crucial $30,000 support level, raising concerns about the possibility of a more significant sell-off. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency's stability at this critical juncture has attracted considerable attention among traders and investors, as they closely monitor its next move. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Wobbles at $30,000 Support – Is a Larger Sell Off on the Way?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-wobbles-at-30000-support-is-larger-sell-off-way.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119228/317154/10.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482367"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin's Optimism Fades as Turmoil and Interest Rates Present Challenges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) fell lower over the course of last week, as optimism faded among market participants in the face of potentially higher interest rates in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
The price of the number one cryptocurrency have largely been in an uptrend since news broke that the world’s largest asset manager BlackRock had filed to list a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the US....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin's Optimism Fades as Turmoil and Interest Rates Present Challenges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoins-optimism-fades-as-turmoil-interest-rates-present-challenges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119209/317076/bull-and-bear.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="164591"/></item></channel></rss>
