<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Fantom Coin is Going to Zero as FTM Price Plummets 15% But All Attention is On Evil Pepe After Raising $160,000 – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>Following a failed recovery rally, Fantom (FTM) is facing a continuation of the bleak price action that has plagued the mid-ranked Layer-1 since May 2022. &lt;br /&gt;
A short-lived +230% rally at the start of the year has given way to a multi-month cascading price action, which has seen a tough -60% bleed-out for dedicated Fantom holders. &lt;br /&gt;
With Fantom price now trading at a lowly $0.2575 (a 24 hour change of -0.08%) many are now wondering whether FTM is destined to fall to zero....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Fantom Coin is Going to Zero as FTM Price Plummets 15% But All Attention is On Evil Pepe After Raising $160,000 – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantom-coin-going-zero-as-ftm-price-plummets-15-but-all-attention-evil-pepe-after-raising-160000-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120264/319260/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="608509"/></item><item><title>Crypto-Based Bank Receives Support from Myanmar's Shadow Government</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm</link><description>Myanmar is all set to launch its first fully crypto-based banking institution, the Spring Development Bank, on July 22.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Spring Development Bank, named after the Spring Revolution, aims to grant the country’s shadow government National Unity Government (NUG) access to financial services and funding from within and outside the country for their fight against the ruling State Administration Council (SAC), which took over Myanmar in February 2021....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto-Based Bank Receives Support from Myanmar's Shadow Government&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Myanmar</category><category>Crypto Bank</category><category>USDT</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-based-bank-receives-support-from-myanmars-shadow-government.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120271/319259/myanmar-flag-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161825"/></item><item><title>DexTools Trending Crypto $HAMS and $MOG Prices Surge 30,000%, But Buy These 2 Coins Before They List Today – Burn Kenny and $EVILPEPE to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm</link><description>DexTools trending crypto $HAMS and $MOG have both seen their prices pump 30,000% since launch, as money continues to chase hot speculative coins listing directly on decentralized exchanges (DEXs). &lt;br /&gt;
And there is no shortage of launches. Burn Kenny ($KENNY) and Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE) are both likely to list today.  &lt;br /&gt;
Indeed, Kenny could be listing on DEXs in the next few hours as it closes in on its presale target of $500,000, with only around $120k to go....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: DexTools Trending Crypto $HAMS and $MOG Prices Surge 30,000%, But Buy These 2 Coins Before They List Today – Burn Kenny and $EVILPEPE to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dextools-trending-crypto-hams-mog-prices-surge-30000-but-you-can-buy-these-2-coins-before-todays-listing-burn-kenny-kenny-evilpepe-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120253/319245/hams-usd-uni-dextools-io-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="514044"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Trading Volume Surges Past $800 Million – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>The Litecoin price has dropped by 2.5% in the past 24 hours, with its fall to $92.11 also marking an 8.5% fall in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC's losses today comes as the cryptocurrency market as a whole slides by 1% since yesterday, although the altcoin remains up by 10% in the last 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;
It's also up by 63% in the past year, while the coin's 24-hour trading volume has passed $800 million, in a sign that market activity remains elevated and could possibly help it recover soon....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Trading Volume Surges Past $800 Million – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 10:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-trading-volume-surges-past-800-million-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120267/319254/litecoin-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1066632"/></item><item><title>FTX Launches Lawsuit Against Ex-Executives, Including Sam Bankman-Fried, to Reclaim $1 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm</link><description>Now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX has filed a complaint against former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried and other key executives to retrieve more than $1 billion in allegedly misappropriated funds.  &lt;br /&gt;
The lawsuit, filed by FTX under the direction of an executive team led by restructuring expert John Ray, named former Alameda Research CEO Caroline Ellison, FTX co-founder Gary Wang, former FTX engineering director Nishad Singh, and Bankman-Fried as defendants. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Launches Lawsuit Against Ex-Executives, Including Sam Bankman-Fried, to Reclaim $1 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Gary Wang</category><category>Caroline Ellison</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-launches-lawsuit-against-ex-executives-including-sam-bankman-fried-to-reclaim-1-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120265/319242/ftx-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="86751"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Seeks Data from FTX Wallets for SEC Lawsuit Defense</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm</link><description>Terraform Labs, the development firm behind Terra network and the failed stablecoin TerraUSD (USTC), is seeking permission from a court to get access to data from the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Terraform Labs, the failure of its UST stablecoin was the result of an attack by large short sellers, which the firm claimed included FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried’s trading firm Alameda Research....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Seeks Data from FTX Wallets for SEC Lawsuit Defense&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Terra</category><category>FTX</category><category>SEC</category><category>Do Kwon</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-seeks-data-from-ftx-wallets-for-sec-lawsuit-defense.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120263/319240/law.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="254349"/></item><item><title>DOGE 2.0 Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Whales Are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – 100x Potential?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm</link><description>So far 2023 has been a year characterised by explosive meme coin runs, perhaps none more successful than the incredible Pepecoin ($PEPE) pump which ignited Spring's ecstatic meme season. &lt;br /&gt;
But the alt coin pumps haven't stopped there, as the eye-watering gains have continued to flow from straight to DEX tokens in months since. &lt;br /&gt;
And in the latest sensation, Dogecoin ($DOGE) spin-off token $DOGE2.0 has surged in price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: DOGE 2.0 Rockets Up 30,000% But Crypto Whales Are Accumulating This Other Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – 100x Potential?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/doge-20-rockets-up-30000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-100x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120262/319239/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1105918"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as XRP Drops 5% in 24 Hours – Is the Rally Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm</link><description>The XRP price has fallen by 5% in the past 24 hours, with the coin's slide to $0.776800 coming as the cryptocurrency market drops by 1%. &lt;br /&gt;
Coming a week after Ripple's positive decision in its case with the SEC, XRP's move today means it's up by only 0.5% in the last week, although it remains 67% up in the last 14 days and up by 125% since the beginning of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as XRP Drops 5% in 24 Hours – Is the Rally Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-drops-5-24-hours-is-rally-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120255/319228/xrp-price-prediction-as-x.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="974959"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction; BTC and ETH Slip Nearly 5%: Potential Weekend Bounce?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-slip-nearly-5-potential-weekend-bounce.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and Ethereum, two of the most prominent cryptocurrencies, have experienced a significant slip, with BTC currently trading at $29,780 and ETH at $1,889.  &lt;br /&gt;
As investors closely monitor these developments, delving into the technical outlook becomes essential to determine the potential price action in the coming days. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-slip-nearly-5-potential-weekend-bounce.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction; BTC and ETH Slip Nearly 5%: Potential Weekend Bounce?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-btc-eth-slip-nearly-5-potential-weekend-bounce.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120242/319199/21.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526351"/></item><item><title>XRP2.0 Price Pumps 31,000%, New Pepe Token BEBE Climbs 36,000% But South Park Coin Burn Kenny is Up $250,000 in Under an Hour and Evil Pepe is Next 1,000x Token</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-price-pumps-31000-new-pepe-token-bebe-climbs-36000-but-south-park-coin-burn-kenny-up-250000-less-than-an-hour.htm</link><description>New cryptocurrency $XRP2.0 is up 31,000%, and the latest take on the Pepe craze – $BEBE coin – climbs 36,000%, but Burn Kenny Coin and Evil Pepe Coin could provide the next best opportunities for stellar returns. &lt;br /&gt;
Launched yesterday, XRP2.0 leverages the positive price pressure XRP has garnered in the light of the recent ruling by the judge in the SEC's case that XRP when sold to retail investors, is not a security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-price-pumps-31000-new-pepe-token-bebe-climbs-36000-but-south-park-coin-burn-kenny-up-250000-less-than-an-hour.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP2.0 Price Pumps 31,000%, New Pepe Token BEBE Climbs 36,000% But South Park Coin Burn Kenny is Up $250,000 in Under an Hour and Evil Pepe is Next 1,000x Token&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp20-price-pumps-31000-new-pepe-token-bebe-climbs-36000-but-south-park-coin-burn-kenny-up-250000-less-than-an-hour.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120239/319192/xrp2-0-coin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="397057"/></item><item><title>Over 70% of Spanish Crypto Traders Declared Losses in FY2022 – Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/over-70-of-spanish-crypto-traders-declared-losses-fy2022-report.htm</link><description>Over 70% of Spanish crypto traders declared losses in the financial year 2022, a new report has found. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Europa Press, the claims were made by TaxCripto, an accountancy firm that specializes in preparing tax returns for crypto holders. &lt;br /&gt;
The declared losses were significantly higher in the case of those investing in crypto derivatives and futures: 91% of this group posted losses....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/over-70-of-spanish-crypto-traders-declared-losses-fy2022-report.htm"&gt;Read More: Over 70% of Spanish Crypto Traders Declared Losses in FY2022 – Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Spain</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/over-70-of-spanish-crypto-traders-declared-losses-fy2022-report.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120217/319100/spain-2007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="567933"/></item><item><title>1.3m+ Crypto Phishing Attacks Foiled in Russia So Far This Year – Kaspersky</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/13m-crypto-phishing-attacks-foiled-russia-so-far-year-kaspersky.htm</link><description>More than 1.3 million crypto-related phishing attacks were stopped in Russia in the first six months of this year, a new report has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Plus World, the cybersecurity provider Kaspersky Lab claimed its solutions thwarted the attacks, which the firm thinks are a direct response to a rise in crypto’s popularity in Russia....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/13m-crypto-phishing-attacks-foiled-russia-so-far-year-kaspersky.htm"&gt;Read More: 1.3m+ Crypto Phishing Attacks Foiled in Russia So Far This Year – Kaspersky&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Phishing</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/13m-crypto-phishing-attacks-foiled-russia-so-far-year-kaspersky.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120126/318879/adobestock-493281945.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="610226"/></item><item><title>Chinese Telecoms Firms Growing Increasingly Keen on Digital Yuan</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-telecoms-firms-growing-increasingly-keen-digital-yuan.htm</link><description>Chinese telecom operators are growing increasingly keen on digital yuan adoption, a report has claimed, as the CBDC finds new adoption strongholds. &lt;br /&gt;
Per EY (via Sohu), the central People’s Bank of China (PBoC) is keen to bring the nation’s biggest operators (the likes of China Telecom and China Unicom) deeper into the pilot. &lt;br /&gt;
The PBoC reportedly believes telecoms firms can help boost adoption....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-telecoms-firms-growing-increasingly-keen-digital-yuan.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Telecoms Firms Growing Increasingly Keen on Digital Yuan&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-telecoms-firms-growing-increasingly-keen-digital-yuan.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120222/319119/china-2007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="988635"/></item><item><title>Rocket Pool Price Prediction as RPL Breaks Below This Key Support Level – Here’s Why RPL Could Continue Struggling</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rocket-pool-price-prediction-as-rpl-breaks-below-key-support-level-heres-why-rpl-could-continue-struggling.htm</link><description>RPL, the utility token that powers the decentralized Rocket Pool Ethereum liquid staking protocol, has been taking a beating on Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;
The token, which is used for staking alongside ETH within the Rocket Pool protocol to incentivize honest node operation, as well as for protocol governance, was last down around 7.5% in the last 24 hours, as per CoinGecko. &lt;br /&gt;
That makes RPL the worst performing cryptocurrency in the top 100 by market cap over that time period....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rocket-pool-price-prediction-as-rpl-breaks-below-key-support-level-heres-why-rpl-could-continue-struggling.htm"&gt;Read More: Rocket Pool Price Prediction as RPL Breaks Below This Key Support Level – Here’s Why RPL Could Continue Struggling&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Rocket Pool</category><category>RPL</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Burn Kenny Coin</category><category>$KENNY</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rocket-pool-price-prediction-as-rpl-breaks-below-key-support-level-heres-why-rpl-could-continue-struggling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120232/319174/rpl.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="564922"/></item><item><title>Will the Bitcoin Price Hit $50k in 2023? BTC20 Presale Pumps Past $450,000</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/will-bitcoin-price-hit-50k-2023-btc20-presale-pumps-past-450000.htm</link><description>The anticipation surrounding the Bitcoin price in 2023 continues to grow as BTC20, a highly-anticipated presale event, experiences a surge, surpassing the remarkable milestone of $450,000.  &lt;br /&gt;
Speculations are mounting among investors and enthusiasts alike, wondering if this upward momentum will propel Bitcoin to reach the coveted $50,000 mark....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/will-bitcoin-price-hit-50k-2023-btc20-presale-pumps-past-450000.htm"&gt;Read More: Will the Bitcoin Price Hit $50k in 2023? BTC20 Presale Pumps Past $450,000&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/will-bitcoin-price-hit-50k-2023-btc20-presale-pumps-past-450000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120223/319162/20.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="484064"/></item><item><title>RFK Jr. Pledges Support for Bitcoin-Backed Dollar and Tax Exemption for BTC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-pledges-support-for-bitcoin-backed-dollar-and-tax-exemption-for-btc.htm</link><description>US Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has said he is in favor of a tax exemption on Bitcoin (BTC), while also unveiling a plan to partly back the US dollar with “real, finite assets” like Bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
“Like Singapore, Germany, Switzerland, Puerto Rico and Portugal, a Kennedy administration will exempt the conversion of Bitcoin to the US dollar from capital gains taxes,” Kennedy said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-pledges-support-for-bitcoin-backed-dollar-and-tax-exemption-for-btc.htm"&gt;Read More: RFK Jr. Pledges Support for Bitcoin-Backed Dollar and Tax Exemption for BTC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Robert F. Kennedy</category><category>Kennedy</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-pledges-support-for-bitcoin-backed-dollar-and-tax-exemption-for-btc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120204/319039/robert-f-kennedy.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="231741"/></item><item><title>New AI Utility Coin yPredict Breaks $3 Million Fundraising Milestone - Here's How it Works</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-ai-utility-coin-ypredict-breaks-3-million-fundraising-milestone-heres-how-it-works.htm</link><description>yPredict, a prominent web3 AI platform, has reached an impressive milestone in its crypto token presale. To date, it has successfully generated over $3 million in the seventh phase of its presale of the native $YPRED token.  &lt;br /&gt;
The AI coin marks the latest advancement in the intersection of artificial intelligence and digital currency. &lt;br /&gt;
Visit yPredict Here...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-ai-utility-coin-ypredict-breaks-3-million-fundraising-milestone-heres-how-it-works.htm"&gt;Read More: New AI Utility Coin yPredict Breaks $3 Million Fundraising Milestone - Here's How it Works&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI coin</category><category>Ai Utility Coin</category><category>Ai Crypto Presale</category><category>Ai Crypto</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><category>Crypto Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-ai-utility-coin-ypredict-breaks-3-million-fundraising-milestone-heres-how-it-works.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120161/318978/f1yk0sdwyaeqwj1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="859715"/></item><item><title>Crypto Firm RISC Zero Secures $40M Funding Round Led by Blockchain Capital</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-risc-zero-secures-40m-funding-round-led-by-blockchain-capital.htm</link><description>RISC Zero, a startup that builds zero-knowledge (ZK) proof software, has raised $40 million in a Series A funding round led by the major crypto-focused investor Blockchain Capital. &lt;br /&gt;
In its announcement of the closing of the funding round, RISC Zero said the fresh capital will be used to bring its Bonsai computing platform to the market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-risc-zero-secures-40m-funding-round-led-by-blockchain-capital.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Firm RISC Zero Secures $40M Funding Round Led by Blockchain Capital&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-firm-risc-zero-secures-40m-funding-round-led-by-blockchain-capital.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120195/319024/investment.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="140803"/></item><item><title>Arkham Top Trending Cryptocurrency on DEXTools - Does Launchpad XYZ Platform Have More Upside Potential Than ARKM</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-top-trending-cryptocurrency-on-dextools-does-launchpad-xyz-platform-have-more-upside-potential-than-arkm.htm</link><description>When Arkham Intelligence's $ARKM made its debut on July 18 with a price of $0.75, it received a warm welcome and immediately achieved a high of $1.05004. &lt;br /&gt;
Although the coin had a promising start, it has since struggled to maintain its bullish momentum as it currently trades at $0.5962, down by 7.5% so far today. &lt;br /&gt;
The hourly Exponential Moving Averages (EMA) paint a somewhat gloomy picture for $ARKM....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-top-trending-cryptocurrency-on-dextools-does-launchpad-xyz-platform-have-more-upside-potential-than-arkm.htm"&gt;Read More: Arkham Top Trending Cryptocurrency on DEXTools - Does Launchpad XYZ Platform Have More Upside Potential Than ARKM&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Arkham Intelligence</category><category>Arkm Price</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Web3 Crypto</category><category>Web3</category><category>Web3 Projects</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Crypto Presale 2023</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>LPX price</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Play To Earn Crypto</category><category>Play To Earn</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/arkham-top-trending-cryptocurrency-on-dextools-does-launchpad-xyz-platform-have-more-upside-potential-than-arkm.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120212/319079/render-an-unsettling-imag.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="3172577"/></item><item><title>21 Arrested in China for $54M USDT Money Laundering Investigation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/21-arrested-china-for-54m-usdt-money-laundering-investigation.htm</link><description>Authorities in China's Shanxi Province have arrested 21 individuals allegedly involved in a major Tether (USDT) money laundering scheme.  &lt;br /&gt;
The scheme, estimated to have generated over $54 million, utilized the US dollar-backed stablecoin USDT to launder money, the country’s national broadcasting service CCTV reported on Tuesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/21-arrested-china-for-54m-usdt-money-laundering-investigation.htm"&gt;Read More: 21 Arrested in China for $54M USDT Money Laundering Investigation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>USDT</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/21-arrested-china-for-54m-usdt-money-laundering-investigation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120216/319085/china-media-library-origi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="185904"/></item></channel></rss>
