<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 04:09:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Hong Kong Government asks Banks to Embrace Crypto Clients]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/hong-kong-government-asks-banks-to-embrace-crypto-clients</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-4.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-4.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-4.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:00:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/hong-kong-government-asks-banks-to-embrace-crypto-clients</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Hong Kong government has proactively advocated for major banks to embrace clients engaged in digital currencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Traditional financial institutions such as HSBC and Standard Chartered are finding themselves confronted with mounting pressure to adapt to Hong Kong&rsquo;s desire to become a hub for crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to an article on CoinTelegraph, both UK- based banks as well as the Bank of China, were pressured by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) in a May meeting to start accepting crypto companies such as exchanges, as clients.</p>
Embracing the Crypto Community
<p>The Hong Kong government's initiative to encourage major banks to accommodate cryptocurrency clients marks a noteworthy milestone in the convergence of traditional finance and digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recognising the demand for crypto-related services, the government appears to be looking to allow crypto-related companies to do their thing and continue to come up with innovations that can disrupt the existing financial system.&nbsp;</p>
Navigating Regulatory Challenges
<p>While the acceptance of cryptocurrencies presents exciting possibilities, it also poses regulatory challenges for traditional banks. Striking a delicate balance between fostering innovation and ensuring compliance with existing regulations is a key consideration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Hong Kong government's push for banks to embrace crypto clients is accompanied by a call for enhanced risk management and regulatory frameworks. This comprehensive approach aims to establish a secure and transparent environment that protects both banks and their cryptocurrency clients from potential risks.</p>
Embracing the Potential of Blockchain
<p>The Hong Kong government's push for banks to embrace crypto clients says much for China&rsquo;s rethinking of the crypto digital asset economy. It also signifies a deeper recognition of the transformative capabilities that blockchain technology holds.&nbsp;</p>
Catalysing Global Innovation
<p>Hong Kong's proactive approach to embracing crypto and its encouragement of banks to accommodate crypto clients sends a resounding message to the global financial industry. By positioning itself as a progressive and innovative hub, Hong Kong aims to attract international businesses and investors who see the potential in crypto and blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Hong Kong government has proactively advocated for major banks to embrace clients engaged in digital currencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Traditional financial institutions such as HSBC and Standard Chartered are finding themselves confronted with mounting pressure to adapt to Hong Kong&rsquo;s desire to become a hub for crypto.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to an article on CoinTelegraph, both UK- based banks as well as the Bank of China, were pressured by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) in a May meeting to start accepting crypto companies such as exchanges, as clients.</p>
Embracing the Crypto Community
<p>The Hong Kong government's initiative to encourage major banks to accommodate cryptocurrency clients marks a noteworthy milestone in the convergence of traditional finance and digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recognising the demand for crypto-related services, the government appears to be looking to allow crypto-related companies to do their thing and continue to come up with innovations that can disrupt the existing financial system.&nbsp;</p>
Navigating Regulatory Challenges
<p>While the acceptance of cryptocurrencies presents exciting possibilities, it also poses regulatory challenges for traditional banks. Striking a delicate balance between fostering innovation and ensuring compliance with existing regulations is a key consideration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Hong Kong government's push for banks to embrace crypto clients is accompanied by a call for enhanced risk management and regulatory frameworks. This comprehensive approach aims to establish a secure and transparent environment that protects both banks and their cryptocurrency clients from potential risks.</p>
Embracing the Potential of Blockchain
<p>The Hong Kong government's push for banks to embrace crypto clients says much for China&rsquo;s rethinking of the crypto digital asset economy. It also signifies a deeper recognition of the transformative capabilities that blockchain technology holds.&nbsp;</p>
Catalysing Global Innovation
<p>Hong Kong's proactive approach to embracing crypto and its encouragement of banks to accommodate crypto clients sends a resounding message to the global financial industry. By positioning itself as a progressive and innovative hub, Hong Kong aims to attract international businesses and investors who see the potential in crypto and blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LEVEL : The Omnichain Liquidity Marketplace Launches on Arbitrum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/level-the-omnichain-liquidity-marketplace-launches-on-arbitrum</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-15-184732.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-15-184732.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-15-184732.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/level-the-omnichain-liquidity-marketplace-launches-on-arbitrum</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Since inception, LEVEL has designed a protocol to serve as a functional alternative to centralized counterparty risk. After half a year of product testing, it&rsquo;s finally time to expand, and the LEVEL DAO has determined that Arbitrum will be the next ecosystem where Level will be deployed on.</p>
<p>LEVEL&rsquo;s Success Story</p>
<p>LEVEL has experienced phenomenal growth. In just the first month, LEVEL witnessed a notable $320 million in volume traded, generating over $400k in fees and bringing in more than 1000 community members.</p>
<p>As a testament to the product-market fit they found, it took just 55 days for the ecosystem to hit $1 billion in trading volume, leading to collecting $8.3 million in fees during that time &ndash; going from strength to strength with over $20 billion traded in the first half of 2023 alone!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Impressively, the most significant daily trading volume was $339 million on April 14, 2023, accounting for around a third of the total volume across Perp DEXs (Delphi Digital).</p>
<p>A Quick Look On-Chain</p>
<p>Total Volume: $17.4 billion, of which leverage trading volume accounts for $14.5 billion</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Total Collected Fees: &gt;$22 million&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interestingly, these collected fees are distributed to:</p>
<ul>
<li>LLPs (supply-side revenue) = 45%</li>
<li>LVL Stakers (protocol revenue) = 10%</li>
<li>LGO Stakers (protocol revenue) = 10%</li>
<li>DAO Treasury (protocol revenue - redeemable against LGO) = 30%</li>
<li>Reserved for Protocol Development (5%)</li>
</ul>
Assets Under Management (AUM): $30 million
<p></p>
<p>During this time, LEVEL has established itself as the leading perpetual decentralized exchange (DEX) on BNB Chain, rivaling even the likes of GMX &ndash; a significant achievement considering the difference in total value locked (TVL) and market cap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Setting itself apart from competitors, LEVEL wrote its own codebase from scratch and pioneered the tranche system in DeFi. By leveraging its innovative dual tokenomics model (LVL and LGO), which perfectly fits a perpetual DEX platform, LEVEL has created a strong protocol growth flywheel, reflected in the simultaneous growth of platform volume and Treasury assets. This has resulted in achieving close to $10M in treasury liquid assets.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Last but not least, LEVEL is taking DeFi on-chain governance to the next level, with more than 19 DAO Proposals submitted.</p>
<p>Truly decentralized governance, driving rapid iteration in product and incentive models for a fast-paced marketplace.</p>
Why Arbitrum?&nbsp;
<p>Even at a glance, Arbitrum looked like the most immediate choice for LEVEL, and this sentiment resonated with the majority of their community.</p>
<p>All new possible chains were evaluated according to their:</p>
<ul>
<li>Liquidity</li>
<li>User profile</li>
<li>Daily active users</li>
<li>Daily number of TXs</li>
</ul>
<p>Arbitrum crushes all of these criteria, securing itself as the fourth chain by TVL, thanks to its deep liquidity and a DeFi-native user base. An equally important factor included the sustained growth of unique addresses in the network, even after the ARB Airdrop.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Many critics speculated that activity on Arbitrum would sink after the airdrop. Nonetheless, the daily transactions on the network are steadily increasing, averaging around 1m per day &mdash; close to ATH if one does not take into account the days of the airdrop.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Considering these factors, it is understandable why the DAO voted for Arbitrum, securing 53% of the total votes across 4 options.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrum is the home of DeFi, and a place full of open collaboration. The composable nature of DeFi on Arbitrum offers endless possibilities for new products and partnerships with other protocols. Some remarkable examples include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Yield Aggregators</li>
<li>Money Markets</li>
<li>Other Derivatives (e.g., hedging, structured products)</li>
</ul>
<p>Furthermore, this Layer 2 protocol is a fantastic fit for LEVEL as it houses a native niche of perp DEX traders who can benefit from the ecosystem&rsquo;s incentivized program for traders, shrewdly configured to drive protocol and treasury growth.</p>
<p>While the expansion to Arbitrum is the project&rsquo;s main priority, LEVEL is not stopping there. LEVEL will continue to expand in its goal to become a key piece of the wider omnichain infrastructure.</p>
Practical Developments
<p>Cross-chain infrastructure is being built to cement the marketplace as an omnichain protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As part of these developments, LEVEL is migrating the LVL and LGO tokens to the &lsquo;Omnichain Fungible Token&rsquo; (OFT) standard.</p>
<p>The ultimate goal is to enable the cross-chain aggregation of fees distributed to its stakeholders so that LEVEL users can earn yield anywhere in the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The DAO treasury will also be united across the entire ecosystem, meaning LGO redemptions against the treasury will occur on all chains.</p>
<p>Following the recently approved proposal, LEVEL is utilizing LayerZero&rsquo;s technology to bridge 5M LVL to Arbitrum, to bootstrap liquidity and trader activity through auctions and other incentive programs.</p>
They have also begun migrating:
<ul>
<li>LVL/USDT Liquidity &mdash; to make LVL tokens more accessible to users on Arbitrum, LEVEL migrating the entire LVL/USDT pool (currently ~ $713,214) to Trader Joe Arbitrum ensures that new users trading for the first time will have the liquidity to access LVL tokens.&nbsp;</li>
<li>LEVEL Trading Pool Liquidity &mdash; enabling access to all trading features, migrating 3,555,192 Senior LLP (currently ~ $4,061,500) from the BNB Chain to seed trading liquidity on Arbitrum (50% of the protocol-owned Senior LLP supply).</li>
</ul>
<p>Future Plans</p>
<p>When it comes to future footprints, a key priority for Level Protocol is for the DAO to steer Level&rsquo;s journey towards exceptional growth.</p>
<p>LEVEL also remains committed to delivering an exceptional user experience, ensuring that their customers receive premium service and can trade using a top-notch UX.</p>
<p>Further solidifying its position in the DeFi space, LEVEL is actively seeking, discussing, and moving forward with several partnerships with additional Tier-1 projects, enabling them to expand its reach and utility across the industry.</p>
<p>LEVEL's success to date was achievable through the tremendous support from its community of users. Expanding to a cross-chain liquidity marketplace, the marketplace will release a first-in-kind utility-based NFT in just 60 days. All of these unique items will be exclusively for LEVEL's community of users, with allocation retroactively determined based on interactions with the protocol on both Arbitrum and BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Three categories will correspond to the three main facets of LEVEL:</p>
<ul>
<li>Stock Broker's Vest, Earned through proving yourself as a trader. The life blood of any financial hub, a Trader needs to look the part at his desk.</li>
<li>Auctioneer's Hammer &ndash;A key group of mechanisms at LEVEL, Auctions serve to widen the reach of the ecosystem as a whole. Embody the power of the Auctioneer with their Hammer.</li>
<li>Tattered Farmer's Hat &ndash; LEVEL wouldn&rsquo;t we be anywhere without liquidity. LPs take on risk enabling the entire marketplace to function. It ain&rsquo;t much, but it&rsquo;s honest work.</li>
</ul>
<p>LEVEL's vision is to become a leading omnichain trading platform, and their recent expansion to Arbitrum marks the first step towards realizing this goal.</p>
<p>Expanding their services into other DeFi sectors is another avenue they are exploring. The goal is to become a multi-chain liquidity aggregator where fragmented liquidity across different ecosystems can be unified in a single pool, allowing users to trade, swap, and borrow seamlessly.</p>
<p>LEVEL is excited to embark on this omnichain journey, transforming the way people engage with DeFi and revolutionizing their trading experience.</p>
Step into the LEVEL Ecosystem!
<ul>
<li>Trade a range of blue chip assets on LEVEL now!</li>
<li>Buy LVL and begin participating in our ecosystem</li>
</ul>

<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since inception, LEVEL has designed a protocol to serve as a functional alternative to centralized counterparty risk. After half a year of product testing, it&rsquo;s finally time to expand, and the LEVEL DAO has determined that Arbitrum will be the next ecosystem where Level will be deployed on.</p>
<p>LEVEL&rsquo;s Success Story</p>
<p>LEVEL has experienced phenomenal growth. In just the first month, LEVEL witnessed a notable $320 million in volume traded, generating over $400k in fees and bringing in more than 1000 community members.</p>
<p>As a testament to the product-market fit they found, it took just 55 days for the ecosystem to hit $1 billion in trading volume, leading to collecting $8.3 million in fees during that time &ndash; going from strength to strength with over $20 billion traded in the first half of 2023 alone!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Impressively, the most significant daily trading volume was $339 million on April 14, 2023, accounting for around a third of the total volume across Perp DEXs (Delphi Digital).</p>
<p>A Quick Look On-Chain</p>
<p>Total Volume: $17.4 billion, of which leverage trading volume accounts for $14.5 billion</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Total Collected Fees: &gt;$22 million&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Interestingly, these collected fees are distributed to:</p>
<ul>
<li>LLPs (supply-side revenue) = 45%</li>
<li>LVL Stakers (protocol revenue) = 10%</li>
<li>LGO Stakers (protocol revenue) = 10%</li>
<li>DAO Treasury (protocol revenue - redeemable against LGO) = 30%</li>
<li>Reserved for Protocol Development (5%)</li>
</ul>
Assets Under Management (AUM): $30 million
<p></p>
<p>During this time, LEVEL has established itself as the leading perpetual decentralized exchange (DEX) on BNB Chain, rivaling even the likes of GMX &ndash; a significant achievement considering the difference in total value locked (TVL) and market cap.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Setting itself apart from competitors, LEVEL wrote its own codebase from scratch and pioneered the tranche system in DeFi. By leveraging its innovative dual tokenomics model (LVL and LGO), which perfectly fits a perpetual DEX platform, LEVEL has created a strong protocol growth flywheel, reflected in the simultaneous growth of platform volume and Treasury assets. This has resulted in achieving close to $10M in treasury liquid assets.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Last but not least, LEVEL is taking DeFi on-chain governance to the next level, with more than 19 DAO Proposals submitted.</p>
<p>Truly decentralized governance, driving rapid iteration in product and incentive models for a fast-paced marketplace.</p>
Why Arbitrum?&nbsp;
<p>Even at a glance, Arbitrum looked like the most immediate choice for LEVEL, and this sentiment resonated with the majority of their community.</p>
<p>All new possible chains were evaluated according to their:</p>
<ul>
<li>Liquidity</li>
<li>User profile</li>
<li>Daily active users</li>
<li>Daily number of TXs</li>
</ul>
<p>Arbitrum crushes all of these criteria, securing itself as the fourth chain by TVL, thanks to its deep liquidity and a DeFi-native user base. An equally important factor included the sustained growth of unique addresses in the network, even after the ARB Airdrop.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Many critics speculated that activity on Arbitrum would sink after the airdrop. Nonetheless, the daily transactions on the network are steadily increasing, averaging around 1m per day &mdash; close to ATH if one does not take into account the days of the airdrop.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Considering these factors, it is understandable why the DAO voted for Arbitrum, securing 53% of the total votes across 4 options.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Arbitrum is the home of DeFi, and a place full of open collaboration. The composable nature of DeFi on Arbitrum offers endless possibilities for new products and partnerships with other protocols. Some remarkable examples include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Yield Aggregators</li>
<li>Money Markets</li>
<li>Other Derivatives (e.g., hedging, structured products)</li>
</ul>
<p>Furthermore, this Layer 2 protocol is a fantastic fit for LEVEL as it houses a native niche of perp DEX traders who can benefit from the ecosystem&rsquo;s incentivized program for traders, shrewdly configured to drive protocol and treasury growth.</p>
<p>While the expansion to Arbitrum is the project&rsquo;s main priority, LEVEL is not stopping there. LEVEL will continue to expand in its goal to become a key piece of the wider omnichain infrastructure.</p>
Practical Developments
<p>Cross-chain infrastructure is being built to cement the marketplace as an omnichain protocol.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As part of these developments, LEVEL is migrating the LVL and LGO tokens to the &lsquo;Omnichain Fungible Token&rsquo; (OFT) standard.</p>
<p>The ultimate goal is to enable the cross-chain aggregation of fees distributed to its stakeholders so that LEVEL users can earn yield anywhere in the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The DAO treasury will also be united across the entire ecosystem, meaning LGO redemptions against the treasury will occur on all chains.</p>
<p>Following the recently approved proposal, LEVEL is utilizing LayerZero&rsquo;s technology to bridge 5M LVL to Arbitrum, to bootstrap liquidity and trader activity through auctions and other incentive programs.</p>
They have also begun migrating:
<ul>
<li>LVL/USDT Liquidity &mdash; to make LVL tokens more accessible to users on Arbitrum, LEVEL migrating the entire LVL/USDT pool (currently ~ $713,214) to Trader Joe Arbitrum ensures that new users trading for the first time will have the liquidity to access LVL tokens.&nbsp;</li>
<li>LEVEL Trading Pool Liquidity &mdash; enabling access to all trading features, migrating 3,555,192 Senior LLP (currently ~ $4,061,500) from the BNB Chain to seed trading liquidity on Arbitrum (50% of the protocol-owned Senior LLP supply).</li>
</ul>
<p>Future Plans</p>
<p>When it comes to future footprints, a key priority for Level Protocol is for the DAO to steer Level&rsquo;s journey towards exceptional growth.</p>
<p>LEVEL also remains committed to delivering an exceptional user experience, ensuring that their customers receive premium service and can trade using a top-notch UX.</p>
<p>Further solidifying its position in the DeFi space, LEVEL is actively seeking, discussing, and moving forward with several partnerships with additional Tier-1 projects, enabling them to expand its reach and utility across the industry.</p>
<p>LEVEL's success to date was achievable through the tremendous support from its community of users. Expanding to a cross-chain liquidity marketplace, the marketplace will release a first-in-kind utility-based NFT in just 60 days. All of these unique items will be exclusively for LEVEL's community of users, with allocation retroactively determined based on interactions with the protocol on both Arbitrum and BNB Chain.</p>
<p>Three categories will correspond to the three main facets of LEVEL:</p>
<ul>
<li>Stock Broker's Vest, Earned through proving yourself as a trader. The life blood of any financial hub, a Trader needs to look the part at his desk.</li>
<li>Auctioneer's Hammer &ndash;A key group of mechanisms at LEVEL, Auctions serve to widen the reach of the ecosystem as a whole. Embody the power of the Auctioneer with their Hammer.</li>
<li>Tattered Farmer's Hat &ndash; LEVEL wouldn&rsquo;t we be anywhere without liquidity. LPs take on risk enabling the entire marketplace to function. It ain&rsquo;t much, but it&rsquo;s honest work.</li>
</ul>
<p>LEVEL's vision is to become a leading omnichain trading platform, and their recent expansion to Arbitrum marks the first step towards realizing this goal.</p>
<p>Expanding their services into other DeFi sectors is another avenue they are exploring. The goal is to become a multi-chain liquidity aggregator where fragmented liquidity across different ecosystems can be unified in a single pool, allowing users to trade, swap, and borrow seamlessly.</p>
<p>LEVEL is excited to embark on this omnichain journey, transforming the way people engage with DeFi and revolutionizing their trading experience.</p>
Step into the LEVEL Ecosystem!
<ul>
<li>Trade a range of blue chip assets on LEVEL now!</li>
<li>Buy LVL and begin participating in our ecosystem</li>
</ul>

<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Blk DNM Introduces Intelligence Into Clothing With Blockchain, In First Use Of ‘Connected Fashion’]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/BLK_DNM_2_1686839415HGxgLXSTI0.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/BLK_DNM_2_1686839415HGxgLXSTI0.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/BLK_DNM_2_1686839415HGxgLXSTI0.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:00:43 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/blk-dnm-introduces-intelligence-into-clothing-with-blockchain-in-first-use-of-connected-fashion</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swedish-American fashion brand BLK DNM today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &lsquo;twinned&rsquo; via technology) with the launch of BLK DNM Society and integration of blockchain-powered hardware and software into its products.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society, built on tech designed by blockchain innovator and BLK DNM owner ChromaWay, will grant each garment a unique and recordable identity in both the physical and virtual worlds, while also rewarding ethical behaviour and granting brand influence to owners.</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Blockchain-powered &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; microchips will give each item a unique identity and record of its history</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Chips form the hardware element of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem and rewards responsible behavior and ownership</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Tech will first appear in BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW 2023 collection</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">The Hardware: Digital Garment IDs</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Future BLK DNM clothing will be fitted with a &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; - an undetectable chip that gives each physical item a unique and recordable identity. Some of the first features of the digital garment IDs will include:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Authentication of the garment as genuine, eliminating fakes and counterfeiting</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Rewarding responsible behaviours of treasuring and caring for clothing long-term, such as refurbs and second-hand purchases</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Recording each individual garment's unique history - owners, events and places worn, repairs and alterations - enabling the item to accrue emotional and monetary value over time</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Acting as a digital ticket for entry to events</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Access to and voting rights within BLK DNM Society</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The digital garment IDs are the first hardware elements of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem. The first example of connected fashion, BLK DNM Society is a community of BLK DNM owners, connected virtually by their physical items, who are rewarded for responsible behaviours and are granted voting rights on key brand decisions based on item ownership - thereby beginning the first ever process of decentralising a fashion brand&rsquo;s stewardship.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Each digital garment ID will create a &lsquo;digital reflection&rsquo; of the physical garment: a twin in the virtual world where the physical item&rsquo;s history and place within BLK DNM Society is recorded. The digital reflection can also be worn in the metaverses, catering especially to younger generations whose identities in virtual worlds are equally as important as in the physical.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">FW 2023</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Digital garment IDs will be revealed at BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW event in Paris on June 21st. For this first collection, the chips will be embedded in only leather items, with subsequent collections introducing more items to BLK DNM Society through embedded blockchain-enabled hardware.</p>Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay, comments: &ldquo;This is totally futuristic. Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. It&rsquo;s very exciting for us, after much hard work, to see our technology elevating one of fashion&rsquo;s iconic brands into something completely unique. This has the potential to transform people&rsquo;s relationships with the clothes they wear and the brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. And each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.&rdquo;<p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, and Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay</p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, comments: &ldquo;BLK DNM&rsquo;s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations - the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.&rdquo;<p>About BLK DNM</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM is a Swedish-American fashion brand that specialises in timeless tailoring, leather, and denim of extraordinary quality. Following its 2023 relaunch as an entry-luxury fashion house under the stewardship of new Creative Director Jessy Heuvelink, BLK DNM&rsquo;s focus on both enduring craftsmanship and aesthetic timelessness encourages customers to love and treasure each item for decades and across generations.</p><p>About ChromaWay</p><p>ChromaWay is an industry leader in blockchain technology and specializes in creating and deploying cutting-edge, scalable blockchain solutions for both businesses and governments. The company, which was established in 2014 and has its headquarters in Stockholm, Sweden, has been at the forefront of driving the widespread adoption of blockchain technology. Its flagship product, relational blockchain Chromia, enables developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) with a relational database model that offers unprecedented scalability and flexibility.</p>ContactFati HakimFati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM bridging the Physical and Virtual Worlds of Fashion through Blockchain Innovation</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Swedish-American fashion brand BLK DNM today unveils the first-ever example of connected fashion (garments that exist both physically and virtually, each aspect &lsquo;twinned&rsquo; via technology) with the launch of BLK DNM Society and integration of blockchain-powered hardware and software into its products.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society, built on tech designed by blockchain innovator and BLK DNM owner ChromaWay, will grant each garment a unique and recordable identity in both the physical and virtual worlds, while also rewarding ethical behaviour and granting brand influence to owners.</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Blockchain-powered &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; microchips will give each item a unique identity and record of its history</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Chips form the hardware element of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem and rewards responsible behavior and ownership</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Tech will first appear in BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW 2023 collection</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">The Hardware: Digital Garment IDs</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Future BLK DNM clothing will be fitted with a &lsquo;digital garment ID&rsquo; - an undetectable chip that gives each physical item a unique and recordable identity. Some of the first features of the digital garment IDs will include:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Authentication of the garment as genuine, eliminating fakes and counterfeiting</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Rewarding responsible behaviours of treasuring and caring for clothing long-term, such as refurbs and second-hand purchases</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Recording each individual garment's unique history - owners, events and places worn, repairs and alterations - enabling the item to accrue emotional and monetary value over time</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Acting as a digital ticket for entry to events</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Access to and voting rights within BLK DNM Society</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM Society</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The digital garment IDs are the first hardware elements of BLK DNM Society, which launches in tandem. The first example of connected fashion, BLK DNM Society is a community of BLK DNM owners, connected virtually by their physical items, who are rewarded for responsible behaviours and are granted voting rights on key brand decisions based on item ownership - thereby beginning the first ever process of decentralising a fashion brand&rsquo;s stewardship.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Each digital garment ID will create a &lsquo;digital reflection&rsquo; of the physical garment: a twin in the virtual world where the physical item&rsquo;s history and place within BLK DNM Society is recorded. The digital reflection can also be worn in the metaverses, catering especially to younger generations whose identities in virtual worlds are equally as important as in the physical.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">FW 2023</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Digital garment IDs will be revealed at BLK DNM&rsquo;s FW event in Paris on June 21st. For this first collection, the chips will be embedded in only leather items, with subsequent collections introducing more items to BLK DNM Society through embedded blockchain-enabled hardware.</p>Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay, comments: &ldquo;This is totally futuristic. Nothing like this has been attempted in fashion before. It&rsquo;s very exciting for us, after much hard work, to see our technology elevating one of fashion&rsquo;s iconic brands into something completely unique. This has the potential to transform people&rsquo;s relationships with the clothes they wear and the brands they buy. No longer does the relationship with the customer end at the checkout. And each beautiful garment now becomes its own living, evolving piece of history.&rdquo;<p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, and Henrik Hjelte, CEO and Co-founder of ChromaWay</p>Toni Collin, CEO of BLK DNM, comments: &ldquo;BLK DNM&rsquo;s philosophy is one of community, and our clothing is designed, through both its craftsmanship and timeless aesthetic, to be treasured and passed down through generations - the antithesis of irresponsible fast fashion. Now, with the introduction of BLK DNM Society and the first embedded hardware in our garments, we take those two pillars to a revolutionary new level. By embedding intelligence in every item, we hope we can inspire our industry to join us in using connected fashion to do better.&rdquo;<p>About BLK DNM</p><p class="ql-align-justify">BLK DNM is a Swedish-American fashion brand that specialises in timeless tailoring, leather, and denim of extraordinary quality. Following its 2023 relaunch as an entry-luxury fashion house under the stewardship of new Creative Director Jessy Heuvelink, BLK DNM&rsquo;s focus on both enduring craftsmanship and aesthetic timelessness encourages customers to love and treasure each item for decades and across generations.</p><p>About ChromaWay</p><p>ChromaWay is an industry leader in blockchain technology and specializes in creating and deploying cutting-edge, scalable blockchain solutions for both businesses and governments. The company, which was established in 2014 and has its headquarters in Stockholm, Sweden, has been at the forefront of driving the widespread adoption of blockchain technology. Its flagship product, relational blockchain Chromia, enables developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) with a relational database model that offers unprecedented scalability and flexibility.</p>ContactFati HakimFati.Hakim@ChromaWay.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Launches Bitcoin Cloud Mining Services]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binance-launches-bitcoin-cloud-mining-services</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-china-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binance-launches-bitcoin-cloud-mining-services</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, has announced the launch of its new subscription-based Bitcoin cloud mining services. The move comes as a surprise amidst the ongoing regulatory challenges Binance is facing in the United States.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's Bitcoin Cloud Mining Service</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance announced the launch on Twitter, claiming that users who are interested in Bitcoin mining but lack the necessary hardware can subscribe to these new cloud mining services and purchase hashrates. Currently, Binance offers 1 Terahash per second (Th/s) at a rate of $10.7280. An increase in the purchased hashrate corresponds to an increased probability of higher Bitcoin earnings through mining.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The BTC mining subscription service will remain active for six months. During this 180-day period, for every TH/s purchased, users could potentially earn 0.0004338 BTC. However, as of now, this product is only available on Binance's global website, indicating that users from the United States cannot access it.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Current Regulatory Trouble</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's decision to launch these cloud mining services comes at a particularly challenging time for the cryptocurrency exchange. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against Binance, alleging violations of securities laws. Alongside this, the SEC has filed for a temporary restraining order to freeze the assets of Binance.US.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC has accused Binance of operating as an unregistered securities exchange, and CZ has been accused of failing to prevent U.S. customers from using the platform and providing misleading information about its market surveillance measures. According to the lawsuit, Binance and CZ were involved in an "elaborate scheme" to evade U.S. federal securities laws, which included creating separate U.S. entities and diverting billions of dollars in customer funds to Merit Peak Limited, a separate company under Zhao's control.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a press release, SEC Chair Gary Gensler stated that the charges against CZ and Binance detail an "extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law." He further accused the defendants of misrepresenting their risk controls, manipulating trading volumes, and actively concealing crucial information, such as the platform's operations, manipulative trading by its affiliated market maker, and the custody of investor funds and crypto assets.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance Building Forward</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the wake of these accusations, CZ has remained unfazed, choosing to dismiss the charges with a tweet stating "4", a reference used within the Binance community to encourage users to ignore fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD). He assured the community that Binance's systems remain stable and that deposits and withdrawals are operating as normal.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In preparation for the legal proceedings, Binance.US has already added former SEC enforcement co-director George Canellos to its legal team. Meanwhile, last week, Binance.US revealed that it has suspended USD deposits on its platform, a significant step in its transition to becoming an exclusively crypto-based exchange. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance is not the only crypto exchange facing regulatory pressures. Coinbase, another prominent cryptocurrency exchange, also found itself on the receiving end of a lawsuit from the SEC for alleged failure to register as a broker, national securities exchange, or clearing agency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance's cloud mining services launch amid such regulatory challenges is a notable step, reflecting the exchange's commitment to advancing its services, even as it grapples with legal and regulatory issues. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange by daily trading volume, has announced the launch of its new subscription-based Bitcoin cloud mining services. The move comes as a surprise amidst the ongoing regulatory challenges Binance is facing in the United States.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's Bitcoin Cloud Mining Service</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance announced the launch on Twitter, claiming that users who are interested in Bitcoin mining but lack the necessary hardware can subscribe to these new cloud mining services and purchase hashrates. Currently, Binance offers 1 Terahash per second (Th/s) at a rate of $10.7280. An increase in the purchased hashrate corresponds to an increased probability of higher Bitcoin earnings through mining.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The BTC mining subscription service will remain active for six months. During this 180-day period, for every TH/s purchased, users could potentially earn 0.0004338 BTC. However, as of now, this product is only available on Binance's global website, indicating that users from the United States cannot access it.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Current Regulatory Trouble</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance's decision to launch these cloud mining services comes at a particularly challenging time for the cryptocurrency exchange. In the United States, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken legal action against Binance, alleging violations of securities laws. Alongside this, the SEC has filed for a temporary restraining order to freeze the assets of Binance.US.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC has accused Binance of operating as an unregistered securities exchange, and CZ has been accused of failing to prevent U.S. customers from using the platform and providing misleading information about its market surveillance measures. According to the lawsuit, Binance and CZ were involved in an "elaborate scheme" to evade U.S. federal securities laws, which included creating separate U.S. entities and diverting billions of dollars in customer funds to Merit Peak Limited, a separate company under Zhao's control.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a press release, SEC Chair Gary Gensler stated that the charges against CZ and Binance detail an "extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law." He further accused the defendants of misrepresenting their risk controls, manipulating trading volumes, and actively concealing crucial information, such as the platform's operations, manipulative trading by its affiliated market maker, and the custody of investor funds and crypto assets.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance Building Forward</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In the wake of these accusations, CZ has remained unfazed, choosing to dismiss the charges with a tweet stating "4", a reference used within the Binance community to encourage users to ignore fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD). He assured the community that Binance's systems remain stable and that deposits and withdrawals are operating as normal.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In preparation for the legal proceedings, Binance.US has already added former SEC enforcement co-director George Canellos to its legal team. Meanwhile, last week, Binance.US revealed that it has suspended USD deposits on its platform, a significant step in its transition to becoming an exclusively crypto-based exchange. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance is not the only crypto exchange facing regulatory pressures. Coinbase, another prominent cryptocurrency exchange, also found itself on the receiving end of a lawsuit from the SEC for alleged failure to register as a broker, national securities exchange, or clearing agency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance's cloud mining services launch amid such regulatory challenges is a notable step, reflecting the exchange's commitment to advancing its services, even as it grapples with legal and regulatory issues. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Major Bearish 24568 Risk - 16 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-major-bearish-24568-risk-16-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-major-bearish-24568-risk-16-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Major Bearish 24568 Risk:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its ongoing slide lower early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 25000 figure for the first time since March 2023, descending to the 24750 level.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 25142.29 area, a previous upside price objective related to legacy buying pressure that emerged around the 3858 area.&nbsp; Large Stops are in place below similar levels around the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26068.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25620.51.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Major Bearish 24568 Risk:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its ongoing slide lower early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 25000 figure for the first time since March 2023, descending to the 24750 level.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 25142.29 area, a previous upside price objective related to legacy buying pressure that emerged around the 3858 area.&nbsp; Large Stops are in place below similar levels around the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26068.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25620.51.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Voyager Could Reopen Customer Withdrawals As Early As 20th June]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/voyager-could-reopen-customer-withdrawals-as-early-as-20-th-june</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/voyager-could-reopen-customer-withdrawals-as-early-as-20-th-june</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Voyager customers were in for some good news a year after their assets were frozen, with the platform stating that they could withdraw a significant chunk of their crypto assets.</p>
<p>The protocol&rsquo;s customers will soon be able to check how much of their assets could be withdrawn, nearly a year after Voyager filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
A Sigh Of Relief&nbsp;
<p>Paul Hage, Voyager&rsquo;s bankruptcy administrator, stated in a court filing on the 14th of June that the Voyager app would be updated by the 15th of June. Once the app has been updated, customers will be able to check the amount they can withdraw. Hage also estimated that the withdrawal period could start between the 20th of June to the 5th of July. The bankruptcy plan was approved in court on the 17th of May and will see Voyager customers initially receive around 35% of their claims through withdrawals from the Voyager app. They can also withdraw in cash after a period of 30 days.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Voyager Court adjourned for the day. Fee examiner&rsquo;s findings approved by the judge app will come back online on or around the 15th of June Estimated window for withdrawals opening the 20th of June to the 5th of July 30 days to withdraw once the window opens all creditors will receive 35.72 initial distribution.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Once submitted, withdrawals will take between 3 and 7 days to process. Additionally, some liquidations may take longer depending on the liquidity available at the time of liquidation. Supported cryptocurrencies will be distributed in kind, while unsupported cryptocurrencies will be distributed in USDC. Hage stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The initial distributions of cryptocurrency will be made to creditors between three to seven calendar days after a withdrawal request is submitted on the Voyager platform.&rdquo;</p>

Three Arrows Capital Still Owes $650 Million&nbsp;
<p>Hage also added that the bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) still owed Voyager around $650 million. The first tranche of withdrawals will allow customers to withdraw just over 35% of their funds. Once completed, the focus of the proceedings will shift to recovering additional assets that can be distributed to creditors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, an additional $445 million in customer funds could be made available to creditors. However, this depends on a final resolution of Alameda Research&rsquo;s preference claim against Voyager, which will happen sometime in September 2023.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Meditation between @investvoyager and @FTX_Official is anticipated to not start until Fall 2023. Anything less than 100% return would be a devastating result for Voyager creditors!&rdquo;</p>

Voyager&rsquo;s Bankruptcy Struggles&nbsp;
<p>Voyager had filed for bankruptcy on the 5th of July, 2022. The company then filed two prior bankruptcy plan proposals, both of which fell through. The first proposal was to the United States arm of FTX. However, this deal fell through after FTX itself filed for bankruptcy. The second was a $1 billion deal with Binance.US. This deal fell through after Binance.US backed out of the deal, citing an uncertain and hostel regulatory climate prevailing in the US. At the time, Binance.US stated in a Twitter communication,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance.US has made the difficult decision to exercise its right to terminate the asset purchase agreement with Voyager. While our hope throughout this process was to help Voyager&rsquo;s customers access their crypto in kind, the hostile and uncertain regulatory climate in the United States has introduced an unpredictable operating environment impacting the entire American business community.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Voyager had expressed disappointment with the outcome, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, we received a letter from Binance.US terminating the asset purchase agreement. While this development is disappointing, our Chapter 11 plan allows for direct distribution of cash and crypto to customers (a &ldquo;toggle option&rdquo;) via the Voyager platform.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Voyager customers were in for some good news a year after their assets were frozen, with the platform stating that they could withdraw a significant chunk of their crypto assets.</p>
<p>The protocol&rsquo;s customers will soon be able to check how much of their assets could be withdrawn, nearly a year after Voyager filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
A Sigh Of Relief&nbsp;
<p>Paul Hage, Voyager&rsquo;s bankruptcy administrator, stated in a court filing on the 14th of June that the Voyager app would be updated by the 15th of June. Once the app has been updated, customers will be able to check the amount they can withdraw. Hage also estimated that the withdrawal period could start between the 20th of June to the 5th of July. The bankruptcy plan was approved in court on the 17th of May and will see Voyager customers initially receive around 35% of their claims through withdrawals from the Voyager app. They can also withdraw in cash after a period of 30 days.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Voyager Court adjourned for the day. Fee examiner&rsquo;s findings approved by the judge app will come back online on or around the 15th of June Estimated window for withdrawals opening the 20th of June to the 5th of July 30 days to withdraw once the window opens all creditors will receive 35.72 initial distribution.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Once submitted, withdrawals will take between 3 and 7 days to process. Additionally, some liquidations may take longer depending on the liquidity available at the time of liquidation. Supported cryptocurrencies will be distributed in kind, while unsupported cryptocurrencies will be distributed in USDC. Hage stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The initial distributions of cryptocurrency will be made to creditors between three to seven calendar days after a withdrawal request is submitted on the Voyager platform.&rdquo;</p>

Three Arrows Capital Still Owes $650 Million&nbsp;
<p>Hage also added that the bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) still owed Voyager around $650 million. The first tranche of withdrawals will allow customers to withdraw just over 35% of their funds. Once completed, the focus of the proceedings will shift to recovering additional assets that can be distributed to creditors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, an additional $445 million in customer funds could be made available to creditors. However, this depends on a final resolution of Alameda Research&rsquo;s preference claim against Voyager, which will happen sometime in September 2023.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Meditation between @investvoyager and @FTX_Official is anticipated to not start until Fall 2023. Anything less than 100% return would be a devastating result for Voyager creditors!&rdquo;</p>

Voyager&rsquo;s Bankruptcy Struggles&nbsp;
<p>Voyager had filed for bankruptcy on the 5th of July, 2022. The company then filed two prior bankruptcy plan proposals, both of which fell through. The first proposal was to the United States arm of FTX. However, this deal fell through after FTX itself filed for bankruptcy. The second was a $1 billion deal with Binance.US. This deal fell through after Binance.US backed out of the deal, citing an uncertain and hostel regulatory climate prevailing in the US. At the time, Binance.US stated in a Twitter communication,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance.US has made the difficult decision to exercise its right to terminate the asset purchase agreement with Voyager. While our hope throughout this process was to help Voyager&rsquo;s customers access their crypto in kind, the hostile and uncertain regulatory climate in the United States has introduced an unpredictable operating environment impacting the entire American business community.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Voyager had expressed disappointment with the outcome, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Today, we received a letter from Binance.US terminating the asset purchase agreement. While this development is disappointing, our Chapter 11 plan allows for direct distribution of cash and crypto to customers (a &ldquo;toggle option&rdquo;) via the Voyager platform.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Parcl Expands Its Real Estate Frontier: Launches Additional Tradable Indexes for Major US Cities Including Austin, Chicago, Seattle, and Boston]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/parcl-expands-its-real-estate-frontier-launches-additional-tradable-indexes-for-major-us-cities-including-austin-chicago-seattle-and-boston</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Header_Graphic_pressrelease_1686757155NLi1j8jRWq.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Header_Graphic_pressrelease_1686757155NLi1j8jRWq.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Header_Graphic_pressrelease_1686757155NLi1j8jRWq.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:50:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/parcl-expands-its-real-estate-frontier-launches-additional-tradable-indexes-for-major-us-cities-including-austin-chicago-seattle-and-boston</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Parcl&rsquo;s market expansion increases access to investors seeking exposure to real estate prices via Real World Asset (RWA) Indexes</p><p>Parcl, the leading blockchain-powered real estate trading platform, announced today the launch of Austin, TX, to its ever-growing list of tradable city indexes. In addition to Austin, Parcl recently launched indexes for Boston, Atlanta, Philadelphia, Chicago, Seattle, Denver, Portland, and Washington, D.C., more than doubling its market pool for investors.</p><p>Parcl makes investing in an entire city's residential real estate market possible, unlocking access to high-demand markets like New York, Los Angeles, and Miami. Parcl merges real estate and DeFi to amplify access and portfolio diversification opportunities for traders around the world.</p><p>Adding Austin, one of the fastest-growing housing markets in the U.S., solidifies Parcl's commitment to providing a broad spectrum of high-potential markets to traders. This increases investor access to 16 dynamic tradable markets and builds upon Parcl&rsquo;s mission of increasing access to real estate investing on a global scale.&nbsp;</p><p>&ldquo;Real estate is the largest asset class in the world &ndash; the largest investment many people will make in their lives. It&rsquo;s also the market that has the lowest liquidity and the highest barriers to entry,&rdquo; said Trevor Bacon, Parcl CEO and co-founder. "Integrating these high-demand markets signifies Parcl&rsquo;s dedication to continuous growth, providing traders access to diverse and burgeoning markets."</p><p>Built on Solana &ndash; a blockchain designed for decentralized, scalable applications &ndash; Parcl facilitates real-world real estate trades in real time. The platform's rapid growth since its launch in February demonstrates significant market need for innovating around real estate investing.</p><p>"Austin&rsquo;s integration provides traders with another dynamic real estate market to diversify their portfolio," Bacon said. "This move is consistent with Parcl&rsquo;s goal to enhance market access and user engagement, as evidenced by all-time highs in user activity, open interest, and trading volume on the decentralized trading application."</p><p>The addition of more North American cities is on the near term horizon, with global cities following shortly thereafter. Parcl&rsquo;s illustrated market growth builds upon its aspiration of becoming the simplest platform for global real estate trading, and illustrates its commitment to the core mission of making real estate investing accessible to everyone, everywhere.</p><p>Parcl is designed which features appeal to the modern investors, offering high liquidity, low transaction fees, and no minimum investment requirements. Traders can now trade real estate indexes as effortlessly as Bitcoin, Ethereum, or other crypto assets.</p><p>About Parcl</p><p>Parcl is a DeFi real estate trading platform revolutionizing the way individuals globally engage with real estate investment. Combining the strengths of blockchain technology with traditional real estate, Parcl offers a simple, efficient, and accessible real estate trading experience.&nbsp;</p><p>For more information, visit www.parcl.co.</p>ContactCMOWill LeathermanParclwill@parcl.co]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Parcl&rsquo;s market expansion increases access to investors seeking exposure to real estate prices via Real World Asset (RWA) Indexes</p><p>Parcl, the leading blockchain-powered real estate trading platform, announced today the launch of Austin, TX, to its ever-growing list of tradable city indexes. In addition to Austin, Parcl recently launched indexes for Boston, Atlanta, Philadelphia, Chicago, Seattle, Denver, Portland, and Washington, D.C., more than doubling its market pool for investors.</p><p>Parcl makes investing in an entire city's residential real estate market possible, unlocking access to high-demand markets like New York, Los Angeles, and Miami. Parcl merges real estate and DeFi to amplify access and portfolio diversification opportunities for traders around the world.</p><p>Adding Austin, one of the fastest-growing housing markets in the U.S., solidifies Parcl's commitment to providing a broad spectrum of high-potential markets to traders. This increases investor access to 16 dynamic tradable markets and builds upon Parcl&rsquo;s mission of increasing access to real estate investing on a global scale.&nbsp;</p><p>&ldquo;Real estate is the largest asset class in the world &ndash; the largest investment many people will make in their lives. It&rsquo;s also the market that has the lowest liquidity and the highest barriers to entry,&rdquo; said Trevor Bacon, Parcl CEO and co-founder. "Integrating these high-demand markets signifies Parcl&rsquo;s dedication to continuous growth, providing traders access to diverse and burgeoning markets."</p><p>Built on Solana &ndash; a blockchain designed for decentralized, scalable applications &ndash; Parcl facilitates real-world real estate trades in real time. The platform's rapid growth since its launch in February demonstrates significant market need for innovating around real estate investing.</p><p>"Austin&rsquo;s integration provides traders with another dynamic real estate market to diversify their portfolio," Bacon said. "This move is consistent with Parcl&rsquo;s goal to enhance market access and user engagement, as evidenced by all-time highs in user activity, open interest, and trading volume on the decentralized trading application."</p><p>The addition of more North American cities is on the near term horizon, with global cities following shortly thereafter. Parcl&rsquo;s illustrated market growth builds upon its aspiration of becoming the simplest platform for global real estate trading, and illustrates its commitment to the core mission of making real estate investing accessible to everyone, everywhere.</p><p>Parcl is designed which features appeal to the modern investors, offering high liquidity, low transaction fees, and no minimum investment requirements. Traders can now trade real estate indexes as effortlessly as Bitcoin, Ethereum, or other crypto assets.</p><p>About Parcl</p><p>Parcl is a DeFi real estate trading platform revolutionizing the way individuals globally engage with real estate investment. Combining the strengths of blockchain technology with traditional real estate, Parcl offers a simple, efficient, and accessible real estate trading experience.&nbsp;</p><p>For more information, visit www.parcl.co.</p>ContactCMOWill LeathermanParclwill@parcl.co]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Launches Web3 Loyalty Program With Flipkart]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-launches-web3-loyalty-program-with-flipkart</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-flipkart-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-flipkart-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-flipkart-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-launches-web3-loyalty-program-with-flipkart</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Flipkart, a leading figure in Indian digital commerce, has formed a key alliance with Polygon, one of the industry's key crypto firms building infrastructure around an ecosystem of Web3 products.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The result of this collaboration is the conception of the Blockchain-eCommerce Centre of Excellence, a hub for research and development. The center's primary focus is to navigate the nascent landscape of Web3 and the metaverse, mapping out the next phase of digital commerce.The Indian digital commerce heavyweight is partnering with Polygon Labs and Hang, a leading next-generation loyalty platform, to introduce a specialized loyalty program named FireDrops 2.0. Aiming to reinvent the wheel of customer engagement and loyalty, FireDrops 2.0, powered by Hang's loyalty platform, will use underlying non-fungible token (NFT) technology to incentivize millions of Flipkart users through gamification. The application of Web3 and NFTs to brand loyalty programs is expected to revolutionize brand marketing, storytelling, and customer engagement.</p>
Polygon x Flipkart: Loyalty NFTs via FireDrops
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The use of NFTs in the program allows for easy ownership and redemption of rewards, thereby generating new revenue streams for brands and enabling customers to participate actively in the loyalty ecosystem. The FireDrops program also envisions a dynamic marketplace where users can buy and sell rewwards, bringing flexibility to loyalty programs and enhancing brand engagement.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">FireDrops 2.0 aims to offer an immersive experience to users, enticing them with surprises, games, and rewards related to their favorite brands. These interactions could allow users to earn benefits like membership passes, lifetime discounts, and more, fosterling deeper connections between users and brands.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnerships underscores Flipkart's commitment to fostering innovation and expanding its tech offerings to transform the experience of online shopping for millions worldwide. As Flipkart steps into the Web3 arena, it is set to reshape the contours of commerce, consumption, and value generation in the digital world.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Jeyandran Venugopal, the Chief Product and Technology Officer at Flipkart, expressed his enthusiasm about the partnership:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Innovation is one of the main pillars for Flipkart and we have consistently worked towards technology solutions to scale new frontiers and introduce new products and services,&rdquo; Venugopal shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Previously, Flipkart made its maiden voyage into the metaverse through eDAO, a project nurtured by Polygon. The venture, known as "Flipverse," has played a crucial role in redefining the dynamic between brands and consumers. It promotes novel, interactive experiences via non-fungible tokens (NFTs). Additionally, Flipkart's FireDrops&mdash;an accessible platform for NFTs&mdash;cultivates a space where creators, brands, and consumers can delve into the multi-dimensional value of NFTs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Prominent brands such as Adidas, Adobe, Robinhood, and Stripe have already chosen Polygon as their entry point to Web3. Flipkart's decision to align with this flourishing ecosystem underscores its forward-thinking approach to harnessing the potential of blockchain. Polygon's recent developments, notably the zkEVM scaling solution, will be pivotal in accommodating the global influx of users in Web3's next chapter.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sandeep Nailwal, Polygon's co-founder, praised the partnership when it first began sometime in late 2022, sharing that Polygon:</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"serves as the bridge to Web3 for the world's biggest corporations. Our goal is to shepherd the next billion users into Web3, so our partnership with Flipkart to create the Blockchain-eCommerce Centre of Excellence is an exciting prospect."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nailwal adds that Polygon recognizes the sheer amount of blockchain talent to be found in the country, and that such a resource forms opportunities for the partnership to stimulate R&amp;D, and further "solidify India's stature as a Web3 titan."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon's Current Regulatory Predicament</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon recently launched its Version 2.0 amid the troubles that it's currently facing with SEC's claim of $MATIC being a security. The crypto firm is currently expanding its efforts at privacy, and has since launched a zero-knowledge identity infrastructure program for Web3 with PolygonID.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to the SEC's allegations, trading platform Robinhood took the step of delisting Solana, Cardano, and Polygon, effective from June 27. However, it reassured its users that the removal would be restricted to SOL, ADA, and MATIC, and no other coins on the platform would be affected.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS) were the other tokens implicated, as regulatory scrutiny also hit major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Flipkart, a leading figure in Indian digital commerce, has formed a key alliance with Polygon, one of the industry's key crypto firms building infrastructure around an ecosystem of Web3 products.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The result of this collaboration is the conception of the Blockchain-eCommerce Centre of Excellence, a hub for research and development. The center's primary focus is to navigate the nascent landscape of Web3 and the metaverse, mapping out the next phase of digital commerce.The Indian digital commerce heavyweight is partnering with Polygon Labs and Hang, a leading next-generation loyalty platform, to introduce a specialized loyalty program named FireDrops 2.0. Aiming to reinvent the wheel of customer engagement and loyalty, FireDrops 2.0, powered by Hang's loyalty platform, will use underlying non-fungible token (NFT) technology to incentivize millions of Flipkart users through gamification. The application of Web3 and NFTs to brand loyalty programs is expected to revolutionize brand marketing, storytelling, and customer engagement.</p>
Polygon x Flipkart: Loyalty NFTs via FireDrops
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The use of NFTs in the program allows for easy ownership and redemption of rewards, thereby generating new revenue streams for brands and enabling customers to participate actively in the loyalty ecosystem. The FireDrops program also envisions a dynamic marketplace where users can buy and sell rewwards, bringing flexibility to loyalty programs and enhancing brand engagement.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">FireDrops 2.0 aims to offer an immersive experience to users, enticing them with surprises, games, and rewards related to their favorite brands. These interactions could allow users to earn benefits like membership passes, lifetime discounts, and more, fosterling deeper connections between users and brands.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnerships underscores Flipkart's commitment to fostering innovation and expanding its tech offerings to transform the experience of online shopping for millions worldwide. As Flipkart steps into the Web3 arena, it is set to reshape the contours of commerce, consumption, and value generation in the digital world.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Jeyandran Venugopal, the Chief Product and Technology Officer at Flipkart, expressed his enthusiasm about the partnership:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Innovation is one of the main pillars for Flipkart and we have consistently worked towards technology solutions to scale new frontiers and introduce new products and services,&rdquo; Venugopal shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Previously, Flipkart made its maiden voyage into the metaverse through eDAO, a project nurtured by Polygon. The venture, known as "Flipverse," has played a crucial role in redefining the dynamic between brands and consumers. It promotes novel, interactive experiences via non-fungible tokens (NFTs). Additionally, Flipkart's FireDrops&mdash;an accessible platform for NFTs&mdash;cultivates a space where creators, brands, and consumers can delve into the multi-dimensional value of NFTs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Prominent brands such as Adidas, Adobe, Robinhood, and Stripe have already chosen Polygon as their entry point to Web3. Flipkart's decision to align with this flourishing ecosystem underscores its forward-thinking approach to harnessing the potential of blockchain. Polygon's recent developments, notably the zkEVM scaling solution, will be pivotal in accommodating the global influx of users in Web3's next chapter.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sandeep Nailwal, Polygon's co-founder, praised the partnership when it first began sometime in late 2022, sharing that Polygon:</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"serves as the bridge to Web3 for the world's biggest corporations. Our goal is to shepherd the next billion users into Web3, so our partnership with Flipkart to create the Blockchain-eCommerce Centre of Excellence is an exciting prospect."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nailwal adds that Polygon recognizes the sheer amount of blockchain talent to be found in the country, and that such a resource forms opportunities for the partnership to stimulate R&amp;D, and further "solidify India's stature as a Web3 titan."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon's Current Regulatory Predicament</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon recently launched its Version 2.0 amid the troubles that it's currently facing with SEC's claim of $MATIC being a security. The crypto firm is currently expanding its efforts at privacy, and has since launched a zero-knowledge identity infrastructure program for Web3 with PolygonID.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to the SEC's allegations, trading platform Robinhood took the step of delisting Solana, Cardano, and Polygon, effective from June 27. However, it reassured its users that the removal would be restricted to SOL, ADA, and MATIC, and no other coins on the platform would be affected.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), Cosmos Hub (ATOM), Filecoin (FIL), Decentraland (MANA), Algorand (ALGO), The Sandbox (SAND), Coti (COTI), and Axie Infinity (AXS) were the other tokens implicated, as regulatory scrutiny also hit major exchanges such as Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Delio Suspends Withdrawals Amid Haru's Financial Irregularities]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/delio-suspends-withdrawals-amid-harus-financial-irregularities</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/delio-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/delio-suspends-withdrawals-amid-harus-financial-irregularities</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Korean-based cryptocurrency lending service, Delio, has temporarily suspended customer withdrawals as a consequence of financial irregularities involving crypto investment firm, Haru.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an update on its website, Delio revealed that it had paused withdrawals due to its funds being inaccessible in Haru. This follows the recent suspension of deposits and withdrawals by Haru itself on June 13, in response to undisclosed complications with one of its service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Haru, a platform that offers users up to a 12% return on its Earn Plus product, has yet to provide a detailed explanation regarding the ongoing issues with its service provider. This lack of communication and the subsequent suspension of services have led to speculation and concerns among its users, resulting in a significant surge in withdrawal requests.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Delio's CEO, Jung Sang-ho, confirmed this increase in a recent interview with Money Today. He noted that the difficulties Delio was facing resulted from a rapid increase in withdrawal requests following Haru's suspension. Jung Sang-ho also acknowledged a transactional relationship between Delio and Haru, but he refrained from commenting on the specific details, including the total amount involved.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Delio's platform offers a range of cryptocurrency lending and borrowing services, with advertised returns of up to 10.7%. According to the claims made on its website, Delio has processed transactions involving significant volumes of cryptocurrencies including 41,700 Bitcoin (valued at approximately $1 billion), 118,000 ether (valued at around $205 million), and $6.2 million worth of various altcoins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The temporary suspension of Delio's withdrawal services has come as a shock to many in the Korean cryptocurrency market, highlighting once again the inherent risks and volatility associated with the industry. The move follows a string of similar incidents involving cryptocurrency platforms globally, underscoring the need for increased transparency, regulation, and security within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These incidents have drawn increased scrutiny from regulatory authorities and have prompted calls for more robust oversight and legislation to protect investors. In many parts of the world, regulators are already working on new frameworks to address these issues and ensure greater security for investors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The events involving Delio and Haru also demonstrate the interconnected nature of many cryptocurrency platforms and services. Problems at one platform can quickly spread to others, causing a ripple effect throughout the industry. This connectivity means that issues at a single platform can lead to broader instability and lack of trust in the market as a whole.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As Delio works to resolve the current situation, users of the platform are left in a state of uncertainty, with their funds temporarily locked. The incident underscores the importance of due diligence and careful risk assessment when choosing a cryptocurrency platform, especially those offering higher-than-average returns.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Korean-based cryptocurrency lending service, Delio, has temporarily suspended customer withdrawals as a consequence of financial irregularities involving crypto investment firm, Haru.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an update on its website, Delio revealed that it had paused withdrawals due to its funds being inaccessible in Haru. This follows the recent suspension of deposits and withdrawals by Haru itself on June 13, in response to undisclosed complications with one of its service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Haru, a platform that offers users up to a 12% return on its Earn Plus product, has yet to provide a detailed explanation regarding the ongoing issues with its service provider. This lack of communication and the subsequent suspension of services have led to speculation and concerns among its users, resulting in a significant surge in withdrawal requests.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Delio's CEO, Jung Sang-ho, confirmed this increase in a recent interview with Money Today. He noted that the difficulties Delio was facing resulted from a rapid increase in withdrawal requests following Haru's suspension. Jung Sang-ho also acknowledged a transactional relationship between Delio and Haru, but he refrained from commenting on the specific details, including the total amount involved.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Delio's platform offers a range of cryptocurrency lending and borrowing services, with advertised returns of up to 10.7%. According to the claims made on its website, Delio has processed transactions involving significant volumes of cryptocurrencies including 41,700 Bitcoin (valued at approximately $1 billion), 118,000 ether (valued at around $205 million), and $6.2 million worth of various altcoins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The temporary suspension of Delio's withdrawal services has come as a shock to many in the Korean cryptocurrency market, highlighting once again the inherent risks and volatility associated with the industry. The move follows a string of similar incidents involving cryptocurrency platforms globally, underscoring the need for increased transparency, regulation, and security within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These incidents have drawn increased scrutiny from regulatory authorities and have prompted calls for more robust oversight and legislation to protect investors. In many parts of the world, regulators are already working on new frameworks to address these issues and ensure greater security for investors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The events involving Delio and Haru also demonstrate the interconnected nature of many cryptocurrency platforms and services. Problems at one platform can quickly spread to others, causing a ripple effect throughout the industry. This connectivity means that issues at a single platform can lead to broader instability and lack of trust in the market as a whole.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As Delio works to resolve the current situation, users of the platform are left in a state of uncertainty, with their funds temporarily locked. The incident underscores the importance of due diligence and careful risk assessment when choosing a cryptocurrency platform, especially those offering higher-than-average returns.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Astar Network Unveils the ‘Astar 2.0 Vision’ to Deliver Web3 Mass Adoption to Billions of Users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-20-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Astar_Hero_Image_1686817431hR6nS5BYuW.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Astar_Hero_Image_1686817431hR6nS5BYuW.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Astar_Hero_Image_1686817431hR6nS5BYuW.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 12:00:44 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/astar-network-unveils-the-astar-20-vision-to-deliver-web3-mass-adoption-to-billions-of-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>Setting the long-term direction, the Astar 2.0 Vision aligns tokenomics, organizational structure, and key pillars of technology to drive Web3 mass adoption<p>Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, is delighted to introduce the &lsquo;Astar 2.0 Vision&rsquo; as it aims to drive mass adoption of Web3 to billions of users. With developers&rsquo; growing interest in base layers that offer scalability, security, and interoperability, Astar Network aims to position itself as the go-to Layer-1 blockchain by providing them with all the tools, resources, and support to help them build unstoppable dApps.</p><p>The &lsquo;Astar 2.0 Vision&rsquo; sets the long-term direction for the rapidly-growing Astar ecosystem. It aligns the network&rsquo;s tokenomics, organizational structure, and pillars of technology to achieve its mission of enabling Web3 innovations that empower billions of people worldwide.</p>1. Tokenomics<p>Astar Network will revamp its current tokenomics to align with the long-term vision and the DAO will make Astar sustainable for the future.</p><p>The Astar Foundation is building this with the community in forums to gain their valuable insights. A redesigned ASTR token better serves the needs of network participants, from users and builders to enterprise partners. It&rsquo;s essential to ensuring a sustainable future of growth and success.</p>2. Astar Link&nbsp;<p>Connects the fragmented layers of the blockchain industry. With customizable options and tailor-made SDKs, developers can create limitless solutions. Astar Link unlocks diverse use cases from gaming to enterprise that is only possible by linking different ecosystems to each other.</p>3. Organizations supporting Astar Network<ol><li>Startale Labs - The enterprise arm that enables users and businesses to embrace blockchain in Japan. With a focus on Web3 infrastructure, Startale aims to build innovative products to enable the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies.</li><li>Astar Foundation - It is currently the main contributor and maintainer of the Astar Network Source Code. The Foundation deploys resources to expand Astar Network through partnerships, community activities, hiring developers, funding projects, and other initiatives.</li><li>Formation of Astar DAO - Astar is actively working with the community to realize this goal in Community Forums. The DAO will help create an unstoppable network by embracing decentralization and handing governance to the community. Anyone can use Astar Network anywhere to improve their communities</li></ol>4. Creating unstoppable dApps&nbsp;<p>Improving the developer experience to help them build unstoppable dApps with two pillars of technology:</p><ol><li>Cross-chain applications - Astar supports both EVM and WebAssembly (WASM) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM). With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of the blockchain. Astar 2.0 brings more options and is scalable.</li><li>DApp staking - Improved tokenomics will return more value to builders and stakers via dApp staking. Astar&rsquo;s innovative Build2Earn program empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the dApps they build. It allows network users to stake their tokens to support their favorite projects.</li></ol>5. Supernova: Paving the path forward<p>Actions speak louder than words. Watch out for our coming updates in the middle of Q3 which will see Astar deliver on its web3 promises. Like a supernova exploding and impacting the universe, Astar aims to have the same impact in the web3 universe. Bringing Astar technology and vision to the masses.</p><p>Interested developers and users can explore the 2.0 Vision here. Moreover, Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations have shown strong belief in Astar&rsquo;s vision and its ability to execute. Astar will share more details later in June and July.</p><p>The Astar Foundation and Startale Labs have been working with many of the world&rsquo;s leading global players to achieve the 2.0 Vision. Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations including Toyota Motor Corporation and Sony Network Communications have teamed up with Astar Network to explore the opportunities in Web3.</p><p>Sota Watanabe, the Founder of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We will push the network to unlock Web3 for billions. Each part of Astar 2.0 is being shaped and improved, starting with token economics and developer tooling to ensure the sustainable long-term growth of the network.&rdquo;</p><p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 in Japan, having been voted the most popular blockchain in the country by the Japanese Blockchain Association. It is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. Astar is also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p><p></p>About Startale Labs <p>Startale Labs is a web3 tech company developing multichain applications and infrastructure. We also conduct R&amp;D and incubation activities based on the experience and connections developed in coordination with Astar Network. In addition, a subsidiary, Startale Labs Japan, was established on January 31st 2023 to provide web3 business development and strategic consulting services to corporate enterprises and governments, leveraging the strengths of Japan&rsquo;s most widely-recognized public blockchain.</p><p></p>About Astar Network<p>Astar is Japan&rsquo;s most popular smart contract platform, supporting both EVM and WebAssembly (Wasm) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine. Astar Network is friendly to all kinds of developers, and tools and languages they already know. Backed by the shared security of Polkadot, Astar shines brilliantly on its own within a vibrant and healthy ecosystem, and is a leading star in the blockchain industry overall, driving international corporate adoption, and consumer interest in web3 technologies.</p><p>For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit | YouTube&nbsp;</p>ContactSota Watanabeinfo@startale.org]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>Setting the long-term direction, the Astar 2.0 Vision aligns tokenomics, organizational structure, and key pillars of technology to drive Web3 mass adoption<p>Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, is delighted to introduce the &lsquo;Astar 2.0 Vision&rsquo; as it aims to drive mass adoption of Web3 to billions of users. With developers&rsquo; growing interest in base layers that offer scalability, security, and interoperability, Astar Network aims to position itself as the go-to Layer-1 blockchain by providing them with all the tools, resources, and support to help them build unstoppable dApps.</p><p>The &lsquo;Astar 2.0 Vision&rsquo; sets the long-term direction for the rapidly-growing Astar ecosystem. It aligns the network&rsquo;s tokenomics, organizational structure, and pillars of technology to achieve its mission of enabling Web3 innovations that empower billions of people worldwide.</p>1. Tokenomics<p>Astar Network will revamp its current tokenomics to align with the long-term vision and the DAO will make Astar sustainable for the future.</p><p>The Astar Foundation is building this with the community in forums to gain their valuable insights. A redesigned ASTR token better serves the needs of network participants, from users and builders to enterprise partners. It&rsquo;s essential to ensuring a sustainable future of growth and success.</p>2. Astar Link&nbsp;<p>Connects the fragmented layers of the blockchain industry. With customizable options and tailor-made SDKs, developers can create limitless solutions. Astar Link unlocks diverse use cases from gaming to enterprise that is only possible by linking different ecosystems to each other.</p>3. Organizations supporting Astar Network<ol><li>Startale Labs - The enterprise arm that enables users and businesses to embrace blockchain in Japan. With a focus on Web3 infrastructure, Startale aims to build innovative products to enable the widespread adoption of Web3 technologies.</li><li>Astar Foundation - It is currently the main contributor and maintainer of the Astar Network Source Code. The Foundation deploys resources to expand Astar Network through partnerships, community activities, hiring developers, funding projects, and other initiatives.</li><li>Formation of Astar DAO - Astar is actively working with the community to realize this goal in Community Forums. The DAO will help create an unstoppable network by embracing decentralization and handing governance to the community. Anyone can use Astar Network anywhere to improve their communities</li></ol>4. Creating unstoppable dApps&nbsp;<p>Improving the developer experience to help them build unstoppable dApps with two pillars of technology:</p><ol><li>Cross-chain applications - Astar supports both EVM and WebAssembly (WASM) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine (XVM). With XVM, smart contracts will work seamlessly regardless of the blockchain. Astar 2.0 brings more options and is scalable.</li><li>DApp staking - Improved tokenomics will return more value to builders and stakers via dApp staking. Astar&rsquo;s innovative Build2Earn program empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the dApps they build. It allows network users to stake their tokens to support their favorite projects.</li></ol>5. Supernova: Paving the path forward<p>Actions speak louder than words. Watch out for our coming updates in the middle of Q3 which will see Astar deliver on its web3 promises. Like a supernova exploding and impacting the universe, Astar aims to have the same impact in the web3 universe. Bringing Astar technology and vision to the masses.</p><p>Interested developers and users can explore the 2.0 Vision here. Moreover, Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations have shown strong belief in Astar&rsquo;s vision and its ability to execute. Astar will share more details later in June and July.</p><p>The Astar Foundation and Startale Labs have been working with many of the world&rsquo;s leading global players to achieve the 2.0 Vision. Japan&rsquo;s leading corporations including Toyota Motor Corporation and Sony Network Communications have teamed up with Astar Network to explore the opportunities in Web3.</p><p>Sota Watanabe, the Founder of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We will push the network to unlock Web3 for billions. Each part of Astar 2.0 is being shaped and improved, starting with token economics and developer tooling to ensure the sustainable long-term growth of the network.&rdquo;</p><p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 in Japan, having been voted the most popular blockchain in the country by the Japanese Blockchain Association. It is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. Astar is also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p><p></p>About Startale Labs <p>Startale Labs is a web3 tech company developing multichain applications and infrastructure. We also conduct R&amp;D and incubation activities based on the experience and connections developed in coordination with Astar Network. In addition, a subsidiary, Startale Labs Japan, was established on January 31st 2023 to provide web3 business development and strategic consulting services to corporate enterprises and governments, leveraging the strengths of Japan&rsquo;s most widely-recognized public blockchain.</p><p></p>About Astar Network<p>Astar is Japan&rsquo;s most popular smart contract platform, supporting both EVM and WebAssembly (Wasm) environments, and interoperability between them using a Cross-Virtual Machine. Astar Network is friendly to all kinds of developers, and tools and languages they already know. Backed by the shared security of Polkadot, Astar shines brilliantly on its own within a vibrant and healthy ecosystem, and is a leading star in the blockchain industry overall, driving international corporate adoption, and consumer interest in web3 technologies.</p><p>For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit | YouTube&nbsp;</p>ContactSota Watanabeinfo@startale.org]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Aave’s Proposal To Freeze Curve Founder Loans Draws Community Ire]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/aaves-proposal-to-freeze-curve-founder-loan-draws-community-ire</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/aave-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/aaves-proposal-to-freeze-curve-founder-loan-draws-community-ire</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>An Aave proposal intended to prevent a particular account from accumulating more debt has led to significant controversy, with some stating that it violates the principle of neutrality in DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposal suggested imposing a cap on using CRV tokens as collateral, preventing the wallet address in question from adding more loans.&nbsp;</p>
The Account In Question&nbsp;
<p>Many believe that Curve (CRV) founder Michael Egonov owns the account in question. Egonov had begun borrowing stablecoins on Aave in April, beginning with $37 million worth of Tether (USDT) being sent to Bitfinex and a further $51 million in USDC being sent to market maker Wintermute. More recently, Egorov deposited $24 million worth of Curve DAO (CRV) tokens to Aave to mitigate the liquidation risk of a $65 million stablecoin loan.</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;Seems like Curve&rsquo;s founder has a $110m leverage position against his $CRV stack across all Defi. If not repaid at some point (spoil: it prob won&rsquo;t, my man is taking profit), this will cascade into a lot of bad debt for lending protocols.&rdquo;</p>

Liquidation Risk&nbsp;
<p>According to the author of the proposal, the address associated with the account (0x7a16ff8270133f063aab6c9977183d9e72835428) has gone on to accumulate over $67 million worth of debt in USDC and USDT using the AAVE v2 protocol and putting up $185 million worth of CRV tokens as collateral. The proposal&rsquo;s author expressed concern that the account could continue increasing its debt, increasing the risk that it could be liquidated if the price of CRV suddenly drops. Adding to the problem is the fact that CRV has suffered a recent decline in liquidity over the past few months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This could lead to considerable slippage if the account is liquidated, as there may not be enough buyers looking to purchase CRV and take on such a significant amount of CRV tokens, leading to millions of dollars worth of bad debt for the Aave protocol.&nbsp;</p>
Freeze on CRV As Collateral&nbsp;
<p>According to Aave user DecentMuse, the wallet address is tagged as belonging to Michael Egonov, the founder of Curve. According to the user, the loan could be a way for Egonov to take profits from his activities on behalf of Curve. Financial modeling platform Gauntlet, the proposal&rsquo;s author suggested that the AAVE decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) freeze further use of CRV tokens as collateral for taking out loans. Such a move would allow the account to hold its current loan position but prevent it from accumulating more debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposal found some support among users who criticized the account for taking on so much debt. One user wondered if the account intended to pay off its debt, adding that it constantly added to its position despite the token losing value.&nbsp;</p>
Proposal Criticized&nbsp;
<p>However, critics of the proposal defended the account. One user suggested that the account owner may believe that CRV tokens are undervalued, leading them to increase their use as collateral as their price declines. Marc Zeller, Aave-Chan Initiative founder, also put forward his views, adding that the AAVE DAO should not violate neutrality, which is one of the core tenets of DeFi.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The intention of users or what they do with their funds is not our primary concern. Users should be free to utilize the protocol as they see fit.&rdquo;</p>

<p>So far, the proposal is only listed as a &ldquo;recommendation,&rdquo; meaning it has not yet been turned into an Aave Improvement Proposal (AIP), which the DAO can vote on. However, Gauntlet has stated that turning it into a formal AIP is the next step.&nbsp;</p>
An Ongoing Debate&nbsp;
<p>There is an ongoing debate in the larger blockchain ecosystem regarding the limits of censorship resistance. In January, Bitcoin saw a similar debate where users complained of high fees caused by some users minting and trading ordinals. Some Bitcoin users wanted a ban on Ordinals, while others opposed a ban, stating it would be censorship. In April, Tether blacklisted an address that drained $25 million from EVM-front-running bots.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Jayanti Kanani, Polygon co-founder, stated that the blacklisting could establish a bad precedent and lead to more transactions being censored. However, ZachXBT, the on-chain sleuth, stated that Tether could have been forced to act by a court order.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Aave proposal intended to prevent a particular account from accumulating more debt has led to significant controversy, with some stating that it violates the principle of neutrality in DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposal suggested imposing a cap on using CRV tokens as collateral, preventing the wallet address in question from adding more loans.&nbsp;</p>
The Account In Question&nbsp;
<p>Many believe that Curve (CRV) founder Michael Egonov owns the account in question. Egonov had begun borrowing stablecoins on Aave in April, beginning with $37 million worth of Tether (USDT) being sent to Bitfinex and a further $51 million in USDC being sent to market maker Wintermute. More recently, Egorov deposited $24 million worth of Curve DAO (CRV) tokens to Aave to mitigate the liquidation risk of a $65 million stablecoin loan.</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;Seems like Curve&rsquo;s founder has a $110m leverage position against his $CRV stack across all Defi. If not repaid at some point (spoil: it prob won&rsquo;t, my man is taking profit), this will cascade into a lot of bad debt for lending protocols.&rdquo;</p>

Liquidation Risk&nbsp;
<p>According to the author of the proposal, the address associated with the account (0x7a16ff8270133f063aab6c9977183d9e72835428) has gone on to accumulate over $67 million worth of debt in USDC and USDT using the AAVE v2 protocol and putting up $185 million worth of CRV tokens as collateral. The proposal&rsquo;s author expressed concern that the account could continue increasing its debt, increasing the risk that it could be liquidated if the price of CRV suddenly drops. Adding to the problem is the fact that CRV has suffered a recent decline in liquidity over the past few months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This could lead to considerable slippage if the account is liquidated, as there may not be enough buyers looking to purchase CRV and take on such a significant amount of CRV tokens, leading to millions of dollars worth of bad debt for the Aave protocol.&nbsp;</p>
Freeze on CRV As Collateral&nbsp;
<p>According to Aave user DecentMuse, the wallet address is tagged as belonging to Michael Egonov, the founder of Curve. According to the user, the loan could be a way for Egonov to take profits from his activities on behalf of Curve. Financial modeling platform Gauntlet, the proposal&rsquo;s author suggested that the AAVE decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) freeze further use of CRV tokens as collateral for taking out loans. Such a move would allow the account to hold its current loan position but prevent it from accumulating more debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposal found some support among users who criticized the account for taking on so much debt. One user wondered if the account intended to pay off its debt, adding that it constantly added to its position despite the token losing value.&nbsp;</p>
Proposal Criticized&nbsp;
<p>However, critics of the proposal defended the account. One user suggested that the account owner may believe that CRV tokens are undervalued, leading them to increase their use as collateral as their price declines. Marc Zeller, Aave-Chan Initiative founder, also put forward his views, adding that the AAVE DAO should not violate neutrality, which is one of the core tenets of DeFi.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The intention of users or what they do with their funds is not our primary concern. Users should be free to utilize the protocol as they see fit.&rdquo;</p>

<p>So far, the proposal is only listed as a &ldquo;recommendation,&rdquo; meaning it has not yet been turned into an Aave Improvement Proposal (AIP), which the DAO can vote on. However, Gauntlet has stated that turning it into a formal AIP is the next step.&nbsp;</p>
An Ongoing Debate&nbsp;
<p>There is an ongoing debate in the larger blockchain ecosystem regarding the limits of censorship resistance. In January, Bitcoin saw a similar debate where users complained of high fees caused by some users minting and trading ordinals. Some Bitcoin users wanted a ban on Ordinals, while others opposed a ban, stating it would be censorship. In April, Tether blacklisted an address that drained $25 million from EVM-front-running bots.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Jayanti Kanani, Polygon co-founder, stated that the blacklisting could establish a bad precedent and lead to more transactions being censored. However, ZachXBT, the on-chain sleuth, stated that Tether could have been forced to act by a court order.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKX Middle East Receives MVP Preparatory License From VARA in Dubai]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-middle-east-receives-mvp-preparatory-license-from-vara-in-dubai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_4_5681292440_1686804403sWOy5def5A.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_4_5681292440_1686804403sWOy5def5A.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_4_5681292440_1686804403sWOy5def5A.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:10:34 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-middle-east-receives-mvp-preparatory-license-from-vara-in-dubai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>UAE to serve as strategic global and regional business hub, OKX to expand to 30 staff</p><p>OKX, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced that OKX Middle East Fintech FZE (OKX Middle East) has received a Minimal Viable Product (MVP) Preparatory license from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA).</p><p>The UAE is a key strategic growth and business hub for OKX globally and in the region, and the company plans to scale OKX Middle East's operations. As part of this effort, OKX has opened a new office in Dubai World Trade Center, and will seek to expand its number of Dubai staff to 30 with a focus on local hires and senior management. OKX also plans to extend its nine-figure brand partnerships to the UAE with customer and fan-focused activations and activities.</p><p>The MVP preparatory licence allows approved licensees to fulfill all pre-conditions required to undertake MVP operations within the VARA regime. Once licensed to be operational, OKX Middle East will be able to extend its approved suite of duly regulated virtual assets activities and will provide spot, derivatives, and fiat services, including USD and AED deposits, withdrawals and spot-pairs, to institutional and qualified retail customers.</p>OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer Lennix Lai said: &ldquo;We're thrilled to receive the MVP preparatory license from VARA. Regulated entities are the future of digital assets and capital markets and Dubai and VARA have succeeded in creating a unique environment where VASPs can thrive. With the expansion into a new office this year, we are focused on hiring local staff and senior management. The MENA region has incredible potential as a center of excellence for Web3 and virtual assets, we look forward to the opportunity to expand the already growing ecosystem across the region.&rdquo;OKX Global Head of Government Relations Tim Byun said: &ldquo;Dubai and VARA are world leaders in crypto regulation by establishing the most timely, comprehensive and built from-the-ground-up framework for virtual assets and Web3. Licensing in Dubai is a critical element of OKX&rsquo;s global regulatory compliance strategy. In today&rsquo;s uncertain market environment, it's of the utmost importance for VASPs to be highly secure, transparent, compliant and backed by strong, clear regulation. Under VARA&rsquo;s comprehensive framework, all operators must meet high standards of compliance, risk management, security and consumer protection, benchmarked against well-known existing regulatory principles for traditional financial services. This provides confidence to operators and customers alike, and positions the crypto and Web3 industry in MENA for increased participation and overall growth in the near and long term.&rdquo;OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: "We've been waiting to enter the UAE and we want people here to experience our products first hand. We're different - we do things in a measured and transparent manner. May was our seventh consecutive month of publishing our proof of reserves, making us the only crypto exchange globally with that commitment. We've done that while out-innovating the industry in Web3 with our leading decentralized ecosystem. We've also launched numerous new security features while adding more depth in markets. This attitude is consistent with the brand partners who represent us, Manchester City Football Club, McLaren Racing, and the Tribeca Festival. We take our time, and do things the right way."<p>For more information on OKX, please visit OKX.com.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as one of the fastest and most reliable crypto trading platforms for investors and professional traders everywhere, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume and is trusted by more than 50 million users.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>About VARA</p><p>Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority [VARA] is the world's first specialized regulator for the Virtual Assets sector. Established in March 2022, following the effect of Law No.4 of 2022, VARA is the competent entity in charge of regulating, supervising, and overseeing VAs and VA activities in all zones across the Emirate of Dubai, including Special Development Zones and Free Zones but excluding the Dubai International Financial Centre.</p><p>VARA plays a central role in creating Dubai's advanced legal framework to protect investors and establish international standards for Virtual Asset industry governance, while supporting the vision for a borderless economy.</p><p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>ContactMarc Rognonmedia@okx.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>UAE to serve as strategic global and regional business hub, OKX to expand to 30 staff</p><p>OKX, the second-largest crypto exchange by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced that OKX Middle East Fintech FZE (OKX Middle East) has received a Minimal Viable Product (MVP) Preparatory license from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA).</p><p>The UAE is a key strategic growth and business hub for OKX globally and in the region, and the company plans to scale OKX Middle East's operations. As part of this effort, OKX has opened a new office in Dubai World Trade Center, and will seek to expand its number of Dubai staff to 30 with a focus on local hires and senior management. OKX also plans to extend its nine-figure brand partnerships to the UAE with customer and fan-focused activations and activities.</p><p>The MVP preparatory licence allows approved licensees to fulfill all pre-conditions required to undertake MVP operations within the VARA regime. Once licensed to be operational, OKX Middle East will be able to extend its approved suite of duly regulated virtual assets activities and will provide spot, derivatives, and fiat services, including USD and AED deposits, withdrawals and spot-pairs, to institutional and qualified retail customers.</p>OKX Global Chief Commercial Officer Lennix Lai said: &ldquo;We're thrilled to receive the MVP preparatory license from VARA. Regulated entities are the future of digital assets and capital markets and Dubai and VARA have succeeded in creating a unique environment where VASPs can thrive. With the expansion into a new office this year, we are focused on hiring local staff and senior management. The MENA region has incredible potential as a center of excellence for Web3 and virtual assets, we look forward to the opportunity to expand the already growing ecosystem across the region.&rdquo;OKX Global Head of Government Relations Tim Byun said: &ldquo;Dubai and VARA are world leaders in crypto regulation by establishing the most timely, comprehensive and built from-the-ground-up framework for virtual assets and Web3. Licensing in Dubai is a critical element of OKX&rsquo;s global regulatory compliance strategy. In today&rsquo;s uncertain market environment, it's of the utmost importance for VASPs to be highly secure, transparent, compliant and backed by strong, clear regulation. Under VARA&rsquo;s comprehensive framework, all operators must meet high standards of compliance, risk management, security and consumer protection, benchmarked against well-known existing regulatory principles for traditional financial services. This provides confidence to operators and customers alike, and positions the crypto and Web3 industry in MENA for increased participation and overall growth in the near and long term.&rdquo;OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: "We've been waiting to enter the UAE and we want people here to experience our products first hand. We're different - we do things in a measured and transparent manner. May was our seventh consecutive month of publishing our proof of reserves, making us the only crypto exchange globally with that commitment. We've done that while out-innovating the industry in Web3 with our leading decentralized ecosystem. We've also launched numerous new security features while adding more depth in markets. This attitude is consistent with the brand partners who represent us, Manchester City Football Club, McLaren Racing, and the Tribeca Festival. We take our time, and do things the right way."<p>For more information on OKX, please visit OKX.com.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as one of the fastest and most reliable crypto trading platforms for investors and professional traders everywhere, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume and is trusted by more than 50 million users.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>About VARA</p><p>Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority [VARA] is the world's first specialized regulator for the Virtual Assets sector. Established in March 2022, following the effect of Law No.4 of 2022, VARA is the competent entity in charge of regulating, supervising, and overseeing VAs and VA activities in all zones across the Emirate of Dubai, including Special Development Zones and Free Zones but excluding the Dubai International Financial Centre.</p><p>VARA plays a central role in creating Dubai's advanced legal framework to protect investors and establish international standards for Virtual Asset industry governance, while supporting the vision for a borderless economy.</p><p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>ContactMarc Rognonmedia@okx.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Labs Maintains Long-Standing Investment in SevenX Ventures, Expanding Ecosystem Partnership]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-maintains-long-standing-investment-in-sevenx-ventures-expanding-ecosystem-partnership</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1686727343MdDZWRACUg.JPEG" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1686727343MdDZWRACUg.JPEG" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1686727343MdDZWRACUg.JPEG" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:15 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-maintains-long-standing-investment-in-sevenx-ventures-expanding-ecosystem-partnership</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, the leading venture fund, has disclosed details of its investment in SevenX Ventures, a research-driven venture capital firm in Web3. The two funds aim to provide comprehensive support for blockchain projects and entrepreneurs worldwide, fueling innovation and fostering global collaboration in Web3.</p><p>With $100 million assets under management (AUM), LBank Labs has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. The venture capitalist arm of LBank, the global cryptocurrency exchange, LBank Labs is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. In addition to direct investments, the fund aims to build a robust network by investing in top global funds, providing financial and resource value-add support to portfolios within the network.</p><p>Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, has personally contributed as a limited partner (LP) to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund, and Lemniscap. Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank, has been an LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II, III and FOF from the very beginning, as well as IOSG Ventures.</p><p>SevenX Ventures, headed by seasoned veterans with an average industry experience of six years, manages three main funds and a Fund of Funds (FOF), totaling approximately $300 million AUM.</p><p>&ldquo;SevenX is dedicated to helping our portfolio and partners build a trustless network to make the value of organizations and individuals come true in crypto and Web3,&rdquo; explained Jon, Founding Partner at SevenX Ventures.</p><p>SevenX Ventures has already weathered three bull and bear cycles, with a portfolio of nearly 100 projects spanning infrastructure, middleware, DeFi, gaming, and social applications. Notable portfolio companies include Near, Arweave, Zerion, YGG, Mask Network, AI Arena, Space and Time, CyberConnect, Debank, and DODO. Furthermore, SevenX Ventures plays a pivotal role in bridging infrastructures and decentralized applications (dapps) between Western and Eastern markets, making the fund an indispensable partner in Asia.</p><p>LBank Labs has brought extensive financial resources and a vast global network to SevenX Ventures over the years, while SevenX Ventures has reciprocated by contributing significant value and knowledge to LBank Labs. As part of their commitment, LBank Labs aims to build a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, enhancing portfolio performance and diversification while emphasizing the inherent value of their ecosystem network. With Labs' presence in seven global regions, they are a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation cross-borders.</p><p>In addition to its partnership with SevenX Ventures, LBank Labs has recently announced investments in Sparkle Ventures and Collab+Currency, two notable venture funds dedicated to supporting and nurturing projects in the Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube&nbsp;</p><p></p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, the leading venture fund, has disclosed details of its investment in SevenX Ventures, a research-driven venture capital firm in Web3. The two funds aim to provide comprehensive support for blockchain projects and entrepreneurs worldwide, fueling innovation and fostering global collaboration in Web3.</p><p>With $100 million assets under management (AUM), LBank Labs has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. The venture capitalist arm of LBank, the global cryptocurrency exchange, LBank Labs is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. In addition to direct investments, the fund aims to build a robust network by investing in top global funds, providing financial and resource value-add support to portfolios within the network.</p><p>Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, has personally contributed as a limited partner (LP) to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund, and Lemniscap. Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank, has been an LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II, III and FOF from the very beginning, as well as IOSG Ventures.</p><p>SevenX Ventures, headed by seasoned veterans with an average industry experience of six years, manages three main funds and a Fund of Funds (FOF), totaling approximately $300 million AUM.</p><p>&ldquo;SevenX is dedicated to helping our portfolio and partners build a trustless network to make the value of organizations and individuals come true in crypto and Web3,&rdquo; explained Jon, Founding Partner at SevenX Ventures.</p><p>SevenX Ventures has already weathered three bull and bear cycles, with a portfolio of nearly 100 projects spanning infrastructure, middleware, DeFi, gaming, and social applications. Notable portfolio companies include Near, Arweave, Zerion, YGG, Mask Network, AI Arena, Space and Time, CyberConnect, Debank, and DODO. Furthermore, SevenX Ventures plays a pivotal role in bridging infrastructures and decentralized applications (dapps) between Western and Eastern markets, making the fund an indispensable partner in Asia.</p><p>LBank Labs has brought extensive financial resources and a vast global network to SevenX Ventures over the years, while SevenX Ventures has reciprocated by contributing significant value and knowledge to LBank Labs. As part of their commitment, LBank Labs aims to build a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, enhancing portfolio performance and diversification while emphasizing the inherent value of their ecosystem network. With Labs' presence in seven global regions, they are a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation cross-borders.</p><p>In addition to its partnership with SevenX Ventures, LBank Labs has recently announced investments in Sparkle Ventures and Collab+Currency, two notable venture funds dedicated to supporting and nurturing projects in the Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube&nbsp;</p><p></p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Fed pauses as crypto market continues slide]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/fed-pauses-as-crypto-market-continues-slide</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:57:35 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/fed-pauses-as-crypto-market-continues-slide</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Reserve did not raise rates for the first time since the inflation-inspired start of its rapid interest rate expansion. However, crypto continues its downward slide.</p>
Fed intervention
<p>A Fed pivot is on the horizon even though it may not start to actually reduce interest rates until next year. This was certainly coming given that the current mad series of interest rate hikes is forcing the economy into recession.</p>
<p>Never before has the Fed tightened as quickly and as harshly as this following Biden and Yellen&rsquo;s claims back in July of 2021 that inflation was only &ldquo;temporary&rdquo;.</p>
<p>History tells us that our boom and bust cycles are caused by government and central bank manipulation of credit, and that government intervention in the markets is always a bad thing and could probably be said to be axiomatic.</p>
Attempted eradication of crypto
<p>In such a chaotic world where the dollar and all other fiat currencies are being debased like crazy, it appears that the last thing the US government needs is the slightest hint of competition to its currency.</p>
<p>It could be argued that the government sees this competition coming on two fronts. It is now understanding the full import of cryptocurrencies - which might be classified as a type of private money.</p>
<p>After huge successes for some cryptocurrencies, admittedly mostly driven by hype and speculation, the US government has probably decided to try and eradicate them through the auspices of its enforcement agencies (SEC and CFTC).</p>
<p>A systemic attack on the crypto ecosystem is now taking place and lacking liquidity and with many crypto investors fleeing the sector the market is bleeding out.</p>
Bitcoin unassailable?
<p>However, there is one cryptocurrency that even the US government would have the devil of a job in taking down, and that is bitcoin. Bitcoin is the most decentralised and secure private money that exists in the world today, and given that it runs purely on code there is nothing any government or agency can do to stop it.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, the rest of the market is obviously having an effect on bitcoin as large crypto businesses run into difficulties with sizable chunks of bitcoin on their books, and Mt Gox and the US government are selling their bitcoin into the market.</p>
<p>Once this selling pressure is gone though it might be expected that bitcoin would begin a dramatic rise as investors rush out of a worsening dollar, to say nothing of the rest of the fiat currencies.</p>
BRICS currency on the horizon
<p>The other front where the US can expect huge competition is from the BRICS nations. In August, at a Summit in South Africa, these nations are expected to announce a new currency which could be backed by gold and/or other commodities, or could even become a rival reserve currency to the dollar by having its own deep and liquid bond market, with the bonds bought by citizens in 20 or so countries that are in or on the point of joining the BRICS nations.</p>
<p>So whether it be Bitcoin or the BRICS nations, the dollar is likely to undergo the most profound and serious rivalry since it came into existence. With the unpayable debts owed by the US government and nothing but thin air and promises backing the currency, a new world order may be on the way.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Federal Reserve did not raise rates for the first time since the inflation-inspired start of its rapid interest rate expansion. However, crypto continues its downward slide.</p>
Fed intervention
<p>A Fed pivot is on the horizon even though it may not start to actually reduce interest rates until next year. This was certainly coming given that the current mad series of interest rate hikes is forcing the economy into recession.</p>
<p>Never before has the Fed tightened as quickly and as harshly as this following Biden and Yellen&rsquo;s claims back in July of 2021 that inflation was only &ldquo;temporary&rdquo;.</p>
<p>History tells us that our boom and bust cycles are caused by government and central bank manipulation of credit, and that government intervention in the markets is always a bad thing and could probably be said to be axiomatic.</p>
Attempted eradication of crypto
<p>In such a chaotic world where the dollar and all other fiat currencies are being debased like crazy, it appears that the last thing the US government needs is the slightest hint of competition to its currency.</p>
<p>It could be argued that the government sees this competition coming on two fronts. It is now understanding the full import of cryptocurrencies - which might be classified as a type of private money.</p>
<p>After huge successes for some cryptocurrencies, admittedly mostly driven by hype and speculation, the US government has probably decided to try and eradicate them through the auspices of its enforcement agencies (SEC and CFTC).</p>
<p>A systemic attack on the crypto ecosystem is now taking place and lacking liquidity and with many crypto investors fleeing the sector the market is bleeding out.</p>
Bitcoin unassailable?
<p>However, there is one cryptocurrency that even the US government would have the devil of a job in taking down, and that is bitcoin. Bitcoin is the most decentralised and secure private money that exists in the world today, and given that it runs purely on code there is nothing any government or agency can do to stop it.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, the rest of the market is obviously having an effect on bitcoin as large crypto businesses run into difficulties with sizable chunks of bitcoin on their books, and Mt Gox and the US government are selling their bitcoin into the market.</p>
<p>Once this selling pressure is gone though it might be expected that bitcoin would begin a dramatic rise as investors rush out of a worsening dollar, to say nothing of the rest of the fiat currencies.</p>
BRICS currency on the horizon
<p>The other front where the US can expect huge competition is from the BRICS nations. In August, at a Summit in South Africa, these nations are expected to announce a new currency which could be backed by gold and/or other commodities, or could even become a rival reserve currency to the dollar by having its own deep and liquid bond market, with the bonds bought by citizens in 20 or so countries that are in or on the point of joining the BRICS nations.</p>
<p>So whether it be Bitcoin or the BRICS nations, the dollar is likely to undergo the most profound and serious rivalry since it came into existence. With the unpayable debts owed by the US government and nothing but thin air and promises backing the currency, a new world order may be on the way.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Pushes Back Against SEC’s Proposed Definition Change]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/coinbase-pushes-back-against-secs-proposed-definition-change</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/coinbase-pushes-back-against-secs-proposed-definition-change</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has become the latest entity to push back against the United States Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s proposed definition change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The SEC had moved to expand its definition of an exchange in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
What&rsquo;s The SEC&rsquo;s Problem With Crypto?
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission has been relentless in its dogged pursuit of everything crypto. In its latest salvo, the regulatory body sued Coinbase in a New York federal court. In its lawsuit, the agency alleged that Coinbase acted as an unregistered broker and exchange and demanded that it be &ldquo;permanently restrained and enjoined&rdquo; from doing so. The lawsuit came just a day after the SEC had sued Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. The SEC in its press release, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Since 2019, Coinbase has been engaging in an unregistered securities offering through its staking-as-a-service program, which allows customers to earn profits from the &ldquo;proof of stake&rdquo; mechanisms of certain blockchains and Coinbase&rsquo;s efforts.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The crypto markets have been fairly nervous since the Securities and Exchange Commission filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, just a day before its action against Coinbase. According to the SEC, Binance mishandled funds and lied to investors and regulators about operations, a claim Binance refutes.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Demands Clarity&nbsp;
<p>Coinbase has pushed back against the Securities and Exchange Commission, urging it to provide better clarity for the crypto industry. The SEC has responded to Coinbase&rsquo;s call for clarity, stating that it requires four months or 120 days to respond. The response comes after a barrage of court filings by both, Coinbase and the SEC. Coinbase had filed a writ of Mandamus against the regulatory body after it stated that it was &ldquo;in no hurry&rdquo; to respond to the exchange&rsquo;s demand for regulatory clarity. Coinbase had accused the agency of wilfully ignoring its request for immediate clarity. Prior to this, the SEC had responded to a previous petition stating that it would not give in to the exchange&rsquo;s demands.&nbsp;</p>
SEC&rsquo;s Proposed Definition Change&nbsp;
<p>In 2022, the Securities and Exchange Commission moved to expand its definition of an exchange. In April 2023, the agency reopened its comment period of the proposal, adding that this was needed as it planned to &ldquo;fold in DeFi and crypto.&rdquo; SEC Chair Gary Gensler stated that this would help address comments on proposals from market participants, particularly those associated with the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase has been pushing back against the SEC, especially since the agency sued the exchange, alleging it was offering its users unregistered securities. In a letter to the SEC, Coinbase stated that it has no authority to ban an entire industry.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As the Supreme Court has repeatedly held, an agency&rsquo;s authority to regulate a particular industry does not include the authority to ban that industry, absent clear Congressional authorization.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase also criticized the SEC&rsquo;s decision to include crypto and DeFi under its planned exchanges definition. The updated definition also applies to more traditional market makers. The exchange stated that it was especially concerned with the proposal&rsquo;s potential impact on decentralized exchanges (DEX). In its letter to the SEC, the exchange stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The proposed rule, as applied to DEXs, would be just such an impossible requirement. When creating a DEX, a software developer typically writes the code that creates the DEX and then publishes the code onto a public, permissionless blockchain, along with a mechanism for widely distributing the governance tokens that enable holders to alter select elements of the DEX going forward.</p>

Criticism From All Quarters&nbsp;
<p>The SEC&rsquo;s proposed exchange definition has come under heavy criticism from all quarters. Critics include the Blockchain Association, Paradigm, DeFi Education Fund (DEF), and Republicans from the House Financial Services Committee, some of whom have urged the SEC to withdraw the proposal. Paradigm stated that a DEX, particularly one using an automated market maker mechanism, does not involve any intermediary between buyers and sellers, adding that it used algorithms to balance crypto pools. It urged the agency to withdraw the proposal, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We write to request that the Commission withdraw its proposed redefinition of &lsquo;exchange&rsquo; and begin its consideration of how to adapt its regulations in the DeFi context anew &mdash; after rigorous economic analysis, genuine, broad engagement with the industry, and a close look at the limits of its statutory jurisdiction.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Paradigm, the Blockchain Association, and Coinbase have also argued that the SEC has violated the Administrative Procedures Act (APA). The APA governs and guides how agencies devise and implement regulations.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The rule change is vague and ambiguous, and the range of activities that may be captured within its scope are not yet fully fleshed out.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has become the latest entity to push back against the United States Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s proposed definition change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The SEC had moved to expand its definition of an exchange in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
What&rsquo;s The SEC&rsquo;s Problem With Crypto?
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission has been relentless in its dogged pursuit of everything crypto. In its latest salvo, the regulatory body sued Coinbase in a New York federal court. In its lawsuit, the agency alleged that Coinbase acted as an unregistered broker and exchange and demanded that it be &ldquo;permanently restrained and enjoined&rdquo; from doing so. The lawsuit came just a day after the SEC had sued Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. The SEC in its press release, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Since 2019, Coinbase has been engaging in an unregistered securities offering through its staking-as-a-service program, which allows customers to earn profits from the &ldquo;proof of stake&rdquo; mechanisms of certain blockchains and Coinbase&rsquo;s efforts.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The crypto markets have been fairly nervous since the Securities and Exchange Commission filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao, just a day before its action against Coinbase. According to the SEC, Binance mishandled funds and lied to investors and regulators about operations, a claim Binance refutes.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Demands Clarity&nbsp;
<p>Coinbase has pushed back against the Securities and Exchange Commission, urging it to provide better clarity for the crypto industry. The SEC has responded to Coinbase&rsquo;s call for clarity, stating that it requires four months or 120 days to respond. The response comes after a barrage of court filings by both, Coinbase and the SEC. Coinbase had filed a writ of Mandamus against the regulatory body after it stated that it was &ldquo;in no hurry&rdquo; to respond to the exchange&rsquo;s demand for regulatory clarity. Coinbase had accused the agency of wilfully ignoring its request for immediate clarity. Prior to this, the SEC had responded to a previous petition stating that it would not give in to the exchange&rsquo;s demands.&nbsp;</p>
SEC&rsquo;s Proposed Definition Change&nbsp;
<p>In 2022, the Securities and Exchange Commission moved to expand its definition of an exchange. In April 2023, the agency reopened its comment period of the proposal, adding that this was needed as it planned to &ldquo;fold in DeFi and crypto.&rdquo; SEC Chair Gary Gensler stated that this would help address comments on proposals from market participants, particularly those associated with the crypto markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase has been pushing back against the SEC, especially since the agency sued the exchange, alleging it was offering its users unregistered securities. In a letter to the SEC, Coinbase stated that it has no authority to ban an entire industry.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As the Supreme Court has repeatedly held, an agency&rsquo;s authority to regulate a particular industry does not include the authority to ban that industry, absent clear Congressional authorization.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase also criticized the SEC&rsquo;s decision to include crypto and DeFi under its planned exchanges definition. The updated definition also applies to more traditional market makers. The exchange stated that it was especially concerned with the proposal&rsquo;s potential impact on decentralized exchanges (DEX). In its letter to the SEC, the exchange stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The proposed rule, as applied to DEXs, would be just such an impossible requirement. When creating a DEX, a software developer typically writes the code that creates the DEX and then publishes the code onto a public, permissionless blockchain, along with a mechanism for widely distributing the governance tokens that enable holders to alter select elements of the DEX going forward.</p>

Criticism From All Quarters&nbsp;
<p>The SEC&rsquo;s proposed exchange definition has come under heavy criticism from all quarters. Critics include the Blockchain Association, Paradigm, DeFi Education Fund (DEF), and Republicans from the House Financial Services Committee, some of whom have urged the SEC to withdraw the proposal. Paradigm stated that a DEX, particularly one using an automated market maker mechanism, does not involve any intermediary between buyers and sellers, adding that it used algorithms to balance crypto pools. It urged the agency to withdraw the proposal, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We write to request that the Commission withdraw its proposed redefinition of &lsquo;exchange&rsquo; and begin its consideration of how to adapt its regulations in the DeFi context anew &mdash; after rigorous economic analysis, genuine, broad engagement with the industry, and a close look at the limits of its statutory jurisdiction.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Paradigm, the Blockchain Association, and Coinbase have also argued that the SEC has violated the Administrative Procedures Act (APA). The APA governs and guides how agencies devise and implement regulations.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The rule change is vague and ambiguous, and the range of activities that may be captured within its scope are not yet fully fleshed out.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Launches Mars Program Becoming the First Cryptocurrency Exchange to Enter Space Exploration]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/huobi-launches-mars-program-becoming-the-first-cryptocurrency-exchange-to-enter-space-exploration</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686816861nmt7oJ5UC4.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686816861nmt7oJ5UC4.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686816861nmt7oJ5UC4.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:18:46 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/huobi-launches-mars-program-becoming-the-first-cryptocurrency-exchange-to-enter-space-exploration</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi, the virtual asset trading platform, announces Phase I of the Huobi Mars Program to kick off its ambitious plan to explore the universe.</p><p>Get Huobi on Mars! By investing big in the space program, Huobi has shown its dedication as the leading cryptocurrency exchange for space exploration. &ldquo;Huobi's aspirations are to reach out far into the universe,&rdquo; said Justin Sun, a member of Huobi Advisory Board. He also mentioned that, &ldquo;Huobi will join hands with its users in embarking on this special journey throughout space and to explore the unknown. Huobi users will become the first in the Web3 field to enter space.&rdquo;</p><p>According to Huobi's announcement, the first phase of the Huobi Mars Program spans from June 2023 to June 2024 and consists of 12 rounds. Each round will include a themed activity under which the participating users need to complete the specified tasks and mint the space NFTs. For each round, one lucky user will be selected to win a monthly reward and the winner will be shortlisted as a candidate space passenger. In the second phase, the 12 candidates will be evaluated based on their physical fitness, training and preparation, community contribution, etc., to determine the eventual passenger for space travel with Justin Sun. The space flight is scheduled at a suitable time after July 2024.</p><p>The first round of the Huobi Mars Program will last from 12:00 (UTC) on June 14 to 15:59 (UTC) on July 5, 2023. Participating users will need to complete the required one-time, revolving, or monthly settlement of spot trading, P2P transactions, futures trading, and Huobi Earn transactions in order to win space NFT rewards. A user will be offered one chance to mint a space NFT for each task completed, without upper limits.</p><p>The space NFTs will be issued on the TRON Network and marketable on various NFT trading platforms. Users will need to link their TRON addresses on the event page in order to receive the minted NFTs. Users are advised to mint the NFTs as soon as possible, as the daily allocated NFT mints are capped and the minting qualification does not carry over to the next round. The first round of NFT minting time lasts from 12:00 (UTC) on June 14 to 15:59 (UTC) on July 15, 2023. The result for the first round will be released at 12:00 (UTC) on July 20, 2023.</p><p>One lucky user will be drawn to win the generous monthly award and shortlisted as a candidate space passenger each month. The space flight will be broadcasted to the world via a livestream. The candidate space passenger shall be the holder of the NFT number that has been drawn. Huobi will also check the lucky NFT holder's TRON address, UID, KYC verification, etc., to verify the winner's identity. Please note that snapshots will be taken at the time of the result release to determine the winner. The winning space NFTs are not transferable. Any such transfer is deemed as a waiver of the reward.</p><p>The lucky users shortlisted during the first round of Huobi Mars Program will not only qualify as a space passenger candidate but also enjoy the privilege of a 180-day exemption from spot trading fees on Huobi.</p><p>Ancient astronomers observed the movement of stars to make calendars. In the contemporary time, Elon Musk's SpaceX has been blasting off next-generation rockets. Huobi is contributing its own share to this great cause. With this Mars Program, Huobi hopes to introduce space travel to more people, inspire more interest and passion, and promote the development of commercial spaceflight. This move demonstrates Huobi's commitment to innovation and exploration, as well as its financial strength.</p><p>Get Huobi on Mars! Huobi will always be on the road and never stop.</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi, the virtual asset trading platform, announces Phase I of the Huobi Mars Program to kick off its ambitious plan to explore the universe.</p><p>Get Huobi on Mars! By investing big in the space program, Huobi has shown its dedication as the leading cryptocurrency exchange for space exploration. &ldquo;Huobi's aspirations are to reach out far into the universe,&rdquo; said Justin Sun, a member of Huobi Advisory Board. He also mentioned that, &ldquo;Huobi will join hands with its users in embarking on this special journey throughout space and to explore the unknown. Huobi users will become the first in the Web3 field to enter space.&rdquo;</p><p>According to Huobi's announcement, the first phase of the Huobi Mars Program spans from June 2023 to June 2024 and consists of 12 rounds. Each round will include a themed activity under which the participating users need to complete the specified tasks and mint the space NFTs. For each round, one lucky user will be selected to win a monthly reward and the winner will be shortlisted as a candidate space passenger. In the second phase, the 12 candidates will be evaluated based on their physical fitness, training and preparation, community contribution, etc., to determine the eventual passenger for space travel with Justin Sun. The space flight is scheduled at a suitable time after July 2024.</p><p>The first round of the Huobi Mars Program will last from 12:00 (UTC) on June 14 to 15:59 (UTC) on July 5, 2023. Participating users will need to complete the required one-time, revolving, or monthly settlement of spot trading, P2P transactions, futures trading, and Huobi Earn transactions in order to win space NFT rewards. A user will be offered one chance to mint a space NFT for each task completed, without upper limits.</p><p>The space NFTs will be issued on the TRON Network and marketable on various NFT trading platforms. Users will need to link their TRON addresses on the event page in order to receive the minted NFTs. Users are advised to mint the NFTs as soon as possible, as the daily allocated NFT mints are capped and the minting qualification does not carry over to the next round. The first round of NFT minting time lasts from 12:00 (UTC) on June 14 to 15:59 (UTC) on July 15, 2023. The result for the first round will be released at 12:00 (UTC) on July 20, 2023.</p><p>One lucky user will be drawn to win the generous monthly award and shortlisted as a candidate space passenger each month. The space flight will be broadcasted to the world via a livestream. The candidate space passenger shall be the holder of the NFT number that has been drawn. Huobi will also check the lucky NFT holder's TRON address, UID, KYC verification, etc., to verify the winner's identity. Please note that snapshots will be taken at the time of the result release to determine the winner. The winning space NFTs are not transferable. Any such transfer is deemed as a waiver of the reward.</p><p>The lucky users shortlisted during the first round of Huobi Mars Program will not only qualify as a space passenger candidate but also enjoy the privilege of a 180-day exemption from spot trading fees on Huobi.</p><p>Ancient astronomers observed the movement of stars to make calendars. In the contemporary time, Elon Musk's SpaceX has been blasting off next-generation rockets. Huobi is contributing its own share to this great cause. With this Mars Program, Huobi hopes to introduce space travel to more people, inspire more interest and passion, and promote the development of commercial spaceflight. This move demonstrates Huobi's commitment to innovation and exploration, as well as its financial strength.</p><p>Get Huobi on Mars! Huobi will always be on the road and never stop.</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC, Binance Talk Freeze Avoidance, Crypto Daily TV 15/6/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-binance-talk-freeze-avoidance-crypto-daily-tv-15-6-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-sec-freeze-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-sec-freeze-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-700-sec-freeze-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sec-binance-talk-freeze-avoidance-crypto-daily-tv-15-6-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Brazil appoints Central Bank and Securities Commission as crypto regulators</p>
<p>Brazil&rsquo;s executive branch has designated the country&rsquo;s Central Bank and its Securities Commission as responsible for overseeing the crypto market. The SC will exercise control over assets considered securities, while the Central Bank will determine the rules that exchanges must follow, including licensing requirements to operate.</p>
<p>SEC and Binance.US to negotiate deal avoiding total asset freeze</p>
<p>Binance.US and the SEC have agreed to work on an arrangement that will allow the exchange to avoid freezing all of its assets.&nbsp; U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson referred the two organizations to a magistrate judge to work toward a compromise arrangement to protect customer funds without having to shut down the exchange.</p>
<p>Bitcoin sinks, altcoins tumble</p>
<p>Bitcoin fell under $25,000 as investors shrugged off the U.S. central bank&rsquo;s widely expected halt to a more than year-long diet of interest rate hikes. Major altcoins took a dive to sink into negative territory, with Ether and ADA dropping 3 and 4%.</p>
BTC/USD dove 3.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 3.0% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 253591 and resistance at 267191.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 5.0% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 5.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1708.0367 and resistance at 1778.7967.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 7.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 7.9% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.4703 and resistance at 0.5894.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 5.9% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair plummeted 5.9% in the last session. The Williams indicator indicates an oversold market. Support is at 74.5967 and resistance at 80.9767.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>EMU Eurogroup Meeting</p>
<p>Eurogroup meetings are attended by the Eurogroup President, the Finance Minister of each Member State of the Euro area, the Commissioner for economic and monetary affairs, and the President of the European Central Bank. The Eurozone's Eurogroup Meeting will be released at 07:00 GMT, the US Initial Jobless Claims at 12:30 GMT, the Dutch Unemployment Rate at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Initial Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Initial Jobless Claims is a measure of the number of people filing first-time claims for state unemployment insurance. </p>
<p>NL Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>US Retail Sales</p>
<p>The Retail Sales measures the total receipts of retail stores. Monthly percent changes reflect the rate of change of such sales. The US Retail Sales will be released at 12:30 GMT, Australia's Employment Change at 01:30 GMT, Japan's Tertiary Industry Index at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Employment Change</p>
<p>The Employment Change is a measure of the change in the number of employed people, which in turn shows the strength of the Labour market.</p>
<p>JP Tertiary Industry Index</p>
<p>The Tertiary Industry Index is an indicator of the health of the domestic service sector and related economic factors.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Brazil appoints Central Bank and Securities Commission as crypto regulators</p>
<p>Brazil&rsquo;s executive branch has designated the country&rsquo;s Central Bank and its Securities Commission as responsible for overseeing the crypto market. The SC will exercise control over assets considered securities, while the Central Bank will determine the rules that exchanges must follow, including licensing requirements to operate.</p>
<p>SEC and Binance.US to negotiate deal avoiding total asset freeze</p>
<p>Binance.US and the SEC have agreed to work on an arrangement that will allow the exchange to avoid freezing all of its assets.&nbsp; U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson referred the two organizations to a magistrate judge to work toward a compromise arrangement to protect customer funds without having to shut down the exchange.</p>
<p>Bitcoin sinks, altcoins tumble</p>
<p>Bitcoin fell under $25,000 as investors shrugged off the U.S. central bank&rsquo;s widely expected halt to a more than year-long diet of interest rate hikes. Major altcoins took a dive to sink into negative territory, with Ether and ADA dropping 3 and 4%.</p>
BTC/USD dove 3.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 3.0% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 253591 and resistance at 267191.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD dove 5.0% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair dove 5.0% in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1708.0367 and resistance at 1778.7967.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD dove 7.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair dove 7.9% in the last session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.4703 and resistance at 0.5894.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 5.9% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair plummeted 5.9% in the last session. The Williams indicator indicates an oversold market. Support is at 74.5967 and resistance at 80.9767.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>EMU Eurogroup Meeting</p>
<p>Eurogroup meetings are attended by the Eurogroup President, the Finance Minister of each Member State of the Euro area, the Commissioner for economic and monetary affairs, and the President of the European Central Bank. The Eurozone's Eurogroup Meeting will be released at 07:00 GMT, the US Initial Jobless Claims at 12:30 GMT, the Dutch Unemployment Rate at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Initial Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Initial Jobless Claims is a measure of the number of people filing first-time claims for state unemployment insurance. </p>
<p>NL Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>US Retail Sales</p>
<p>The Retail Sales measures the total receipts of retail stores. Monthly percent changes reflect the rate of change of such sales. The US Retail Sales will be released at 12:30 GMT, Australia's Employment Change at 01:30 GMT, Japan's Tertiary Industry Index at 04:30 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Employment Change</p>
<p>The Employment Change is a measure of the change in the number of employed people, which in turn shows the strength of the Labour market.</p>
<p>JP Tertiary Industry Index</p>
<p>The Tertiary Industry Index is an indicator of the health of the domestic service sector and related economic factors.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Exchange Will List 6 Pack Rick (6PR) on June 15, 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-exchange-will-list-6-pack-rick-6pr-on-june-15-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686804881xr8Pex3dwe.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686804881xr8Pex3dwe.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1600-900_en_1686804881xr8Pex3dwe.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 07:15:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-exchange-will-list-6-pack-rick-6pr-on-june-15-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list 6 Pack Rick (6PR) on Jun 15, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the 6PR/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023.</p><p>6 Pack Rick (6PR) is a muscular revolution in the memeverse, who inspires Mortys and Mortettes everywhere to flex their might, rise above, and aim to transform memecoins, all while leading an epic journey of conquering the memeverse as true champions with the mantra, "Wubba lubba dub dub!". </p><p>Introducing 6 Pack Rick</p><p>Its native token, 6PR, will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023, with the goal of expanding its global footprint and supporting the realization of its forward-thinking objectives.</p><p>The project has set forth a turbocharged roadmap, taking aim at the moon with ambitions as robust as 6 Pack Rick's muscles. The token might appear as futile as the vast cosmos they inhabit, yet in this limitless multiverse with its infinite use cases, it has found it's niche. The unique allure emanates from being as buffed as one can be while simultaneously achieving a splendid degree of inactivity. In essence, its innovatively redefining the concept of uselessness, raising it to unprecedented heights, much like a weightlifter hoisting a weighty barbell into the air. The aim is not merely existing within the cosmic playground, but actively engaging in it, albeit in a distinctively lethargic manner.</p><p>About 6PR Token</p><p>Based on ERC-20, 6PR has a total supply of 420.69 trillion (i.e. 420,690,000,000,000). The token distribution for this project is designed to support various aspects, with 50.00% allocated for presale, 30.00% set aside to ensure liquidity, 8.00% dedicated to centralized exchanges (CEX), 7.00% marked for marketing, and the remaining 5.00% reserved for advisors. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023, investors who are interested in 6PR can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of 6PR token on LBank Exchange will help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p><p>Learn More about 6PR Token:</p><p>Official Website: https://6packrick.com/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/6packrick</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/sixpackrick</p><p>Contract: https://etherscan.io/address/0xA4637f40D17C7cF074e35877d86A8c24Cb1CFf1C</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Exchange, a global digital asset trading platform, will list 6 Pack Rick (6PR) on Jun 15, 2023. For all users of LBank Exchange, the 6PR/USDT trading pair will be officially available for trading at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023.</p><p>6 Pack Rick (6PR) is a muscular revolution in the memeverse, who inspires Mortys and Mortettes everywhere to flex their might, rise above, and aim to transform memecoins, all while leading an epic journey of conquering the memeverse as true champions with the mantra, "Wubba lubba dub dub!". </p><p>Introducing 6 Pack Rick</p><p>Its native token, 6PR, will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023, with the goal of expanding its global footprint and supporting the realization of its forward-thinking objectives.</p><p>The project has set forth a turbocharged roadmap, taking aim at the moon with ambitions as robust as 6 Pack Rick's muscles. The token might appear as futile as the vast cosmos they inhabit, yet in this limitless multiverse with its infinite use cases, it has found it's niche. The unique allure emanates from being as buffed as one can be while simultaneously achieving a splendid degree of inactivity. In essence, its innovatively redefining the concept of uselessness, raising it to unprecedented heights, much like a weightlifter hoisting a weighty barbell into the air. The aim is not merely existing within the cosmic playground, but actively engaging in it, albeit in a distinctively lethargic manner.</p><p>About 6PR Token</p><p>Based on ERC-20, 6PR has a total supply of 420.69 trillion (i.e. 420,690,000,000,000). The token distribution for this project is designed to support various aspects, with 50.00% allocated for presale, 30.00% set aside to ensure liquidity, 8.00% dedicated to centralized exchanges (CEX), 7.00% marked for marketing, and the remaining 5.00% reserved for advisors. It will be listed on LBank Exchange at 12:00 UTC on Jun 15, 2023, investors who are interested in 6PR can easily buy and sell it on LBank Exchange by then. The listing of 6PR token on LBank Exchange will help it further expand its business and draw more attention in the market.</p><p>Learn More about 6PR Token:</p><p>Official Website: https://6packrick.com/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/6packrick</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/sixpackrick</p><p>Contract: https://etherscan.io/address/0xA4637f40D17C7cF074e35877d86A8c24Cb1CFf1C</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users' funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now: lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedmarketing@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Green Economy - Bitcoin mining grows greener]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/green-economy-bitcoin-mining-grows-greener</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-635.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-635.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-635.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 01:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/green-economy-bitcoin-mining-grows-greener</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the coming years, the tone of the cryptocurrency market will be set by environmental projects, which will be increasingly used for mining around the world. New technologies and developments will be implemented in different parts of the world. And maybe even in outer space - such ideas and proposals already exist and are being discussed within the professional community. Interesting discussions took place at the Bitcoin Miami conference in the USA at the end of May.</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining was one of the key topics in the latest report by Messari, a leader in cryptocurrency market research and analysis. The authors believe that the green agenda will increasingly dominate in this field, and it will be the driving force of the industry in the years to come.On the one hand, environmental friendliness will grow into an actual trend, and crypto enthusiasts will adhere to ESG (Environmental, Social, Governance) Investing approach - environmental, social, governance aspects of investing. On the other hand, this trend will be supported by economic considerations, and the high cost of energy. As for this point, Messari analytics highlights a very indicative example for Bitcoin mining cost: in 2021, the mining of 1 bitcoin cost American miners in Texas about $5-10 thousand, and the coin itself was trading at around $50-60 thousand; its value went down in 2022, and the best price was estimated at $20 thousand with $15-20 thousand of mining cost.</p>
<p></p>
Serhiy Tron, Owner of White Rock Management, speaking at the Bitcoin 2023 conference
<p>As the coins value decreased, miners actively went looking for ways to reduce their energy costs. First of all, by making mining more environmentally friendly. The interest in hydroelectric power and electricity generation by flaring gas, byproduct of oil production, has grown tremendously. The latter technology not only provides cheaper energy for cryptocurrency mining, but also significantly reduces carbon dioxide emissions into the atmosphere. Reduction of the negative impact of mining on the environment.</p>
<p></p>

<p>"Being environmentally friendly is not just a fashion trend, but an economically profitable direction for mining. In some regions, the share of renewable energy in this field amounts to 40%, and even exceeds 70% in other regions. I think that interest will keep on growing, and global oil and gas corporations will cooperate more actively with the cryptocurrency industry. For example, our company has various projects in the U.S. underway: gas flaring in Texas and hydropower near Niagara Falls in the state of New York," said the founder of one of the world's largest mining companies, White Rock Management, Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>White Rock Management, along with 250 other companies, has joined the Crypto Climate Accord for environmentally friendly and safe cryptocurrency mining. With operating offices in Canada, Sweden, Kazakhstan and the United States, the company implements a number of green projects and has plans to develop data centers in Switzerland and the U.S.Tron believes that coal, oil and gas constituents will gradually be outed from the energy consumed by miners. A similar opinion has been voiced by Coin Metrics co-founder Nick Carter, who has high hopes about the use of energy from flare gas in bitcoin mining; he believes this type of fuel can completely cover the needs of all miners worldwide inside the next 10 years. Crypto analysts' predictions regarding the development of alternative sources are backed by energy experts.A new report from a global energy think tank Ember emphasizes that the global energy system will very shortly enter a &ldquo;new era of reduction of fossil fuel production&rdquo;. Gas and coal generation volumes are expected to decrease, with alternative sources in extensive use.Ember's findings note that at the end of 2022, the expansion of wind and solar power accounted for 80% of the growth in electricity demand, and when combined with hydropower and bioenergy, 92% of the growth. By the end of 2023, low-carbon sources are expected to provide 100% of the growth in energy demand. Analysts provide an interesting example: the solar power plants launched worldwide last year would be powerful enough to supply an entire country like South Africa for a year, and wind power plants would provide almost the entire 12-month supply for the United Kingdom.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>"The price/quality principle will be always at work. Miners will do everything to reduce their costs, and increase their income from cryptocurrency mining, while preventing methane emissions and being environmentally conscious along the way. This, in my opinion, is worth the support of local authorities in different regions. For example, by tax incentives or other means," says financial analyst Vladyslav Kravets.</p>

<p>Particular interest in "green" mining is growing in the U.S. Local Marathon Digital Holdings launched the King Mountain data center in Texas, with a capacity of 280 MW, carbon-neutral by 70%. In addition, this spring the company announced a joint project with Zero Two, designed to construct two new 200 MW and 50 MW zero-carbon sites in the UAE (Abu Dhabi). Also, BIT Mining Limited reported building a 57.2 MW facility in the same state, running by 85% on clean energy.</p>
<p></p>
<p>This does not come as a surprise, since the Americans have been growing generally more interested in cryptocurrency as of late. The bigger it is, the greater the interest of local miners in more environmentally friendly and cheaper crypto mining. The analytics service Ahrefs recently estimated that the word "Bitcoin" has been looked up 1.9 million times in Google search in the U.S. over the past 12 months. It topped the search ranking, coming before the scandalous former president Donald Trump, news, Elvis Presley, Disney and Spider-Man.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>"For years, Texas was considered the home of the American shale gas and oil revolution, but it has now become the go-to place for cryptocurrency miners. Miners have realized that energy from flare gas can be used profitably to mine crypto. Our company is using it already. Also, this way we significantly reduce CO2 emissions. Around 400 million tons of carbon dioxide make their way to the atmosphere annually, but the crypto community can reduce this figure significantly," assures Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>There is no doubt that the miners&rsquo; interest in green energy will grow as the interest in cryptocurrencies as such multiplies. This process is gradually spreading around the world, although not always in transparent ways.For example, in May, during the bankruptcy of BlockFi and Celsius, it was revealed that Druk Holding &amp; Investments (DHI), a state-owned investment bank in the Asian Kingdom of Bhutan, was secretly (without public knowledge) mining bitcoin. This country employs hydropower, with natural availability of high-altitude mountains with fresh air that allow cooling down the equipment. Mining is carbon-neutral and, as DHI assures, self-sustaining.The interest in cryptocurrencies is increased in the Seychelles, and local Finance Minister Naadir Hassan stated in April that his government is working out the requirements for the registration and licensing of specialized companies. Also, state authorities in Europe's Liechtenstein have recently declared they&rsquo;re going to allow their citizens to use bitcoin to pay for public services. Although the head of the government, Daniel Risch, did not specify when such a possibility was to come in effect, but was adamant that it eventually would.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Regardless of what goes on in the crypto market and no matter what skeptics say about this industry, the interest for it does not decrease. Even after significant price swings of several coins and frightening statements about the crypto-winter. Steady focus of the investors and hi-tech companies is backed not only by the projects that&rsquo;s been already greenlit, but with new developments, ideas and discussions that do not stop. At the end of May, for instance, active debates on the future development of the market and its prospects took place in the United States, at the Bitcoin Miami conference.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Rather interesting and large-scale event, which was helpful not for professional players alone, but for the curious newcomers as well. Highly-esteemed and acknowledged experts were represented at the event: Christopher Grilhault des Fontaines from Dfns, Joseph Ziolkowski from Relm Insurance, Domenic Carosa from Banxa and many others. Not only current problems were discussed, but some new developments, including those in the space industry, were spoken of openly, too. Quite gripping and productive. Once again, we were able to make sure that Bitcoin remains a powerful asset, and amid the challenging situation in the global economy and growing rates of inflation everywhere, attention and trust to Bitcoin is on the steady rise&rdquo;, summed up Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the coming years, the tone of the cryptocurrency market will be set by environmental projects, which will be increasingly used for mining around the world. New technologies and developments will be implemented in different parts of the world. And maybe even in outer space - such ideas and proposals already exist and are being discussed within the professional community. Interesting discussions took place at the Bitcoin Miami conference in the USA at the end of May.</p>
<p>Bitcoin mining was one of the key topics in the latest report by Messari, a leader in cryptocurrency market research and analysis. The authors believe that the green agenda will increasingly dominate in this field, and it will be the driving force of the industry in the years to come.On the one hand, environmental friendliness will grow into an actual trend, and crypto enthusiasts will adhere to ESG (Environmental, Social, Governance) Investing approach - environmental, social, governance aspects of investing. On the other hand, this trend will be supported by economic considerations, and the high cost of energy. As for this point, Messari analytics highlights a very indicative example for Bitcoin mining cost: in 2021, the mining of 1 bitcoin cost American miners in Texas about $5-10 thousand, and the coin itself was trading at around $50-60 thousand; its value went down in 2022, and the best price was estimated at $20 thousand with $15-20 thousand of mining cost.</p>
<p></p>
Serhiy Tron, Owner of White Rock Management, speaking at the Bitcoin 2023 conference
<p>As the coins value decreased, miners actively went looking for ways to reduce their energy costs. First of all, by making mining more environmentally friendly. The interest in hydroelectric power and electricity generation by flaring gas, byproduct of oil production, has grown tremendously. The latter technology not only provides cheaper energy for cryptocurrency mining, but also significantly reduces carbon dioxide emissions into the atmosphere. Reduction of the negative impact of mining on the environment.</p>
<p></p>

<p>"Being environmentally friendly is not just a fashion trend, but an economically profitable direction for mining. In some regions, the share of renewable energy in this field amounts to 40%, and even exceeds 70% in other regions. I think that interest will keep on growing, and global oil and gas corporations will cooperate more actively with the cryptocurrency industry. For example, our company has various projects in the U.S. underway: gas flaring in Texas and hydropower near Niagara Falls in the state of New York," said the founder of one of the world's largest mining companies, White Rock Management, Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>White Rock Management, along with 250 other companies, has joined the Crypto Climate Accord for environmentally friendly and safe cryptocurrency mining. With operating offices in Canada, Sweden, Kazakhstan and the United States, the company implements a number of green projects and has plans to develop data centers in Switzerland and the U.S.Tron believes that coal, oil and gas constituents will gradually be outed from the energy consumed by miners. A similar opinion has been voiced by Coin Metrics co-founder Nick Carter, who has high hopes about the use of energy from flare gas in bitcoin mining; he believes this type of fuel can completely cover the needs of all miners worldwide inside the next 10 years. Crypto analysts' predictions regarding the development of alternative sources are backed by energy experts.A new report from a global energy think tank Ember emphasizes that the global energy system will very shortly enter a &ldquo;new era of reduction of fossil fuel production&rdquo;. Gas and coal generation volumes are expected to decrease, with alternative sources in extensive use.Ember's findings note that at the end of 2022, the expansion of wind and solar power accounted for 80% of the growth in electricity demand, and when combined with hydropower and bioenergy, 92% of the growth. By the end of 2023, low-carbon sources are expected to provide 100% of the growth in energy demand. Analysts provide an interesting example: the solar power plants launched worldwide last year would be powerful enough to supply an entire country like South Africa for a year, and wind power plants would provide almost the entire 12-month supply for the United Kingdom.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>"The price/quality principle will be always at work. Miners will do everything to reduce their costs, and increase their income from cryptocurrency mining, while preventing methane emissions and being environmentally conscious along the way. This, in my opinion, is worth the support of local authorities in different regions. For example, by tax incentives or other means," says financial analyst Vladyslav Kravets.</p>

<p>Particular interest in "green" mining is growing in the U.S. Local Marathon Digital Holdings launched the King Mountain data center in Texas, with a capacity of 280 MW, carbon-neutral by 70%. In addition, this spring the company announced a joint project with Zero Two, designed to construct two new 200 MW and 50 MW zero-carbon sites in the UAE (Abu Dhabi). Also, BIT Mining Limited reported building a 57.2 MW facility in the same state, running by 85% on clean energy.</p>
<p></p>
<p>This does not come as a surprise, since the Americans have been growing generally more interested in cryptocurrency as of late. The bigger it is, the greater the interest of local miners in more environmentally friendly and cheaper crypto mining. The analytics service Ahrefs recently estimated that the word "Bitcoin" has been looked up 1.9 million times in Google search in the U.S. over the past 12 months. It topped the search ranking, coming before the scandalous former president Donald Trump, news, Elvis Presley, Disney and Spider-Man.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>"For years, Texas was considered the home of the American shale gas and oil revolution, but it has now become the go-to place for cryptocurrency miners. Miners have realized that energy from flare gas can be used profitably to mine crypto. Our company is using it already. Also, this way we significantly reduce CO2 emissions. Around 400 million tons of carbon dioxide make their way to the atmosphere annually, but the crypto community can reduce this figure significantly," assures Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>There is no doubt that the miners&rsquo; interest in green energy will grow as the interest in cryptocurrencies as such multiplies. This process is gradually spreading around the world, although not always in transparent ways.For example, in May, during the bankruptcy of BlockFi and Celsius, it was revealed that Druk Holding &amp; Investments (DHI), a state-owned investment bank in the Asian Kingdom of Bhutan, was secretly (without public knowledge) mining bitcoin. This country employs hydropower, with natural availability of high-altitude mountains with fresh air that allow cooling down the equipment. Mining is carbon-neutral and, as DHI assures, self-sustaining.The interest in cryptocurrencies is increased in the Seychelles, and local Finance Minister Naadir Hassan stated in April that his government is working out the requirements for the registration and licensing of specialized companies. Also, state authorities in Europe's Liechtenstein have recently declared they&rsquo;re going to allow their citizens to use bitcoin to pay for public services. Although the head of the government, Daniel Risch, did not specify when such a possibility was to come in effect, but was adamant that it eventually would.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Regardless of what goes on in the crypto market and no matter what skeptics say about this industry, the interest for it does not decrease. Even after significant price swings of several coins and frightening statements about the crypto-winter. Steady focus of the investors and hi-tech companies is backed not only by the projects that&rsquo;s been already greenlit, but with new developments, ideas and discussions that do not stop. At the end of May, for instance, active debates on the future development of the market and its prospects took place in the United States, at the Bitcoin Miami conference.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Rather interesting and large-scale event, which was helpful not for professional players alone, but for the curious newcomers as well. Highly-esteemed and acknowledged experts were represented at the event: Christopher Grilhault des Fontaines from Dfns, Joseph Ziolkowski from Relm Insurance, Domenic Carosa from Banxa and many others. Not only current problems were discussed, but some new developments, including those in the space industry, were spoken of openly, too. Quite gripping and productive. Once again, we were able to make sure that Bitcoin remains a powerful asset, and amid the challenging situation in the global economy and growing rates of inflation everywhere, attention and trust to Bitcoin is on the steady rise&rdquo;, summed up Serhiy Tron.</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the 12 winners of the 2023 CryptoDaily™ Awards]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/celebrating-the-12-winners-of-the-2023-cryptodaily-awards</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/artboard-1-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/artboard-1-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/artboard-1-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/celebrating-the-12-winners-of-the-2023-cryptodaily-awards</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>CryptoDaily&trade;&nbsp;is thrilled to announce the winners of our annual international award for daring Web3 builders and popularizers. Between May 22nd and June 5th, the expert jury reviewed dozens of stars that were shining in the industry throughout the past year, recognizing honorees across 4 categories: Entrepreneurship, Development, Design, and Marketing &amp; PR.</p>
<p>Driven by the genuine belief that the community should acknowledge its heroes, we established&nbsp;CryptoDaily&trade; Awards in 2022 to reward the most outstanding talents based on their merits. They all contributed to the Web3 ecosystem in many ways, from significantly improving its infrastructure and user experience to amplifying the Web3 business sector and promoting decentralized applications to the mass population.</p>
<p>While the main goal of CryptoDaily&trade; Awards remained the same, we brought a couple of novelties to the evaluation process. So, before we proceed with disclosing this year&rsquo;s results, let us first introduce you to the changes made. &nbsp;</p>
Panel of Judges
<p>To highlight the Web3&rsquo;s best and brightest minds of 2023, we invited the Fantastic Four team of subject matter judges, each contributing to the long-term trends in their own focus area throughout a year. We have thoughtfully chosen the jury members among 20 candidates for each category, paying special attention to their in-depth knowledge of the industry, multi-faceted activity, and remarkable individual achievements.</p>
<p>Some of them have promoted dozens of new millionaire businesses for the Web3 and blockchain era. Others have traversed the severe crypto market turmoil of 2022 with honor, and still others have proved that they were rightly praised by the previous&nbsp;CryptoDaily&trade; Awards.</p>
So let us dive straight into the list without further ado.
<p></p>
Entrepreneurship
<p>Jo&atilde;o Fouad, a disruptive entrepreneur specializing in Web3, finance, investments, and the startup ecosystem; an international speaker and entrepreneurial mentor; CEO and founder of Highline Venture Builder.</p>
<p></p>
Development
<p>Kirill Arutyunov, a professional software engineer and developer with over 10 years of experience in Web3, fintech, and edtech; a seasoned entrepreneur and C-level executive; CTO of M&uuml;nzen.</p>
<p></p>
Design
<p>Valery Lebedenko, an internationally acclaimed UX/UI designer for Web3, crypto and blockchain&nbsp;projects; an expert blogger, columnist, and judge at Web3 hackathons; the 2022 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards winner.</p>
<p></p>
Marketing &amp; PR
<p>Mike Ermolaev, a recognized crypto journalist and PR specialist; author of the signature series &ldquo;Crypto Opinion with Mike Ermolaev&rdquo; for Benzinga.com; market analyst for Cointelegraph Brazil; founder of Outset PR agency.</p>
<p></p>
Honorable Jury&rsquo;s Member
<p>Cal Evans,&nbsp;a Managing Associate of Gresham International - the world&rsquo;s largest Digital Asset only legal service and law firm; headliner of several large events alongside people such as Gary Vee and Nick Spanos.</p>
Renewed Methodology
<p>This year, the focus of the award was slightly shifted towards showcasing Web3's famous personalities and rising superstars who stood out with brilliant results and dynamic development. Our jury leveraged their professional outlook to make decisions, following a numerical and quantitative methodology with specific weighting given to:</p>
<ul class="lst-kix_i1vygxemccds-0 start">
<li>Evidence of leading the development and delivery of cutting-edge Web3 projects;</li>
<li>Evidence of engagement with the business to drive Web3 adoption;</li>
<li>Evidence of skill set growth and personal accomplishments;</li>
<li>Evidence of exceptional leadership and excellence in the field;</li>
<li>Evidence of results implemented because of the honoree's work;</li>
<li>Demonstrable enthusiasm for and creativity in Web3.</li>
</ul>
<p>All judges had two weeks to carefully evaluate more than 50 most ambitious Web3 innovators in their respective categories. Adhering strongly to the award&rsquo;s criteria, each jury member finally came up with two winners, presenting them as:</p>
<ul class="lst-kix_vwxb9fh82j84-0 start">
<li>Jury&rsquo;s choice&nbsp;&ndash; unrivaled gainers whose individual performance is the most worthy by all criteria;</li>
<li>Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick&nbsp;&ndash; those who were one step away from the Jury&rsquo;s choice but couldn't outperform the winners. &nbsp; &nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>In order to prolong the pleasure, CryptoDaily&trade; decided not to depart from participation in the assessment of nominees. The judges had final say, but we gave an opportunity to enjoy the celebration to our 4 personal favorites, rewarding them with a very special honorable mention&nbsp;&ndash; the prestiges title from CryptoDaily&trade; editorial board.</p>
Winners
<p>And now, when all the formalities are met, it&rsquo;s time to pull back the curtain &ndash; we are ready to reveal the official results of the 2023 from CryptoDaily&trade; editorial board.</p>
Entrepreneurship
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Drew Beechler, CEO and founder of Holder
<p></p>
<p>Drew Beechler&nbsp;has won the Jury&rsquo;s choice prize due to the launch of Holder, a revolutional CRM and marketing automation platform, in April 2022. The company helps NFT projects and Web3 businesses to align their products with customer needs and engage with their audiences in a more meaningful way. Before starting Holder, Beechler, a career brand and marketing leader with a huge love for decentralized tech, startups, and data-driven marketing, has helped to co-found 30+ B2B SaaS startups in 7 years as the CEO of the High Alpha venture capital firm with over $200 million in AUM. &nbsp;</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Daniel Rose, CEO and co-founder of Doshi
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title goes to Daniel Rose&nbsp;who is a passionate company builder holding leadership roles in strategy and product development, data-driven experimentation, and operations. As the CEO of Doshi, a crypto wallet designed for teenagers, Daniel combines his commercial skills in technology and gamification with a purpose-led mission to establish greater financial confidence for next-gen investors, making learning about Web3 and blockchain easy, engaging, and relevant. Before he started Doshi, Rose was a full-time crypto trader and worked as an innovation consultant for IKEA and King Games.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention &ndash; Andr&eacute;s Soltermann, co-founder of Grizzly.fi
<p></p>
<p>We decided to assign our honorable mention to Andr&eacute;s Soltermann, the long-term crypto enthusiast and the frontman of Grizzly.fi, a sensational startup that aims to create the DeFi 2.0 platform and revolutionize token launches. Soltermann is an early adopter of DeFi, fueled by the desire to make it accessible for everyone. At Grizzly.fi, Andr&eacute;s is responsible for the innovations and technical developments that brought his project to the list of top hits on Product Hunt. Apart from that, Soltermann contributes to the governance of $DCHF, a decentralized stablecoin pegged to the Swiss Franc and backed by Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
Development
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Magomed Aliev, chief developer and founder of the Gravix&nbsp;derivatives exchange
<p></p>
<p>Magomed Aliev&nbsp;was awarded with the Jury&rsquo;s choice prize as a Web3 engineer and TVM developer. A graduate of the elite Higher School of Economics specializing in machine learning and data science, Aliev has since become one of the foundational developers of the Venom Bridge&nbsp;and the Octus Bridge. He made major contributions to all key ecosystem applications in the Venom and Everscale networks, including DEXs, scanners, Venom Stake, portfolio analyzers, and Snipa.finance. Additionally, Magomed developed Locklift, the contract writing framework used to write all Venom applications.</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Illia Polosukhin, cutting-edge software engineer, co-founder of NEAR Protocol
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title was given to Illia Polosukhin, the co-founder of NEAR Protocol&nbsp;that is currently evolving from a L1 blockchain for creating smart contracts to the full-fledged Blockchain Operating System (BOS) for Web3. This revolution is powered by Pagoda, a vertical in the NEAR ecosystem formerly known as Near Inc. With BOS, Polosukhin&rsquo;s goal is to build an open web world where developers can easily create new experiences, while end users can control their assets, data, content, and power of governance. Illia has also been engaged in sharing his wealth of knowledge as the speaker of numerous Web3 and blockchain conferences.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade;&nbsp;honorable mention &ndash; Anton Bukov, forward-thinking blockchain developer and engineer, co-founder of 1inch Network
<p></p>
<p>The CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention goes to Anton Bukov&nbsp;who elevates the potential of 1inch Network, the platform ensuring the most lucrative, fastest and protected DeFi operations. Due to his efforts, the company recorded a notable growth across its protocols, with the total number of users approaching 2.6 million. For 7 years in blockchain development, Bukov has achieved strong C++ skills, working deep with a network stack of protocols, algorithms, compilers, disassemblers, and profilers. Today Anton is actively exploring DeFi, GameFi, NFTs, P2E, the metaverse, and consensus problem solutions for crypto projects.</p>
Design
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Rahul Singh Bhadoriya, a Web3 designer collaborating with multiple trending projects
<p></p>
<p>An ex-design project manager at Polygon, Rahul Singh Bhadoriya&nbsp;is this year&rsquo;s Jury&rsquo;s choice winner. As a self-taught designer, Rahul also dedicated himself to supporting other self-learning designers by sharing his knowledge at subject matter conferences and showcasing his work on his personal website and social media. Bhadoriya was Polygon&rsquo;s brand identity and experience designer from May 2022 to February 2023, expanding the attractiveness of the blockchain ecosystem with top-notch UX and UI. Since then, he has been engaged in building several Web3 projects such as Wagmipedia, Notific, Superteam, and Makerdock. &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Patrick N. Lewis, head of design at Floor
<p></p>
<p>Welcome Patrick N. Lewis&nbsp;as the Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick honoree. As the lead designer for the ground-breaking Floor&nbsp;app, his mission is to create a more equitable future for Web3 and make NFTs easy-to-understand. Lewis is also the founding designer of LinksDAO, a Web3-oriented project building the world&rsquo;s best golf club. Earlier in his career, Patrick acted as the first design hire and second employee at Button where he participated in developing products, design systems, and identity. His portfolio features commerce products for Uber, Amazon, and dozens of the world&rsquo;s top companies.</p>
Crypto Daily&rsquo;s honorable mention &ndash; Rob Sven&scaron;ek, product designer at Sismo
<p></p>
<p>Our next honorable mention is for Rob Sven&scaron;ek, Web3 product designer from Ljubljana. With his &ldquo;strategic and pragmatic, yet playful and expressive&rdquo; approach to design, Sven&scaron;ek is currently creating functional and aesthetic relevant UX/UI solutions that bring value to Sismo, a breakthrough communication protocol enabling users to aggregate and selectively disclose personal data to applications. Prior to that, Rob was the lead product designer at Niftify, a buzzing no-code NFT store builder for businesses. His works are visually strong, with great emphasis put on usability and character.</p>
Marketing &amp; PR
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Serge Baloyan, founder of X10 marketing agency
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s choice fell on Serge Baloyan&nbsp;who&rsquo;s standing at the helm of X10 Agency, one of the most reputable and influential crypto and NFT marketing service providers in the industry. He has garnered significant attention over the past year due to catering over 150 projects as a recognized expert in his field. Baloyan's insightful predictions and deep industry knowledge enable him to participate in global conferences as a keynote speaker, popularizing the future of blockchain and demonstrating his commitment to innovation that has already made a lasting impact in the crypto world.</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash;&nbsp;Nicola Da Dalto, digital marketing manager at Exclusible
<p></p>
<p>Meet Nicola Da Dalto, awarded with the Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title. The Web3 projects Nicola works with have become the latest talk of the town in the NFT and Metaverse sector due to his creative marketing approach. As of today, Da Dalto is responsible for the management and implementation of digital marketing strategies at Exclusible, a one-stop platform and marketing agency that helps both individuals and businesses to successfully navigate the world of digital assets. Nicola is also recognized for his role as CMO and co-founder of Cryptoverse, a Web3 agency that brings brands to the Metaverse.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention &ndash; Maria Isabel F&eacute;lix de Matos, head of marketing on blockchain projects
<p></p>
<p>The last but not least honorable mention from CryptoDaily&trade; goes to Maria Isabel F&eacute;lix de Matos&nbsp;who has been the head of community at the WYTLAND gaming &amp; AI studio since December 2022. Thanks to her efforts, the company has built a reputation for being accessible and responsive and has earned the trust and loyalty of its community members. Maria keeps onboarding users to the possibilities of Web3 for the travel industry, while also representing WYTLAND in the metaverse. As a result-driven marketer, she believes in the power of storytelling and defines her biggest value as being empathic.</p>
Looking Forward to the 2024 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards
<p>We would like to express a sincere gratitude to our expert judges whose participation has made the 2023 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards possible. And of course, a heartfelt thank you to all of the talented builders who keep shaping our common future. We believe that each honoree should be incredibly proud of what they&rsquo;ve accomplished and will continue to demonstrate exciting performance throughout their professional journeys.</p>
<p>We can&rsquo;t wait to celebrate another wave of trailblazers through the next Crypto Daily Awards, from entrepreneurs and developers whose careers in Web3 are resounding success to designers and marketers with outside-the-box thinking.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s do it again in 2024 and see who will earn a standing ovation!</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CryptoDaily&trade;&nbsp;is thrilled to announce the winners of our annual international award for daring Web3 builders and popularizers. Between May 22nd and June 5th, the expert jury reviewed dozens of stars that were shining in the industry throughout the past year, recognizing honorees across 4 categories: Entrepreneurship, Development, Design, and Marketing &amp; PR.</p>
<p>Driven by the genuine belief that the community should acknowledge its heroes, we established&nbsp;CryptoDaily&trade; Awards in 2022 to reward the most outstanding talents based on their merits. They all contributed to the Web3 ecosystem in many ways, from significantly improving its infrastructure and user experience to amplifying the Web3 business sector and promoting decentralized applications to the mass population.</p>
<p>While the main goal of CryptoDaily&trade; Awards remained the same, we brought a couple of novelties to the evaluation process. So, before we proceed with disclosing this year&rsquo;s results, let us first introduce you to the changes made. &nbsp;</p>
Panel of Judges
<p>To highlight the Web3&rsquo;s best and brightest minds of 2023, we invited the Fantastic Four team of subject matter judges, each contributing to the long-term trends in their own focus area throughout a year. We have thoughtfully chosen the jury members among 20 candidates for each category, paying special attention to their in-depth knowledge of the industry, multi-faceted activity, and remarkable individual achievements.</p>
<p>Some of them have promoted dozens of new millionaire businesses for the Web3 and blockchain era. Others have traversed the severe crypto market turmoil of 2022 with honor, and still others have proved that they were rightly praised by the previous&nbsp;CryptoDaily&trade; Awards.</p>
So let us dive straight into the list without further ado.
<p></p>
Entrepreneurship
<p>Jo&atilde;o Fouad, a disruptive entrepreneur specializing in Web3, finance, investments, and the startup ecosystem; an international speaker and entrepreneurial mentor; CEO and founder of Highline Venture Builder.</p>
<p></p>
Development
<p>Kirill Arutyunov, a professional software engineer and developer with over 10 years of experience in Web3, fintech, and edtech; a seasoned entrepreneur and C-level executive; CTO of M&uuml;nzen.</p>
<p></p>
Design
<p>Valery Lebedenko, an internationally acclaimed UX/UI designer for Web3, crypto and blockchain&nbsp;projects; an expert blogger, columnist, and judge at Web3 hackathons; the 2022 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards winner.</p>
<p></p>
Marketing &amp; PR
<p>Mike Ermolaev, a recognized crypto journalist and PR specialist; author of the signature series &ldquo;Crypto Opinion with Mike Ermolaev&rdquo; for Benzinga.com; market analyst for Cointelegraph Brazil; founder of Outset PR agency.</p>
<p></p>
Honorable Jury&rsquo;s Member
<p>Cal Evans,&nbsp;a Managing Associate of Gresham International - the world&rsquo;s largest Digital Asset only legal service and law firm; headliner of several large events alongside people such as Gary Vee and Nick Spanos.</p>
Renewed Methodology
<p>This year, the focus of the award was slightly shifted towards showcasing Web3's famous personalities and rising superstars who stood out with brilliant results and dynamic development. Our jury leveraged their professional outlook to make decisions, following a numerical and quantitative methodology with specific weighting given to:</p>
<ul class="lst-kix_i1vygxemccds-0 start">
<li>Evidence of leading the development and delivery of cutting-edge Web3 projects;</li>
<li>Evidence of engagement with the business to drive Web3 adoption;</li>
<li>Evidence of skill set growth and personal accomplishments;</li>
<li>Evidence of exceptional leadership and excellence in the field;</li>
<li>Evidence of results implemented because of the honoree's work;</li>
<li>Demonstrable enthusiasm for and creativity in Web3.</li>
</ul>
<p>All judges had two weeks to carefully evaluate more than 50 most ambitious Web3 innovators in their respective categories. Adhering strongly to the award&rsquo;s criteria, each jury member finally came up with two winners, presenting them as:</p>
<ul class="lst-kix_vwxb9fh82j84-0 start">
<li>Jury&rsquo;s choice&nbsp;&ndash; unrivaled gainers whose individual performance is the most worthy by all criteria;</li>
<li>Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick&nbsp;&ndash; those who were one step away from the Jury&rsquo;s choice but couldn't outperform the winners. &nbsp; &nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p>In order to prolong the pleasure, CryptoDaily&trade; decided not to depart from participation in the assessment of nominees. The judges had final say, but we gave an opportunity to enjoy the celebration to our 4 personal favorites, rewarding them with a very special honorable mention&nbsp;&ndash; the prestiges title from CryptoDaily&trade; editorial board.</p>
Winners
<p>And now, when all the formalities are met, it&rsquo;s time to pull back the curtain &ndash; we are ready to reveal the official results of the 2023 from CryptoDaily&trade; editorial board.</p>
Entrepreneurship
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Drew Beechler, CEO and founder of Holder
<p></p>
<p>Drew Beechler&nbsp;has won the Jury&rsquo;s choice prize due to the launch of Holder, a revolutional CRM and marketing automation platform, in April 2022. The company helps NFT projects and Web3 businesses to align their products with customer needs and engage with their audiences in a more meaningful way. Before starting Holder, Beechler, a career brand and marketing leader with a huge love for decentralized tech, startups, and data-driven marketing, has helped to co-found 30+ B2B SaaS startups in 7 years as the CEO of the High Alpha venture capital firm with over $200 million in AUM. &nbsp;</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Daniel Rose, CEO and co-founder of Doshi
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title goes to Daniel Rose&nbsp;who is a passionate company builder holding leadership roles in strategy and product development, data-driven experimentation, and operations. As the CEO of Doshi, a crypto wallet designed for teenagers, Daniel combines his commercial skills in technology and gamification with a purpose-led mission to establish greater financial confidence for next-gen investors, making learning about Web3 and blockchain easy, engaging, and relevant. Before he started Doshi, Rose was a full-time crypto trader and worked as an innovation consultant for IKEA and King Games.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention &ndash; Andr&eacute;s Soltermann, co-founder of Grizzly.fi
<p></p>
<p>We decided to assign our honorable mention to Andr&eacute;s Soltermann, the long-term crypto enthusiast and the frontman of Grizzly.fi, a sensational startup that aims to create the DeFi 2.0 platform and revolutionize token launches. Soltermann is an early adopter of DeFi, fueled by the desire to make it accessible for everyone. At Grizzly.fi, Andr&eacute;s is responsible for the innovations and technical developments that brought his project to the list of top hits on Product Hunt. Apart from that, Soltermann contributes to the governance of $DCHF, a decentralized stablecoin pegged to the Swiss Franc and backed by Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
Development
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Magomed Aliev, chief developer and founder of the Gravix&nbsp;derivatives exchange
<p></p>
<p>Magomed Aliev&nbsp;was awarded with the Jury&rsquo;s choice prize as a Web3 engineer and TVM developer. A graduate of the elite Higher School of Economics specializing in machine learning and data science, Aliev has since become one of the foundational developers of the Venom Bridge&nbsp;and the Octus Bridge. He made major contributions to all key ecosystem applications in the Venom and Everscale networks, including DEXs, scanners, Venom Stake, portfolio analyzers, and Snipa.finance. Additionally, Magomed developed Locklift, the contract writing framework used to write all Venom applications.</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Illia Polosukhin, cutting-edge software engineer, co-founder of NEAR Protocol
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title was given to Illia Polosukhin, the co-founder of NEAR Protocol&nbsp;that is currently evolving from a L1 blockchain for creating smart contracts to the full-fledged Blockchain Operating System (BOS) for Web3. This revolution is powered by Pagoda, a vertical in the NEAR ecosystem formerly known as Near Inc. With BOS, Polosukhin&rsquo;s goal is to build an open web world where developers can easily create new experiences, while end users can control their assets, data, content, and power of governance. Illia has also been engaged in sharing his wealth of knowledge as the speaker of numerous Web3 and blockchain conferences.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade;&nbsp;honorable mention &ndash; Anton Bukov, forward-thinking blockchain developer and engineer, co-founder of 1inch Network
<p></p>
<p>The CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention goes to Anton Bukov&nbsp;who elevates the potential of 1inch Network, the platform ensuring the most lucrative, fastest and protected DeFi operations. Due to his efforts, the company recorded a notable growth across its protocols, with the total number of users approaching 2.6 million. For 7 years in blockchain development, Bukov has achieved strong C++ skills, working deep with a network stack of protocols, algorithms, compilers, disassemblers, and profilers. Today Anton is actively exploring DeFi, GameFi, NFTs, P2E, the metaverse, and consensus problem solutions for crypto projects.</p>
Design
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Rahul Singh Bhadoriya, a Web3 designer collaborating with multiple trending projects
<p></p>
<p>An ex-design project manager at Polygon, Rahul Singh Bhadoriya&nbsp;is this year&rsquo;s Jury&rsquo;s choice winner. As a self-taught designer, Rahul also dedicated himself to supporting other self-learning designers by sharing his knowledge at subject matter conferences and showcasing his work on his personal website and social media. Bhadoriya was Polygon&rsquo;s brand identity and experience designer from May 2022 to February 2023, expanding the attractiveness of the blockchain ecosystem with top-notch UX and UI. Since then, he has been engaged in building several Web3 projects such as Wagmipedia, Notific, Superteam, and Makerdock. &nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash; Patrick N. Lewis, head of design at Floor
<p></p>
<p>Welcome Patrick N. Lewis&nbsp;as the Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick honoree. As the lead designer for the ground-breaking Floor&nbsp;app, his mission is to create a more equitable future for Web3 and make NFTs easy-to-understand. Lewis is also the founding designer of LinksDAO, a Web3-oriented project building the world&rsquo;s best golf club. Earlier in his career, Patrick acted as the first design hire and second employee at Button where he participated in developing products, design systems, and identity. His portfolio features commerce products for Uber, Amazon, and dozens of the world&rsquo;s top companies.</p>
Crypto Daily&rsquo;s honorable mention &ndash; Rob Sven&scaron;ek, product designer at Sismo
<p></p>
<p>Our next honorable mention is for Rob Sven&scaron;ek, Web3 product designer from Ljubljana. With his &ldquo;strategic and pragmatic, yet playful and expressive&rdquo; approach to design, Sven&scaron;ek is currently creating functional and aesthetic relevant UX/UI solutions that bring value to Sismo, a breakthrough communication protocol enabling users to aggregate and selectively disclose personal data to applications. Prior to that, Rob was the lead product designer at Niftify, a buzzing no-code NFT store builder for businesses. His works are visually strong, with great emphasis put on usability and character.</p>
Marketing &amp; PR
Jury&rsquo;s choice &ndash; Serge Baloyan, founder of X10 marketing agency
<p></p>
<p>The Jury&rsquo;s choice fell on Serge Baloyan&nbsp;who&rsquo;s standing at the helm of X10 Agency, one of the most reputable and influential crypto and NFT marketing service providers in the industry. He has garnered significant attention over the past year due to catering over 150 projects as a recognized expert in his field. Baloyan's insightful predictions and deep industry knowledge enable him to participate in global conferences as a keynote speaker, popularizing the future of blockchain and demonstrating his commitment to innovation that has already made a lasting impact in the crypto world.</p>
Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick &ndash;&nbsp;Nicola Da Dalto, digital marketing manager at Exclusible
<p></p>
<p>Meet Nicola Da Dalto, awarded with the Jury&rsquo;s runner-up pick title. The Web3 projects Nicola works with have become the latest talk of the town in the NFT and Metaverse sector due to his creative marketing approach. As of today, Da Dalto is responsible for the management and implementation of digital marketing strategies at Exclusible, a one-stop platform and marketing agency that helps both individuals and businesses to successfully navigate the world of digital assets. Nicola is also recognized for his role as CMO and co-founder of Cryptoverse, a Web3 agency that brings brands to the Metaverse.</p>
CryptoDaily&trade; honorable mention &ndash; Maria Isabel F&eacute;lix de Matos, head of marketing on blockchain projects
<p></p>
<p>The last but not least honorable mention from CryptoDaily&trade; goes to Maria Isabel F&eacute;lix de Matos&nbsp;who has been the head of community at the WYTLAND gaming &amp; AI studio since December 2022. Thanks to her efforts, the company has built a reputation for being accessible and responsive and has earned the trust and loyalty of its community members. Maria keeps onboarding users to the possibilities of Web3 for the travel industry, while also representing WYTLAND in the metaverse. As a result-driven marketer, she believes in the power of storytelling and defines her biggest value as being empathic.</p>
Looking Forward to the 2024 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards
<p>We would like to express a sincere gratitude to our expert judges whose participation has made the 2023 CryptoDaily&trade; Awards possible. And of course, a heartfelt thank you to all of the talented builders who keep shaping our common future. We believe that each honoree should be incredibly proud of what they&rsquo;ve accomplished and will continue to demonstrate exciting performance throughout their professional journeys.</p>
<p>We can&rsquo;t wait to celebrate another wave of trailblazers through the next Crypto Daily Awards, from entrepreneurs and developers whose careers in Web3 are resounding success to designers and marketers with outside-the-box thinking.</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s do it again in 2024 and see who will earn a standing ovation!</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
