<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 18:31:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SSV Network DAO Launches $50 Million Ecosystem Fund </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ssv-network-dao-launches-50-million-ecosystem-fund/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake (PoS)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233977</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Crypto_Funding.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Crypto_Funding.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The project plans to dedicate the new capital to the DVT use cases.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Open source and decentralized protocol ssv.network DAO has launched a $50 million Ecosystem Fund dedicated to supporting the development of Distributed Validator Technology (&#8220;DVT&#8221;) based applications.</p>
<p class="p2">According to a press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the project secured the funds from various industry investors, including DCG, OKX, HashKey, NGC, Everstake, HackVC, GSR, Chorus.One SevenX, and 1kx.</p>
<p class="p2">ssv.network noted that the fund is the first to be dedicated solely to DVT use cases, adding that its primary purpose is to &#8220;solidify DVT as critical Ethereum infrastructure.&#8221;</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>What is DVT?</b></h2>
<p class="p2">DVT is one of the key developments in Ethereum&#8217;s roadmap. DVT is an infrastructure primitive that enables <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-tops-500000-validators-as-staking-withdrawal-deadline-approaches/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">validators&#8217;</span></a> key sharing between non-trusting parties on the Ethereum network. The technology relies on a network of nodes that operate under consensus to help generate ETH rewards for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ssv-network-bags-10m-from-dao-partners-to-scale-eth-2-0-staking/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">stakers</span></a>.</p>
<p class="p2">For larger validators, DVT provides high availability and reduces infrastructure costs while it ensures a comparable level of protection that a larger validator would have for smaller validators.</p>
<p class="p2">Commenting on the development, Alon Muroch, Core Contributor at ssv.network, said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;DVT&#8217;s aim is to distribute Ethereum&#8217;s security by offering quick and easy access to an open-source, public good which will completely change the way staking is operated today.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Muroch added that over 20 companies are already building on top of ssv.network&#8217;s DVT protocol, and that number is expected to increase with the launch of the $50 million Ecosystem Fund.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Staked ETH Surpasses 16M</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The latest development comes as the Ethereum network reaches a new milestone. According to data from <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x00000000219ab540356cbb839cbe05303d7705fa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">Etherscan</span></a>, the amount of staked ether (ETH) has grown by 18% to over 16 million since the network transitioned to a proof-of-stake (PoS) network in 2022. The staked amount represents more than 13.28% of ETH&#8217;s total supply, worth $22.42 billion.</p>
<p class="p2">However, the majority of the staked ETH is concentrated in the hands of a few players, which leaves the Ethereum network in demand for decentralizing factors like the DVT.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ssv-network-dao-launches-50-million-ecosystem-fund/" rel="nofollow">SSV Network DAO Launches $50 Million Ecosystem Fund </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Thiel&#8217;s Fund Cashed Out $1B Worth Crypto After Holding for 8 Years: FT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiels-fund-cashed-out-1b-worth-crypto-after-holding-for-8-years-ft/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233988</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/PeterThiel-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/PeterThiel-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Thiel predicted 100x gains for Bitcoin a month around the same time his fund sold its crypto holdings. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Peter Thiel has been a long-time Bitcoin backer. But his fund closing almost all its crypto positions shortly before the market went downhill did not sit well with many.</p>
<p>According to Fortune&#8217;s latest <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/01/18/peter-thiels-founders-fund-sold-crypto-just-before-markets-soured/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, Thiel&#8217;s VC firm &#8211; Founders Fund &#8211; cashed out all of its bets on cryptocurrencies and made $1.8 billion in profit while doing so.</p>
<ul>
<li>The San Francisco-based fund bought Bitcoin over eight years ago when the flagship crypto was trading under $1,000. Over the next few years, it increased its holdings substantially.</li>
<li>Speaking at the Bitcoin 2022 conference in Miami in April, Thiel continued to champion Bitcoin and called for its increased adoption. He even went on to say, &#8220;we are at the end of the fiat game regime,&#8221; while highlighting that Bitcoin was still undervalued but has the potential to replace Gold.</li>
<li>Backing Bitcoin, Theil also said that he expects the crypto&#8217;s price to increase 100-fold from its then trading value of $44,000.</li>
<li>However, the billionaire venture capitalist made no revelation about Founders Fund cashing out the previous month.</li>
<li>It is worth noting that the fund&#8217;s decision to offload its tokens was timed perfectly because Bitcoin would then see a massive plunge, even briefly falling below $16k later that year.</li>
<li>Currently, the fund does not have any significant exposure to crypto, as per FT&#8217;s sources.</li>
<li>Furthermore, the PayPal co-founder had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/i-feel-underinvested-in-bitcoi-paypal-co-founder-peter-thiel-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that he felt &#8220;underinvested&#8221; in Bitcoin just months before Founders Fund cashed out of its bets on digital assets.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiels-fund-cashed-out-1b-worth-crypto-after-holding-for-8-years-ft/" rel="nofollow">Peter Thiel&#8217;s Fund Cashed Out $1B Worth Crypto After Holding for 8 Years: FT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys and Amber Group Join List of Companies Dismissing Employees</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-and-amber-group-join-list-of-companies-dismissing-employees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 20:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MetaMask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233924</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Consensys.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Consensys.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ConsenSys will reduce its headcount by 11%, while Amber Group will supposedly halve its Hong Kong division.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ConsenSys &#8211; a blockchain software technology company &#8211; and Amber Group &#8211; a cryptocurrency platform based in Singapore &#8211; are the latest entities in the digital asset sector to announce staff layoffs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former will trim its team by approximately 11%, while the latter reportedly plans to reduce its Hong Kong division by 50%.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Adjusting to &#8216;Uncertain Market Conditions&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Joseph Lubin &#8211; CEO of ConsenSys &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://consensys.net/blog/news/consensys-focuses-its-strategy-to-ensure-future-growth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his organization made the &#8220;extremely difficult decision&#8221; to lay off 96 of its employees, or 11% of the total workforce. He outlined the current challenging macroeconomic environment (driven by surging inflation and geopolitical unrest) as the main reason for the amendments.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lubin assured that all departing individuals will receive &#8220;generous severance packages,&#8221; extension of healthcare benefits, and support with their transition to another firm. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The executive argued that the layoffs will not divert ConsenSys from its main goals: to keep developing the crypto wallet MetaMask and the Web3 API provider Infura. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We will also pursue innovative new offerings to empower developers and creators to thrive in Web3, grow Web3 commerce and DAO communities, and amplify the decentralized identity and verifiable credentials ecosystems,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lubin opined that the ongoing uncertainty could be a great opportunity for the industry to move from &#8220;outsourcing trust&#8221; to a future where decentralized systems enable individuals &#8220;to exercise control over their own digital assets.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group Dismisses More People</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The cryptocurrency platform, backed by the investment giant Temasek Holdings, will reportedly </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/tech-trends/article/3207265/cryptocurrency-firm-amber-scrambles-cut-costs-industry-battles-shock-waves-created-ftx-collapse" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lay off</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 40 Hong Kong-based employees (around 50% of that division) to endure the crypto winter. The departing members are mainly IT specialists and auditors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A person familiar with the matter informed that Amber Group moved its office from Hong Kong&#8217;s city center to a cheaper area in Causeway Bay and delayed payments to third-party vendors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group has previously stated it is &#8220;anticipating and preparing itself for an extremely conservative position so that it can go the long mile, even if it means having to go back to core business fundamentals during this period.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">2022 has been quite destructive for the platform. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/downturn-effects-amber-groups-workforce-to-see-5-10-reduction-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dismissed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 5-10% of its headcount in September and continued the spree in December. Amber Group also applied salary reductions and annulled some of its collaborations, including the one with the popular English soccer club &#8211; Chelsea FC.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The most shocking event for the company was the unexpected death of the Co-Founder &#8211; Tiantian Kullander. The 30-year-old mysteriously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-recent-wave-of-mysterious-deaths-in-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">passed away</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in his sleep in November.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The demise of FTX also harmed Amber Group&#8217;s operations. The latter assured it had no exposure to the collapsed exchange or Alameda Research, but it was an &#8220;active trading participant&#8221; in FTX. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/distressed-crypto-platform-amber-group-secures-a-300-million-fundraiser/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">secured</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a $300 million fundraiser in December and vowed to distribute the capital to clients affected by the aforementioned crash.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-and-amber-group-join-list-of-companies-dismissing-employees/" rel="nofollow">ConsenSys and Amber Group Join List of Companies Dismissing Employees</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect After Bitcoin&#8217;s Latest Bounce: Arthur Hayes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-to-expect-after-bitcoins-latest-bounce-arthur-hayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234061</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/arthur_hayes.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/arthur_hayes.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes doesn’t believe the Fed is ready to pivot quite yet, meaning Bitcoin could retrace back to its lows. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s weekly surge beyond $20,000 doesn’t necessarily mean the bull market is back, according to BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes’ latest analysis. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The former CEO recently detailed some possible scenarios that will trigger Bitcoin’s next big move – which mostly boils down to how the Federal Reserve behaves in the near term. </span></p>
<h2>Analyzing the Bitcoin Bounce</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://cryptohayes.medium.com/bouncy-castle-1b92183c61a1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">medium post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> titled “Bouncy Castle” published on Thursday, Hayes began by positing two theories about what is actually driving Bitcoin’s pump from its lows. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The first is that this is a natural bounce from its local bottom below $16,000 – in which case Bitcoin may continue trading sideways “until USD liquidity conditions improve.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Alternatively, the rally has been sparked by the Bureau of Labor Statistics’ latest CPI report, which showed annual inflation had dropped to 6.5% in December. According to Hayes’ the market may interpret the figure as a sign that the Federal Reserve will soon “pivot” away from its tight monetary policy. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Thus, market participants may be hurrying to buy crypto while its cheap, before the central bank opens its liquidity floodgates. In this case, the market will either revert to its former lows if the Fed doesn’t pivot (Scenario 2A), or continue to rally if the central bank actually does reverse course (Scenario 2B). </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Obviously, we all want to believe that we are headed toward Scenario 2B,” wrote Hayes. “That said, I think we are actually going to be facing some combination of Scenarios 1 and 2A — which is causing my itchy “Buy” trigger finger to hesitate a bit.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Central bank behavior has already proven to be a major driver behind Bitcoin’s price moves. The asset rose from $3000 to $69,000 in 2020, and 2021, when the Federal Reserve’s benchmark interest rate was at a historic low of just 0.25%. Meanwhile, the price plummeted throughout 2022 as the central bank rose that rate beyond 4% – triggering </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">mass layoffs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and multiple </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-could-file-for-bankruptcy-this-week-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">bankruptcies</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> among crypto’s biggest firms. </span></p>
<h2>Will the Fed Pivot?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hayes said he doesn’t expect the Fed to return to its covid-era monetary policy simply based on promising CPI figures. Rather chairman Jerome Powell has indicated that he “focuses on the interplay between wage growth (US hourly earnings) and core personal consumption expenditure (Core PCE). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At present, US hourly earnings are rising at roughly the same rate as inflation. That means the cost of consumer goods may continue to rise as producers keep raising prices to match those wages, giving the central bank justification to continue raising rates. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Another more plausible case for the Fed pivoting, according to Hayes, is if “part of the US credit market breaks,” creating a “meltdown across a broad swath of financial assets,” including crypto.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This scenario is less ideal because it would mean that everyone who is buying risky assets now would be in store for massive drawdowns in performance,” explained the co-founder. “2023 could be just as bad as 2022 until the Fed pivots.” </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-to-expect-after-bitcoins-latest-bounce-arthur-hayes/" rel="nofollow">What to Expect After Bitcoin&#8217;s Latest Bounce: Arthur Hayes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitKeep Expects to Compensate All Victims of $8M Exploit by March-End</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitkeep-expects-to-compensate-all-victims-of-8m-exploit-by-march-end/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233975</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BitKeep_Return.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BitKeep_Return.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The popular wallet provider had lost about $8 million worth of crypto assets. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multi-chain crypto wallet BitKeep revealed that it will launch the compensation portal in the first week of February, and 50% of the funds are expected to be returned to users by the end of the same month. The remaining funds will be distributed by the end of March.</p>
<p>To avoid fluctuation, the asset valuation of the compensation will be converted to USDT stablecoin.</p>
<ul>
<li>In a series of <a href="https://twitter.com/BitKeepOS/status/1615643114445889538" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweets</a>, BitKeep said that its technical team, as well as security agencies, devised a closed-loop verification system that included the affected users&#8217; multi-dimensional information, such as wallet addresses, stolen amounts, and token details.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Hackers never sleep-pls take good care of your assets &amp; be mindful to not trust any messages of &#8220;warm-hearted customer service&#8221; or &#8220;help you recover your assets&#8221;. BitKeep always puts the interests of users as our top priority and many thanks for your support and understanding!&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Multiple BitKeep users <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitkeep-wallet-exploited-for-8m-in-bnb-eth-usdt-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that their wallets were emptied during Christmas.</li>
<li>The preliminary investigation pointed to several APK package downloads which were hijacked by the attackers and installed with malicious code.</li>
<li>As a result, the users ended up <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitkeep-wallet-exploited-for-8m-in-bnb-eth-usdt-dai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">losing</a> roughly worth $8 million in various digital assets, BNB, ETH, USDT, and DAI.</li>
<li>BitKeep previously advised users who downloaded the trojanized APK package to transfer all their funds to the official store after downloading the official apps from Google Play or App Store.</li>
<li>This was its second attack in 2022. Just two months earlier, hackers <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hacker-drains-1m-from-bitkeep-wallet-in-swap-feature-exploit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">drained</a> $1 million in funds from Bitkeep after exploiting a vulnerability in its swap feature.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitkeep-expects-to-compensate-all-victims-of-8m-exploit-by-march-end/" rel="nofollow">BitKeep Expects to Compensate All Victims of $8M Exploit by March-End</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Battles For $21K Following US DOJ News, Volatility Incoming? (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-battles-for-21k-following-us-doj-news-volatility-incoming-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234009</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price rally, many assume that the bear market is over. But is it too early to call bottoms? Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the price has been rallying over the past couple of weeks, breaking above multiple static resistance levels and the significant 200-day moving average. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Bitcoin&#8217;s recent price rally, many assume that the bear market is over. But is it too early to call bottoms?</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price has been rallying over the past couple of weeks, breaking above multiple static resistance levels and the significant 200-day moving average. The large falling wedge pattern has also been broken to the upside, which is usually considered a bullish reversal signal.</p>
<p>From a classical price action standpoint, the cryptocurrency seems likely to target the $25K level in the short term.</p>
<p>However, the RSI indicator suggests that BTC is massively overbought, and a bearish pullback or reversal is also highly probable in the short term. In this case, the broken 200-day moving average located around the $19,500 mark and the $18K area could be counted on as potential support levels, which could push the price higher toward the $25K mark.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234011" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234011" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234011 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1901231" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jan-19-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234011" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour chart, the price has been rising rapidly and breaking above multiple resistance levels.</p>
<p>However, the $21K area is currently preventing BTC from climbing, and a short-term pullback is seemingly imminent. This takes place following yesterday&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-doj-issues-international-cryptocurrency-enforcement-action/" data-wpel-link="internal">announcement</a> of the DOJ.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator also shows warning signals in this timeframe, as a clear bearish divergence has been forming between the recent price highs. Therefore, a drop back towards the $18K support area could be expected in the short term, with multiple analysis tools on both the 4-hour and daily timeframes validating this scenario.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234012" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234012" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234012 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1901232" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSDT-4H-Jan-19-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234012" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2><strong>On-chain Analysis</strong></h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/profile/u/Edris?tab=quicktake" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>Bitcoin Net Unrealized Profit Loss</h3>
<p>With the recent surge in Bitcoin&#8217;s price, many holders are climbing back above breakeven, and market sentiment is turning positive. The latter usually provides valuable insights for more precise price action prediction, and one of the most useful on-chain metrics for achieving this is the Net Unrealized Profit Loss.</p>
<p>Net Unrealized Profit and Loss (NUPL) is the difference between the market cap and the realized cap divided by the market cap. NUPL indicates the total amount of profit/loss in all the coins represented as a ratio. It could be interpreted as the ratio of investors in profit, with values above 0, meaning more coins are in profit and vice versa.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234010" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234010" style="width: 2378px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234010 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023.jpg" alt="btc_nupl_chart_1901231" width="2378" height="1496" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023.jpg 2378w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-1024x644.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-768x483.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-1536x966.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-2048x1288.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-NUPL-Jan-19-2023-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2378px) 100vw, 2378px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234010" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>Recently, the NUPL has increased above 0 due to the price rally after months of negative values, indicating that more investors are in profit now. While this could be interpreted as a bullish signal since fewer market participants are under pressure to sell their coins and prevent further losses, it could also be considered as a warning sign.</p>
<p>Many of these investors may be tempted to exit the market at breakeven or with tiny amounts of profit, and the resulting selling pressure could overflow the market with supply.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-battles-for-21k-following-us-doj-news-volatility-incoming-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Battles For $21K Following US DOJ News, Volatility Incoming? (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>John Ray Says Reviving FTX is on the Table: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/john-ray-says-reviving-ftx-is-on-the-table-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234031</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1200x-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1200x-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[John Ray said that they might try to restart the FTX international exchange, if this makes sense for making creditors whole. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acting Chief Executive Officer of FTX, John J. Ray III, who is in charge of making sure that the creditors of the bankrupt exchange receive as much compensation as possible, said that the platform might restart.</p>
<ul>
<li>In an <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-ftx-chief-says-crypto-exchange-could-restart-11674143168?mod=hp_lead_pos3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with <em>The Wall Street Journal, </em>John J. Ray III said that restarting the exchange is on the table.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Everything is on the table. If there is a path forward on that, then we will not only explore that, we will do it.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>FTX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for Bankruptcy back in November 2022, using Chapter 11.</li>
<li>Mr. Ray further clarified that he will be looking into whether restarting the international exchange would recover more value for the company&#8217;s creditors than his team could potentially get from simply liquidating the assets or selling the entire thing.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>There are stakeholders we&#8217;re working with who&#8217;ve identified what they see as a viable business.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/john-ray-says-reviving-ftx-is-on-the-table-report/" rel="nofollow">John Ray Says Reviving FTX is on the Table: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockchainSpace Makes A Move for Web3 Community Support with Metasports Acquisition</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockchainspace-makes-a-move-for-web3-community-support-with-metasports-acquisition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233984</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BlockchainSpace.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BlockchainSpace.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manila, Philippines, 19th January 2023] BlockchainSpace CEO and Founder Peter Ing, Metasports CBO and Co-Founder Lars Hernandez, and Metasports CEO and Co-Founder Joe Josue are optimistic that the majority acquisition of Metasports will make waves in Web3 and bring great value to their stakeholders in the coming years. lockchainSpace (BSPC), the leading [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manila, Philippines, 19th January 2023]</strong></p>
<p>BlockchainSpace CEO and Founder Peter Ing, Metasports CBO and Co-Founder Lars Hernandez, and Metasports CEO and Co-Founder Joe Josue are optimistic that the majority acquisition of Metasports will make waves in Web3 and bring great value to their stakeholders in the coming years.</p>
<p>lockchainSpace (BSPC), the leading data aggregator and infrastructure provider for guilds and Web3 projects, is confident that 2023 will be a banner year following the majority acquisition of Intellectual Property (IP) House, Metasports.</p>
<p>Peter Ing, Chief Executive Officer and Founder of BSPC, believes the synergistic partnership with Metasports will bring more value to the partner guilds under BSPC’s flagship product, Guild Hub, and give Metasports an unbridled springboard to high-impact Web3 communities.</p>
<p>“BlockchainSpace is looking to scale faster this year. It doesn&#8217;t matter if it&#8217;s a bull market or a bear market – innovation doesn’t stop. We’ve always been focused on strengthening our resources to support our mission, with a more consolidated approach through Guild Hub,” stressed Ing.</p>
<p>Launched in late 2022, Guild Hub is BSPC’s initiative to help create legitimacy among Web3 communities by delivering an effective way of policing the community and providing a venue to create impactful and valuable partnerships. The Metasports acquisition will be instrumental in fostering further business growth, allowing BSPC to continue supporting the community.</p>
<p>“Esports and guilds are not going away as they are integral to Web3 gaming,” added Ing. “Metasports will be essential in serving these guilds.&#8221;</p>
<p>The acquisition of Metasports, with its proven capabilities in the gaming and content creator space, will further expand the opportunities for $GUILD token integration, solidifying BSPC’s position as a leader in providing comprehensive and user-friendly solutions for guilds and Web3 projects.</p>
<p>Metasports, which launched in December 2021, focuses on Web3 and Web2 gaming IPs across esports, creator networks, and news and media verticals. It has quickly proven its value in the Web3 space through the Lunacian Sports League (LSL), the first professionally organized and longest-running esports league for Axie Infinity, and the establishment of its Creator Business Management with renowned content creator KookooTV as the first partner.</p>
<p>While many veer away from high-risk decisions given the market conditions, the two companies view the acquisition as a strategic move based on a thorough understanding of the market, thanks to BSPC’s readily available and growing data sets through Guild Hub.</p>
<p>Joe Josue, CEO and Co-Founder of Metasports, is confident they can strengthen their commitment to enhance experiences around gaming and will bring value to their stakeholders through this acquisition.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We saw an incredible opportunity to grow and invest in more IPs, and that&#8217;s when we started to seek venture. In BlockchainSpace, we found a partner that would be the backbone which we could build on Web3. By tapping BlockchainSpace’s infrastructure, we will finally be able to build technology-backed IPs, which is a powerful next step for us,” Josue shared.</p></blockquote>
<p>With BSPC’s and Metasports’ sights set on scalability this year, both companies look forward to bringing in major changes that will not only impact their business development but contribute to the success and longevity of the growing global Web3 community.</p>
<h2>About BlockchainSpace</h2>
<p>BlockchainSpace is the one-stop-shop for all guild needs that provides essential, scalable infrastructure, digital tools, financing solutions, and networking opportunities. To date, BSPC enables over 24,000 Guilds and 2 million players to scale in the Metaverse, successfully managing and growing their communities.</p>
<p>For more information about the $GUILD token, head over to <a href="http://blockchainspace.asia/guild-token-page" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">blockchainspace.asia/guild-token-page</a></p>
<h2>About Metasports</h2>
<p><a href="http://metasports.gg/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Metasports</a> is an IP House centered on Web3 gaming and esports across three verticals: Esports Experiences, Creator Networks, and News &amp; Media.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchainspace-makes-a-move-for-web3-community-support-with-metasports-acquisition/" rel="nofollow">BlockchainSpace Makes A Move for Web3 Community Support with Metasports Acquisition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 On-Chain Factors Suggest Bitcoin&#8217;s Bull Run Could Have Started: Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/5-on-chain-factors-suggest-bitcoins-bull-run-could-have-started-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233986</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoinbull_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoinbull_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CryptoQuant joins Glassnode in predicting that BTC's year-long bear cycle could be done.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With bitcoin&#8217;s price surging by over $5,000 since the start of the year and reclaiming $20,000, the number of analysts predicting that the asset is out of the woods continues to increase.</p>
<p>CryptoQuant is the latest analytics company to offer some insight into the key on-chain signals that could suggest the start of a bull run.</p>
<ul>
<li>Shortly after Santiment <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-sees-historic-drop-on-exchanges-heres-what-it-means/" data-wpel-link="internal">informed</a> that the supply of bitcoin held on centralized exchanges had dropped to a multi-year low, CryptoQuant <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/quicktake/63c8aa40bf0caf3db2054852-Five-On-chain-Indicators-that-Signal-for-an-Early-Bull-Market-Cycle?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=sns&amp;utm_content=WeeklyIndicator&amp;utm_campaign=Quicktake" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">outlined</a> the movements between different types of trading venues as the first positive sign for BTC.</li>
<li>More precisely, the analysts believe the transfers of assets from spot to derivatives platforms show that traders have entered a &#8220;risk-on&#8221; mode, which suggests &#8220;the beginning of a new bull cycle.&#8221;</li>
<li>The MVRV ratio is next, which shows whether BTC&#8217;s price is under or overvalued, comparing the actual market cap with the asset&#8217;s market price.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;MVRV is above 1 (1.07), and it is close to its 365-day moving average (orange line), which shows that bitcoin is about to start a new uptrend.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The Net Unrealized Profit/Loss (NUPL) is also close to the 365-day MA, which suggests the same as the MVRL.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_233989" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233989" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233989" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1.jpg" alt="Bitcoin MVRV. Source: CryptoQuant" width="1280" height="806" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1.jpg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Pic1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233989" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin MVRV. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li>The Puell Multiple &#8211; showing the ratio of the daily dollar worth of newly issued BTC to their one-year MA &#8211; is the fourth signal. It displays positive signs as the asset&#8217;s price passed its 365-day MA for the first time in over two years.</li>
<li>Lastly, CryptoQuant&#8217;s P&amp;L index, which combines several indicators (the MVRV ratio, NUPL, and LTH/STH SOPR) into one, is &#8220;close to giving a buying signal for BTC.&#8221; Although the company said the Index still shows that bitcoin is expensive in the short term, it&#8217;s on the verge of changing its tides.</li>
<li>Recall that Glassnode also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> there are early signs of a starting bull market after a bear cycle that lasted for about a year.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-on-chain-factors-suggest-bitcoins-bull-run-could-have-started-analysis/" rel="nofollow">5 On-Chain Factors Suggest Bitcoin&#8217;s Bull Run Could Have Started: Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Releases Proof-of-Reserves Report With $7.5B &#8220;Clean Assets&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-releases-proof-of-reserves-report-with-7-5b-clean-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKEx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233946</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The reserves do not contain OKX's native token. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After the excessive turmoil in the crypto market triggered by the FTX liquidity and bankruptcy scandal, several crypto service providers began publishing their reserve funds.</p>
<p>Popular crypto exchange OKX <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/01/19/2591456/0/en/OKX-Publishes-January-Proof-of-Reserves-Report-Shows-Largest-100-Clean-Asset-Reserves-Among-Major-Exchanges.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">released</a> its third Proof-of-Reserves (PoR), in which it revealed holding &#8220;clean assets&#8221; worth $7.5 billion in BTC, ETH, and USDT.</p>
<p>In a statement, OKX&#8217;s Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Security, transparency, and trust are core tenets of the OKX business process and customer service philosophy. We’ve already taken a leadership position by publishing our PoR monthly. As industry standards for PoR continue to take shape, we expect that our reserve asset quality will be one of many key differentiating factors for OKX in the market.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>OKX&#8217;s Third PoR Report</h2>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves/detail" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a>, OKX’s wallets held 123,914 BTC against a user balance of 117,682 BTC as of January 18th. The exchange is overcollateralized with a Bitcoin reserve ratio of 101%, unchanged since the PoR <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-proof-of-reserves-report-bitcoin-ether-tether-reserve-ratios-over-100/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> last month.</p>
<p>Similarly, the reserve ratio for Ethereum stood at 105%, a slight increase from 103% over the past month. OKX held 1,178,993 ETH against a user balance of 1,233,714 ETH. At 101%, Tether reserves also remained unchanged. OKX held 2,979,866,301 USDT holdings against 2,955,696,824 USDT in user balance.</p>
<p>The exchange further revealed publishing over 23,000 addresses for its Merkle Tree Proof-of-Reserves program and will continue to use these to make viewing of asset flows accessible to the community.</p>
<h2>Clean Assets</h2>
<p>Citing blockchain analytics firm CryptoQuant&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/dashboard/proof-of-reserve" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">findings</a>, OKX assured the community this is the &#8220;largest clean asset reserves among major exchanges.&#8221; For context, CryptoQuant earlier stated that 100% of OKX&#8217;s wallets are clean. Contrastingly, it found that 87.67% of Binance, 60.1% of Huobi, 69.85% of Bitfinex, 81.26% of Kucoin, and 95.49% of Crypto.com are clean.</p>
<p>OKX explained that asset reserves are deemed &#8220;clean&#8221; when a third-party analysis establishes the reserves do not include a crypto exchange&#8217;s native token and constitute exclusively of high-market cap &#8220;traditional&#8221; crypto-assets such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tether.</p>
<p>In the aftermath of FTX&#8217;s collapse, allegations of violating its own Terms of Service, as well as misusing user funds, have shaken investor confidence. Despite the trials and tribulations of the previous decades, OKX’s director of financial markets, Lennix Lai, said the cryptocurrency industry will &#8220;change the world.&#8221; The exec also said that OKX &#8220;has never misappropriated user assets before and never will.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-releases-proof-of-reserves-report-with-7-5b-clean-assets/" rel="nofollow">OKX Releases Proof-of-Reserves Report With $7.5B &#8220;Clean Assets&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
