<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:31:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>DOJ Wants SBF Detained and His Bail Revoked Following Witness Tampering Efforts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/doj-wants-sbf-detained-and-his-bail-revoked-following-witness-tampering-efforts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263365</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Sam-Bankman-Fried-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The DOJ said SBF's actions have shown that no set of pretrial release conditions can assure the safety of witnesses.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has requested that the bail bond of Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the founder and former CEO of bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX, be revoked and that the court impose a detention order against him due to his attempts to tamper with witnesses.</p>
<p>According to a letter <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.184.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">submitted</a> to Judge Lewis Kaplan of the U.S. Court for the Southern District of New York, SBF&#8217;s attempts to tamper with witnesses in his fraud case would interfere with the government&#8217;s and public&#8217;s right to a fair trial and the administration of justice.</p>
<h2>SBF&#8217;s Witness Tampering Attempts</h2>
<p>The DOJ disclosed that after SBF was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-who-co-signed-sam-bankman-frieds-250-million-bail-bond/" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> on a bail bond in December, he reached out to the current general counsel of FTX.US in January through emails and Signal, an encrypted messaging application. Among other things, SBF expressed his desire to reconnect with the counsel and build a &#8220;constructive relationship&#8221; that would entail using each other as resources when possible.</p>
<p>The Justice Department pointed out that SBF had a history of using Signal for obstructive purposes in the years that led to his firm&#8217;s bankruptcy. The court eventually modified his bail conditions, prohibiting contact with FTX and Alameda Research employees and using encrypted or ephemeral messaging applications.</p>
<p>The New York Times recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/caroline-ellison-felt-unsuited-to-run-alameda-amid-sbf-relationship-drama/" data-wpel-link="internal">published</a> an article on the private writings and psychology of Caroline Ellison, the former CEO of Alameda and SBF&#8217;s ex-girlfriend, in the months leading up to FTX&#8217;s implosion. After several investigations, the DOJ found that SBF had released the writings to reporters.</p>
<p>A deeper probe showed that in the past few months, SBF had sent more than 100 emails and been on over 1,000 phone calls with media members. He also had over 100 phone calls with one of the authors of the New York Times Ellison article, with several lasting for roughly 20 minutes. In addition, the FTX founder used virtual private networks to conceal his online activities.</p>
<h2>DOJ Wants SBF Detained Ahead of Trial</h2>
<p>SBF&#8217;s actions have shown that no pretrial release conditions can assure the safety of witnesses and that he is unlikely to abide by his bail conditions, according to the DOJ.</p>
<p>Prosecutors have already sought a gag order, which SBF <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-agrees-to-gag-order-requests-one-for-rivals-too/" data-wpel-link="internal">accepted</a> last week, to prevent further witness tampering actions. Nonetheless, the U.S. government wants him detained ahead of his trial scheduled for October 2, 2023.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/doj-wants-sbf-detained-and-his-bail-revoked-following-witness-tampering-efforts/" rel="nofollow">DOJ Wants SBF Detained and His Bail Revoked Following Witness Tampering Efforts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Becomes World&#8217;s First Exchange to be Granted Dubai&#8217;s Operational License</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-becomes-worlds-first-exchange-to-be-granted-dubais-operational-license/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 21:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263343</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/binance_dubai_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/binance_dubai_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The issuance of the operational MVP license permits Binance to operate two licensed activities. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid regulatory turmoil elsewhere, Binance&#8217;s Dubai affiliate, Binance FZE, managed to score an Operational Minimum Viable Product license from the Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA).</p>
<p>Binance has now become the first crypto trading platform to receive Dubai&#8217;s Operational MVP license enabling it to offer services such as exchange and broker-dealer services. The company is permitted to serve only institutional and qualified retail investors for now.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Dubai Expansion</h2>
<p>Eligible users in Dubai will be allowed to access authorized services such as converting digital assets to fiat under VARA-designated standards compliant with Intergovernmental Financial Action Task Force (FATF).</p>
<p>In an official <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-is-the-first-virtual-asset-exchange-to-receive-an-operational-mvp-license-in-dubai-7342057061995039467" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, Binance&#8217;s Head of Regional Markets, Richard Teng, said the priority is to operate this first fully regulated exchange in and from the city in an ecosystem that&#8217;s compliant with the FATF while focussing on global scalability.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are honored to be the first exchange to be granted an operational Minimum Viable Product License by VARA &#8211; a result of over a year of due diligence, collaboration, and consistent demonstration of responsible intent &#8211; that now allows us to be able to leverage the potential of a progressive regulatory framework, enabling innovation while furthering user protection.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The latest development comes after Binance <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-awarded-limited-crypto-asset-license-in-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">obtained</a> a provisional MVP license in March 2022, followed by a preparatory MVP <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-another-crypto-license-in-dubai/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">license</a> five months later.</p>
<p>Binance has so far completed three out of four stages of Dubai&#8217;s licensing procedure.</p>
<p>The fourth phase involves obtaining Full Market Product (FMP) license, until which the virtual asset service provider is not permitted to cater services to mass retail investors.</p>
<h2>Crypto Hotbed: Dubai</h2>
<p>In recent years, Dubai has emerged as a hotbed for crypto activity owing to the emirate&#8217;s strategic policies. The establishment of VARA was a major turning point for the region, which has, so far, proved instrumental in providing clarity to several crypto firms distressed by the US&#8217;s approach to regulating the industry.</p>
<p>Despite <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-forbids-operations-with-monero-zcash-and-other-privacy-coins/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">prohibiting</a> involvement with privacy-centric coins under the new regulatory regime, the city has opened arms to several crypto exchanges, including OKX, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-scores-preparatory-license-by-dubais-virtual-assets-regulatory-authority/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Bybit</a>, and more.</p>
<p>A recent study published by Recap <a href="https://recap.io/blog/the-rise-of-crypto-hubs-which-cities-are-leading-the-way-in-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that Dubai hosts nearly 800 crypto-based companies as of January 2023 for residents to choose from when it comes to finding a career in the sector. Its 0% tax regime also makes it a favorable venue for crypto investors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-becomes-worlds-first-exchange-to-be-granted-dubais-operational-license/" rel="nofollow">Binance Becomes World&#8217;s First Exchange to be Granted Dubai&#8217;s Operational License</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Holds $3.3 Billion In Excess Reserves: Q2 2023 Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-holds-3-3-billion-in-excess-reserves-q2-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 20:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263524</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TetherUSD.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TetherUSD.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether enjoyed another quarter of immense profit, most of which is being used to reinforce its stablecoin reserves.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether, the world’s largest stablecoin issuer, released an assurance report on Monday covering its financials as of June 30.</p>
<p>The Q2 attestation showed that the issuer now holds over $3.3 billion in excess reserves to back its USDT tokens.</p>
<h2>Tether’s Massive Surplus</h2>
<p>As explained by Tether in an accompanying <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-excess-reserves-increase-by-850m-to-reach-3-3b-as-leading-stablecoin-reveals-72-5b-overall-exposure-in-us-t-bills-and-unveils-energy-related-investments/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a>, the issuer’s excess reserves stem from the profits generated by its existing reserves. These profits are not distributed to shareholders and are instead solely used as insurance to back its tokens.</p>
<p>USDT is designed to maintain parity with the U.S. dollar and is always convertible 1:1 for dollars within the company’s reserves.</p>
<p>“Tether is again demonstrating its commitment to transparency by disclosing its direct, indirect exposure (via Money Market Funds) to US Treasury bills as well as the Treasuries collateralizing the Overnight Repo,” the company stated. “By aggregating them together, the amount of Treasuries backing Tether’s stablecoins is about $72.5B.”</p>
<p>Tether generated $1.5 billion in net profit in Q1, followed by over $1 billion between April and June. From its Q2 profit, $115 million was spent on share buybacks, while the remainder went toward the company’s excess reserves.</p>
<p>Tether’s consolidated total assets amounted to $86.5 billion as of June 30, versus $83.2 billion in liabilities, of which $83.17 billion “relate to digital tokens issued.” This leaves Tether with a near 4% surplus, combatting previous criticisms that the firm’s reserves once drew dangerously close to leaving it insolvent.</p>
<p>According to Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino, Tether wants its reliable reserves to act as a <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1685993811774738432" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">“counterbalance”</a> to recent bank failures, caused by fractional reserve lending and duration mismatches.</p>
<h2>Any Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>In Q1, Tether <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-generated-1-5b-in-profits-in-q1-2023-holds-2-bitcoin-in-total-reserves/" data-wpel-link="internal">disclosed</a> that 2% of its reserves were being held in Bitcoin (BTC), breaking a prior trend of stablecoin issuers only profiting through U.S. government debt.</p>
<p>Alongside Tether, rival company Circle – the issuer of USDC) – only generates profit using government debt, with the remainder of its reserves being in cash.</p>
<p>Tether’s latest report stated that 85% of its assets are in “cash and cash equivalents,” leaving its reserves “extremely liquid.”</p>
<p>While not providing updates on the company’s Bitcoin allocation, Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino clarified that a relatively small portion of Tether’s profits are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-joins-1-billion-bitcoin-mining-initiative-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">invested</a> in the Bitcoin mining industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-holds-3-3-billion-in-excess-reserves-q2-2023-report/" rel="nofollow">Tether Holds $3.3 Billion In Excess Reserves: Q2 2023 Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How An Old ENS User Just Reclaimed Over $73 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-old-ens-user-just-reclaimed-over-73-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263514</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There are still tens of thousands of ETH left to claim for old registrants of Ethereum domain names.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An early user of the Ethereum Name Service (ENS) just reclaimed tens of thousands of Ether (ETH) that he’d locked up in the old ENS registrar over 4 years ago.</p>
<p>Having appreciated substantially since that time, the value of those 39,712 ETH is now worth roughly $74 million.</p>
<h2>Reclaiming Old Funds</h2>
<p>According to blockchain analysts at <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1685935783612764160" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Lookonchain</a>, darkmarket.eth was responsible for reclaiming the funds – the largest owner of locked Ether within the old registrar until now.</p>
<p>After reclaiming his funds, the user sent 63,734 ETH ($119 million) to a new wallet.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">After 2.7 years of dormancy, darkmarket.eth reclaimed 39,712 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a> ($74.17M) locked in the ENS auction just now.</p>
<p>And transferred 63,734 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a>($119M) out to a new wallet.<a href="https://t.co/OtXYRpcOhn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/OtXYRpcOhn</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1685935783612764160?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ens-ethereum-name-service/" data-wpel-link="internal">ENS</a> allows crypto users to assign human-readable names to cryptocurrency addresses, which are otherwise presented as long and complex strings of letters and numbers.</p>
<p>When first launched in 2017, the Ethereum Foundation held an auction in which users could bid their ETH to secure these unique domain names for themselves. This was to incentivize claimants not to immediately try selling their domains for exorbitant prices after claiming them, and instead demonstrate a commitment to the domain they had bought.</p>
<p>That ETH was locked within the original ENS smart contract and would remain that way until users either gave up their domains or the contract itself was updated.</p>
<h2>The Old ENS Treasure Trove</h2>
<p>The latter occurred in July 2019, allowing users to reclaim their locked ETH without forfeiting their domain. Under the new system, users were only required to pay a small yearly fee to keep their names.</p>
<p>Yet after the upgrade, many of the old registrants had still not claimed their former funds. According to lead ENS developer <a href="https://twitter.com/nicksdjohnson/status/1685958239278575616" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Nick Johnson</a>, there are still over 100k domains for which deeds remain unclaimed, holding “tens of thousands of ETH.”</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Basically, they bid on (and won) a bunch of names back in ~2016/2017, and when we switched to the new system in 2019, they never released the deeds to claim their locked funds back,&#8221; ENS lead developer Nick Johnson told The Block.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-old-ens-user-just-reclaimed-over-73-million/" rel="nofollow">How An Old ENS User Just Reclaimed Over $73 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert Kiyosaki Says America is Broke, Reiterates Support for Bitcoin and Gold</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/robert-kiyosaki-says-america-is-broke-reiterates-support-for-bitcoin-and-gold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263389</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kiyosaki believes the stock market is rising because of the removal of the U.S. debt ceiling.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert Kiyosaki, an American businessman and author of the best-selling book Rich Dad, Poor Dad, believes the United States is broke as the country&#8217;s debt keeps increasing, countering claims that the world&#8217;s largest economy is strong.</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1685824108087623680" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a>, Kiyosaki called the media agency Wall Street Journal (WSJ) &#8220;numb nuts&#8221; because it failed to decipher whether the stock market was up due to President Joe Biden raising America&#8217;s debt ceiling.</p>
<h2>America is Broke: Kiyosaki</h2>
<p>Kiyosaki&#8217;s comments were in response to a recent <a href="https://www.wsj.com/amp/articles/us-gdp-report-economic-growth-92482437" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> by WSJ, which claimed that the U.S. was steering clear of recession due to several factors, including a 2.4% economic growth in Q2 and a similar increase in the country&#8217;s gross domestic product, significantly faster than experts&#8217; predictions.</p>
<p>With a decline in customer spending, the records defied expectations of a downturn starting in the middle of the year due to higher interest rates. WSJ stated that a more robust labor market would add to the prospect of &#8220;a soft landing,&#8221; where inflation falls close to the Federal Reserve&#8217;s 2% target without a recession.</p>
<p>However, Kiyosaki thinks the opposite. As <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-robert-kiyosaki-sticks-with-real-assets-like-bitcoin-and-gold/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier this month, he believes the stock market is rising because of the U.S. debt ceiling removal.</p>
<p>Recall that in June, Biden signed a bill suspending the U.S. government&#8217;s $31.4 trillion <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-rallies-4-on-us-debt-limit-suspension-deal/" data-wpel-link="internal">debt ceiling</a> till January 2025, avoiding the nation&#8217;s first-ever default. The suspension calmed the economic crisis that threatened to disrupt financial markets and trigger a recession. Since then, large U.S. stock market indexes like the S&amp;P 500, Dow Jones, and Nasdaq have recorded notable gains, sparking claims of a stronger economy.</p>
<p>The renowned author said the national debt is rising alongside the financial market; hence, WSJ&#8217;s claims that America&#8217;s economy is strong are wrong because the country is broke.</p>
<h2>Kiyosaki Prefers Bitcoin, Gold, and Silver</h2>
<p>While America&#8217;s economy dwindles, Kiyosaki reiterated his support and preference for bitcoin (BTC), gold, and silver, which he frequently refers to as real assets and real money. He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-explode-to-120k-in-2024-the-us-dollar-will-die-rober-kiyosaki/" data-wpel-link="internal">believes</a> the U.S. dollar will die while the largest cryptocurrency and precious metals will thrive and act as protection measures.</p>
<p>As a BTC proponent, the Rich Dad, Poor Dad author believes the asset could soar to $120,000 in 2024 and hit $500,000 by 2025.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-kiyosaki-says-america-is-broke-reiterates-support-for-bitcoin-and-gold/" rel="nofollow">Robert Kiyosaki Says America is Broke, Reiterates Support for Bitcoin and Gold</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CRV Trades at Premium on Bithumb and CoinOne Following Curve Finance Hack</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crv-trades-at-premium-on-bithumb-and-coinone-following-curve-finance-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263385</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Curve_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Curve_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the Curve Finance hacking attack, the price of CRV spiked above $5.80 on Bithumb and $3 on CoinOne.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CRV &#8211; the native token of the DeFi exchange Curve Finance &#8211; has plunged over 12% following the recent exploit on several stable pools of the project. However, the token&#8217;s price took a somewhat interesting trajectory on the leading South Korean cryptocurrency exchanges Bithumb and CoinOne, currently trading at a 510% and a 220% premium, respectively.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Separately, Upbit (another major Korean digital asset platform) paused CRV deposits and withdrawals shortly after the latest exploit in the DeFi space. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CRV Shoots to the Opposite Direction</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-finance-hacker-returns-5-4-million-but-crv-dumps-15/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier today, Curve Finance suffered an attack on a number of its stable pools that were using Vyper versions 0.2.15, 0.2.16, and 0.3.0. The entity disclosed that the affected pools included alTH, msETH, and pETH, with the reason being &#8220;a malfunctioning reentrancy lock.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The estimated loss of the attack was initially set at over $40 million, whereas in the following hours, that number might have <a href="https://twitter.com/tayvano_/status/1685789453556846592?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">risen</a> to approximately $70 million.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Expectedly, the USD valuation of Curve DAO (CRV) &#8211; the utility token of the DeFi protocol &#8211; headed south as a consequence of the event. It currently trades at around $0.64 (per GoinGeko&#8217;s data), or 12% less than yesterday&#8217;s figure.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_263410" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263410" style="width: 508px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263410" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV.png" alt="CRV Price" width="508" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV.png 840w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV-300x236.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV-768x604.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CRV-50x39.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 508px) 100vw, 508px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263410" class="wp-caption-text">CRV Price, Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the asset&#8217;s price is quite similar on leading crypto exchanges, such as </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/price/curve-dao-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> and Coinbase, this is not the case for two of the biggest digital asset marketplaces in South Korea &#8211; Bithumb and CoinOne. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CRV currently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bithumb.com/react/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">trades</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at $3.90 on Bithumb or a 510% premium. The price on CoinOne is </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://coinone.co.kr/exchange/trade/crv/krw" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hovering</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> around $2.06 (220% more than the valuation on other platforms).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Upbit&#8217;s Suspension</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The largest South Korean cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Upbit &#8211; took immediate action and temporarily </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://sg.upbit.com/service_center/notice?id=2745" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">halted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> all deposits and withdrawals involving CRV shortly after the Curve Finance attack.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Today, certain vulnerabilities have been discovered in some of the stablecoin pools associated with Curve (CRV). As a result, CRV is currently experiencing significant volatility. We advise exercising caution when considering any investments related to CRV.</span></p>
<p>Additionally, to ensure the safety of digital asset transactions, we have temporarily suspended deposits and withdrawals for CRV,&#8221; the company announced.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Upbit vowed to &#8220;closely monitor the situation&#8221; and warned its users to be utterly careful when dealing with the digital asset. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crv-trades-at-premium-on-bithumb-and-coinone-following-curve-finance-hack/" rel="nofollow">CRV Trades at Premium on Bithumb and CoinOne Following Curve Finance Hack</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Would it Take for XRP to Reach $0.9? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-it-take-for-xrp-to-reach-0-9-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XMRUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263233</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price is currently in a correction phase after a significant spike a few weeks ago. Nonetheless, there are several support levels against both USDT and BTC. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe of the USDT paired chart, the price has recently been rejected from the $0.9 level and is [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price is currently in a correction phase after a significant spike a few weeks ago. Nonetheless, there are several support levels against both USDT and BTC.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe of the USDT paired chart, the price has recently been rejected from the $0.9 level and is currently declining. The $0.6 support level and the 50-day moving average located around the same area are probable targets for a deep pullback.</p>
<p>However, the price could rebound before reaching those levels. In that case, a breakout above the $0.9 resistance level could be expected. This could lead to a higher rally, and XRP could be trade $1 in the coming months.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263482" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263482" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263482" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="XRPUSDT Daily - Jul 31 2023" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263482" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>Against Bitcoin, the situation is similar. The price has failed to break above the 2,800 SAT level twice over the past few weeks. The market is currently demonstrating bearish price action, with the 2,200 SAT area being the first significant support level.</p>
<p>The 50-day moving average trending around the 2,000 SAT mark would also be the next support element in line in case a deeper decline is on the horizon.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the RSI indicator is displaying values above 50%, indicating that the buyers are still in control, and a breakout from the 2,800 SAT resistance zone might still materialize in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263487" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263487" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263487" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="XRPBTC Daily - Jul 31 2023" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRPBTC-Daily-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263487" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-it-take-for-xrp-to-reach-0-9-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">What Would it Take for XRP to Reach $0.9? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calm Before the Storm? ETH Flat Above $1.8K (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-eth-flat-above-1-8k-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263225</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The price of Ethereum has been held by the 100-day moving average, which has prevented further decline for several months. However, despite multiple attempts, the cryptocurrency has been unable to surpass the crucial resistance level at $2K, indicating a lack of demand. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart On the daily chart, the price [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Ethereum has been held by the 100-day moving average, which has prevented further decline for several months.</p>
<p>However, despite multiple attempts, the cryptocurrency has been unable to surpass the crucial resistance level at $2K, indicating a lack of demand.</p>
<h1>Technical Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price faced rejection after the third attempt to break through the $2K resistance region within the last month. This rejection coincided with a decline in bullish momentum, attributed to increased selling pressure around that level, resulting in minor rejections and relatively stable price action.</p>
<p>The 100-day MA, currently at $1,854, has consistently provided support and prevented further declines over the past few weeks. Nevertheless, the breakout from the significant price range between the 100-day MA and the $2K resistance level will likely play a crucial role in determining Ethereum&#8217;s prospects in the mid-term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263479" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263479" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263479" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="ETH Daily - Jul 31 2023" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263479" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Meanwhile, on the 4-hour chart, Ethereum experienced a bullish rally in mid-June, leading to a test of the major resistance at $2K in mid-July. However, it is now facing the 0.5 Fibonacci retracement level at $1827, which serves as significant support for the price.</p>
<p>However, ETH remains trapped between two critical price levels: the static resistance at $2K and the critical support at $1,850. This suggests the possibility of a range-bound market characterized by consolidation candles.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the price seems more likely to continue trading within this range until a breakout occurs, providing insight into Ethereum&#8217;s upcoming direction. In the event of a break below the 50% Fibonacci level, the next potential stop for Ethereum could be the 61.8% level at $1780.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263480" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263480" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263480 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="ETH 4H - Jul 31 2023" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263480" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-eth-flat-above-1-8k-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Calm Before the Storm? ETH Flat Above $1.8K (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Possible Targets for BTC in the Short Term (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/two-possible-targets-for-btc-in-the-short-term-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[btc]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263450</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price action has been relatively stagnant over the past few days. The market is still hanging around the $30K level, but this consolidation phase will not continue forever. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily chart, the 50-day moving average is currently holding the price around the $30K level. However, it [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price action has been relatively stagnant over the past few days. The market is still hanging around the $30K level, but this consolidation phase will not continue forever.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3><strong>The Daily Chart:</strong></h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the 50-day moving average is currently holding the price around the $30K level. However, it has failed to push the market back above the $30K mark over the last few days.</p>
<p>There is a probability for the price to break to the downside and drop towards the 200-day moving average located around the $27K mark.</p>
<p>The 200-day MA is a key indicator and might push the price higher once more, as it did back in February. On the other hand, if the price climbs back above the key $30K level, a rally higher and an eventual test of the $38K resistance zone could be expected in the next few weeks.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263454" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263454" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263454 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_3107231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263454" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>The 4-Hour Chart:</strong></h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour chart, things appear more interesting for BTC. A large falling wedge pattern has been forming since the beginning of July. However, the price is seemingly breaking out to the upside. If the breakout is valid, the market is likely to enter a new bullish phase and surge higher.</p>
<p>Yet, there is still a chance for the breakout to be a fake one, which would be disastrous.</p>
<p>Fake breakouts usually lead to massive crashes, and in this case, might result in a rapid decline towards the $27,500 support level in the short term. Nevertheless, with the RSI indicator showing values above 50%, the momentum is in favor of buyers, and a bullish move is looking more probable.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263452" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263452" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263452 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_3107231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSDT-4H-Jul-31-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263452" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/profile/u/Edris?tab=quicktake" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Funding Rates</strong></p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has shown little intention of rising or falling and has been consolidating around the $30K level for the last few weeks. While the action fails to give any clues, analyzing the futures market sentiment might be insightful.</p>
<p>This chart demonstrates the funding rates, which are periodic payments to either long or short traders based on the difference between perpetual contract markets and spot prices.</p>
<p>Funding rates represent traders&#8217; sentiments in the perpetual futures market, and the amount is proportional to the number of contracts. Positive values indicate that long-position traders are dominant and are willing to pay funding to short traders. Negative funding rates indicate that short-position traders are dominant and are willing to pay long traders.</p>
<p>This metric has recently shown positive values, indicating the relatively bullish sentiment in the futures market. It also displayed a huge spike yesterday, but the price is yet to move upward. While positive sentiment is not a bad thing, the price&#8217;s failure to climb higher is a red flag. If this pattern continues, the market might drop in the short term, as a long liquidation cascade may be on the horizon.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263453" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263453" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263453 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_funding_rates_chart_3107231" width="2560" height="1617" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-1024x647.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-768x485.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-1536x970.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-2048x1294.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Jul-31-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263453" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/two-possible-targets-for-btc-in-the-short-term-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Two Possible Targets for BTC in the Short Term (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>IOTA20 Token Presale Launched On ETH, 100x Cheaper Than IOTA Price Today   </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/iota20-token-presale-launched-on-eth-100x-cheaper-than-iota-price-today/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263458</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iota20_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/iota20_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[IOTA20 ($IOTA20), a new entrant in the crypto scene, has kickstarted its presale phase with an aim to tackle the hurdles confronted by its namesake, IOTA ($MIOTA). Early investors in IOTA20 ($IOTA20) have the opportunity to acquire $IOTA20 tokens during this presale phase for $0.00145, a price point that&#8217;s 100 times lower than the IOTA [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IOTA20 ($IOTA20), a new entrant in the crypto scene, has kickstarted its presale phase with an aim to tackle the hurdles confronted by its namesake, IOTA ($MIOTA).</p>
<p>Early investors in <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_iota20_662?referrer=iota20-token-presale-launched-on-eth-100x-cheaper-than-iota-price-today" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">IOTA20 ($IOTA20)</a> have the opportunity to acquire $IOTA20 tokens during this presale phase for $0.00145, a price point that&#8217;s 100 times lower than the IOTA price today (approximately $0.17).</p>
<p>Given the prior success of $MIOTA, many in the crypto community are already anticipating that IOTA20 could follow a similar trajectory – providing a potentially lucrative opportunity for early investors.</p>
<h2>IOTA20 Presale Presents Early-Bird Opportunity for Crypto Investors</h2>
<p>The launch of $IOTA20’s presale phase at <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_iota20_662?referrer=iota20-token-presale-launched-on-eth-100x-cheaper-than-iota-price-today" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">iota20.com</a> has taken the low-cap crypto space by storm, presenting an opportunity for investors to buy into a promising project on the ground floor.</p>
<p>$IOTA20&#8217;s presale will have one stage, with tokens fixed at $0.00145 to ensure a fair launch and high upside potential, being over 100x lower than the IOTA price.</p>
<p>Regarding tokenomics, <a href="https://iota20.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">IOTA20’s whitepaper</a> notes that the total token supply is capped at 2,779,530,232, mirroring the original IOTA.</p>
<p>Significantly, half of these tokens, amounting to 1,389,530,282 $IOTA20, will be up for grabs during the presale.</p>
<p>Naturally, this large allocation creates a window of opportunity for early investors to acquire a substantial stake in the project at the earliest point possible.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the remaining 50% of the token supply will be used for staking rewards and Uniswap liquidity, helping create a balanced ecosystem.</p>
<h2>$IOTA20’s Staking Mechanism &amp; Impressive Growth Potential Sparks Investor Demand</h2>
<p>One of the most compelling features of the IOTA20 project is its simple staking mechanism, which capitalizes on the Ethereum blockchain’s robust security.</p>
<p>This mechanism is designed to be accessible to investors of all experience levels, allowing users to stake their tokens, secure the network, and earn recurring rewards.</p>
<p>Over 1.1 billion $IOTA20 tokens have been set aside for staking rewards, underlining the development team’s commitment to incentivizing long-term holding.</p>
<p>However, the financial prospects of $IOTA20 go well beyond just staking rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263460" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.png" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="188" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2-300x94.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2-50x16.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>With the token’s initial market cap being over considerably less than $IOTA’s all-time low market cap, the room for growth is there.</p>
<p>Although this level of success isn’t guaranteed, the potential for exponential growth is proving to be a strong driver of early demand.</p>
<h2>IOTA20 Sets Sights on Enhancing Original IOTA’s Vision</h2>
<p>While $IOTA20’s potential for gains has captured investors’ attention, the real innovation comes from the developers’ aim to address the challenges faced by the original IOTA project.</p>
<p>Despite its innovative &#8220;Tangle&#8221; technology, the original IOTA has struggled with complexity and security vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>Thus, $IOTA20 emerges as a promising solution, enhancing the core strengths of the original token while overcoming its issues.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263461" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-1.png" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="276" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-1.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-1-300x138.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-1-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Importantly, $IOTA20&#8217;s creators have committed to full transparency and community engagement, fostering trust and excitement among the growing investor base.</p>
<p>As the presale phase gains traction, the $IOTA20 project offers a second chance for those who missed the original IOTA’s bull run and aspire to capitalize on the initiation of a promising new project.</p>
<p>Based on this and the factors mentioned in this article, $IOTA20 could be a token worth watching in the coming weeks &#8211; follow <a href="https://twitter.com/iota20token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">@iota20token</a> on Twitter to keep up to date with the project.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_iota20_662?referrer=iota20-token-presale-launched-on-eth-100x-cheaper-than-iota-price-today" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit IOTA20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/iota20-token-presale-launched-on-eth-100x-cheaper-than-iota-price-today/" rel="nofollow">IOTA20 Token Presale Launched On ETH, 100x Cheaper Than IOTA Price Today   </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
