<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Argentinian Regulator Says it Wants to Adopt FATF Crypto Regulations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-regulator-says-it-wants-adopt-fatf-crypto-regulations.htm</link><description>Argentina’s top financial regulator says it wants to adopt the crypto regulations set out by the Financial Action Task Force (FATF), the international money laundering and terrorist financing watchdog. &lt;br /&gt;
The comments came from Sebastián Negri, the President of the National Securities Commission (CNV), and were reported by the media outlet Criptonoticias. &lt;br /&gt;
Negri spoke of an “urgent” need for “compliance with FATF standards.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-regulator-says-it-wants-adopt-fatf-crypto-regulations.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentinian Regulator Says it Wants to Adopt FATF Crypto Regulations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-regulator-says-it-wants-adopt-fatf-crypto-regulations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118116/315056/arg-2806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="626639"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Daily Trading Volume Surpasses $10 Billion and Pushes BTC Into the Green – Is the Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-daily-trading-volume-surpasses-10-billion-pushes-btc-into-green-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin's (BTC) daily trading volume soars above the $10 billion mark, pushing the price of Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency, into positive territory, the persistent question arises: has the bear market ended?  &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst this momentum, an intriguing development in the form of a surge in cryptocurrency mining stocks, with Hut 8 Mining leading the pack, further fuels optimism in the cryptocurrency sphere....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-daily-trading-volume-surpasses-10-billion-pushes-btc-into-green-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Daily Trading Volume Surpasses $10 Billion and Pushes BTC Into the Green – Is the Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-daily-trading-volume-surpasses-10-billion-pushes-btc-into-green-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118214/315240/28.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="485105"/></item><item><title>Prime Trust Faces Closure as Nevada Regulators Take Action – Another Bear Market Victim?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/prime-trust-faces-closure-as-nevada-regulators-take-action-another-bear-market-victim.htm</link><description>Crypto custodian Prime Trust is facing imminent closure as Nevada regulators move to shut down the troubled company, potentially making it the latest victim of the crypto bear market. &lt;br /&gt;
The regulatory action comes after it was discovered that Prime Trust owed millions of dollars to its customers, placing it in an "unsafe financial condition and/or insolvent," according to the Nevada Financial Institutions Division (FID)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/prime-trust-faces-closure-as-nevada-regulators-take-action-another-bear-market-victim.htm"&gt;Read More: Prime Trust Faces Closure as Nevada Regulators Take Action – Another Bear Market Victim?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Prime Trust</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/prime-trust-faces-closure-as-nevada-regulators-take-action-another-bear-market-victim.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118205/315210/closure.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="436997"/></item><item><title>This Snoop Dogg Linked Meme Coin Could Be The Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/snoop-dogg-linked-meme-coin-could-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>Is Snoop Dogg behind a new meme coin token called Thug Life that has set the Twittersphere ablaze? &lt;br /&gt;
Some investors aren't waiting to find out and have already ploughed nearly $50,000 into the new project in the past two hours. &lt;br /&gt;
What do buyers get for their money? Well, $THUG is looking to raise $2 million to build a community of thugs that will out smart the likes of Pepe, Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. It could be the most viral-friendly token ever....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/snoop-dogg-linked-meme-coin-could-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: This Snoop Dogg Linked Meme Coin Could Be The Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/snoop-dogg-linked-meme-coin-could-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118193/315204/thug-life-token.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="980799"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Jack Dorsey Challenges Tim Cook Over Apple Pay's Lack of Bitcoin Support Amid Damus Controversy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-jack-dorsey-challenges-tim-cook-over-apple-pays-lack-of-bitcoin-support-amid-damus-controversy.htm</link><description>Former Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey has questioned Apple CEO Tim Cook about the lack of Bitcoin (BTC) support on Apple Pay, the firm's mobile payment service. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes after Apple threatened to remove the Bitcoin-friendly social media app Damus from the App Store for violating its terms of service....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-jack-dorsey-challenges-tim-cook-over-apple-pays-lack-of-bitcoin-support-amid-damus-controversy.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Jack Dorsey Challenges Tim Cook Over Apple Pay's Lack of Bitcoin Support Amid Damus Controversy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Jack Dorsey</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Apple</category><category>Twitter</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-jack-dorsey-challenges-tim-cook-over-apple-pays-lack-of-bitcoin-support-amid-damus-controversy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118183/315175/b7bb5c7eb6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="59519"/></item><item><title>Paradigm Co-founder Matt Huang Deems AI 'Too Interesting to Ignore' but Remains Devoted to Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-co-founder-matt-huang-deems-ai-too-interesting-to-ignore-but-remains-devoted-to-crypto.htm</link><description>Matt Huang, co-founder of crypto-focused investment firm Paradigm, says he is still devoted to crypto even though artificial intelligence (AI) in his opinion is “too interesting to ignore.” &lt;br /&gt;
"We’ve never been more excited about crypto and we continue to invest across all stages," Huang said Tuesday on Twitter, while adding "We’re also a group of curious nerds and the developments in AI are too interesting to ignore."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-co-founder-matt-huang-deems-ai-too-interesting-to-ignore-but-remains-devoted-to-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Paradigm Co-founder Matt Huang Deems AI 'Too Interesting to Ignore' but Remains Devoted to Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>AI</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Paradigm</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-co-founder-matt-huang-deems-ai-too-interesting-to-ignore-but-remains-devoted-to-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118189/315186/ai-chip.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1518047"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange FTX Puts a Pause on Anthropic Stake Sale</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-puts-pause-anthropic-stake-sale.htm</link><description>Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has put a pause on the sale of its stake in the AI startup Anthropic.  &lt;br /&gt;
The boutique investment bank that acts as an adviser to FTX, Perella Weinberg Partners,  informed bidders this month about the abrupt halt in the sale of the exchange’s stake in Antropic, Bloomberg reported.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the past few months, multiple potential buyers assessed private information about the Anthropic stake, the report added citing people close to the matter. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-puts-pause-anthropic-stake-sale.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange FTX Puts a Pause on Anthropic Stake Sale&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-ftx-puts-pause-anthropic-stake-sale.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118196/315214/ftx-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="105442"/></item><item><title>Next Meme Coin to Explode? Thug Life Token $2 Million Presale Expected to Sell Out Fast</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/next-meme-coin-explode-thug-life-token-2-million-presale-expected-sell-out-fast.htm</link><description>Wednesday, 28th of June - A brand-new meme coin project called Thug Life Token ($THUG) is making waves on social media and within web3 circles. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite only launching its token presale a few hours ago, the project has already raised a whopping $45,000 via $THUG sales. &lt;br /&gt;
As the word of $THUG spreads, more meme coin-hunting degenerates are expected to pile cash into the project....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/next-meme-coin-explode-thug-life-token-2-million-presale-expected-sell-out-fast.htm"&gt;Read More: Next Meme Coin to Explode? Thug Life Token $2 Million Presale Expected to Sell Out Fast&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/next-meme-coin-explode-thug-life-token-2-million-presale-expected-sell-out-fast.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118204/315211/thug-website.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="732695"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as Bears Send LUNC Toward $0.00008 Support – What Happens Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bears-send-lunc-toward-000008-support-what-happens-next.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bears-send-lunc-toward-000008-support-what-happens-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as Bears Send LUNC Toward $0.00008 Support – What Happens Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bears-send-lunc-toward-000008-support-what-happens-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118202/315208/lunc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="575673"/></item><item><title>UK Law Commission Calls for Special Legal Framework for Crypto as Collateral</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-law-commission-calls-for-special-legal-framework-for-crypto-as-collateral.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-law-commission-calls-for-special-legal-framework-for-crypto-as-collateral.htm"&gt;Read More: UK Law Commission Calls for Special Legal Framework for Crypto as Collateral&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-law-commission-calls-for-special-legal-framework-for-crypto-as-collateral.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118201/315203/adobestock-295812359.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="177436"/></item><item><title>MicroStrategy Acquires Additional $347 Million in Bitcoin, Total Investment Surpasses $4.5 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategy-acquires-additional-347-million-bitcoin-total-investment-surpasses-45-billion.htm</link><description>Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy has added an additional 12,333 Bitcoin to its portfolio, in the last two months. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a company report, MicroStrategy, together with its subsidiaries, bought the asset between April 29 and June 27, for approximately $347.0 million in cash, at an average price of approximately $28,136 per Bitcoin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategy-acquires-additional-347-million-bitcoin-total-investment-surpasses-45-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: MicroStrategy Acquires Additional $347 Million in Bitcoin, Total Investment Surpasses $4.5 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategy-acquires-additional-347-million-bitcoin-total-investment-surpasses-45-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118191/315187/pexels-david-mcbee-730564.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2615095"/></item><item><title>KuCoin Implements Mandatory KYC for All Users, Strengthening Security Measures</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/kucoin-implements-mandatory-kyc-for-all-users-strengthening-security-measures.htm</link><description>KuCoin, a major cryptocurrency exchange, will require all users to undergo mandatory know-your-customer (KYC) procedures before July 15, 2023.  &lt;br /&gt;
This move comes amidst heightened regulatory scrutiny, including the case involving Binance and the U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to its announcement today, June 28, to bolster its security system and also to enhance user experiences on the platform, KuCoin is implementing stricter identity verification measures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kucoin-implements-mandatory-kyc-for-all-users-strengthening-security-measures.htm"&gt;Read More: KuCoin Implements Mandatory KYC for All Users, Strengthening Security Measures&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>KuCoin</category><category>KYC</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/kucoin-implements-mandatory-kyc-for-all-users-strengthening-security-measures.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118182/315183/kucoin-kyc-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161622"/></item><item><title>Three Arrows Capital Founders Face $1.3 Billion Claim from Liquidators</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-founders-face-13-billion-claim-from-liquidators.htm</link><description>The founders of the now-bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital, also known as 3AC, are facing a $1.3 billion recovery claim from the fund’s liquidators. &lt;br /&gt;
The liquidators, who are also partners at the consulting and advisory firm Teneo, have accused the firm’s co-founders Su Zhu and Kyle Davies of incurring debt when the firm was insolvent....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-founders-face-13-billion-claim-from-liquidators.htm"&gt;Read More: Three Arrows Capital Founders Face $1.3 Billion Claim from Liquidators&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-founders-face-13-billion-claim-from-liquidators.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118180/315178/adobe.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="491269"/></item><item><title>Azuki NFTs Lose Value as Investors Criticize 'Identical' Elementals Artwork – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/azuki-nfts-lose-value-as-investors-criticize-identical-elementals-artwork-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Following the success of the original Azuki NFT collection, the NFT collectors were beyond excited for the sequel — Azuki Elementals.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, after the new NFT dropped, the first Azuki collection started losing value quickly, with collectors even selling under the mint price.  &lt;br /&gt;
It wasn’t long before the collectors started pointing out the similarities between the new and original collections, alleging that “Azuki stole their own artwork."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/azuki-nfts-lose-value-as-investors-criticize-identical-elementals-artwork-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Azuki NFTs Lose Value as Investors Criticize 'Identical' Elementals Artwork – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/azuki-nfts-lose-value-as-investors-criticize-identical-elementals-artwork-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118148/315103/azuki-nfts-lose-value-as-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="520673"/></item><item><title>Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Praises Blockchain Technology and Says Right to Use and Hold Bitcoin Will Be 'Inviolable' If Elected</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-praises-blockchain-technology-says-right-use-hold-bitcoin-will-inviolable-if-elected.htm</link><description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the pro-Bitcoin presidential candidate, recently held a speech in which he vowed to defend the US citizens’ right to hold and use Bitcoin (BTC).  &lt;br /&gt;
He said that his campaign would be the first to accept Bitcoin donations.  &lt;br /&gt;
More than that, if elected president, he promised to make sure that “your right to use and hold Bitcoin is inviolable.” &lt;br /&gt;
In continuation of his speech, Kennedy said, ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-praises-blockchain-technology-says-right-use-hold-bitcoin-will-inviolable-if-elected.htm"&gt;Read More: Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Praises Blockchain Technology and Says Right to Use and Hold Bitcoin Will Be 'Inviolable' If Elected&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-praises-blockchain-technology-says-right-use-hold-bitcoin-will-inviolable-if-elected.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118146/315099/presidential-candidate-ro.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="410342"/></item><item><title>Breaking: FTX Has Begun Talks to Relaunch International Exchange – Rebranding Will Likely Be Part of the Process</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-ftx-begun-talks-relaunch-international-exchange-rebranding-will-likely-part-of-process.htm</link><description>The failed crypto company FTX is apparently having initial talks with investors on bringing back the FTX.com exchange through structures such as a joint venture, a WSJ report said. &lt;br /&gt;
It is expected that FTX would undergo a rebranding process and also involve potential compensation arrangements for specific current clients, through the provision of ownership stakes in the restructured company, a source familiar with the matter told the Journal....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-ftx-begun-talks-relaunch-international-exchange-rebranding-will-likely-part-of-process.htm"&gt;Read More: Breaking: FTX Has Begun Talks to Relaunch International Exchange – Rebranding Will Likely Be Part of the Process&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/breaking-ftx-begun-talks-relaunch-international-exchange-rebranding-will-likely-part-of-process.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118144/315199/adobestock-545798265-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="107294"/></item><item><title>Bank of England's CBDC 'Britcoin' May Not Rely on Blockchain</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-englands-cbdc-britcoin-may-not-rely-blockchain.htm</link><description>The Bank of England is still mulling over which technology will underpin its Central Bank-Backed Digital Currency (CBDC).  &lt;br /&gt;
All other central banks are using Blockchain technology to issue their national digital currencies. However, the Bank of England has not decided on it yet.  &lt;br /&gt;
The head of the BOE’s CBDC project, Tom Mutton, said that all options are on the table as the central bank continues its research on whether building a digital pound, dubbed as Britcoin, is worth it. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-englands-cbdc-britcoin-may-not-rely-blockchain.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of England's CBDC 'Britcoin' May Not Rely on Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Bank of England</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-englands-cbdc-britcoin-may-not-rely-blockchain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118158/315127/bank-of-england-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="109953"/></item><item><title>Israel Confiscates Cryptocurrency Allegedly Used for Funding Hezbollah and Iran's Revolutionary Guard</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/israel-confiscates-cryptocurrency-allegedly-used-for-funding-hezbollah-irans-revolutionary-guard.htm</link><description>Israel has seized millions of dollars worth of cryptocurrency allegedly used to finance the Iran-backed militant groups. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Tuesday announcement, Israeli Defense Minister Yoav Gallant said he had spearheaded the operation and ordered the confiscation of cryptocurrency wallets involved in these financing schemes, according to a report by The Washington Post....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/israel-confiscates-cryptocurrency-allegedly-used-for-funding-hezbollah-irans-revolutionary-guard.htm"&gt;Read More: Israel Confiscates Cryptocurrency Allegedly Used for Funding Hezbollah and Iran's Revolutionary Guard&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Israel</category><category>Iran</category><category>Terrorist Financing</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/israel-confiscates-cryptocurrency-allegedly-used-for-funding-hezbollah-irans-revolutionary-guard.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118141/315091/b7bb5c7eb6.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="59519"/></item><item><title>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares Hit Yearly High, Discount Shrinks to 30% as Wall Street Giants Enter Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-hit-yearly-high-discount-shrinks-30-as-wall-street-giants-enter-crypto.htm</link><description>The share price of Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) reached a one-year high on Tuesday, fueled by renewed optimism surrounding the potential conversion of the trust into an exchange-traded fund (ETF). &lt;br /&gt;
The surge came in response to reports that asset manager Fidelity Investments is preparing to follow BlackRock's lead in filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-hit-yearly-high-discount-shrinks-30-as-wall-street-giants-enter-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares Hit Yearly High, Discount Shrinks to 30% as Wall Street Giants Enter Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>ETF</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-hit-yearly-high-discount-shrinks-30-as-wall-street-giants-enter-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118151/315102/grayscale-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="59087"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction Amid Cathie Wood's ARK Seeking 'Premier Position' in Bitcoin ETF Race</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-amid-cathie-woods-ark-seeking-premier-position-bitcoin-etf-race.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin currently stands at $30,442, reflecting a less than 0.50% drop on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
As Cathie Wood's ARK Investment Management positions itself for a leading role in the Bitcoin ETF race, all eyes turn to the potential impact on Bitcoin's price trajectory.  &lt;br /&gt;
This update delves into the Bitcoin price prediction amid these unfolding market dynamics and explores the potential implications of ARK's ambitious move in the cryptocurrency ETF space....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-amid-cathie-woods-ark-seeking-premier-position-bitcoin-etf-race.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction Amid Cathie Wood's ARK Seeking 'Premier Position' in Bitcoin ETF Race&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-amid-cathie-woods-ark-seeking-premier-position-bitcoin-etf-race.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118110/315078/28.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="529508"/></item></channel></rss>
