<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>BitGo Crypto Custodian Secures $100 Million in Funding, Valuation Reaches $1.75 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm</link><description>Crypto custody provider BitGo has raised $100 million in a Series C funding round to reach a valuation of $1.75 billion, the firm announced on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Participating in the funding round were several “new, outside strategic investors,” BitGo said in the announcement. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm did not name any of the investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: BitGo Crypto Custodian Secures $100 Million in Funding, Valuation Reaches $1.75 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>BitGo</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122694/324471/bitgo-ceo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="74618"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as $1.4 Billion Sends XRP Down 1.5% – Are Whales Selling?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm</link><description>The XRP price has dropped by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, slipping to $0.585019 as the cryptocurrency market as a whole falls by 2% within the same timeframe. &lt;br /&gt;
The market has been pulled down by a number of factors today, from ongoing weakness in stock markets to disappointment over delayed Bitcoin ETF decisions, with XRP sharing in the general negativity....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as $1.4 Billion Sends XRP Down 1.5% – Are Whales Selling?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122689/324460/xrp-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1694720"/></item><item><title>Valkyrie Funds Looks to Launch Ethereum Strategy ETF</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm</link><description>Asset management firm Valkyrie Funds has filed for an Ethereum Strategy exchange-traded fund (ETF) that will invest in Ether futures. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Wednesday filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission, the new fund, called the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF, aims to capitalize on the growing interest in Ethereum (ETH) futures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm"&gt;Read More: Valkyrie Funds Looks to Launch Ethereum Strategy ETF&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Valkyrie Funds</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122685/324445/ethereum-coin-media-libra.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="106104"/></item><item><title>Sichuan Province of China Targets Metaverse Industry Expansion to Reach $34.4 Billion by 2025</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm</link><description>Sichuan, a southwestern Chinese province, once recognized as a thriving crypto mining hub prior to the national ban on mining, is now looking to expand the metaverse industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
Sichuan’s government unveiled an ambitious draft action plan with an aim to cultivate the nascent metaverse industry into a colossal market worth 250 billion yuan ($34.4 billion) by the year 2025. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm"&gt;Read More: Sichuan Province of China Targets Metaverse Industry Expansion to Reach $34.4 Billion by 2025&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>China</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122690/324464/china-metaverse.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="183738"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Drops 7.5% After Shibarium Launch – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The Shiba Inu price has dropped by more than 7.5% today, with its slide to $0.00000888 coming after the full public launch of the much-anticipated Shibarium layer-two network. &lt;br /&gt;
This means SHIB is down by 9% in the past week, with Shibarium's arrival being plagued by technical issues that have dragged down the meme token's price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Drops 7.5% After Shibarium Launch – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122676/324458/shiba-inu-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1303493"/></item><item><title>Judge Approves Investment Banker as Declarant in SEC vs. Ripple Legal Battle – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-approves-investment-banker-as-declarant-sec-vs-ripple-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm</link><description>In the latest development of the legal case between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission and Ripple Labs, Judge Analisa Torres has approved the participation of an investment banker declarant, Andrew A. Kunsak....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-approves-investment-banker-as-declarant-sec-vs-ripple-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Judge Approves Investment Banker as Declarant in SEC vs. Ripple Legal Battle – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Ripple vs. SEC</category><category>XRP</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-approves-investment-banker-as-declarant-sec-vs-ripple-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122683/324454/ripple-logo-media-library.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="145662"/></item><item><title>Kaiko Research: Bitcoin and Ethereum Are Now Less Volatile Than Ethereum Amid Dwindling Liquidity</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/kaiko-research-bitcoin-ethereum-are-now-less-volatile-than-ethereum-amid-dwindling-liquidity.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) are now slightly less volatile than oil as both assets continue to trade sideways this summer. &lt;br /&gt;
According to new research from Kaiko, the notorious trend of cryptocurrency volatility has taken a sharp decline due to several factors ranging from government policies to wider macroeconomic factors. &lt;br /&gt;
The slowed volatility change in the top two digital assets has now seen it drop to “multi-year lows, slightly below oil prices.” ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kaiko-research-bitcoin-ethereum-are-now-less-volatile-than-ethereum-amid-dwindling-liquidity.htm"&gt;Read More: Kaiko Research: Bitcoin and Ethereum Are Now Less Volatile Than Ethereum Amid Dwindling Liquidity&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Oil</category><category>Volatility</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/kaiko-research-bitcoin-ethereum-are-now-less-volatile-than-ethereum-amid-dwindling-liquidity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122681/324437/bitcoin-gd222dceae-1280-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="303357"/></item><item><title>Rollbit Coin is Going to Zero as RLB Plummets 11% in Hours While This New Meme Coin Approaches $50,000 – 100x Potential?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-plummets-11-hours-while-new-meme-coin-approaches-50000-100x-potential.htm</link><description>As the GambleFi narrative continues to grip crypto markets, leading crypto gamling platform Rollbit coin (RLB) appears to be attempting a bounce back - but amid a major tumble many are asking is Rollbit going to zero? &lt;br /&gt;
With markets excited about the growth prospects for crypto projects taking aim at the $63Bn global online gambling space, top online casino projects have exploded across the summer tailing market leader RLB which surged +197% so far this month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-plummets-11-hours-while-new-meme-coin-approaches-50000-100x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: Rollbit Coin is Going to Zero as RLB Plummets 11% in Hours While This New Meme Coin Approaches $50,000 – 100x Potential?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rollbit-coin-going-zero-as-rlb-plummets-11-hours-while-new-meme-coin-approaches-50000-100x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122673/324432/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1246537"/></item><item><title>US Rep. Warren Davidson Claims Some XRP Holders “So Hyper-Defensive” of Ripple’s CBDC Work</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-rep-warren-davidson-claims-some-xrp-holders-so-hyper-defensive-of-ripples-cbdc-work.htm</link><description>US Congressman Warren Davidson who has been increasingly vocal against a central bank digital currency (CBDC) lately, said that some Ripple token (XRP) holders are “hyper-defensive” about Ripple’s recent CBDC moves. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Twitter (X) post on Aug. 15, Davidson noted that he was surprised by the responses from the XRP Twitter community regarding Ripple’s venture into CBDCs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-rep-warren-davidson-claims-some-xrp-holders-so-hyper-defensive-of-ripples-cbdc-work.htm"&gt;Read More: US Rep. Warren Davidson Claims Some XRP Holders “So Hyper-Defensive” of Ripple’s CBDC Work&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-rep-warren-davidson-claims-some-xrp-holders-so-hyper-defensive-of-ripples-cbdc-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122674/324419/coin-3786691-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="183412"/></item><item><title>McDonald's Offers Exclusive Grimace NFTs: Collectible, But No Trading Option</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mcdonalds-offers-exclusive-grimace-nfts-collectible-but-no-trading-option.htm</link><description>McDonald's Singapore has teamed up with crypto infrastructure startup Bandwagon Labs and local non-fungible token (NFT) artist 'The Hidden Walls' to launch Grimace digital collectibles - soulbound tokens and keepsakes that can be minted for free, but not traded or transferred. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mcdonalds-offers-exclusive-grimace-nfts-collectible-but-no-trading-option.htm"&gt;Read More: McDonald's Offers Exclusive Grimace NFTs: Collectible, But No Trading Option&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>McDonald's</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Art</category><category>Polygon</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mcdonalds-offers-exclusive-grimace-nfts-collectible-but-no-trading-option.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122659/324412/screenshot-2023-08-17-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="235834"/></item><item><title>XBULL Token is Up 1,000% Today But Crypto Experts Say It's a Scam – Here's What They're Stacking Instead</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xbull-token-up-1000-today-but-crypto-experts-say-its-scam-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm</link><description>XBULL is the latest straight-to-DEX meme coin making waves in crypto markets this week, after huge traction fuelled a sensational +1,000% opening pump on launch. &lt;br /&gt;
The spectacular display comes amid a frenzy in DEX markets, which has seen upstart projects explode on the back of trending crypto narratives like BASE and Telegram Bots. &lt;br /&gt;
XBULL appears to tap into the narrative surrounding Elon Musk's rebranding of Twitter to X....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xbull-token-up-1000-today-but-crypto-experts-say-its-scam-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm"&gt;Read More: XBULL Token is Up 1,000% Today But Crypto Experts Say It's a Scam – Here's What They're Stacking Instead&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xbull-token-up-1000-today-but-crypto-experts-say-its-scam-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122663/324411/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1341850"/></item><item><title>Former President Donald Trump's Crypto Wallet Being Monitored by Arkham Intelligence – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-president-donald-trumps-crypto-wallet-being-monitored-by-arkham-intelligence-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Blockchain intelligence firm Arkham Intelligence has revealed that it is now actively tracking the wallet it believes belongs to former President Donald Trump to gather more information.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a series of Twitter threads on Wednesday, Arkham claimed that Trump is the owner of a cryptocurrency wallet that is collecting millions in royalty payments from non-fungible tokens (NFTs). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-president-donald-trumps-crypto-wallet-being-monitored-by-arkham-intelligence-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Former President Donald Trump's Crypto Wallet Being Monitored by Arkham Intelligence – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Arkham Intelligence</category><category>Donald Trump</category><category>NFTs</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-president-donald-trumps-crypto-wallet-being-monitored-by-arkham-intelligence-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122670/324404/c911318571-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="62408"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Investors in UK Face Setback as Paypal Suspends Crypto Purchases</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-investors-uk-face-setback-as-paypal-suspends-crypto-purchases.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin price grapples with a decline, trading at $28,643 and witnessing a decrease of nearly 2% on Thursday, BTC investors in the UK face a new challenge. &lt;br /&gt;
Paypal, a major facilitator of online transactions, has temporarily halted all cryptocurrency purchases in the UK, attributing the move to recent regulatory changes. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-investors-uk-face-setback-as-paypal-suspends-crypto-purchases.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Investors in UK Face Setback as Paypal Suspends Crypto Purchases&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-investors-uk-face-setback-as-paypal-suspends-crypto-purchases.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122652/324377/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1526945"/></item><item><title>Prosecution's Strategy: Caroline Ellison's Personal Notes to Serve as Key Evidence Against Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/prosecutions-strategy-caroline-ellisons-personal-notes-to-serve-as-key-evidence-against-former-ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-1.htm</link><description>In an August 14 submission to the U.S. District Court in the Southern District of New York, prosecutors stated their plan to introduce Caroline Ellison's to-do lists and notes as evidence, including a note labeled "Things Sam is Freaking Out About."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/prosecutions-strategy-caroline-ellisons-personal-notes-to-serve-as-key-evidence-against-former-ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Prosecution's Strategy: Caroline Ellison's Personal Notes to Serve as Key Evidence Against Former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>SBF</category><category>FTX</category><category>Caroline Ellison</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/prosecutions-strategy-caroline-ellisons-personal-notes-to-serve-as-key-evidence-against-former-ftx-ceo-sam-bankman-fried-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122646/324370/ftx-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="121337"/></item><item><title>Kazakhstan Takes Another Step Closer to CBDC Launch – Digital Tenge on Its Way?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/kazakhstan-takes-another-step-closer-cbdc-launch-digital-tenge-its-way.htm</link><description>Kazakhstan is edging closer to the “launch” of a CBDC, making it the latest former Soviet nation to announce its foray into the digital fiat sphere. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Telesputnik, the Central Bank laid out a detailed proposal for a digital version of the fiat tenge to the nation’s Supreme Audit Chamber. &lt;br /&gt;
The bank began initial tests on a CBDC back in 2021, but was previously reluctant to commit to a rollout....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/kazakhstan-takes-another-step-closer-cbdc-launch-digital-tenge-its-way.htm"&gt;Read More: Kazakhstan Takes Another Step Closer to CBDC Launch – Digital Tenge on Its Way?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Kazakhstan</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/kazakhstan-takes-another-step-closer-cbdc-launch-digital-tenge-its-way.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122631/324328/adobestock-626771541.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="596894"/></item><item><title>‘High-Net-Worth’ Chileans Growing Crypto Keen, Says Expert</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/high-net-worth-chileans-growing-crypto-keen-says-expert.htm</link><description>“High-net-worth-individuals” in Chile are growing increasingly keen on crypto investment, an expert has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
Per America Economia, the comments were made by Christopher Storaker, the CEO of Arch Finance, a crypto investment firm with a presence in the Latin American country. &lt;br /&gt;
Storaker said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/high-net-worth-chileans-growing-crypto-keen-says-expert.htm"&gt;Read More: ‘High-Net-Worth’ Chileans Growing Crypto Keen, Says Expert&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Chile</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/high-net-worth-chileans-growing-crypto-keen-says-expert.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122523/324095/adobestock-433818109.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="684348"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now August 16 – SEI, THORChain, Toncoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency markets fell on Wednesday, with total market cap dropping by around $16 billion to around $1.1 trillion, Bitcoin (BTC) dropping 1.5% to around $28,700 and Ether (ETH) dropping 1.1% to just above $1,800, where it is now finding support from its 200DMA. &lt;br /&gt;
Downward moves in the crypto market come amid macro headwinds, with US stock markets falling while long-dated US government bond yields and the US dollar rise in wake of the latest Fed minutes release....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now August 16 – SEI, THORChain, Toncoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sei blockchain</category><category>SEI</category><category>Toncoin</category><category>TON</category><category>THORChain</category><category>RUNE</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122643/324346/best-crypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Developers Launch Shibarium, Ushering In New Era of Growth for SHIB Ecosystem</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu developers have launched their highly anticipated, purpose-built Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Shibarium, ushering in a new era of growth for one of the crypto industry’s largest decentralized communities. &lt;br /&gt;
The launch announcement was made at the Blockchain Futurist Conference/ETH Toronto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Developers Launch Shibarium, Ushering In New Era of Growth for SHIB Ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Shibarium</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Ethereum layer-2</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122634/324342/adobestock-468262659-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4483045"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Tumble and BTC Falls to $29,000 – Here are Key Levels to Watch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</link><description>The volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market is once again underscored as Bitcoin, the foremost digital currency, witnesses a significant drop, plummeting to levels around $29,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst an overall tumble in crypto prices, the immediate trajectory and stability of Bitcoin remain the subjects of fervent debate. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Tumble and BTC Falls to $29,000 – Here are Key Levels to Watch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122633/324341/16-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="490072"/></item><item><title>Cat Coin, Shibarium Token Pumping on Uniswap - Are They Scams? Best Meme Coin Alternatives</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm</link><description>A BNB blockchain-based meme coin called Cat (CAT) is has pumped up over 100% on Wednesday, while another meme coin called Shibarium Token (SHIBARIUM) is up over 130%. &lt;br /&gt;
The former’s latest rally has pushed its market cap back to the north of $1 million, with over $2.5 million in trading volumes coming in in the last 24 hours alone. &lt;br /&gt;
CAT now has nearly 12,000 holders, impressive stuff....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm"&gt;Read More: Cat Coin, Shibarium Token Pumping on Uniswap - Are They Scams? Best Meme Coin Alternatives&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shibie</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122632/324331/shibie.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="214151"/></item></channel></rss>
