<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:07:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ankr Taps Matter Labs to Launch zkSync Era Nodes, Hyperchains on Microsoft&#8217;s Azure</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ankr-taps-matter-labs-to-launch-zksync-era-nodes-hyperchains-on-microsofts-azure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261353</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ankr-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ankr-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The collaboration between Ankr, Microsoft Azure, and zkSync Era, is being touted as "infrastructure trifecta."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The decentralized blockchain infrastructure provider, Ankr, has teamed up with Matter Labs to launch dedicated zkSync Era Nodes and Hyperchain blockchain solutions on the Microsoft Azure Marketplace. The main objective is to promote Web3 development growth and enterprise adoption by providing a gateway that is readily accessible to blockchain infrastructure available to Azure&#8217;s customers.</p>
<p>Ankr’s specialized solutions, coupled with zkSync Era’s scalable blockchain network, as well as Microsoft’s cloud infrastructure, are expected to lower the barrier to entry and ignite enterprise adoption of blockchains.</p>
<h2>Infrastructure Trifecta Promoting Web3 Growth</h2>
<p>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the new solutions for the zkSync Era network will be available on the recently launched Ankr’s Microsoft Azure Marketplace listings.</p>
<p>The zkSync Era node deployment service will provide worldwide blockchain connectivity, enabling any enterprise or web3 project to establish connections or develop web3 applications on zkSync Era, which happens to be a zkEVM Ethereum Layer-2 scaling protocol.</p>
<p>The future zkSync Era Hyperchains solution, on the other hand, is designed to allow enterprises to seamlessly build and launch their own dedicated Hyperchain blockchain. These Hyperchains will offer complete customization options to meet their specific requirements for privacy, performance, and security. Additionally, Ankr&#8217;s team will provide comprehensive engineering and support services to empower enterprises in implementing their web3 strategies.</p>
<p>Matter Labs&#8217; senior vice president of business and operations, Marco Cora, highlighted the need to accommodate the complex web2 use cases with the most stringent requirements in terms of security, performance, and privacy, among other factors to scale blockchain technology like the internet.</p>
<p>To that extent, Cora believes that the collaboration between Ankr, Microsoft Azure, and zkSync Era, which the exec refers to as an &#8220;infrastructure trifecta,&#8221; will diminish the barrier to entry and spark widespread enterprise adoption of blockchains. Coupled with the recently announced ZK Stack, Cora anticipates more enterprise use cases to accelerate on zkSync Era.</p>
<p>Talking about the latest development, Chandler Song, Ankr&#8217;s Co-Founder and CEO, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By offering the ability to build on zkSync Era via Ankr’s Microsoft Azure Marketplace solutions, we are breaking barriers to entry for an array of businesses that need their unique scalability and performance requirements met before they begin building out their Web3 initiatives.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Ankr <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ankr-partners-with-microsoft-to-offer-enterprise-node-hosting-services/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with Microsoft in February this year to offer an enterprise node hosting service. More recently, the Web 3 infrastructure provider <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ankrs-enterprise-rpc-services-goes-live-on-microsofts-azure-marketplace/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the launch of Enterprise RPC services on Microsoft’s Azure Marketplace to offer a gateway to blockchain infrastructure for the cloud computing platform&#8217;s customers.</p>
<h2>Buzz Around Zero-Knowledge Proofs</h2>
<p>Zero-knowledge rollups (ZK-rollups) have gained significant prominence this year with multiple launches and subsequent optimizations. Matter Labs is the team behind zkSync Era, Ethereum&#8217;s third-largest Layer 2 network, which became the first zkEVM to be made publicly available in March. ZK Stack was introduced in June that leverages recursive scaling and &#8220;hyperchains&#8221; to build an ecosystem of interoperable protocols and sovereign chains.</p>
<p>Despite a muted start, zkSync Era has steadily continued its uptrend <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/projects/zksync-era" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">notching</a> an all-time high of over $735 million in total value locked in the first week of July.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ankr-taps-matter-labs-to-launch-zksync-era-nodes-hyperchains-on-microsofts-azure/" rel="nofollow">Ankr Taps Matter Labs to Launch zkSync Era Nodes, Hyperchains on Microsoft&#8217;s Azure</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Whale and Ethereum ICO Member Deposit $250 Million Holdings To Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-whale-and-ethereum-ico-member-deposit-250-million-holdings-to-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ICO]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261490</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WhaleEthereum-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/WhaleEthereum-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[On-chain finds that a whale holding coins from Ethereum’s launch has finally moved his $116 million holdings.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two separate whales each holding over 9 figures worth of crypto have transferred to holdings to exchanges over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>One whale owned an address that participated in Ethereum’s ICO back in 2014, and hadn’t moved his coins since.</p>
<ul>
<li>As <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1681476159253680128" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> by the Twitter blockchain tracker Lookonchain, an Ethereum ICO participant moved 61,216 ETH worth $116 million to the crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-the-fbi-raided-kraken-founder-jesse-powells-home-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kraken</a> on Tuesday.</li>
<li>According to <a href="https://t.co/HLSXvqyBDb" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Etherscan</a>, the address had zero other significant activity, having received its entire ETH stash from the Ethereum Genesis address over 2,911 days ago. At that time, ETH was worth just $0.31.</li>
<li>The Genesis address is often referred to as a “Black hole”: any crypto sent there cannot be retrieved, yet it remains one of the wealthier Ethereum addresses on the network, holding 11,743 ETH at writing time.</li>
<li>Before his transfer, the ICO participant appeared to conduct a test transaction worth 0.5 ETH, before sending his entire ETH stash into the exchange.<br />
The following day, Lookonchain <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1681584804779933696" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> that a separate Bitcoin (BTC) whale had transferred a whopping $4,451 BTC over to Binance, worth another $133 million.</li>
<li>
<blockquote><p>“The last time the whale deposited a large amount of BTC(5,000 BTC, worth $118M) to Binance was on Jan 30, and the price of BTC dropped by ~4.2% after depositing,” the account stated.</p></blockquote>
</li>
<li>Experts often view a rising Bitcoin balance on exchanges as a signal that investors intend to sell their coins.</li>
<li>This year, the U.S. government announced an even larger sale of Bitcoin pertaining to the large stack – ~9000 BTC – seized from the Silk Road hacker in 2021.</li>
<li>On-chain data shows that the government <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dump-incoming-us-government-moves-another-9000-btc-from-silk-road/" data-wpel-link="internal">transferred</a> a similar size batch of BTC out of its wallet this month, possibly indicating another sale.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-whale-and-ethereum-ico-member-deposit-250-million-holdings-to-exchanges/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Whale and Ethereum ICO Member Deposit $250 Million Holdings To Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX COO Hired by Sino Global Capital: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-coo-hired-by-sino-global-capital-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261335</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ftx_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ftx_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After FTX went down, Ms Wang took a short hiatus before returning to the crypto sector.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While FTX and SBF, respectively, continue to appear in court, former executives of the defunct crypto trading group have started to pop up elsewhere.</p>
<p>Amy Wu, who was previously an executive at FTX Ventures, has since joined Menlo Ventures, a mainstay of Silicon Valley’s venture capital ecosystem. Brett Harrison, who led FTX US before <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ex-ftx-us-president-hints-at-future-disclosure-of-insider-info/" data-wpel-link="internal">resigning</a> two months prior to the collapse, is banking on the AI hype train and has since founded a startup that plans to build a trading algorithm around GPT-4.</p>
<p>Zhe “Constance” Wang – the former Chief Operating Officer of FTX – allegedly left for China shortly after FTX imploded and has since been hired by Sino Global Capital, a China-based crypto investment fund.</p>
<h2>New Position in Line With Previous Experience</h2>
<p>For the past four and a half years, Wang has been an executive at FTX, serving as COO for 3 years and nine months.</p>
<p>Zhe Wang’s experience in the crypto sector goes further back than her stint as FTX COO. Before joining the former behemoth, Wang worked as an investment analyst at Credit Suisse for two years before a brief stint at Huobi, according to her LinkedIn <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/constancewz/?originalSubdomain=bs" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">profile</a>.</p>
<p>Wang’s new career move was <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-19/ex-ftx-chief-operating-officer-constance-wang-joins-vc-firm-sino-global-capital#xj4y7vzkg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by Bloomberg, which cited a confidential source that refrained from revealing too many details about the position.</p>
<h2>Previous Ties to SGC</h2>
<p>It’s important to note that Brett Harrison, Amy Wu, and Zhe Wang have not been accused of any wrongdoing – and with the treasure trove of evidence unearthed by U.S. authorities, evidence of intentional wrongdoing would probably have since surfaced.</p>
<p>However, the ties between SGC and FTX go back to the very beginning, according to SBF himself.</p>
<p>SGC, which was founded in 2015 by Beijing-based investor Matthew Graham, was an early investor in FTX. As recently as 2021, SGC launched a brand new $200 million fund with FTX acting as one of the leading investors.<br />
SBF thanked the SGC team for their collaboration, mentioning the powerful impact they allegedly had on FTX.</p>
<blockquote><p>“From the very beginning, Matthew and the Sino Global Capital team supported the FTX vision and then worked with us to help make it a reality.”</p></blockquote>
<p>As acting COO, it’s not hard to imagine that Wang benefited from networking with the SGC team – networking that has since led to a new position in the crypto investment sector.</p>
<p>For now, Zhe Wang is not listed as a member of <a href="https://www.sinoglobalcapital.com/team/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">SGC</a>, and her alleged new position within the firm is as of yet unknown.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-coo-hired-by-sino-global-capital-report/" rel="nofollow">Former FTX COO Hired by Sino Global Capital: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Burn Kenny ICO Launch Generating Excitement Following Success of Fellow South Park Token Mr. Hankey Coin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/burn-kenny-ico-launch-generating-excitement-following-success-of-fellow-south-park-token-mr-hankey-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261424</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kenny_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/kenny_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[An incredible 30% token burn has seen Burn Kenny ($KENNY) become the biggest name on the lips of meme coin buyers across Web3 ahead of its ICO launch this week. The newly launched Burn Kenny ($KENNY) has become one of the most talked about projects in the space as it follows in the footsteps of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An incredible 30% token burn has seen Burn Kenny ($KENNY) become the biggest name on the lips of meme coin buyers across Web3 ahead of its ICO launch this week.</p>
<p>The newly launched <a href="https://bs_fa368e66.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=burn-kenny-ico-launch-generating-excitement-following-success-of-fellow-south-park-token-mr-hankey-coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Burn Kenny ($KENNY)</a> has become one of the most talked about projects in the space as it follows in the footsteps of another South Park-themed token, Mr Hankey Coin.</p>
<p>Not only did $HANKEY sell out its presale in just 10 hours, it then went on to pump nearly 200% after reaching exchanges.</p>
<p>KENNY may well go one better and is shaping up to beat that record and sell out in even quicker time.</p>
<h2>Excitement Grows Over Burn Potential</h2>
<p>Token burns have long been an extremely effective method of increasing prices, sparking pumps and increasing the long-term health of a coin.</p>
<p>The likes of Shiba Inu, Cronos, and Luna Classic have all employed token burns that had hugely successful impacts on their projects, and Burn Kenny is the latest to employ a significant burn.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261428" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="936" height="694" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23-300x222.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23-768x569.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-23-50x37.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>While LUNC, for example, has burned only 1% of its massive token supply, KENNY is set to burn 30% of its tokens.</p>
<p>Furthermore, that burn will take place over just three days &#8211; which could see incredible volume and interest as buyers rush to secure their tokens.</p>
<p>The total supply is 6,666,666,666 tokens, but 2 billion of those will be removed in 72 hours, with Burn Kenny to remove 10% per day for the first three days after launching on a decentralized exchange.</p>
<p>This could not only spark FOMO from other investors but also incentivizes holding &#8211; with buyers holding onto tokens for longer, knowing a price jump is possibly coming.</p>
<h2>Discreet ICO Could Sell Out in Hours</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_fa368e66.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=burn-kenny-ico-launch-generating-excitement-following-success-of-fellow-south-park-token-mr-hankey-coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Burn Kenny</a> has followed in the footsteps of another shitcoin, Mr. Hankey Coin, to offer a discreet ICO launch that will bring several benefits to the project as a whole.</p>
<p>Expected on Thursday, July 20, the ICO is rumored to be starting at 6 pm CET &#8211; however, buyers will need to follow the project’s social media channels (below) to get an exact time of the launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261427" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="936" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22-300x106.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22-768x272.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-22-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>That secret launch has sparked yet more buyer interest, while the ICO has a small hard cap of just $500k and a fixed price of $0.0001875.</p>
<p>This small price, with no minimum or maximum investment, makes it open to all and also stops early adopters from dumping on latecomers &#8211; something that has been seen in multiple presales in recent times.</p>
<p>HANKEY sold out in just 10 hours but KENNY could go one better given its robust burn, something that Mr Hankey Coin did not offer.</p>
<p>The presale will offer 2,666,666,666 tokens (40% of supply) with the final 30% set aside for liquidity.</p>
<p>This large amount of liquidity will ensure that all trades are met and should ensure high trading volume &#8211; liquidity is also locked meaning there is no chance of a rug pull or pump-and-dump.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261426" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="936" height="748" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16-300x240.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16-768x614.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-16-50x40.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>The Burn Kenny token has been developed by an anonymous group but they are extremely well placed in Web3 with long experience of success and connections in multiple alpha investment groups and with exchanges.</p>
<p>KENNY has also already caught the attention of token analysts and traders on YouTube, <a href="https://youtu.be/Kfk6zTghPDc" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">with one describing it as a ‘rocket ship’</a>.</p>
<p>For more information on the project, read through the <a href="https://burnkenny.vip/assets/pdf/Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a> &#8211; tokens can be purchased on <a href="https://bs_fa368e66.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">burnkenny.vip</a> with ETH or USDT.</p>
<p>Follow the <a href="https://twitter.com/BurnKennyCoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter page</a> and join the <a href="https://t.me/BurnKennyOfficial" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram group</a> to get the exact times on the launch and the latest news on the project.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_fa368e66.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=burn-kenny-ico-launch-generating-excitement-following-success-of-fellow-south-park-token-mr-hankey-coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Burn Kenny</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/burn-kenny-ico-launch-generating-excitement-following-success-of-fellow-south-park-token-mr-hankey-coin/" rel="nofollow">Burn Kenny ICO Launch Generating Excitement Following Success of Fellow South Park Token Mr. Hankey Coin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy to Back the US Dollar With Bitcoin if Elected</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-to-back-the-us-dollar-with-bitcoin-if-elected/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 19:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261316</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kennedy's possible cabinet could back 1% of issued T-bills with bitcoin or precious metals, whereas later it could dive deeper. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US presidential candidate from the Democratic party &#8211; Robert F. Kennedy &#8211; vowed to strengthen America&#8217;s official currency by backing it with bitcoin, gold, silver, and platinum.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several finance experts, such as Robert Kiyosaki, have predicted a gloomy future for the dollar, advising consumers to invest in the primary cryptocurrency or precious metals. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy&#8217;s Next Plan Involving Bitcoin</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy &#8211; the nephew of the former US President John F. Kennedy &#8211; has presented himself as one of the most passionate advocates of bitcoin. The 69-year-old environmental lawyer has also positioned the leading digital asset at the center of his presidential campaign. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cdn.jwplayer.com/previews/5S9igNBe" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">appearance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the Heal-the-Divide PAC, he vowed to back the American dollar with &#8220;real finite assets,&#8221; including bitcoin and certain precious metals should he become the 47th President of the States. In his view, the move will guarantee the strength of the greenback and its &#8220;continuous success&#8221; as the world&#8217;s reserve currency.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy explained that such potential backing would include US treasury bills, notes, and bonds as his cabinet will act quite carefully at first: </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;My plan would be to start very, very small: perhaps 1% of issued T-bills would be backed by hard currency: by gold, silver, platinum, or bitcoin, and then depending on the outcome, we would increase that annually.&#8221;<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249147" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249147" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249147" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b.jpg 1500w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Robert-Kennedy-Jr-b94f6316ca2e4850b0e6ed6da75bd74b-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249147" class="wp-caption-text">Robert Kennedy Jr. Source: People</figcaption></figure></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The presidential candidate outlined the worrying economic condition of the United States caused by the global COVID-19 pandemic, the increasing interest rates by the Federal Reserve, and the subsequent inflation. Kennedy believes backing treasury bills with bitcoin could strengthen the value of those short-term securities and thus support local businesses.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is not the first time Kennedy has fired shots at the US central bank. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/jfks-nephew-bitcoin-is-an-escape-route-from-the-turmoil-caused-by-the-fed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in April that the institution had collaborated with numerous banks between 2008-2022 to print a colossal amount of money. He also claimed BTC could serve as an &#8220;escape route&#8221; amid the consecutive turbulence. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Making America a Global Crypto Hub</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy, a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-holds-bitcoin-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC HODLer</a> with up to $250,000 worth of the asset, has pledged that one mission of his administration would be to turn the United States into a global cryptocurrency center. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes employing renewable energy in bitcoin mining, and the multiple initiatives surrounding the biggest crypto asset could attract investors and entrepreneurs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Democrat claimed his cabinet will make sure to recognize BTC as &#8220;not a security&#8221; and create &#8220;strong barriers&#8221; against the issuance of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, he assured he would &#8220;exempt the conversion of bitcoin to the US dollar from capital gains taxes.&#8221;</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-to-back-the-us-dollar-with-bitcoin-if-elected/" rel="nofollow">Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy to Back the US Dollar With Bitcoin if Elected</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Schiff&#8217;s Son Is No Longer A Bitcoin Believer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-schiffs-son-is-no-longer-a-bitcoin-believer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261457</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/peterschiff_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/peterschiff_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Spencer Schiff once believed Bitcoin would be worth tens of millions of dollars some day. Now, he says it's headed to zero.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Once a fervent and laser-eyed Bitcoin (BTC) bull, Spencer Schiff – son of crypto critic and gold bug Peter Schiff – is now in agreement with his father that Bitcoin’s price is headed to zero.</p>
<p>His reasoning, however, greatly differs from his father’s, who he believes is “completely wrong about the economy.”</p>
<h2>No Longer A Bitcoin Believer?</h2>
<p>Spencer Schiff voiced his new take on Bitcoin in response to ZeroHedge on Twitter, who published a blog post predicting an incoming “Great Depression.”</p>
<p>The former strongly <a href="https://twitter.com/SpencerKSchiff/status/1681310274295599107" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">disagreed</a>, claiming that the economy was about to enter “an unfathomably enormous economic boom,” that would greatly bolster the average American’s standard of living. Yet in his view, this boom will not relate to Bitcoin:</p>
<p>“I don’t think Bitcoin will have a major impact on the world, and its price will probably fall to near zero over the next few years,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/SpencerKSchiff/status/1681322456030560256" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">predicted</a> on Tuesday. “My thesis is an AI thesis.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">My changing views have nothing to do with the bear market. I was still mega bullish on bitcoin on the day it bottomed  late last year. I even convinced my mom to buy some right at the bottom. The only reason I don’t care about bitcoin anymore is AI. If not for AI, I would still…</p>
<p>&mdash; Spencer Schiff (@SpencerKSchiff) <a href="https://twitter.com/SpencerKSchiff/status/1681497776406900738?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Spencer Schiff has for years opined that Bitcoin is an excellent long-term investment and inflation hedge. In March 2021, his father <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-schiffs-son-goes-all-in-on-bitcoin-hes-hodling-to-infinity-or-bust/" data-wpel-link="internal">claimed</a> that he went “all in” on Bitcoin shortly after Bitcoin’s price dropped below $50,000.</p>
<p>Though Bitcoin’s price has fluctuated far lower since that time, he said as recently as April 2023 that Bitcoin was “likely to demonetize gold” in the long term. Both assets are often compared as inflation hedges due to their limited supply relative to fiat currencies.</p>
<p>While Schiff once believed that irresponsible monetary policy would soon lead to hyperinflation of the US dollar, he now asserts that productivity gains from artificial intelligence will trigger exponential growth in productivity that solves any societal problems related to inflation.</p>
<p>“No matter how much they print, prices will still collapse,” he said. “Central banks don’t matter anymore. Annual economic output is about to increase 1,000x from 2023’s output. Maybe 1,000,000x higher by 2040.”</p>
<h2>Not Like His Father</h2>
<p>In a reply to <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Spencer Schiff clarified that while he now believes his father’s long-term price forecast for Bitcoin is correct, it is “only by accident”:</p>
<p>“My dad’s anti-bitcoin arguments are really bad and don’t even make sense,” he said. “He’s completely wrong about the economy and I strongly discourage people from following his investment advice.”</p>
<p>Peter Schiff has blasted Bitcoin investors for over a decade for thinking the asset can be effective money, arguing that it lacks “intrinsic value.” By contrast, his son still believes Bitcoin is superior money compared to the dollar, but that its benefits will be <a href="https://twitter.com/SpencerKSchiff/status/1681672546515648519" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">“trivial”</a> thanks to AI’s seismic increases in global productivity.</p>
<p>In April, Peter Schiff <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-schiff-applauds-chatgpt-for-not-recommending-bitcoin-investments/" data-wpel-link="internal">applauded</a> the AI bot ChatGPT for seemingly recommending gold as an investment over Bitcoin. Nevertheless, he still claimed AI is a “passing fad” on Wednesday, and that much of its young fan base will outgrow the technology – as with Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">My son <a href="https://twitter.com/SpencerKSchiff?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SpencerKSchiff</a> is no longer bullish on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a>. As young people typically do, he&#39;s lost interest in a passing fad and moved on to something new. In this case it&#39;s <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#AI</a> that&#39;s captivated his attention. As Bitcoin&#39;s young fan base matures many more will grow out of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>&mdash; Peter Schiff (@PeterSchiff) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterSchiff/status/1681664026592309250?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-schiffs-son-is-no-longer-a-bitcoin-believer/" rel="nofollow">Peter Schiff&#8217;s Son Is No Longer A Bitcoin Believer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Records 661% Increase in Hash Rate in 2 Years: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-records-661-increase-in-hash-rate-in-2-years-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261421</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bitcoin_Network.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bitcoin_Network.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin network fundamentals are stronger than ever, according to CryptoQuant's exec.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The choppy market has caused severe headwinds for Bitcoin miners as the hash rate reaches new record highs. The rise comes ahead of the much anticipated halving event slated for next spring that is expected to catalyze the largest crypto asset&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p>Recent data suggested that Bitcoin&#8217;s hash rate has increased by nearly 661% in the last two years. According to CryptoQuant CEO Ki Young Ju, such a feat demonstrates that the &#8220;network fundamentals are the strongest ever.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a>&#8216;s network fundamentals are the strongest ever, with a 661% increase in hash rate in two years.<a href="https://t.co/IwcFXPKOjH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/IwcFXPKOjH</a> <a href="https://t.co/rczHpmZ9lC" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/rczHpmZ9lC</a></p>
<p>— Ki Young Ju (@ki_young_ju) <a href="https://twitter.com/ki_young_ju/status/1681545197015146497?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>The hash rate can be referred to as the computational power used to mine a cryptocurrency. The upcoming halving event will slash the miners&#8217; rewards by half.</li>
<li>The rising hash rate comes the backdrop of an all-time mining difficulty of the network, which currently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-exceeds-50t-for-the-first-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">stands</a> near 54 trillion.</li>
<li>The Ordinals&#8217; craze has a crucial role to play as well, as Bitcoin miners started deploying more and more mining machines, thereby boosting the network’s computing power.</li>
<li>While high hash rates and mining difficulty hovering near record highs indicate that miners are bullish on Bitcoin, that has not stopped them from selling large volumes of BTC to crypto exchanges at a profit, as per Bitfinex&#8217;s latest <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/bitfinex-alpha/bitfinex-alpha-bitcoin-miners-make-hay-while-the-sun-shines-but-are-hedging-their-bets-too/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">study</a>. Such a trend &#8220;potentially showcases new miner behavior.&#8221;</li>
<li>Meanwhile, JPMorgan analysts suggest that Bitcoin&#8217;s price, as well as the transaction fees, will need to rise significantly to compensate for the lower block reward following the upcoming halving event, especially with volatile electricity costs and increasing competition among miners that has shot up the cost of production.</li>
<li>The multinational investment bank previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-what-needs-to-happen-for-bitcoin-to-reach-45k-this-year-according-to-jpmorgan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> that Bitcoin could go up by another 75% this year if it gets embraced as a similar investment tool as gold.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-records-661-increase-in-hash-rate-in-2-years-data/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Records 661% Increase in Hash Rate in 2 Years: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Societe Generale&#8217;s Crypto Arm Becomes First Entity to Score France&#8217;s DASP License</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/societe-generales-crypto-arm-becomes-first-entity-to-score-frances-dasp-license/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[France]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261437</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/SG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/SG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The development comes three months after SG Forge launched a stablecoin pegged to the euro on Ethereum, called 'EUR CoinVertible.']]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Societe Generale&#8217;s crypto arm &#8211; SG Forge &#8211; announced acquiring a regulatory license approval as Digital Asset Service Provider from the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF). With it, SG Forge has become the first company to receive a license from France&#8217;s financial regulator as a digital asset provider.</p>
<p>The DASP license represents the highest level of regulatory certification currently possible for digital asset activities. It is important to note that over 80 entities are currently <a href="https://www.amf-france.org/en/professionals/fintech/my-relations-amf/obtain-dasp-authorisation#List_of_DASPs_licensed_by_the_AMF" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">registered</a> with the AMF, including Binance. But none of them have managed to score a full license until SG Forge&#8217;s approval.</p>
<h2>French DASP License</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.sgforge.com/first-dasp-license-amf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, SG Forge will be able to serve French customers as a custodian for digital assets, enable the buying and selling of them using legal tender, trade them for other digital assets, and handle third-party orders.</p>
<p>the approval by a major EU national regulator is a huge milestone for SG Forge, especially for the development of its recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/societe-generales-crypto-arm-unveils-euro-stablecoin-on-ethereum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">deployed</a> Euro CoinVertible (EURCV). SocGen said that the move is also crucial for its plans to meet the demands from institutional clients for digital assets.</p>
<p>In a statement, Jean-Marc Stenger, Chief Executive Officer of SocGen&#8217;s Forge, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the DASP license approval, Societe Generale &#8211; FORGE confirms its pioneering role in the crypto assets ecosystem. This step will allow us to continue supporting our institutional clients wishing to benefit from services on digital assets that meet the highest standards of compliance and banking security.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>France Crypto License Process</h2>
<p>Over the past couple of years, France has attracted several prominent crypto firms to establish their footprint. For the purpose of operation and offering services such as crypto custody, exchange, or trading services in the country, it&#8217;s mandatory for companies to register with relevant authorities.</p>
<p>But obtaining a license is a complex process as the crypto companies need to establish a base in France and comply with specific regulations stated by the French financial regulator, AMF.</p>
<p>Hence, SocGen said the license approval for its crypto venture depicts a &#8220;comprehensive level of security and reliability of compliance, internal control, and cybersecurity processes and systems, as well as the maintenance of sufficient regulatory capital.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/societe-generales-crypto-arm-becomes-first-entity-to-score-frances-dasp-license/" rel="nofollow">Societe Generale&#8217;s Crypto Arm Becomes First Entity to Score France&#8217;s DASP License</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Hedge Fund Manager Backs Bitcoin &#038; Ethereum Prices to Keep Rising, with BTC20 Also Turning Heads</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-hedge-fund-manager-backs-bitcoin-ethereum-prices-to-keep-rising-with-btc20-also-turning-heads/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261411</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_btc20_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_btc20_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are showing remarkable resilience amidst a turbulent economic environment, evidenced by their decoupling from traditional asset classes. Dan Morehead, CEO of Pantera Capital, predicts this dynamic will allow major cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum to continue rallying over the medium term. Although these two cryptos remain the most talked-about in the space, investors are [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies are showing remarkable resilience amidst a turbulent economic environment, evidenced by their decoupling from traditional asset classes.</p>
<p>Dan Morehead, CEO of Pantera Capital, predicts this dynamic will allow major cryptos like Bitcoin and Ethereum to continue rallying over the medium term.</p>
<p>Although these two cryptos remain the most talked-about in the space, investors are also paying attention to BTC20 – an innovative new token that combines elements of both Bitcoin and Ethereum and has just launched an eagerly-anticipated presale phase.</p>
<h2>Crypto Guru Dan Morehead Forecasts Rally for Bitcoin &amp; Ethereum</h2>
<p>Veteran hedge fund manager Dan Morehead has a long history of successfully investing in top cryptocurrencies before major price increases.</p>
<p>As CEO of Pantera Capital, a US-based hedge fund established in 2003, Morehead has managed a Bitcoin fund that has produced over 42,000% in returns since its inception.</p>
<p>Considering his background and successful track record, Morehead&#8217;s optimistic perspective on Bitcoin and Ethereum is highly influential in the crypto community.</p>
<p>In a recent interview with <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/07/18/we-can-rally-now-the-feds-15-trillion-reason-behind-this-crypto-legends-flip-after-huge-xrp-bombshell-triggered-a-bitcoin-and-ethereum-price-boom/?sh=6aaf9c4a3af7" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Forbes</a>, Morehead stated that “we can rally now” in reference to the potential for the crypto market to recover after a difficult year in 2022.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261415" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="602" height="597" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3-300x298.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-3-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This optimism stems from his interpretation of the Federal Reserve&#8217;s recent activity in the bond markets.</p>
<p>Over the past 15 years, the Fed has purchased huge amounts of bonds – a strategy known as &#8220;quantitative easing.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to Morehead, this aggressive monetary policy artificially suppressed yields, leading investors into the stock market.</p>
<p>However, now that the Fed’s quantitative easing is ending, stocks are expected to decline – yet Morehead highlights that blockchain assets have “massively decoupled” from the equity market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261414" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-2.jpg" alt="Picture8" width="602" height="171" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-2-300x85.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-2-50x14.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This is due to the decentralized nature of cryptocurrencies, combined with their different value drivers relative to stocks.</p>
<p>As such, the crypto market is demonstrating resilience and not being affected as heavily as the stock market.</p>
<p>Consequently, cryptocurrencies can now trade based on their inherent value.</p>
<p>This dynamic is why Morehead is confident that Bitcoin and Ethereum will continue on an upward trajectory.</p>
<p>If crypto adoption continues growing, Morehead sees tremendous potential, even though price volatility remains high.</p>
<h2>Could New Token BTC20 Pump Like Bitcoin &amp; Ethereum?</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=this-hedge-fund-manager-backs-bitcoin-ethereum-prices-to-keep-rising-with-btc20-also-turning-heads" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BTC20 ($BTC20)</a> has emerged as a standout candidate for those searching for high-potential alternatives to Bitcoin and Ethereum.</p>
<p>This new ERC-20 token is attracting attention for its unique blend of Bitcoin’s tokenomics and Ethereum’s advanced technology.</p>
<p>BTC20’s flagship feature is its stake-to-earn protocol, designed for investors seeking a passive income stream.</p>
<p>Operating on a Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus, this protocol is significantly less energy-intensive than Bitcoin mining, making it much more sustainable and environmentally friendly.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261413" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-2.jpg" alt="Picture9" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-2-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-2-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>After BTC20’s presale concludes, a minimum of 14.95 million $BTC20 tokens will be locked into a staking contract and gradually enter circulation over an estimated 120 years.</p>
<p>Per BTC20’s <a href="https://btc20.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, this setup will ensure a consistent income stream for token holders.</p>
<p>Regarding the presale, BTC20&#8217;s team has ingeniously mirrored Bitcoin&#8217;s original supply from 2009.</p>
<p>A total of 6.05 million $BTC20 tokens will be offered during the presale, priced at $1 per token – a homage to when $BTC had the same price.</p>
<p>This enticing setup has attracted crypto enthusiasts and new investors alike, leading to a surge in members of the BTC20 <a href="https://t.me/BTC20Token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a>.</p>
<p>With the presale having already raised $144,000 in just two days, the buzz around BTC20 is beginning to grow – making it an exciting project to watch in the cryptocurrency space.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=this-hedge-fund-manager-backs-bitcoin-ethereum-prices-to-keep-rising-with-btc20-also-turning-heads" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit BTC20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-hedge-fund-manager-backs-bitcoin-ethereum-prices-to-keep-rising-with-btc20-also-turning-heads/" rel="nofollow">This Hedge Fund Manager Backs Bitcoin &#038; Ethereum Prices to Keep Rising, with BTC20 Also Turning Heads</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Q2 2023 Seemed Like a Lost Quarter in the Crypto World: CoinMarketCap Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/q2-2023-seemed-like-a-lost-quarter-in-the-crypto-world-coinmarketcap-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261350</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/crypto_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Q2 lacked strong market narratives compared to Q1, which saw developments like bitcoin price doubling and the rise of layer-2 protools.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report by digital asset price-tracking platform CoinMarketCap revealed that the second quarter (Q2) of 2023 seemed like a lost one in the crypto world because it failed to produce groundbreaking developments.</p>
<p>According to a document seen by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Q2 lacked strong market narratives compared to Q1, which saw developments like bitcoin price <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-skyrockets-to-25k-as-bulls-take-control-heres-the-next-target-bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">doubling</a>, the rise of layer-2 protocols, and a more active non-fungible token (NFT) market.</p>
<h2>A Lost Quarter</h2>
<p>Q2, on the other hand, recorded trends like the memecoin season and the rise of BRC-20 tokens, which CoinMarketCap said was noteworthy but failed to generate the level of excitement witnessed in the previous quarter.</p>
<p>The first and second quarters ended with a similar global crypto market capitalization. The end of Q2 saw the total market cap at $1.17 trillion, indicating a 48% year-to-date increase, but most of that was generated in Q1.</p>
<p>The total spot trading volume of the top 20 crypto exchanges plunged by 36%, reaching an almost dormant state by the end of Q2. After peaking in March, the total trade volume declined to c.$523 billion per month.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261356" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261356" style="width: 512px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TradingVol.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-261356" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TradingVol.png" alt="Spot Trading Volume on Crypto Exchanges. Source: CoinMarketCap" width="512" height="279" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TradingVol.png 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TradingVol-300x163.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TradingVol-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261356" class="wp-caption-text">Spot Trading Volume on Crypto Exchanges. Source: CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<p>Notably, the CoinMarketCap fear and greed index, which began the year at roughly 30, indicating fear, ended the first half at neutral (52), showing a significant improvement in market sentiment.</p>
<h2>Significant Developments</h2>
<p>While Q2 seemed like a lost quarter, some notable events occurred in the crypto space within the timeframe.</p>
<p>One such event is BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, with roughly $9 trillion in assets under management, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). The move <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">spurred</a> several traditional finance giants like ARK Invest, Fidelity Digital, Valkyrie, VanEck, and 21Shares to seek approval from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission for similar Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>Another notable development was the surge in Liquid Staking Derivatives (LSDs), which CoinMarketCap attributed to the Ethereum Shapella upgrade in April. By the end of June, LSD platforms had secured more than a third of Ethereum’s total value staked.</p>
<p>Other significant events include the emergence of an ecosystem of projects focused on making real-world assets tradeable on-chain, the introduction of Decentralized Physical Infrastructure solutions, the increased use of zero-knowledge Sync solutions, and the inception of platforms that enable the restaking of staked ether.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/q2-2023-seemed-like-a-lost-quarter-in-the-crypto-world-coinmarketcap-report/" rel="nofollow">Q2 2023 Seemed Like a Lost Quarter in the Crypto World: CoinMarketCap Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
