<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 10:53:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Three Things That Went Wrong for FTX According to Ripple CTO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-three-things-that-went-wrong-for-ftx-according-to-ripple-cto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228101</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GCCM6JEOHJD5VJAVV44QECLTQQ.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GCCM6JEOHJD5VJAVV44QECLTQQ.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple CTO believes FTX's collapse was due to "incompetence" and "fraud."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>But blockchain firm Ripple&#8217;s Chief Technology Officer, David Schwartz, weighed in on Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s sympathizers but also went on to detail what went wrong with the company.</p>
<h2>Ripple CTO&#8217;s Take on FTX Collapse</h2>
<p>The exec <a href="https://twitter.com/JoelKatz/status/1601004815256981505" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">listed</a> out three things that went &#8220;horribly wrong.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>FTX customer fiat assets were left in Alameda accounts and used by Alameda.</li>
<li>Customer deposits FTX was just supposed to hold were commingled with assets used in riskier ways.</li>
<li>Alameda was supposed to be executing risk-managed, nearly delta-neutral strategies. Somehow, positions weren&#8217;t tracked, risks weren&#8217;t managed at all, and strategies were not at all delta-neutral.</li>
</ul>
<p>While the exec does not want to believe that corruption may have taken place in FTX, he added that even &#8220;willful blindness&#8221; on the leadership of the bankrupt firm&#8217;s part is equally appalling. Schwartz contemplated that &#8220;bad luck&#8221; during a long bear market may cause a lot of crypto companies to shut shop. But that is not the case with FTX and its sister trading firm Alameda.</p>
<h2>Shark Tank Star&#8217;s Puzzling Take on SBF</h2>
<p>But there are industry experts who do not share the same belief that Bankman-Fried may have committed a crime. One such is Shark Tank star and investor Kevin O&#8217;Leary, who confessed to losing $15 million that FTX paid him to be its official spokesperson.</p>
<p>At a time when a major chunk of the crypto community has turned against Bankman-Fried, the television personality&#8217;s comments naturally attracted a significant backlash. The investor had recently stated that SBF should be treated as innocent until proven guilty. In yet another interview, O&#8217;Leary <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftx-bankruptcy-kevin-oleary-would-still-invest-in-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">asserted</a> that he would invest in the disgraced founder should he come up with a new venture.</p>
<p>But Ripple CTO David Schwartz is having a tough time cracking Mr. Wonderful&#8217;s take on the whole fiasco, especially after the latter reinstated faith in the Bankman-Fried&#8217;s trading prowess. Schwartz <a href="https://twitter.com/JoelKatz/status/1600980143354179585" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweeted</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Maybe his thinking is &#8220;Hey, lots of people lost a lot of money, but Sam made sure I made out okay so I&#8217;d do business with him again&#8221;. But if there&#8217;s any other possible explanation, I&#8217;d prefer to believe that. The thing is, I&#8217;m not sure there is any other possible explanation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-three-things-that-went-wrong-for-ftx-according-to-ripple-cto/" rel="nofollow">The Three Things That Went Wrong for FTX According to Ripple CTO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kazakhstan Lawmakers Pass New Bitcoin Mining Bills</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-lawmakers-pass-new-bitcoin-mining-bills/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kazakhstan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227749</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Kazakhstan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Kazakhstan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kazakhstan may no longer be the bitcoin sanctuary it once was, thanks to the new regulation on crypto mining.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers in the country have passed the &#8220;On Digital Assets of the Republic of Kazakhstan&#8221; crypto assets bill and other laws that focus on crypto mining. The Mäjilis, or the lower hours of the Parliament of Kazakhstan, approved the four bills.</p>
<p>Following the Chinese miner exodus, Kazakhstan emerged as one of the preferred destinations due to cheap electricity. However, as crypto mining boomed, lawmakers have come up with hostile measures against the industry.</p>
<h2>Stringent Rules</h2>
<p>The details of the five bills that introduce a new scheme of electricity purchasing for mining equipment, as well as updated licensing and taxation schemes, were shared by Didar Bekbauov, co-founder of Xive, a crypto mining solutions platform.</p>
<p>Miners will now be required to purchase only surplus electricity from the public grid. Exclusive purchase of electricity through the Kazakhstan Electricity and Power Market Operator [KOREM] exchange can also be carried out by the miners. However, not everyone will be able to make this purchase as electricity would sell in an auction form &#8211; meaning the highest bids win.</p>
<p>The mining license procedure is categorized into two. The first one will involve the digital miners who own the appropriate infrastructure &#8211; data processing centers with the appropriate requirements for equipment, location, and security.</p>
<p>The second category is for digital miners &#8211; equipment owners who rent cells in data processing centers and do not claim an energy quota.</p>
<p>Commenting on the bill, a member of the Mäjilis’ Committee on Economic Reform and Regional Development, Ekaterina Smyshlyaeva, <a href="https://twitter.com/didar_bekbau/status/1600442939959693313" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said:</a></p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The bill, in addition to mandatory accreditation, introduces separate requirements for mining pools in terms of the location of their server capacities in Kazakhstan and compliance with information security rules.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Clampdown Inevitable?</h2>
<p>New crypto taxes have also been presented that include provisions for miners, mining pool commission, value-added tax, and tax on crypto exchanges as business entities.</p>
<p>With the new rules approved, both single miners and mining pools will be imposed corporate income tax based on the value of the crypto-asset as well as the commission rates for the pools. In addition to that, the Majilis is also looking to enforce a blanket ban on advertising crypto transactions and design regulations specifically for &#8220;cryptocurrency securities.&#8221;</p>
<p>Moreover, individuals conducting crypto transactions will also be levied value-added tax along with corporate income tax on crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The latest development comes over a month after the Mäjilis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-wants-more-regulations-for-crypto-miners-with-new-bill-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">greenlighted</a> bills that sought to establish appropriate rules in the domestic crypto sector. As such, crypto miners and mining pools will come under the purview of the Ministry of Digital Development, Innovation, and Aerospace Industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-lawmakers-pass-new-bitcoin-mining-bills/" rel="nofollow">Kazakhstan Lawmakers Pass New Bitcoin Mining Bills</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bear Market, Luna Crash, FTX Meltdown: How it Impacted Crypto&#8217;s Public Perception (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bear-market-luna-crash-ftx-meltdown-how-it-impacted-cryptos-public-perception-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227843</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinAdoption.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinAdoption.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[43% of the US participants in the survey currently have a negative view of digital currencies, while just 8% are supportive of them.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent study conducted by CNBC estimated that only 8% of American participants currently have a favorable view of cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Those who supported the asset class in March 2022 were 19%. The market has been through a lot since then &#8211; the prices plummeted, the Terra ecosystem crashed, and FTX filed for bankruptcy.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Change of Trends</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">43% of the US participants in CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;All-America Economic Survey&#8221; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/editorialfiles/2022/12/07/allamericafourthquarter.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> they have a negative view of digital currencies, while this figure was 25% nine months ago. The proponents of the asset class have shrunk to 8%, down from 19%, and 18% feel neutral. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the results, 24% of the respondents admitted having invested, traded, or used crypto in the past (up 6% from the March results).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">17% of those who have allocated some of their wealth in bitcoin or altcoins have a &#8220;very negative&#8221; stance, while 47% of the non-investors showed such an attitude.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The increased criticism could be a result of the numerous adverse events that the world of crypto endured throughout the ongoing year, with Terra&#8217;s collapse and the crash of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> being some of them. Former giants like </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Three Arrows Capital, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-files-for-bankruptcy-following-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BlockFi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and many others filed for bankruptcy, while the global crypto market capitalization has slipped below $1 trillion.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The rise of negativity toward cryptocurrencies coincides with record-low confidence in stocks. Only 26% of the participants believe now is the right moment to invest in equities which is the most pessimistic level in the 15-year history of the research. 51% think they should stay away.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Young Americans are More Supportive</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A survey carried out by Bank of America <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/75-of-young-us-investors-want-to-diversify-portfolios-with-crypto-boa-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">estimated</a> that 75% of American respondents aged 21-42 believe it is impossible to achieve above-average returns relying only on traditional finance. They think crypto should be one of the instruments to diversify with.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">32% of the older individuals share the same stance but prefer to invest their funds in equities. Just 5% of those above 42 years old have hopped on the cryptocurrency bandwagon.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The research further informed that 68% of the polled parents have already had an educational discussion with their children on how to transfer the family wealth to them. Generation X and Millennials are expected to inherit around $84 trillion by 2045.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Those two demographic groups have been among the most active on the crypto scene. A research conducted in 2021 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-millennials-have-a-large-chunk-of-their-wealth-in-crypto-cnbc-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">showed</a> that 47% of Millennial millionaires have invested at least a quarter of their total funds in bitcoin or alternative coins. 36% <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-millennials-and-generation-z-prefer-to-get-parts-of-their-salaries-in-bitcoin-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> they would like to receive some of their salaries in digital currencies instead of fiat. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bear-market-luna-crash-ftx-meltdown-how-it-impacted-cryptos-public-perception-survey/" rel="nofollow">Bear Market, Luna Crash, FTX Meltdown: How it Impacted Crypto&#8217;s Public Perception (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Scammers Are Getting More Creative, Microsoft Warns of New Threats</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scammers-are-getting-more-creative-microsoft-warns-of-new-threats/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227735</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hack_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The threat actor appears to be well-versed in the inner workings of the crypto industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft revealed that malicious entities are getting more sophisticated by the day. According to a new report, Telegram chat groups are being used to target cryptocurrency investment companies.</p>
<p>The tech giant identified a threat actor &#8211; DEV-0139 &#8211; who infiltrated Telegram groups posing as a representative of a crypto platform.</p>
<h2>Targetted Attacks Against Crypto Companies</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/security/blog/2022/12/06/dev-0139-launches-targeted-attacks-against-the-cryptocurrency-industry/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a> published by Microsoft&#8217;s Security Threat Intelligence team stated the threat actors had significant knowledge of the crypto investment industry and invited at least one target (posing as representatives of other crypto asset management firms) to another Telegram group. The main goal is to engage and discuss a relevant topic to gain the target&#8217;s trust.</p>
<p>The attackers sent them malware-laced Excel spreadsheets that contain well-crafted information to appear legitimate. Once opened, the weaponized Excel file enables macros, and a second worksheet embedded in the file will download and parse a PNG file to extract a malicious DLL, an XOR-encoded backdoor, and a legitimate Windows executable later used to sideload the DLL, which will decrypt and load the backdoor. This will essentially provide the threat actor with remote access to the target&#8217;s compromised system.</p>
<p>Microsoft could not retrieve the final payload but detected another variant of this attack and retrieved the payload. The company&#8217;s findings highlighted the existence of other campaigns that leverage the same techniques to target crypto companies.</p>
<p>The report concluded:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The cryptocurrency market remains a field of interest for threat actors. Targeted users are identified through trusted channels to increase the chance of success. While the biggest companies can be targeted, smaller companies can also be targets of interest.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Scammers&#8217; Landscape So Far</h2>
<p>The crypto market remains a field of interest for threat actors who have now leaned towards more sophisticated attacks to increase the chance of success.</p>
<p>According to recent <a href="https://www.privacyaffairs.com/cryptocurrency-scams-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">research</a> conducted by cybersecurity and data privacy firm Privacy Affairs, the value of crypto siphoned by threat actors in the first 11 months of the year surged by 37% to $4.3 billion. Of the 11 biggest cryptocurrency scams committed in 2022, Privacy Affairs claimed that the top five are the failure of FTX, Axie Infinity&#8217;s Ronin Network <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ronin-network-announces-bridge-restart-date-three-months-after-625m-hack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">attack</a> in March ($615 million), the Wormhole crypto bridge hack in February ($320 million), the JuicyFields.io scam in July ($273 million) and others.</p>
<p>Rug pulls took a big share as more than 188,000 of them were recorded on various blockchains, including BNB and Ethereum.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scammers-are-getting-more-creative-microsoft-warns-of-new-threats/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Scammers Are Getting More Creative, Microsoft Warns of New Threats</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Axie Infinty (AXS) Explodes 20% Weekly, Bitcoin Remains Stable Above $17K: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/axie-infinty-axs-explodes-20-weekly-bitcoin-remains-stable-above-17k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 09:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity (AXS)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228182</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/axie_inifnity.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/axie_inifnity.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market remains calm through the day, but some coins are already pulling ahead on a weekly basis. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The broader cryptocurrency market didn&#8217;t see a major change in the past 24 hours, as its total capitalization remains the same.</p>
<p>As we go into the weekend, it becomes clear that some cryptocurrencies performed really well throughout the week, so let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stable Above $17K</h2>
<p>The BTC price didn&#8217;t go through any major moves in the past 24 hours and remains above $17K. It&#8217;s worth noting, however, that it had increased up to $17,360 in the early afternoon yesterday, but the bulls were unable to continue the push and the price was sent back toward $17,100.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228183" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228183" style="width: 1527px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228183" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201.png" alt="btc_price_101201" width="1527" height="853" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201.png 1527w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201-300x168.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201-1024x572.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201-768x429.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_101201-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1527px) 100vw, 1527px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228183" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance via TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>This puts BTC on a 0.4% loss for the past 24 hours and a 0.4% increase for the past week, showcasing the markets&#8217; inability to break away from the current trading range.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Stagnate Toward the Downside</h2>
<p>The majority of the altcoin market has also been stagnating in the past day, but toward the downside, as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228185" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228185" style="width: 1492px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228185" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001.png" alt="heatmap_121001" width="1492" height="782" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001.png 1492w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001-300x157.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001-1024x537.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001-768x403.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/heatmap_121001-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1492px) 100vw, 1492px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228185" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>One of the best performers for the day is OKT, which is 8%, followed by Axie Infinity&#8217;s AXS &#8211; up 7%. This puts the total gains for AXS upwards of a whopping 20% for the week, which is considerable, given the current market conditions.</p>
<p>On the other hand, XCN seems to be the worst performer for the day, followed by BTSE token, both of which are down by some 4%.</p>
<p>All in all, the day failed to produce any meaningful movements in either direction and it appears that this is reflected in the overall trading volume, which sits at around $38 billion for the past 24 hours. Typically, such periods of calmness and lack of volatility lead to explosive moves in either direction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/axie-infinty-axs-explodes-20-weekly-bitcoin-remains-stable-above-17k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Axie Infinty (AXS) Explodes 20% Weekly, Bitcoin Remains Stable Above $17K: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is the Most Diabolical Thing About FTX and SBF According to Michael Saylor</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-the-most-diabolical-thing-about-ftx-and-sbf-according-to-michael-saylor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 04:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228176</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Michael Saylor claims Sam Bankman-Fried committed a slew of legal crimes including securities and banking fraud. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">MicroStrategy Executive Chairman Michael Saylor spoke on Tuesday about the layers of evil and mismanagement behind FTX’s collapse last month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The executive accused the exchange’s former CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried, of both committing securities fraud through FTT, and using the asset as collateral to gamble away his depositor’s money.</span></p>
<h2>Dissecting the FTX Fraud</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RI4xEHI7tGg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with Patrick Bet David on Monday, Saylor – a self-proclaimed “Bitcoin Maximalist” – began by naming what he sees as Bankman-Fried and the crypto industry’s first moral crime: the “sin of shitcoinery.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Sam and most of the people in the crypto world were always guilty of pumping and promoting unregistered securities,” he said. “That was obvious to the chair of the SEC [and] most politicians.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankman-Fried’s company was responsible for issuing a token called </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-still-thinks-ftt-was-more-legit-than-most-tokens/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">FTT</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, which offered various benefits to users of his exchange. Once a top 25 cryptocurrency, the asset collapsed by over 90% in value during a run on FTX last month, after which its bankruptcy quickly followed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Saylor, Bankman Fried’s use of FTT and other tokens as collateral for taking out loans was “particularly diabolical,” given their relative illiquidity. However, traditional banks such as Goldman Sachs would refuse to lend money on such risky collateral.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As such Bankman-Fried turned “to himself” – using Alameda to “borrow” FTX users’ funds on the FTT collateral. Then, Alameda used those funds to prop up the price of FTT, allowing the company to borrow even more funds and slide money into Sam Bankman-Fried’s holding company, Paper Bird. </span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">While SBF maintains that he had little knowledge of what happened internally at Alameda Research, it is widely suspected that the trading desk was closely involved in the events leading up to both companies’ bankruptcies. Court filings </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alameda-secretly-exempted-from-ftxs-auto-liquidation-engine-court-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">revealed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> last month the Alameda was secretly exempted from FTX’s auto liquidation mechanism – a privilege Saylor referred to as “god mode.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“He generated $10 billion in an unregistered security, and then just borrowed $10 billion secretly from his depositors,” explained Saylor. “Gambled it, traded it, spent it, lost it.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Saylor added that VCs investing in FTX had effectively supported an “offshore unregulated casino” and hadn’t done due diligence. Kevin O’Leary, a paid spokesperson and early investor in FTX, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-kevin-oleary-got-paid-to-promote-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">admitted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Thursday that he and other investors had over-relied on each other’s due diligence processes.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Sam scraped billions from unsuspecting investors in Silicon Valley. They should’ve known better,” said Saylor.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>The Truth Behind the BlockFi Bailout</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Sam Bankman-Fried was regarded as an industry savior mere months ago, as his company stepped in to provide emergency liquidity for multiple failing firms including </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-ceo-provides-more-details-on-the-250m-revolving-credit-taken-from-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">BlockFi</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Voyager. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At the time, SBF framed his rescue action as an altruistic attempt to protect the industry, rather than to make a profit. However, Saylor alleges that Bankman-Fried only intended to protect those companies to prevent them from calling for their money back from Alameda.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“If I can simply give them a billion dollars of equity, take over the company, and not pay the loan back, I can roll the entire fraud forward,” he said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ultimately, Saylor believes FTX’s extremely low trading fees were a ploy to lure traders to put assets on the platform, which SBF could then freely trade with.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-the-most-diabolical-thing-about-ftx-and-sbf-according-to-michael-saylor/" rel="nofollow">This is the Most Diabolical Thing About FTX and SBF According to Michael Saylor</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>After Binance, CryptoCom Reveals Proof of Reserves </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/after-binance-cryptocom-reveals-proof-of-reserves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228164</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CryptoCom.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/CryptoCom.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CryptoCom has provided proof of reserves for nine crypto assets, using the same auditor as Binance.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoCom is the latest exchange to provide proof of reserves amid soaring demand for industry transparency stemming from FTX’s collapse. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The audit found that its customers’ balances for multiple top cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin and Ethereum, are over 100% backed. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As the exchange </span><a href="https://crypto.com/company-news/crypto-com-releases-proof-of-reserves" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Friday, its proof of reserves featured an audit from Mazars Group – an independent crypto-focused advisory firm that also carried out Binance’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binances-bitcoin-reserves-are-101-backed-confirms-auditor/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">proof of reserves</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> last month. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The auditing group used “advanced cryptographic procedures” to ensure the availability of customer funds. It compared the assets held on CryptoCom-controlled addresses with customer balances as of December 7, using a live query of an auditor-overseen live query of a production database. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The results found that BTC and ETH had reserve ratios of 102% and 101% respectively. Meanwhile, top stablecoins including USDC and USDT were respectively backed 102% and 106%.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Other audited coins with full reserve ratios included XRP, DOGE, SHIB, LINK and MANA. However, the exchange has not provided exact figures for its assets and liabilities.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Providing audited Proof of Reserves is an important step for the entire industry to increase transparency and begin the process of restoring trust,” said Kris Marszalek, CEO of Crypto.com, in a statement. </span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Like Binance, CryptoCom now allows users to confirm that their individual assets remain secure and accessible through both their app and website.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Proof of reserves is a transparency tool that uses public blockchain data to prove the safety of users’ assets on exchanges. Proper implementation of this system still requires an external auditor to analyze a company’s liabilities to ensure it is entirely solvent. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">This fact has been repeatedly pointed out by Kraken CEO Jesse Powell, who criticized apparent holes in Binance’s proof of reserves earlier this week. </span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">ok, I&#39;ll give you a hint. This is just the easy stuff that says this OBVIOUSLY is not a traditional Proof of Reserves, and should immediately have had actual journalists digging.</p>
<p>Why use collateral value? Why negative balances included? No wallet signing? Who issues BTCB &amp; BBTC? <a href="https://t.co/F9u4XJ5WSi" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/F9u4XJ5WSi</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Jesse Powell (@jespow) <a href="https://twitter.com/jespow/status/1600787933065117696?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 8, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-binance-cryptocom-reveals-proof-of-reserves/" rel="nofollow">After Binance, CryptoCom Reveals Proof of Reserves </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried to Binance CEO: You Won, Stop Lying</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-binance-ceo-you-won-stop-lying/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228155</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance and FTX’s bosses have two different accounts of their exchange’s business dealings prior to the latter firm’s collapse. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) and ex-FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) traded barbs over Twitter on Friday as each contested the true nature of their private business dealings.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the exchange, Bankman-Fried asked CZ why he would “lie” about their situation, given he had already “won,” post bankruptcy.</span></p>
<h2>CZ’s Story</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1601140809491185664" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">began</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with reference to Kevin O’Leary’s latest comments on FTX’s fallout. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In his interview with CNBC, the Shark Tank star suggested that FTX spent much of its cash attempting to buy back its equity from Binance due to the latter’s “opque” ownership. He also refrained from accusing Bankman-Fried of fraud, as he has done </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftx-bankruptcy-kevin-oleary-would-still-invest-in-sbf/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">multiple times</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> since FTX’s bankrupcy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O’Leary was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-kevin-oleary-got-paid-to-promote-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">paid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> $15 million to promote FTX’s brand in August 2021, and was an early investor in the company. CZ believes this has something to do with why he would seemingly run defense for FTX and SBF – even after the exchange’s collapse. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Unlike Kevin O’Leary, we continue to do due diligence even after we make an investment,” said CZ. “As an early investor in FTX, we became increasingly uncomfortable with Alameda/SBF and initiated the exit process more than 1.5 years ago.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to CZ, Binance began to leave behind its equity position in July 2021 due to worries about SBF and Alameda’s practices. This, per the Binance CEO, set off Bankman-Fried on multiple “unhinged” tirades against Binance team members, wherein the former billionaire threatened to “go to extraordinary lengths” to punish Binance. “We still have those text messages,” said CZ. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This apparently sparked FTX to launch a mass investment campaign among “friends in high places,” including media, politicans, and celebrities like Kevin O’Leary to steer public opinion in favor of FTX, and against its opponents. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In early November, CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1589374530413215744" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">implied</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that FTX was lobbying against other player in the crypto industry in congress. Later that month, congressman Tom Emmer said he’d received reports of SBF </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-conspired-with-sec-for-special-treatment-us-congressman/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">conspiring</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with the SEC to forge a regulatory monopoly for FTX in the exchange business. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You don&#8217;t have to be a genius to know something don&#8217;t smell right at FTX,” continued CZ. “They were 1/10th our size, yet outspent us 100/1 on marketing &amp; &#8220;partnerships&#8221;, fancy parties in the Bahamas, trips across the globe, and mansions for all of their senior staff.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-expanding-hirings-amid-falling-crypto-market/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">boasted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in June that his company was especially frugal during the 2021 crypto bull market, and had developed a large “war chest” relative to other more profligate competitors. </span></p>
<h2>SBF’s Story</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike CZ, Bankman-Fried </span><a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX/status/1601191234034274304" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">alleged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that his company was the one that initiated talks about buying out Binance’s stake in FTX, echoing his word to Kevin O’Leary on the matter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He also claimed that Binance never had the right to pull out as an investor unless FTX voluntarily opted for a buyout. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“But again, none of this is necessary. You won. Why are you lying about this now?” he asked. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ contested SBF’s framing of their dealings as a “competition” or “fight,” asserting that “no one won,” as an outcome. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1601204678184013826</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-binance-ceo-you-won-stop-lying/" rel="nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried to Binance CEO: You Won, Stop Lying</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Willing to Testify Before US House Committee of Financial Services Next Week</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-willing-to-testify-before-us-house-committee-of-financial-services-next-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228115</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried promised to testify before the US House Committee on Financial Services on December 13.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The former CEO of FTX &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; said he is &#8220;willing&#8221; to testify before the relevant US authorities on December 13.</p>
<p>He vowed to shed more light on the reasons behind his exchange&#8217;s collapse and his own failures as a leader.</p>
<ul>
<li>The US House Committee on Financial Services <a href="https://twitter.com/RepMaxineWaters/status/1599858166359068676" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claimed</a> earlier this week that the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX crisis</a> caused colossal investor losses and urged Bankman-Fried to testify on the matter on December 13.</li>
<li>SBF took it to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX/status/1601186246990401537?t=UzKt6Rq-UcE9W9K2fZ2Vug&amp;s=35" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announce</a> he is ready to satisfy the Committee&#8217;s request.</li>
<li>However, he said he doesn&#8217;t have access to much of his data (personal or professional), hence the limit on what he will be able to reveal.</li>
<li>SBF pledged to be &#8220;helpful&#8221; during the hearing and bring more clarity to significant problems, including FTX US&#8217; solvency and what American and international users should do to obtain their lost assets.</li>
<li>He will also explain the main reasons that triggered the crash and what he could have done better to prevent it.</li>
<li>Subsequently, he blamed himself for changing from a &#8220;model CEO&#8221; to &#8220;lazy or disconnected.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-willing-to-testify-before-us-house-committee-of-financial-services-next-week/" rel="nofollow">SBF Willing to Testify Before US House Committee of Financial Services Next Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CZ Binance Spats With SBF, Crypto Markets Go Back and Forth, More Proof of Reserves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-spats-with-sbf-crypto-markets-go-back-and-forth-more-proof-of-reserves-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228042</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SBF and CZ go head to head, CryptoCom publishes its proof-of-reserves, while the cryptocurrency market ends up where it was last week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With certain slight exceptions, the cryptocurrency market is found more or less where it was during the same time last week. The total capitalization sits at around $890 billion, according to data from CoinGecko and Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance is at 37%.</p>
<p>Speaking of Bitcoin, the primary cryptocurrency went back and forth (just like the rest of the market, dipping below $17K on a few occasions throughout the week. However, the bulls were successful in reclaiming this important level, and the price is now found above it for an increase of 1% throughout the past seven days.</p>
<p>Most of the major cryptocurrencies are trading roughly at similar prices compared to last week, with certain exceptions. For example, DOGE is down 5%, and XRP is down 3%. On the other hand, Uniswap&#8217;s UNI and Avalanche&#8217;s AVAX are up by 6.4% and 4.9% respectively. In any case, the BTC dominance remained at 37%, which shows that there&#8217;s no serious imbalance in the market between the primary cryptocurrency and altcoins.</p>
<p>Perhaps more interestingly, the FTX drama rages on. Earlier on Friday, 3AC&#8217;s co-founder &#8211; Zhu Su, took a stab at SBF (the exchange&#8217;s former CEO) for allegedly exercising pressure over media. The latter denied categorically.</p>
<p>A few hours later, the CEO of Binance, Changpeng Zhao, had another go at SBF and people who used to represent FTX. More precisely, CZ was talking about Kevin O&#8217;Leary and the way he looks at the whole fiasco. SBF responded, acknowledging again that CZ &#8220;won,&#8221; causing many to believe that he treats the entire ordeal as some sort of a game. Binance&#8217;s CEO said no one is a winner in this case.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, CryptoCom also published its Proof of Reserves report and allowed users to verify their holdings. The company handling the PoR was Mazars Group but it&#8217;s worth noting that they didn&#8217;t carry a financial report but rather carried out agreed-upon procedures (AUPs) requested by CryptoCom in advance.</p>
<p>All in all, it&#8217;s shaping up to be quite exciting in the cryptocurrency market, especially given that the US Bureau of Labor Statistics is going to announce the November CPI numbers on December 13th.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $892B | 24H Vol: 48B | BTC Dominance: 37%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BTC:</strong> $17,162 (+1%) | <strong>ETH:</strong> $1,275 (-0.1%) | <strong>BNB</strong>: $289 (-0.9%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228144" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg" alt="09.12" width="1000" height="500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-768x384.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Federal Judge Dismisses Kim Kardashian&#8217;s Crypto Promotion Lawsuit. </strong>A US federal judge has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-judge-dismisses-kim-kardashians-crypto-promotion-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">dismissed</a> the lawsuit against Kim Kardashian, Floyd Mayweather, and other top celebrities. It was for promoting a cryptocurrency project called EthereumMax (EMAX).</p>
<p><strong>SBF Could Have Reportedly Been Involved in Terra&#8217;s Collapse, Do Kwon Chips In. </strong>A new report <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-could-have-reportedly-been-involved-in-terras-collapse-do-kwon-chips-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">suggested</a> that Sam Bankman-Fried may have been involved in the crash of the Terra-Luna ecosystem. Do Kwon also chipped in with some questions to the former CEO of the bankrupt FTX exchange.</p>
<p><strong>Senator Lummis Now Believes Ether is a Security. </strong>Senator Cynthia Lummis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-lummis-now-believes-ether-is-a-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">thinks</a> that Bitcoin is the only cryptocurrency that could be considered a security. The main reason for her changing her mind on Ether is the inability to de-stake, which makes it &#8220;susceptible to being a security.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>3AC Co-Founders Su Zhu, Kyle Davies Subpoenaed in Bankruptcy Case. </strong>A federal judge has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founders-su-zhu-kyle-davies-subpoenaed-in-bankruptcy-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">approved</a> the issuance of subpoenas to the founders of Three Arrows Capital (the hedge fund that collapsed earlier in 2022). The document was published on Tuesday by the Southern District Court of New York.</p>
<p><strong>5 Failing Crypto Narratives of Late, According to CZ Binance. </strong>The CEO of the world&#8217;s leading exchange came out on Twitter with five failing cryptocurrency narratives. He openly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-failing-crypto-narratives-of-late-according-to-cz-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">called</a> Sam Bankman-Fried &#8220;one of the greatest fraudsters in history.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Goldman Sachs to Invest Millions in Crypto Businesses Following FTX Meltdown. </strong>The multinational investment giant Goldman Sachs sees opportunities in the cryptocurrency market following the crash of FTX. The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/goldman-sachs-to-invest-millions-in-crypto-businesses-following-ftx-meltdown/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that some valuations are now much more reasonable and plans to invest millions in the industry.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Litecoin – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-9-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-ltc/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-spats-with-sbf-crypto-markets-go-back-and-forth-more-proof-of-reserves-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">CZ Binance Spats With SBF, Crypto Markets Go Back and Forth, More Proof of Reserves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
