<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 04:44:41 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Three Coins for Big Gains: Uwerx (WERX), GALA (GALA), and Stellar (XLM)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/three-coins-for-big-gains-uwerx-werx-gala-gala-and-stellar-xlm</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-638.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-638.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-638.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/three-coins-for-big-gains-uwerx-werx-gala-gala-and-stellar-xlm</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[Three coins stand out with their unique offerings and promising prospects for investors, GALA (GALA), Stellar (XLM), and Uwerx.&nbsp;
<p>From Uwerx's disruptive approach to revolutionizing freelancing to GALA's (GALA) vibrant gaming ecosystem and Stellar's (XLM) mission to transform global financial systems, each coin brings something distinct to the table.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Keep reading to uncover the factors that make them worthy contenders for significant gains in every savvy investor&rsquo;s portfolio.</p>
Riding the Waves of GALA (GALA)
<p>GALA (GALA) token is like the lifeblood of the Gala Games ecosystem. It&rsquo;s a digital utility token that fuels everything within the Gala Games world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>What's cool is that GALA (GALA) is secured using advanced cryptography and is unique to the Gala Games ecosystem. With GALA (GALA), users have full control.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As for the price, GALA (GALA) is currently valued at $0.03041 and has been showing some promising trading volume of $52,405,654 over the past 24 hours. Our GALA (GALA) forecast predicts a potential 100% increase, reaching around $0.0640 by Q4 2024.</p>
Stellar (XLM): Uniting the World with Seamless Transactions
<p>Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized network that aims to bridge the gap between global financial systems. It was launched in 2015 by The Stellar Development Foundation. Since then, this peer-to-peer platform has made transactions simple and affordable.</p>
<p>Designed with the goal of enabling swift and reliable movement of financial resources, Stellar (XLM) acts as a protocol for payment providers and financial institutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) serves as a crucial link, connecting individuals, banks, and payment processors, while offering the ability to create, send, and trade various types of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Currently priced at $0.08818, with a market cap of $2,363,744,799, Stellar (XLM) holds promising potential. Crypto analysts foresee it reaching $0.0932 by Q3 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, amidst the excitement surrounding GALA (GALA) and Stellar (XLM), it's essential not to overlook the incredible prospects of Uwerx, making it a standout choice for the coming year.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale Shatters Records with Stage 1 in 17 Days and Stage 2 in Just 8 Days
<p>The Uwerx community has spoken! With an overwhelming 98.2% support from a Twitter poll, the Test Airdrop is set to take place on July 31st, marking a significant milestone for the platform.</p>
<p>Listening to the community's voice, Uwerx is implementing an imminent token lock supported by 82.8% of voters. This 25-year lock ensures long-term stability, assuring investors of the platform's commitment to their security.</p>
<p>Uwerx's presale progress has been astounding, with Stage 1 completed in a mere 17 days and Stage 2 taking just 8 days. The community's enthusiasm and rapid response showcase the platform's undeniable appeal.</p>
<p>Uwerx's presale is in full swing, currently at Stage 5, offering tokens at an attractive price of $0.041 each with a generous 15% bonus on every purchase. Don't miss out on this opportunity to join the Uwerx revolution.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) on the Rise: CoinSniper Listing and Uniswap Arrival Accelerate Growth
<p>Transparency and fairness are at the core of Uwerx's philosophy. The team will renounce the contracts when the project is ready to launch on centralized exchanges, and taxes are zero.</p>
<p>Say goodbye to exorbitant transaction fees! Uwerx has set its platform transaction fee at a minimal 1%, contrasting sharply with industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr. Uwerx is committed to empowering freelancers and clients alike.</p>
<p>The Uwerx Vault is a groundbreaking feature that allows users to securely store their WERX tokens for various periods, akin to staking while earning rewards based on platform variables.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Trust and credibility are paramount for Uwerx. The platform has undergone thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network, ensuring the integrity and reliability of its infrastructure.</p>
<p>Uwerx's journey continues to gain momentum with its listing on CoinSniper and an upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st. These listings bolster Uwerx's visibility and open doors for increased engagement with the platform. The Uwerx community is growing and has amassed over 5,500 sign-ups, 1,600 Twitter followers, and 1,600 Telegram members.</p>
<p>The clock is ticking! The hard-cap presale end date is set for July 31st, 2023. Don't miss your chance to be part of this transformative journey.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Unveils Alpha Platform: PDF Release and Anticipation for the Web-Based Launch
<p>Uwerx values its community and has responded to feedback. The team has made modifications to token allocations, ensuring fairness and addressing the demands arising from the dynamic presale environment.</p>
<p>The Alpha Platform is beginning to take shape. On May 19, the PDF version was made available, but that was just the beginning. Prepare yourself for the web-based launch that will include elements like the landing page, sign-in/sign-up page, user dashboard, and more.</p>
<p>Stay tuned for continuous updates! Uwerx will release more parts of the Alpha platform in the coming weeks, allowing users to explore features such as settings, posting jobs, finding jobs, and more.</p>
<p>The transition from the Alpha Version to the Beta Version is on the horizon. Soon, users will have the chance to actively test the platform themselves, contributing to its refinement and improvement.</p>
<p>Uwerx values your input! Share your thoughts, recommendations, and ideas on the platform's design through the dedicated feedback email at feedback@uwerx.network. Together, let's shape the future of the freelance industry.</p>
Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[Three coins stand out with their unique offerings and promising prospects for investors, GALA (GALA), Stellar (XLM), and Uwerx.&nbsp;
<p>From Uwerx's disruptive approach to revolutionizing freelancing to GALA's (GALA) vibrant gaming ecosystem and Stellar's (XLM) mission to transform global financial systems, each coin brings something distinct to the table.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Keep reading to uncover the factors that make them worthy contenders for significant gains in every savvy investor&rsquo;s portfolio.</p>
Riding the Waves of GALA (GALA)
<p>GALA (GALA) token is like the lifeblood of the Gala Games ecosystem. It&rsquo;s a digital utility token that fuels everything within the Gala Games world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>What's cool is that GALA (GALA) is secured using advanced cryptography and is unique to the Gala Games ecosystem. With GALA (GALA), users have full control.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As for the price, GALA (GALA) is currently valued at $0.03041 and has been showing some promising trading volume of $52,405,654 over the past 24 hours. Our GALA (GALA) forecast predicts a potential 100% increase, reaching around $0.0640 by Q4 2024.</p>
Stellar (XLM): Uniting the World with Seamless Transactions
<p>Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized network that aims to bridge the gap between global financial systems. It was launched in 2015 by The Stellar Development Foundation. Since then, this peer-to-peer platform has made transactions simple and affordable.</p>
<p>Designed with the goal of enabling swift and reliable movement of financial resources, Stellar (XLM) acts as a protocol for payment providers and financial institutions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) serves as a crucial link, connecting individuals, banks, and payment processors, while offering the ability to create, send, and trade various types of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Currently priced at $0.08818, with a market cap of $2,363,744,799, Stellar (XLM) holds promising potential. Crypto analysts foresee it reaching $0.0932 by Q3 2024.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, amidst the excitement surrounding GALA (GALA) and Stellar (XLM), it's essential not to overlook the incredible prospects of Uwerx, making it a standout choice for the coming year.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale Shatters Records with Stage 1 in 17 Days and Stage 2 in Just 8 Days
<p>The Uwerx community has spoken! With an overwhelming 98.2% support from a Twitter poll, the Test Airdrop is set to take place on July 31st, marking a significant milestone for the platform.</p>
<p>Listening to the community's voice, Uwerx is implementing an imminent token lock supported by 82.8% of voters. This 25-year lock ensures long-term stability, assuring investors of the platform's commitment to their security.</p>
<p>Uwerx's presale progress has been astounding, with Stage 1 completed in a mere 17 days and Stage 2 taking just 8 days. The community's enthusiasm and rapid response showcase the platform's undeniable appeal.</p>
<p>Uwerx's presale is in full swing, currently at Stage 5, offering tokens at an attractive price of $0.041 each with a generous 15% bonus on every purchase. Don't miss out on this opportunity to join the Uwerx revolution.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) on the Rise: CoinSniper Listing and Uniswap Arrival Accelerate Growth
<p>Transparency and fairness are at the core of Uwerx's philosophy. The team will renounce the contracts when the project is ready to launch on centralized exchanges, and taxes are zero.</p>
<p>Say goodbye to exorbitant transaction fees! Uwerx has set its platform transaction fee at a minimal 1%, contrasting sharply with industry giants like Upwork and Fiverr. Uwerx is committed to empowering freelancers and clients alike.</p>
<p>The Uwerx Vault is a groundbreaking feature that allows users to securely store their WERX tokens for various periods, akin to staking while earning rewards based on platform variables.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Trust and credibility are paramount for Uwerx. The platform has undergone thorough audits by renowned firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network, ensuring the integrity and reliability of its infrastructure.</p>
<p>Uwerx's journey continues to gain momentum with its listing on CoinSniper and an upcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st. These listings bolster Uwerx's visibility and open doors for increased engagement with the platform. The Uwerx community is growing and has amassed over 5,500 sign-ups, 1,600 Twitter followers, and 1,600 Telegram members.</p>
<p>The clock is ticking! The hard-cap presale end date is set for July 31st, 2023. Don't miss your chance to be part of this transformative journey.</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Unveils Alpha Platform: PDF Release and Anticipation for the Web-Based Launch
<p>Uwerx values its community and has responded to feedback. The team has made modifications to token allocations, ensuring fairness and addressing the demands arising from the dynamic presale environment.</p>
<p>The Alpha Platform is beginning to take shape. On May 19, the PDF version was made available, but that was just the beginning. Prepare yourself for the web-based launch that will include elements like the landing page, sign-in/sign-up page, user dashboard, and more.</p>
<p>Stay tuned for continuous updates! Uwerx will release more parts of the Alpha platform in the coming weeks, allowing users to explore features such as settings, posting jobs, finding jobs, and more.</p>
<p>The transition from the Alpha Version to the Beta Version is on the horizon. Soon, users will have the chance to actively test the platform themselves, contributing to its refinement and improvement.</p>
<p>Uwerx values your input! Share your thoughts, recommendations, and ideas on the platform's design through the dedicated feedback email at feedback@uwerx.network. Together, let's shape the future of the freelance industry.</p>
Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Price Today: Will Bitcoin and Ethereum Regain Support Level? Tradecurve Stage 3 50% Sold Already]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-price-today-will-bitcoin-and-ethereum-regain-support-level-tradecurve-stage-3-50-sold-already</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-637.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-637.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-637.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-price-today-will-bitcoin-and-ethereum-regain-support-level-tradecurve-stage-3-50-sold-already</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>VanEck has made a bold prediction, suggesting that Ethereum will reach $50,000 by 2030. The investment management firm's claim is based on Ethereum's presence in crucial industry sectors and its potential to revolutionize finance, banking, payments, social interactions, gaming, and infrastructure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum's token supply reduction, where transaction fees result in Ethereum burning, contributes to its value. The question is not if, but when, will Ethereum reach support levels and all-time highs due to its enduring demand? Looking at the chart, it is evident that bulls have maintained their position above the falling wedge pattern's resistance line, indicating demand at lower levels.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Glassnode's Ethereum and Bitcoin Analysis
<p>Glassnode has focused its attention on Bitcoin and has identified an upcoming transition point in the market cycle. This transition, coupled with macroeconomics and price action for Bitcoin and Ethereum, is expected to lead to increased price volatility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given the ongoing SEC situation, the macro environment will become more unpredictable from next week onwards. Despite this uncertainty, the price of Bitcoin has managed to stay above the crucial support at $25,000, suggesting that recent SEC events are already factored into the price.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Traders are keen to buy the dip, with notable figures like ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood investing millions of dollars in Coinbase stock and Block Inc. shares.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve: A Comprehensive Web3 Trading Solution
<p>Tradecurve.io provides customers with a hybrid platform for trading cryptocurrencies and derivatives from a single account, eliminating the need to disclose personal information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As one of the fastest-growing projects in the DeFi space, Tradecurve.io offers a unique hybrid exchange that removes entry barriers, provides deep liquidity, enables anonymous trading, and ensures fast execution. It is one of the first decentralized exchanges to use cryptocurrencies as collateral, offering spot trading for traditional assets such as stocks, forex, commodities, and cryptocurrencies like Ethereum and Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Onboarding on Tradecurve is straightforward, requiring users to connect their wallets to the Ethereum network, deposit crypto, and begin trading. Traders can subscribe to AI and algorithmic trading bots or use copy trading features to replicate the strategies of top traders in the market. Beginners can benefit from the metaverse trading academy, which offers a wide range of learning opportunities and live lectures.</p>
<p>TCRV tokens are currently available for purchase at $0.015 in the soon-to-end stage 3 of the ongoing presale. The value will increase by 25% to $0.018 when entering stage 4. By the end of the presale period alone, TCRV is projected to achieve a 5,000% gain, positioning Tradecurve as potentially one of the most promising investments in the market.</p>
<p>Discover more surrounding Tradecurve and TCRV below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>VanEck has made a bold prediction, suggesting that Ethereum will reach $50,000 by 2030. The investment management firm's claim is based on Ethereum's presence in crucial industry sectors and its potential to revolutionize finance, banking, payments, social interactions, gaming, and infrastructure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum's token supply reduction, where transaction fees result in Ethereum burning, contributes to its value. The question is not if, but when, will Ethereum reach support levels and all-time highs due to its enduring demand? Looking at the chart, it is evident that bulls have maintained their position above the falling wedge pattern's resistance line, indicating demand at lower levels.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Glassnode's Ethereum and Bitcoin Analysis
<p>Glassnode has focused its attention on Bitcoin and has identified an upcoming transition point in the market cycle. This transition, coupled with macroeconomics and price action for Bitcoin and Ethereum, is expected to lead to increased price volatility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given the ongoing SEC situation, the macro environment will become more unpredictable from next week onwards. Despite this uncertainty, the price of Bitcoin has managed to stay above the crucial support at $25,000, suggesting that recent SEC events are already factored into the price.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Traders are keen to buy the dip, with notable figures like ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood investing millions of dollars in Coinbase stock and Block Inc. shares.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve: A Comprehensive Web3 Trading Solution
<p>Tradecurve.io provides customers with a hybrid platform for trading cryptocurrencies and derivatives from a single account, eliminating the need to disclose personal information.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As one of the fastest-growing projects in the DeFi space, Tradecurve.io offers a unique hybrid exchange that removes entry barriers, provides deep liquidity, enables anonymous trading, and ensures fast execution. It is one of the first decentralized exchanges to use cryptocurrencies as collateral, offering spot trading for traditional assets such as stocks, forex, commodities, and cryptocurrencies like Ethereum and Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Onboarding on Tradecurve is straightforward, requiring users to connect their wallets to the Ethereum network, deposit crypto, and begin trading. Traders can subscribe to AI and algorithmic trading bots or use copy trading features to replicate the strategies of top traders in the market. Beginners can benefit from the metaverse trading academy, which offers a wide range of learning opportunities and live lectures.</p>
<p>TCRV tokens are currently available for purchase at $0.015 in the soon-to-end stage 3 of the ongoing presale. The value will increase by 25% to $0.018 when entering stage 4. By the end of the presale period alone, TCRV is projected to achieve a 5,000% gain, positioning Tradecurve as potentially one of the most promising investments in the market.</p>
<p>Discover more surrounding Tradecurve and TCRV below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Orbiting 26587 Objective - 19 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-26587-objective-19-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-18-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-18-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-18-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 16:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-26587-objective-19-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 26587 Objective:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 19 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) moderated early in the Asian session as the pair continues to orbit the 26587.57 area, an upside price objective above which Stops were recently executed and that is associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders recently pushed BTC/USD up to the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26326.83 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26169.53.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly abov SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 26587 Objective:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 19 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) moderated early in the Asian session as the pair continues to orbit the 26587.57 area, an upside price objective above which Stops were recently executed and that is associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders recently pushed BTC/USD up to the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26326.83 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26169.53.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly abov SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Where to put wealth in a complex economic world: Bitcoin?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/where-to-put-wealth-in-a-complex-economic-world-bitcoin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-46.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-46.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-46.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:59:44 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/where-to-put-wealth-in-a-complex-economic-world-bitcoin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Retail investors with any &lsquo;savings&rsquo; must be wondering where on earth they are going to put them in order to survive the potential armageddon to come.</p>
Few understand what is coming financially
<p>The fact probably needs to be faced that the vast majority of the world&rsquo;s citizens still have no clue of the financial maelstrom that will hit them at some point over the next few months or years.</p>
<p>Governments take advantage of, and it probably could be argued that they encourage, the ridiculously low level of financial education among the citizenry in general.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If it weren&rsquo;t for various internet platforms even those who do want to know what is really happening would just be stuck with media such as television where even the most benign debates are just a circus show and an excuse for proper economic conversations among experts.</p>
Holding fiat will not protect you
<p>So back to the savings, a process once viewed as a perfectly normal and intelligent thing to do. Anyway, people still do it, probably blissfully unaware of how what they have saved has reduced in purchasing power - the more drastically the longer it has been saved.</p>
<p>It could probably be safely argued that in general keeping one&rsquo;s currency in traditional areas such as bonds, stocks, and even in real estate, will not protect the wealth of the individual if the worst is to happen.</p>
<p>What could that &lsquo;worst&rsquo; be? That doesn&rsquo;t come into the scope of this article, but suffice to say that a black swan, such as a really bad recession, could lead to governments having the excuse they need to impose their central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), and then also bring in their &lsquo;great reset&rsquo;, which could make the existing fiat currency worthless. That sort of scenario and how it might be survived is indeed food for thought.</p>
A traditional hedge
<p>Traditionally, in order to add some measure of protection and insurance to one's portfolio, gold is the asset to have. This is still true today, although with the caveat that the gold price is still arguably manipulated by banks. Even so, gold should at least protect what you have.</p>
Bitcoin even better?
<p>This finally brings us to Bitcoin, an asset that is similar to gold, in that it has a scarce supply, and cannot be debased, although it must be recognised that gold does have a 2% inflation each year which is equivalent to the newly mined supply that is added to the total of above ground stocks.</p>
<p>Contrary to this, Bitcoin has a halving every 4 years that is built into the code, and this cuts the supply in 2. Add to this the portability of bitcoin - it recognises no national borders and can be sent to anyone in any country in the world, cheaply and without any bank, regulatory agency or government being able to say no.</p>
<p>Gold and silver have had their prices manipulated on the Western LBMA and COMEX exchanges for decades, so even though they are sound money they have been able to be controlled by the big banks.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is outside of the system so the banks and government cannot do much about it. However, the recent Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF filing could be a first step for government, through the proxy of the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, to be able to start exerting some control over Bitcoin should at least one scenario play out.</p>
Now is a time for decision
<p>We have arrived at the junction of a new world order and what the average investor does now can go a long way towards protecting them in what is likely to be a very different monetary system.</p>
<p>Bearing in mind that all fiat currencies in history have always gone to zero, it will be incumbent for every investor to watch their government and central bank very closely and to do their research on the options that might protect them.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Retail investors with any &lsquo;savings&rsquo; must be wondering where on earth they are going to put them in order to survive the potential armageddon to come.</p>
Few understand what is coming financially
<p>The fact probably needs to be faced that the vast majority of the world&rsquo;s citizens still have no clue of the financial maelstrom that will hit them at some point over the next few months or years.</p>
<p>Governments take advantage of, and it probably could be argued that they encourage, the ridiculously low level of financial education among the citizenry in general.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If it weren&rsquo;t for various internet platforms even those who do want to know what is really happening would just be stuck with media such as television where even the most benign debates are just a circus show and an excuse for proper economic conversations among experts.</p>
Holding fiat will not protect you
<p>So back to the savings, a process once viewed as a perfectly normal and intelligent thing to do. Anyway, people still do it, probably blissfully unaware of how what they have saved has reduced in purchasing power - the more drastically the longer it has been saved.</p>
<p>It could probably be safely argued that in general keeping one&rsquo;s currency in traditional areas such as bonds, stocks, and even in real estate, will not protect the wealth of the individual if the worst is to happen.</p>
<p>What could that &lsquo;worst&rsquo; be? That doesn&rsquo;t come into the scope of this article, but suffice to say that a black swan, such as a really bad recession, could lead to governments having the excuse they need to impose their central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), and then also bring in their &lsquo;great reset&rsquo;, which could make the existing fiat currency worthless. That sort of scenario and how it might be survived is indeed food for thought.</p>
A traditional hedge
<p>Traditionally, in order to add some measure of protection and insurance to one's portfolio, gold is the asset to have. This is still true today, although with the caveat that the gold price is still arguably manipulated by banks. Even so, gold should at least protect what you have.</p>
Bitcoin even better?
<p>This finally brings us to Bitcoin, an asset that is similar to gold, in that it has a scarce supply, and cannot be debased, although it must be recognised that gold does have a 2% inflation each year which is equivalent to the newly mined supply that is added to the total of above ground stocks.</p>
<p>Contrary to this, Bitcoin has a halving every 4 years that is built into the code, and this cuts the supply in 2. Add to this the portability of bitcoin - it recognises no national borders and can be sent to anyone in any country in the world, cheaply and without any bank, regulatory agency or government being able to say no.</p>
<p>Gold and silver have had their prices manipulated on the Western LBMA and COMEX exchanges for decades, so even though they are sound money they have been able to be controlled by the big banks.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is outside of the system so the banks and government cannot do much about it. However, the recent Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF filing could be a first step for government, through the proxy of the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, to be able to start exerting some control over Bitcoin should at least one scenario play out.</p>
Now is a time for decision
<p>We have arrived at the junction of a new world order and what the average investor does now can go a long way towards protecting them in what is likely to be a very different monetary system.</p>
<p>Bearing in mind that all fiat currencies in history have always gone to zero, it will be incumbent for every investor to watch their government and central bank very closely and to do their research on the options that might protect them.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: SEC Under Fire And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-weekly-roundup-sec-under-fire-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-weekly-roundup-sec-under-fire-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC has been facing increasing levels of scrutiny and criticism over its less than ideal approach to regulating the industry. It has come under fire from various industry leaders and a bill to dismiss the chairperson has even garnered support from several lawmakers. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>The world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, BlackRock, has filed an application for a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF).&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are concerns that Blackrock could, in one fail swoop, take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance has announced the launch of its new subscription-based Bitcoin cloud mining services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve did not raise rates for the first time since the inflation-inspired start of its rapid interest rate expansion. However, crypto continues its downward slide.</p>
Ethereum
<p>The Bank of China (BOCI) has made history by issuing tokenized securities on the Ethereum blockchain in Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>Frax Finance has unveiled its plans to roll out an Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain, aptly named Fraxchain.</p>
<p>Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p>Uniswap has also unveiled plans for Uniswap v4, the next iteration of the hugely popular crypto platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An Aave proposal intended to prevent a particular account from accumulating more debt has led to significant controversy, with some stating that it violates the principle of neutrality in DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>A group of Terra Classic Core developers, the Joint L1 Task Force (L1TF), has announced that it is ready for the Parity Upgrade, set for the 14th of June, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution Polygon (MATIC) has unveiled its Version 2.0, the blueprint for which will be revealed over the next few weeks.</p>
Technology
<p>Polygon recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
Business
<p>The Banco de la Republica, Colombia&rsquo;s Central Bank, has announced a partnership with Ripple as it looks to explore the use of blockchain technology in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto investment arm of venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, a16z, announced it would be opening its first overseas office in London.</p>
<p>Korean-based cryptocurrency lending service, Delio, has temporarily suspended customer withdrawals due to financial irregularities involving crypto investment firm Haru.</p>
<p>Voyager customers were in for some good news a year after their assets were frozen, with the platform stating that they could withdraw a significant chunk of their crypto assets from June 20.&nbsp;</p>
<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations, citing challenges arising from the prolonged bear market.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Tether, the issuer of the leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p>Binance is reportedly under scrutiny from French financial regulatory authorities, who have been investigating the exchange's activities since at least the early quarter of 2022.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKCoin has come under the scrutiny of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) over accusations of making false promises to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Blockchain Association has filed a Freedom of Information Act request with the SEC over the regulator's interactions with Prometheum.</p>
<p>The Hong Kong government has proactively advocated for major banks to embrace clients engaged in digital currencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase has become the latest entity to push back against the SEC&rsquo;s proposal of changing the definition of an exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Tim Draper, the SEC Chair Gary Gensler is stifling the crypto sector leading to a potential long-term detrimental effect on technology in the US.</p>
<p>Following a Financial Services Committee hearing on Tuesday, a digital asset bill will be voted on in July which will give clarity to the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The SEC has requested four more months to respond to Coinbase&rsquo;s call for crypto regulatory clarity.</p>
<p>Crypto billionaires Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss cautioned the Democratic Party that its &ldquo;war on crypto&rdquo; will result in its losing crucial voters.</p>
<p>United States Congressman Warren Davidson has filed a new bill called the SEC Stabilization Act, which looks to restructure the regulatory body, including the dismissal of current SEC Chair Gary Gensler.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lawyers for FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried have stated that litigation proceedings against him could be significantly delayed if further charges are added against the founder.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Nike has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move - introducing a collection of sneaker NFTs in Fortnite.</p>
<p>Indian e-commerce giant Flipkart has formed a key alliance with Polygon, one of the industry's key crypto firms building infrastructure around an ecosystem of Web3 products.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC has been facing increasing levels of scrutiny and criticism over its less than ideal approach to regulating the industry. It has come under fire from various industry leaders and a bill to dismiss the chairperson has even garnered support from several lawmakers. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>The world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, BlackRock, has filed an application for a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF).&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are concerns that Blackrock could, in one fail swoop, take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance has announced the launch of its new subscription-based Bitcoin cloud mining services.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve did not raise rates for the first time since the inflation-inspired start of its rapid interest rate expansion. However, crypto continues its downward slide.</p>
Ethereum
<p>The Bank of China (BOCI) has made history by issuing tokenized securities on the Ethereum blockchain in Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>Frax Finance has unveiled its plans to roll out an Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain, aptly named Fraxchain.</p>
<p>Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p>Uniswap has also unveiled plans for Uniswap v4, the next iteration of the hugely popular crypto platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>An Aave proposal intended to prevent a particular account from accumulating more debt has led to significant controversy, with some stating that it violates the principle of neutrality in DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
Altcoins
<p>A group of Terra Classic Core developers, the Joint L1 Task Force (L1TF), has announced that it is ready for the Parity Upgrade, set for the 14th of June, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ethereum Layer-2 scaling solution Polygon (MATIC) has unveiled its Version 2.0, the blueprint for which will be revealed over the next few weeks.</p>
Technology
<p>Polygon recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
Business
<p>The Banco de la Republica, Colombia&rsquo;s Central Bank, has announced a partnership with Ripple as it looks to explore the use of blockchain technology in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto investment arm of venture capital firm Andreessen Horowitz, a16z, announced it would be opening its first overseas office in London.</p>
<p>Korean-based cryptocurrency lending service, Delio, has temporarily suspended customer withdrawals due to financial irregularities involving crypto investment firm Haru.</p>
<p>Voyager customers were in for some good news a year after their assets were frozen, with the platform stating that they could withdraw a significant chunk of their crypto assets from June 20.&nbsp;</p>
<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations, citing challenges arising from the prolonged bear market.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Tether, the issuer of the leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p>Binance is reportedly under scrutiny from French financial regulatory authorities, who have been investigating the exchange's activities since at least the early quarter of 2022.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKCoin has come under the scrutiny of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) over accusations of making false promises to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Blockchain Association has filed a Freedom of Information Act request with the SEC over the regulator's interactions with Prometheum.</p>
<p>The Hong Kong government has proactively advocated for major banks to embrace clients engaged in digital currencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinbase has become the latest entity to push back against the SEC&rsquo;s proposal of changing the definition of an exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Tim Draper, the SEC Chair Gary Gensler is stifling the crypto sector leading to a potential long-term detrimental effect on technology in the US.</p>
<p>Following a Financial Services Committee hearing on Tuesday, a digital asset bill will be voted on in July which will give clarity to the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The SEC has requested four more months to respond to Coinbase&rsquo;s call for crypto regulatory clarity.</p>
<p>Crypto billionaires Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss cautioned the Democratic Party that its &ldquo;war on crypto&rdquo; will result in its losing crucial voters.</p>
<p>United States Congressman Warren Davidson has filed a new bill called the SEC Stabilization Act, which looks to restructure the regulatory body, including the dismissal of current SEC Chair Gary Gensler.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lawyers for FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried have stated that litigation proceedings against him could be significantly delayed if further charges are added against the founder.&nbsp;</p>
NFT
<p>Nike has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move - introducing a collection of sneaker NFTs in Fortnite.</p>
<p>Indian e-commerce giant Flipkart has formed a key alliance with Polygon, one of the industry's key crypto firms building infrastructure around an ecosystem of Web3 products.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Twitter Bans 100K+ Accounts Linked To Crypto Project Metatime]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/twitter-bans-100k-accounts-linked-to-crypto-project-metatime</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-23.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-23.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image-23.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/twitter-bans-100k-accounts-linked-to-crypto-project-metatime</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>A few months before he bought Twitter, Elon Musk signaled that under his stewardship the microblogging platform would become a bastion of free speech.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But since buying the company, Twitter has become anything but. In the latest example of Twitter&rsquo;s heavy-handed censorship last week, a staggering 100,000+ accounts were reportedly either blocked or suspended simply for mentioning an aspiring crypto project, Metatime, as part of a token airdrop campaign.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter is one of the favorite social media platforms of crypto projects, serving as a place to share information and hold discussions with their communities. So the decision to ban over 100,000 accounts simply for retweeting and sharing messages posted by Metatime was a huge shock.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Horrified by Twitter&rsquo;s latest act of censorship, the crypto community sprung into action, with thousands of people sharing the hashtag #FreeMetaTime to draw attention to what happened and try to get the accounts unblocked.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The #FreeMetaTime campaign was inspired by a tweet from Metatime CEO Yusuf Sevim, who appealed to Musk personally to intervene and get the locked, banned and suspended accounts back to their rightful owners.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In his Tweet, Sevim explained that Metatime is a &ldquo;freedom project&rdquo; that has already brought hope to more than 350,000 supporters globally since its launch just six months ago. He explained how the MetaAirdrop campaign gives those people a chance to earn free MetatimeCoin ($MTC) tokens by sharing their ideas and support for the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Unfortunately, today, Twitter accounts of more than 100,000 users (some of them following&nbsp;</p>
<p>@MetatimeCom and our other Metatime ecosystem accounts and most of them are at least 5 years old), were locked, banned, or suspended without any justified reason,&rdquo; Sevim said. &ldquo;Overnight, the voices of thousands of people sharing the hope of Metatime and MetaAirdrop were attempted to be silenced. Notably, this calamity struck the very morning after the day we announced our listing on the stock exchange on 26.06.2023.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Sevim said the decision to ban so many accounts isn&rsquo;t just a problem for Metatime, but for everyone who uses Twitter and social media platforms. He said it raises serious questions about who determines what the boundaries of freedom of thought and expression are.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;@ElonMusk, I reach out to you as a powerful businessperson, innovator, and thought leader. We ask you to defend our thoughts, our voice, and our community's right to stand together and express our ideas freely,&rdquo; Sevim said. &ldquo;What is being done to Metatime today might have been done to you in the past, and could be done to any free-thinking individual tomorrow.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hello @ElonMusk, with great hope and warm regards,Metatime is a freedom project powered by Blockchain technology that, in just a short 6 months, has brought hope to more than 350,000 people worldwide, helping them forge their freedoms and futures. With MetaAirdrop, tens of&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Yusuf Sevim (@Yusuf_Metatime) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Sadly for Metatime, Sevim&rsquo;s tweet and a follow up post have both gone unanswered and it&rsquo;s believed that many thousands of accounts still remain inaccessible to their users. Though it&rsquo;s undoubtedly true that Musk is an extremely busy man and may not have seen Sevim&rsquo;s tweet, his inaction stands at odds with public statements from him and Twitter&rsquo;s new CEO Linda Yaccarino.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In a recent memo to employees after taking up her role as CEO, Yaccarino stated that a healthy civilization needs an "unfiltered exchange of information and open dialogue about the things that matter most to us." She added that, &ldquo;You should have the freedom to speak your mind. We all should.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s no reason to disbelieve Yaccarino&rsquo;s comment, but what happened to Metatime clearly demonstrates that Twitter still has a lot of work to do if it&rsquo;s too live up to those promises.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the meantime, Metatime&rsquo;s co-founder Hys Sahin stated that the project will keep up the pressure on Musk and Twitter until every single blocked account is restored to its user:&nbsp;</p>
<p>A heartfelt thank you to all who stood by our fellow members with suddenly blocked Twitter accounts. Your support, shown through "Free Metatime" posts, is truly remarkable,&rdquo; Sahin said. &ldquo;Together, we'll continue supporting one another until every account is unblocked. Thank you for being an incredible community!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A few months before he bought Twitter, Elon Musk signaled that under his stewardship the microblogging platform would become a bastion of free speech.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But since buying the company, Twitter has become anything but. In the latest example of Twitter&rsquo;s heavy-handed censorship last week, a staggering 100,000+ accounts were reportedly either blocked or suspended simply for mentioning an aspiring crypto project, Metatime, as part of a token airdrop campaign.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter is one of the favorite social media platforms of crypto projects, serving as a place to share information and hold discussions with their communities. So the decision to ban over 100,000 accounts simply for retweeting and sharing messages posted by Metatime was a huge shock.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Horrified by Twitter&rsquo;s latest act of censorship, the crypto community sprung into action, with thousands of people sharing the hashtag #FreeMetaTime to draw attention to what happened and try to get the accounts unblocked.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The #FreeMetaTime campaign was inspired by a tweet from Metatime CEO Yusuf Sevim, who appealed to Musk personally to intervene and get the locked, banned and suspended accounts back to their rightful owners.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In his Tweet, Sevim explained that Metatime is a &ldquo;freedom project&rdquo; that has already brought hope to more than 350,000 supporters globally since its launch just six months ago. He explained how the MetaAirdrop campaign gives those people a chance to earn free MetatimeCoin ($MTC) tokens by sharing their ideas and support for the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Unfortunately, today, Twitter accounts of more than 100,000 users (some of them following&nbsp;</p>
<p>@MetatimeCom and our other Metatime ecosystem accounts and most of them are at least 5 years old), were locked, banned, or suspended without any justified reason,&rdquo; Sevim said. &ldquo;Overnight, the voices of thousands of people sharing the hope of Metatime and MetaAirdrop were attempted to be silenced. Notably, this calamity struck the very morning after the day we announced our listing on the stock exchange on 26.06.2023.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Sevim said the decision to ban so many accounts isn&rsquo;t just a problem for Metatime, but for everyone who uses Twitter and social media platforms. He said it raises serious questions about who determines what the boundaries of freedom of thought and expression are.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;@ElonMusk, I reach out to you as a powerful businessperson, innovator, and thought leader. We ask you to defend our thoughts, our voice, and our community's right to stand together and express our ideas freely,&rdquo; Sevim said. &ldquo;What is being done to Metatime today might have been done to you in the past, and could be done to any free-thinking individual tomorrow.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hello @ElonMusk, with great hope and warm regards,Metatime is a freedom project powered by Blockchain technology that, in just a short 6 months, has brought hope to more than 350,000 people worldwide, helping them forge their freedoms and futures. With MetaAirdrop, tens of&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Yusuf Sevim (@Yusuf_Metatime) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Sadly for Metatime, Sevim&rsquo;s tweet and a follow up post have both gone unanswered and it&rsquo;s believed that many thousands of accounts still remain inaccessible to their users. Though it&rsquo;s undoubtedly true that Musk is an extremely busy man and may not have seen Sevim&rsquo;s tweet, his inaction stands at odds with public statements from him and Twitter&rsquo;s new CEO Linda Yaccarino.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In a recent memo to employees after taking up her role as CEO, Yaccarino stated that a healthy civilization needs an "unfiltered exchange of information and open dialogue about the things that matter most to us." She added that, &ldquo;You should have the freedom to speak your mind. We all should.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>
<p>There&rsquo;s no reason to disbelieve Yaccarino&rsquo;s comment, but what happened to Metatime clearly demonstrates that Twitter still has a lot of work to do if it&rsquo;s too live up to those promises.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the meantime, Metatime&rsquo;s co-founder Hys Sahin stated that the project will keep up the pressure on Musk and Twitter until every single blocked account is restored to its user:&nbsp;</p>
<p>A heartfelt thank you to all who stood by our fellow members with suddenly blocked Twitter accounts. Your support, shown through "Free Metatime" posts, is truly remarkable,&rdquo; Sahin said. &ldquo;Together, we'll continue supporting one another until every account is unblocked. Thank you for being an incredible community!&rdquo;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Proposes New Ecosystem Council]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-proposes-new-ecosystem-council</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-proposes-new-ecosystem-council</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon, the renowned Ethereum scaling solution, recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This proposal, revolving around the establishment of an "Ecosystem Council," will redefine how system smart contracts within the Polygon environment are managed and upgraded. This proposal indicates the continuous efforts by Polygon to strike a perfect balance between community-driven governance and efficient decision-making in a decentralized network.</p>
A New System for Decentralized Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">System smart contracts represent a fundamental element of the blockchain infrastructure. They can directly or indirectly influence user funds and the infrastructure's functioning. A crucial aspect of these contracts is their upgradeability, which allows seamless migration to improved versions under specific circumstances. The importance of this feature is evident in various Layer 2 (L2) solutions, such as Optimism, Arbitrum, and zkSync, where an efficient means of patching bugs and upgrading pivotal architecture components is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the proposal, the Ecosystem Council would comprise technically proficient and value-aligned individuals, elected and removable by the community. This council will be responsible for performing timelock-limited upgrades to system smart contracts across Polygon networks, such as Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For example, in the case of non-emergency or routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the timelock as usual. On the other hand, if there is a perceived threat to user funds due to potential vulnerabilities in smart contracts, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect assets. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polygon community will be empowered with three competencies: the election and removal of Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit an Emergency State, and the power to veto any upgrade proposed by the Ecosystem Council. This model is expected to increase community engagement while retaining a level of control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
The Ecosystem Council: Balancing Efficiency and Decentralization
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposed model suggests the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a group consisting of reputable, technically adept, and value-aligned individuals. These individuals would be democratically elected by the community and could also be removed by them. The council's primary role would be to perform timelock-limited upgrades to the system's smart contracts across the Polygon networks, including the Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The governance model will allow the council to handle both routine and sensitive proposals. In the case of routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the standard timelock protocol. However, if a potential vulnerability poses a risk to user funds, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect the funds. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To maintain a balance between efficiency and community engagement, Polygon proposes empowering the community with several competencies. These include the power to elect and remove Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit the Emergency State, and the authority to veto any upgrade proposed and scheduled by the Ecosystem Council. By bestowing the community with these powers, Polygon hopes to increase the overall community engagement while maintaining a level of centralized control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
Navigating the Transition: Inviting Community Input
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the proposed model promises improved governance and security, its rollout must be gradual and well planned, especially considering the live nature of the blockchain. To ensure a seamless transition, the Polygon team is inviting its community to participate in the process, providing feedback, and assisting in answering open questions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The community is particularly encouraged to contribute ideas regarding incentivizing participation in the model and establishing a robust and secure voting mechanism. Decisions around these aspects, like the general design principles, voting power proxy, and architecture, will be crucial to the model's success. The team is also considering the use of the $MATIC token as a voting power proxy, which would provide broad ecosystem inclusion and legitimize the Ecosystem Council.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Polygon's proposed Ecosystem Council represents an exciting step towards more robust, efficient, and community-driven governance of system smart contracts. By integrating elements of both centralized and decentralized decision-making, the model aims to bring the best of both worlds to the Polygon network. This move could help Polygon maintain its reputation as a leading Layer 2 solution, offering an improved governance framework that values efficiency, security, and community inclusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon, the renowned Ethereum scaling solution, recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This proposal, revolving around the establishment of an "Ecosystem Council," will redefine how system smart contracts within the Polygon environment are managed and upgraded. This proposal indicates the continuous efforts by Polygon to strike a perfect balance between community-driven governance and efficient decision-making in a decentralized network.</p>
A New System for Decentralized Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">System smart contracts represent a fundamental element of the blockchain infrastructure. They can directly or indirectly influence user funds and the infrastructure's functioning. A crucial aspect of these contracts is their upgradeability, which allows seamless migration to improved versions under specific circumstances. The importance of this feature is evident in various Layer 2 (L2) solutions, such as Optimism, Arbitrum, and zkSync, where an efficient means of patching bugs and upgrading pivotal architecture components is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the proposal, the Ecosystem Council would comprise technically proficient and value-aligned individuals, elected and removable by the community. This council will be responsible for performing timelock-limited upgrades to system smart contracts across Polygon networks, such as Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For example, in the case of non-emergency or routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the timelock as usual. On the other hand, if there is a perceived threat to user funds due to potential vulnerabilities in smart contracts, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect assets. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polygon community will be empowered with three competencies: the election and removal of Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit an Emergency State, and the power to veto any upgrade proposed by the Ecosystem Council. This model is expected to increase community engagement while retaining a level of control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
The Ecosystem Council: Balancing Efficiency and Decentralization
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposed model suggests the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a group consisting of reputable, technically adept, and value-aligned individuals. These individuals would be democratically elected by the community and could also be removed by them. The council's primary role would be to perform timelock-limited upgrades to the system's smart contracts across the Polygon networks, including the Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The governance model will allow the council to handle both routine and sensitive proposals. In the case of routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the standard timelock protocol. However, if a potential vulnerability poses a risk to user funds, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect the funds. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To maintain a balance between efficiency and community engagement, Polygon proposes empowering the community with several competencies. These include the power to elect and remove Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit the Emergency State, and the authority to veto any upgrade proposed and scheduled by the Ecosystem Council. By bestowing the community with these powers, Polygon hopes to increase the overall community engagement while maintaining a level of centralized control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
Navigating the Transition: Inviting Community Input
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the proposed model promises improved governance and security, its rollout must be gradual and well planned, especially considering the live nature of the blockchain. To ensure a seamless transition, the Polygon team is inviting its community to participate in the process, providing feedback, and assisting in answering open questions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The community is particularly encouraged to contribute ideas regarding incentivizing participation in the model and establishing a robust and secure voting mechanism. Decisions around these aspects, like the general design principles, voting power proxy, and architecture, will be crucial to the model's success. The team is also considering the use of the $MATIC token as a voting power proxy, which would provide broad ecosystem inclusion and legitimize the Ecosystem Council.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Polygon's proposed Ecosystem Council represents an exciting step towards more robust, efficient, and community-driven governance of system smart contracts. By integrating elements of both centralized and decentralized decision-making, the model aims to bring the best of both worlds to the Polygon network. This move could help Polygon maintain its reputation as a leading Layer 2 solution, offering an improved governance framework that values efficiency, security, and community inclusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Price Prediction: LTC Halving Draws Close; Uwerx (WERX) Bullish Run Continues as Listing Nears]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/litecoin-ltc-price-prediction-ltc-halving-draws-close-uwerx-werx-bullish-run-continues-as-listing-nears</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/litecoin-ltc-price-prediction-ltc-halving-draws-close-uwerx-werx-bullish-run-continues-as-listing-nears</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the countdown to the Litecoin (LTC) halving event begins, the crypto community eagerly awaits the potential price implications of this significant milestone. Simultaneously, the market is enthusiastic as Uwerx approaches its highly anticipated listing.</p>
<p>In this article, we delve into the Litecoin (LTC) price prediction and the bullish momentum surrounding Uwerx, providing valuable insights to navigate these exciting developments. </p>
<p class="s8">Litecoin (LTC): Price Prediction</p>
<p>Revolutionizing digital payments, Litecoin (LTC) leverages blockchain technology to ensure swift, secure, and cost-effective transactions. </p>
<p>While sharing similarities with Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC) distinguishes itself with unique attributes like a different hashing algorithm, rapid block transaction times, and a capped maximum supply.</p>
<p>Presently valued at $91.15, Litecoin (LTC) boasts a market cap of $6,652,668,844, firmly establishing its position as a significant contender in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Industry analysts anticipate promising growth for Litecoin (LTC), envisioning a potential value of $153 by Q4 2024, reflecting its upward trajectory and future potential. </p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Fueling the Freelance Revolution with Unparalleled Backing</p>
<p>Boasting an impressive tally of over 5,500 sign-ups, a thriving Twitter following surpassing 1,600, and a vibrant Telegram community exceeding 1,600 members, Uwerx has amassed remarkable interest and unwavering support. Such fervent backing is a testament to the platform's tremendous potential for success. Brace yourself for the dawn of a groundbreaking era in freelancing.</p>
<p>Uwerx is preparing for a fascinating Test Airdrop, receiving resounding support of 98.2% in a Twitter poll. This happens on July 31st &nbsp;as the presale concludes, marking the highly anticipated occasion.</p>
<p>Responding to the community's demands, Uwerx is swiftly implementing a 25-year token lock, endorsed by 82.8% of voters. This strategic move ensures enduring stability and security, solidifying Uwerx's unwavering commitment to its valued investors.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Accelerating through Presale Stages, Unleashing Limitless Potential</p>
<p>Embark on an exhilarating journey with Uwerx as its presale rapidly advances through Stage 5, offering a captivating WERX token price of $0.041 with a juicy bonus on orders of 15%. This extraordinary opportunity awaits those seeking to join Uwerx'svoyage of growth and triumph.</p>
<p>Witness the extraordinary pace of Uwerx's presale stages, where Stage 1 to Stage 4 achieved an impressive completion in a short time. These remarkable achievements showcase the unwavering enthusiasm and unwavering confidence surrounding Uwerx'srevolutionary vision.</p>
<p>Setting a groundbreaking precedent, Uwerx distinguishes itself from industry giants by introducing a minimal transaction fee of just 1%, an exceptional contrast to the burdensome charges of 10% by Upwork and 20% by Fiverr. This revolutionary fee structure brings forth equity, benefiting freelancers and clients and fostering a harmonious and thriving ecosystem.</p>
<p>Reinforcing its commitment to security and trust, Uwerxundergoes comprehensive audits by the esteemed SolidProofand InterFi Network, ensuring unparalleled integrity and reliability. These rigorous evaluations provide users with unwavering assurance, establishing Uwerx as a platform built on transparency and accountability.</p>
<p>Emphasizing transparency and autonomy, Uwerx plans to renounce its contracts upon readiness for centralized exchange listings, solidifying its commitment to a decentralized future. Additionally, the platform's commitment to fairness is further reinforced by reducing taxes to zero, enabling an environment of equal opportunities and independence.</p>
<p>Introducing the revolutionary Uwerx Vault, an impregnable storage solution for WERX tokens. Users can securely store their tokens within the vault and engage in staking and unlocking rewards based on platform variables. This groundbreaking feature amplifies active participation and fosters an engaged community within the dynamic Uwerx ecosystem.</p>
<p>Uwerx's imminent listing on CoinSniper and its forthcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st propels its visibility and accessibility to new heights. These strategic listings broaden Uwerx's horizons, opening abundant avenues for users to immerse themselves in the platform and actively contribute to its exponential growth. Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey with Uwerx, where limitless potential awaits.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX) Nears Beta Platform Launch: Empowering Users through Testing and Feedback</p>
<p>The wait is over! Uwerx has made its Alpha platform available to the public, ushering in a new era of possibilities. But guess what? Uwerx isn't one to rest on its laurels. With the Beta platform on the horizon, the future's looking brighter than ever.</p>
<p>With impressive progress, an unwaveringly supportive community, and an ambitious roadmap, Uwerx emerges as a trailblazer, spearheading the revolution in the freelance industry. Its distinct approach and exclusive attributes offer a compelling investment opportunity that astute investors should consider seizing to maximize their gains. </p>
<p>More update on the Alpha platform has been released as PDFs again. Included is a total of TEN pages, ranging from Signing Up, Logging In, Forgot password, Freelancer or Client initiation, Initial step of Job Creation and initial step of Finding Talent, My activity page, Hiring dashboard page, Job creation process page(s). There&rsquo;s also more to come in during the week!</p>
<p>Share your design suggestions, feedback, thoughts, and recommendations by emailing feedback@uwerx.network. Your contribution will help shape the future of Uwerx. Unleash your potential with Uwerx as it forges ahead, fueled by innovation and user-centricity.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the countdown to the Litecoin (LTC) halving event begins, the crypto community eagerly awaits the potential price implications of this significant milestone. Simultaneously, the market is enthusiastic as Uwerx approaches its highly anticipated listing.</p>
<p>In this article, we delve into the Litecoin (LTC) price prediction and the bullish momentum surrounding Uwerx, providing valuable insights to navigate these exciting developments. </p>
<p class="s8">Litecoin (LTC): Price Prediction</p>
<p>Revolutionizing digital payments, Litecoin (LTC) leverages blockchain technology to ensure swift, secure, and cost-effective transactions. </p>
<p>While sharing similarities with Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC) distinguishes itself with unique attributes like a different hashing algorithm, rapid block transaction times, and a capped maximum supply.</p>
<p>Presently valued at $91.15, Litecoin (LTC) boasts a market cap of $6,652,668,844, firmly establishing its position as a significant contender in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Industry analysts anticipate promising growth for Litecoin (LTC), envisioning a potential value of $153 by Q4 2024, reflecting its upward trajectory and future potential. </p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Fueling the Freelance Revolution with Unparalleled Backing</p>
<p>Boasting an impressive tally of over 5,500 sign-ups, a thriving Twitter following surpassing 1,600, and a vibrant Telegram community exceeding 1,600 members, Uwerx has amassed remarkable interest and unwavering support. Such fervent backing is a testament to the platform's tremendous potential for success. Brace yourself for the dawn of a groundbreaking era in freelancing.</p>
<p>Uwerx is preparing for a fascinating Test Airdrop, receiving resounding support of 98.2% in a Twitter poll. This happens on July 31st &nbsp;as the presale concludes, marking the highly anticipated occasion.</p>
<p>Responding to the community's demands, Uwerx is swiftly implementing a 25-year token lock, endorsed by 82.8% of voters. This strategic move ensures enduring stability and security, solidifying Uwerx's unwavering commitment to its valued investors.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Accelerating through Presale Stages, Unleashing Limitless Potential</p>
<p>Embark on an exhilarating journey with Uwerx as its presale rapidly advances through Stage 5, offering a captivating WERX token price of $0.041 with a juicy bonus on orders of 15%. This extraordinary opportunity awaits those seeking to join Uwerx'svoyage of growth and triumph.</p>
<p>Witness the extraordinary pace of Uwerx's presale stages, where Stage 1 to Stage 4 achieved an impressive completion in a short time. These remarkable achievements showcase the unwavering enthusiasm and unwavering confidence surrounding Uwerx'srevolutionary vision.</p>
<p>Setting a groundbreaking precedent, Uwerx distinguishes itself from industry giants by introducing a minimal transaction fee of just 1%, an exceptional contrast to the burdensome charges of 10% by Upwork and 20% by Fiverr. This revolutionary fee structure brings forth equity, benefiting freelancers and clients and fostering a harmonious and thriving ecosystem.</p>
<p>Reinforcing its commitment to security and trust, Uwerxundergoes comprehensive audits by the esteemed SolidProofand InterFi Network, ensuring unparalleled integrity and reliability. These rigorous evaluations provide users with unwavering assurance, establishing Uwerx as a platform built on transparency and accountability.</p>
<p>Emphasizing transparency and autonomy, Uwerx plans to renounce its contracts upon readiness for centralized exchange listings, solidifying its commitment to a decentralized future. Additionally, the platform's commitment to fairness is further reinforced by reducing taxes to zero, enabling an environment of equal opportunities and independence.</p>
<p>Introducing the revolutionary Uwerx Vault, an impregnable storage solution for WERX tokens. Users can securely store their tokens within the vault and engage in staking and unlocking rewards based on platform variables. This groundbreaking feature amplifies active participation and fosters an engaged community within the dynamic Uwerx ecosystem.</p>
<p>Uwerx's imminent listing on CoinSniper and its forthcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st propels its visibility and accessibility to new heights. These strategic listings broaden Uwerx's horizons, opening abundant avenues for users to immerse themselves in the platform and actively contribute to its exponential growth. Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey with Uwerx, where limitless potential awaits.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX) Nears Beta Platform Launch: Empowering Users through Testing and Feedback</p>
<p>The wait is over! Uwerx has made its Alpha platform available to the public, ushering in a new era of possibilities. But guess what? Uwerx isn't one to rest on its laurels. With the Beta platform on the horizon, the future's looking brighter than ever.</p>
<p>With impressive progress, an unwaveringly supportive community, and an ambitious roadmap, Uwerx emerges as a trailblazer, spearheading the revolution in the freelance industry. Its distinct approach and exclusive attributes offer a compelling investment opportunity that astute investors should consider seizing to maximize their gains. </p>
<p>More update on the Alpha platform has been released as PDFs again. Included is a total of TEN pages, ranging from Signing Up, Logging In, Forgot password, Freelancer or Client initiation, Initial step of Job Creation and initial step of Finding Talent, My activity page, Hiring dashboard page, Job creation process page(s). There&rsquo;s also more to come in during the week!</p>
<p>Share your design suggestions, feedback, thoughts, and recommendations by emailing feedback@uwerx.network. Your contribution will help shape the future of Uwerx. Unleash your potential with Uwerx as it forges ahead, fueled by innovation and user-centricity.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Discover InQubeta, The 50x Crypto Powering The Future of AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/discover-inqubeta-the-50x-crypto-powering-the-future-of-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/discover-inqubeta-the-50x-crypto-powering-the-future-of-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">InQubeta, an innovative AI technology startup, is revolutionizing the landscape of artificial intelligence. With its groundbreaking solutions and visionary approach, InQubeta is at the forefront of transforming industries and unlocking the true potential of AI. </p>
<p class="s5">As we delve into the world of InQubeta, we embark on a captivating journey that showcases the magic of this remarkable platform and its potential to shape the future.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta Is Powered By Its Unique Token QUBE</p>
<p class="s5">At the core of InQubeta lies its native token, QUBE. This token serves as the gateway to an ecosystem where AI and blockchain converge. With its deflationary nature, QUBE offers a unique investment opportunity for crypto enthusiasts looking to diversify their portfolios. InQubeta has implemented a buy and sell tax mechanism that allocates 2% of transactions to a burn wallet and directs 5% to a dedicated reward pool. This deflationary model not only encourages long-term holding but also creates a scarcity effect that could potentially drive the value of QUBE upward over time.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, QUBE plays a pivotal role in the InQubetaecosystem, extending its utility beyond a mere investment vehicle. By leveraging QUBE on the InQubeta NFT marketplace, investors gain access to fractional investment opportunities in AI startups. The platform introduces innovative reward and equity-based NFTs, providing a seamless and efficient investment process. Powered by blockchain technology, this marketplace ensures transparency, security, and democratization, enabling investors of all backgrounds to participate in the AI revolution.</p>
<p class="s5">The transformative power of InQubeta extends beyond financial gains. QUBE serves as a governance token, empowering holders to participate in the decision-making processes of the platform actively. </p>
<p class="s5">Through a decentralized governance model, QUBE holders can propose ideas, engage in discussions, and cast votes on crucial matters that shape the future of InQubeta. This inclusive approach fosters a strong community and aligns the project's interests with those of its stakeholders, ensuring a collective effort in driving InQubeta's success.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta&rsquo;s Presale Surpasses $400,000 Milestone</p>
<p class="s5">As the InQubeta journey unfolds, investors are met with an enticing opportunity: the ongoing presale of QUBE tokens. This presale has already surpassed the impressive milestone of $400,000, highlighting the immense interest and support behind InQubeta's vision. By participating in the presale, investors can secure their stake in the future of AI and position themselves for potential exponential growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Joining the InQubeta presale is straightforward and accessible. With a minimum investment requirement that allows for wider participation, investors can contribute to the growth of this groundbreaking project. The presale accepts popular cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and USDT, ensuring a seamless investment process for all. The presale also allows you to purchase QUBE tokens with credit or debit cards.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">Don&rsquo;t Miss Out On InQubeta</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta is redefining the way we perceive and interact with artificial intelligence, unlocking new possibilities and paving the way for transformative advancements. The successful start to the presale, is a testament to the widespread enthusiasm and confidence in InQubeta's vision.</p>
<p class="s5">The combination of InQubeta's innovative solutions, the deflationary nature of QUBE, and the growing demand for AI technologies set the stage for a promising future for QUBE token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">Investing in QUBE tokens during the presale is not just an investment in the future of AI; it is an opportunity to be part of a revolutionary movement. With the potential for a 50x growth, according to industry experts, investing in QUBE today could yield significant returns in the future. Seize this moment, join the InQubeta presale, and be part of the magic reshaping the artificial intelligence world. The future awaits, and InQubeta is leading the way.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p>https://inqubeta.ai</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">InQubeta, an innovative AI technology startup, is revolutionizing the landscape of artificial intelligence. With its groundbreaking solutions and visionary approach, InQubeta is at the forefront of transforming industries and unlocking the true potential of AI. </p>
<p class="s5">As we delve into the world of InQubeta, we embark on a captivating journey that showcases the magic of this remarkable platform and its potential to shape the future.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta Is Powered By Its Unique Token QUBE</p>
<p class="s5">At the core of InQubeta lies its native token, QUBE. This token serves as the gateway to an ecosystem where AI and blockchain converge. With its deflationary nature, QUBE offers a unique investment opportunity for crypto enthusiasts looking to diversify their portfolios. InQubeta has implemented a buy and sell tax mechanism that allocates 2% of transactions to a burn wallet and directs 5% to a dedicated reward pool. This deflationary model not only encourages long-term holding but also creates a scarcity effect that could potentially drive the value of QUBE upward over time.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, QUBE plays a pivotal role in the InQubetaecosystem, extending its utility beyond a mere investment vehicle. By leveraging QUBE on the InQubeta NFT marketplace, investors gain access to fractional investment opportunities in AI startups. The platform introduces innovative reward and equity-based NFTs, providing a seamless and efficient investment process. Powered by blockchain technology, this marketplace ensures transparency, security, and democratization, enabling investors of all backgrounds to participate in the AI revolution.</p>
<p class="s5">The transformative power of InQubeta extends beyond financial gains. QUBE serves as a governance token, empowering holders to participate in the decision-making processes of the platform actively. </p>
<p class="s5">Through a decentralized governance model, QUBE holders can propose ideas, engage in discussions, and cast votes on crucial matters that shape the future of InQubeta. This inclusive approach fosters a strong community and aligns the project's interests with those of its stakeholders, ensuring a collective effort in driving InQubeta's success.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta&rsquo;s Presale Surpasses $400,000 Milestone</p>
<p class="s5">As the InQubeta journey unfolds, investors are met with an enticing opportunity: the ongoing presale of QUBE tokens. This presale has already surpassed the impressive milestone of $400,000, highlighting the immense interest and support behind InQubeta's vision. By participating in the presale, investors can secure their stake in the future of AI and position themselves for potential exponential growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Joining the InQubeta presale is straightforward and accessible. With a minimum investment requirement that allows for wider participation, investors can contribute to the growth of this groundbreaking project. The presale accepts popular cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and USDT, ensuring a seamless investment process for all. The presale also allows you to purchase QUBE tokens with credit or debit cards.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">Don&rsquo;t Miss Out On InQubeta</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta is redefining the way we perceive and interact with artificial intelligence, unlocking new possibilities and paving the way for transformative advancements. The successful start to the presale, is a testament to the widespread enthusiasm and confidence in InQubeta's vision.</p>
<p class="s5">The combination of InQubeta's innovative solutions, the deflationary nature of QUBE, and the growing demand for AI technologies set the stage for a promising future for QUBE token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">Investing in QUBE tokens during the presale is not just an investment in the future of AI; it is an opportunity to be part of a revolutionary movement. With the potential for a 50x growth, according to industry experts, investing in QUBE today could yield significant returns in the future. Seize this moment, join the InQubeta presale, and be part of the magic reshaping the artificial intelligence world. The future awaits, and InQubeta is leading the way.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p>https://inqubeta.ai</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  26587 Target Absorbed - 18 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-26587-target-absorbed-18-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-26587-target-absorbed-18-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Absorbs 26587 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 18 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Significant Stops were also elected above the 26587.57 area during the climb, an upside price objective associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26661.17 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25913.83.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Absorbs 26587 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 18 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Significant Stops were also elected above the 26587.57 area during the climb, an upside price objective associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26661.17 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25913.83.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tether Responds to Account Deactivation Controversy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/tether-responds-to-account-deactivation-controversy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/tether-responds-to-account-deactivation-controversy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to information released by the New York Attorney General (NYAG), Tether, the issuer of leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">While reasons for the individual account terminations remain undisclosed, the named entities included MoonPay, BlockFi, CMS Holdings, and Galois Capital.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Responding to the unfolding situation, Tether indicated its reluctance to comment on specific customer relationships, noting that each party had undergone stringent compliance checks both during onboarding and throughout their relationship, in line with Tether's compliance policies.</p>
NYAG Investigation and Tether's Commitment to Transparency
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the NYAG investigation wrapped up in early 2021, some of the documents in question extend until June of that year. These documents were collected during the NYAG's probe into Tether and sister company Bitfinex over the alleged misappropriation of $850 million. During this investigation, iFinex, the parent company of both entities, requested an extension to produce the required financial documents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Following a settlement that included an $18.5 million penalty and the cessation of trading in New York, media outlets and Coinbase sought the public disclosure of Tether&rsquo;s initial quarterly report under the Freedom of Information Act. However, Tether opposed this motion, citing the need to protect its customers' confidential data.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite Tether's objections, the NYAG granted media outlets access to the documents, leading to the revelation about the deacttivation of numerous company accounts. </p>
Tether's Stance on Transparency and Risk Management
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether remains adamant about its commitment to transparency while prioritizing its customers' privacy and security. Following the settlement with the NYAG, Tether has diligently completed its quarterly reporting obligations, affirming its commitment to openness and transparency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, Tether claims that it takes pride in its meticulous development of risk metrics and processes, enabling its investment and financial teams to thoroughly assess the risk tied to the company's financial interactions. Tether has continually demonstrated its commitment to sustaining its business objectives while adhering to a robust risk management culture.</p>
Tether's Reserves and Commercial Papers
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether's dedication to maintaining the highest standards is evident in its transparent dealings regarding its lending program and reserves. Tether's reserves have proven to be extremely liquid, high-quality, and readily available to support any size of redemption, demonstrated by the repayment of US$7 billion in 48 hours in 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the released documents, Tether has consistently maintained an A2 or better rating for the majority of its commercial papers, and none of its past statements have undergone any changes. This commitment to upholding the highest standards has been echoed in the company's dedication to accountability and its unwavering risk management culture. The firm, however, has been severely criticized over past decisions, especially in the case of blocking an MEV Validator as a security response.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether says that while media outlets have rushed to present this information to readers, Tether remains committed to its users, as well as for the benefit of the the broader crypto community. The company is keen to provide a factual point of reference about the disclosed materials, and it continues to cooperate with law enforcement, having assisted in over 150 investigations across four continents in the past 18 months. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to information released by the New York Attorney General (NYAG), Tether, the issuer of leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">While reasons for the individual account terminations remain undisclosed, the named entities included MoonPay, BlockFi, CMS Holdings, and Galois Capital.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Responding to the unfolding situation, Tether indicated its reluctance to comment on specific customer relationships, noting that each party had undergone stringent compliance checks both during onboarding and throughout their relationship, in line with Tether's compliance policies.</p>
NYAG Investigation and Tether's Commitment to Transparency
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the NYAG investigation wrapped up in early 2021, some of the documents in question extend until June of that year. These documents were collected during the NYAG's probe into Tether and sister company Bitfinex over the alleged misappropriation of $850 million. During this investigation, iFinex, the parent company of both entities, requested an extension to produce the required financial documents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Following a settlement that included an $18.5 million penalty and the cessation of trading in New York, media outlets and Coinbase sought the public disclosure of Tether&rsquo;s initial quarterly report under the Freedom of Information Act. However, Tether opposed this motion, citing the need to protect its customers' confidential data.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite Tether's objections, the NYAG granted media outlets access to the documents, leading to the revelation about the deacttivation of numerous company accounts. </p>
Tether's Stance on Transparency and Risk Management
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether remains adamant about its commitment to transparency while prioritizing its customers' privacy and security. Following the settlement with the NYAG, Tether has diligently completed its quarterly reporting obligations, affirming its commitment to openness and transparency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, Tether claims that it takes pride in its meticulous development of risk metrics and processes, enabling its investment and financial teams to thoroughly assess the risk tied to the company's financial interactions. Tether has continually demonstrated its commitment to sustaining its business objectives while adhering to a robust risk management culture.</p>
Tether's Reserves and Commercial Papers
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether's dedication to maintaining the highest standards is evident in its transparent dealings regarding its lending program and reserves. Tether's reserves have proven to be extremely liquid, high-quality, and readily available to support any size of redemption, demonstrated by the repayment of US$7 billion in 48 hours in 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the released documents, Tether has consistently maintained an A2 or better rating for the majority of its commercial papers, and none of its past statements have undergone any changes. This commitment to upholding the highest standards has been echoed in the company's dedication to accountability and its unwavering risk management culture. The firm, however, has been severely criticized over past decisions, especially in the case of blocking an MEV Validator as a security response.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether says that while media outlets have rushed to present this information to readers, Tether remains committed to its users, as well as for the benefit of the the broader crypto community. The company is keen to provide a factual point of reference about the disclosed materials, and it continues to cooperate with law enforcement, having assisted in over 150 investigations across four continents in the past 18 months. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap Aligns with Wormhole and Axelar for Cross-Chain Bridging]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uniswap-aligns-with-wormhole-and-axelar-for-cross-chain-bridging</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uniswap-aligns-with-wormhole-and-axelar-for-cross-chain-bridging</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These selections are the result of a comprehensive analysis conducted by Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee, which evaluated a range of potential protocols. The proposed changes are also aligned to the protocol's recent disclosure of its plans for V4.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Diving Deep into the Decision</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee scrutinized multiple contenders, namely Wormhole, Celer, DeBridge, LayerZero, Axelar, and Multichain (CRP). Each of these was rigorously assessed for its proficiency in facilitating cross-chain governance. Out of the competition, Wormhole and Axelar emerged victorious, with the committee endorsing these two for utilization across all cross-chain deployments.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the committee puts it, both Wormhole and Axelar have demonstrated their aptness in managing governance messaging for potential cross-chain deployments. They, however, advised the community to persistently review these and other bridge providers, bearing in mind the dynamics of the industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cross-Chain Governance and Its Implications</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The fundamental application for Uniswap DAO's cross-chain bridge lies in its ability to relay governance messages from Ethereum to other chains for execution. All Uniswap deployment proposals undertake a formal voting procedure on Ethereum. Any upgrades for deployments on alternate chains are then communicated via a cross-chain messaging protocol.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Wormhole and Axelar have gained the committee's approval, this doesn't entirely exclude other bridges. The report also pointed out that those deemed unsuitable for Uniswap's present cross-chain governance needs might still satisfy the prerequisites of other protocols and applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Vulnerabilities and Controversies: The Story of Cross-Chain Bridges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The controversy around cross-chain bridges in the Web3 sphere is nothing new. In 2022, these bridging protocols proved to be a weak spot, with hackers successfully exploiting them and causing billions in losses. As per data from Rekt, four out of the top five most expensive DeFi breaches targeted bridges, resulting in an aggregated loss of over $2.1 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to these vulnerabilities, Uniswap has formed its Cross-Chain Bridge Assessment Committee to aid governance delegates and the Uniswap community in making well-informed decisions regarding cross-chain bridging protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Committee's evaluations covered more than 130 assessment questions for each protocol, taking into account their ability to ensure "safety, liveness, and censorship resistance". Looking ahead, Celer and DeBridge might be reassessed despite their current shortcomings in slashing mechanisms and security assurances. The report was notably critical of Multichain for its lack of transparency and ineffective deterrents to prevent validator collusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To underscore the context, Uniswap has over $5.9 billion locked in its protocol as of May 2023, with daily transaction volume frequently exceeding $1 billion. Given these figures, Uniswap's choice of Wormhole and Axelar could have significant implications for both the involved protocols and Uniswap's ongoing cross-chain operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These selections are the result of a comprehensive analysis conducted by Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee, which evaluated a range of potential protocols. The proposed changes are also aligned to the protocol's recent disclosure of its plans for V4.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Diving Deep into the Decision</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee scrutinized multiple contenders, namely Wormhole, Celer, DeBridge, LayerZero, Axelar, and Multichain (CRP). Each of these was rigorously assessed for its proficiency in facilitating cross-chain governance. Out of the competition, Wormhole and Axelar emerged victorious, with the committee endorsing these two for utilization across all cross-chain deployments.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the committee puts it, both Wormhole and Axelar have demonstrated their aptness in managing governance messaging for potential cross-chain deployments. They, however, advised the community to persistently review these and other bridge providers, bearing in mind the dynamics of the industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cross-Chain Governance and Its Implications</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The fundamental application for Uniswap DAO's cross-chain bridge lies in its ability to relay governance messages from Ethereum to other chains for execution. All Uniswap deployment proposals undertake a formal voting procedure on Ethereum. Any upgrades for deployments on alternate chains are then communicated via a cross-chain messaging protocol.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Wormhole and Axelar have gained the committee's approval, this doesn't entirely exclude other bridges. The report also pointed out that those deemed unsuitable for Uniswap's present cross-chain governance needs might still satisfy the prerequisites of other protocols and applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Vulnerabilities and Controversies: The Story of Cross-Chain Bridges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The controversy around cross-chain bridges in the Web3 sphere is nothing new. In 2022, these bridging protocols proved to be a weak spot, with hackers successfully exploiting them and causing billions in losses. As per data from Rekt, four out of the top five most expensive DeFi breaches targeted bridges, resulting in an aggregated loss of over $2.1 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to these vulnerabilities, Uniswap has formed its Cross-Chain Bridge Assessment Committee to aid governance delegates and the Uniswap community in making well-informed decisions regarding cross-chain bridging protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Committee's evaluations covered more than 130 assessment questions for each protocol, taking into account their ability to ensure "safety, liveness, and censorship resistance". Looking ahead, Celer and DeBridge might be reassessed despite their current shortcomings in slashing mechanisms and security assurances. The report was notably critical of Multichain for its lack of transparency and ineffective deterrents to prevent validator collusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To underscore the context, Uniswap has over $5.9 billion locked in its protocol as of May 2023, with daily transaction volume frequently exceeding $1 billion. Given these figures, Uniswap's choice of Wormhole and Axelar could have significant implications for both the involved protocols and Uniswap's ongoing cross-chain operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Nike Teases Airphoria NFT Collab With Fortnite and Unreal Engine]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/nike-teases-airphoria-nft-collab-with-fortnite-and-unreal-engine</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/nike-teases-airphoria-nft-collab-with-fortnite-and-unreal-engine</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike, a titan in the world of footwear and apparel, has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move: introducing a collection of sneaker nonfungible tokens (NFTs) in Fortnite, the massively popular online game developed by Epic Games.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Rumors of Airphoria: A Possible Revolution in the Gaming Industry</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a series of June 16 social media posts, Nike teased an event set for June 20, which they termed the "ultimate Sneakerhunt". A promotional video showcased the logos of both Fortnite and Nike's Air Max amidst floating clouds. As the video transitions, it unveils the name of this intriguing venture, 'Airphoria', ending with a display of Nike's Web3 platform .SWOOSH logo alongside that of Epic Games' Unreal Engine.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">On 6.20 the ultimate Sneakerhunt begins. AirphoriaAirphoria pic.twitter.com/QgMyA1uXRT</p>
&mdash; Nike (@Nike) June 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">However, specific details remain elusive. Members of the NFT community have begun to speculate that Nike might have employed Fortnite Creative 2.0, a tool that allows users to craft their own virtual island game maps utilizing Fortnite assets, to devise an NFT-related game.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Leap Into Web3 for Nike with .SWOOSH</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This wouldn't be Nike's first foray into gaming. The company has been stepping up its efforts to merge its NFT unit, .SWOOSH, into traditional gaming. Just recently, on June 1, .SWOOSH announced its intention to incorporate its NFTs into games developed by EA Sports, a household name responsible for the incredibly successful FIFA soccer game franchise, among others. Although it's still not confirmed which EA Sports games will incorporate Nike NFTs, this latest hint seems to suggest that Nike's integration into the gaming world might be deeper than previously anticipated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although not yet confirmed, the probability of NFTs featuring in Airphoria is high, given .SWOOSH's involvement and Epic Games' known affinity for NFT gaming. If the speculations prove to be true, the move could provide a considerable opportunity for Web3 adoption amongst traditional gamers. Considering Fortnite's impressive player base of over 242.9 million active players in the past 30 days, as reported by Active Player, the potential impact could be monumental.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike has previously launched NFT sneakers on Polygon, as well as an earlier collaboration with RTFKT. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike, a titan in the world of footwear and apparel, has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move: introducing a collection of sneaker nonfungible tokens (NFTs) in Fortnite, the massively popular online game developed by Epic Games.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Rumors of Airphoria: A Possible Revolution in the Gaming Industry</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a series of June 16 social media posts, Nike teased an event set for June 20, which they termed the "ultimate Sneakerhunt". A promotional video showcased the logos of both Fortnite and Nike's Air Max amidst floating clouds. As the video transitions, it unveils the name of this intriguing venture, 'Airphoria', ending with a display of Nike's Web3 platform .SWOOSH logo alongside that of Epic Games' Unreal Engine.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">On 6.20 the ultimate Sneakerhunt begins. AirphoriaAirphoria pic.twitter.com/QgMyA1uXRT</p>
&mdash; Nike (@Nike) June 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">However, specific details remain elusive. Members of the NFT community have begun to speculate that Nike might have employed Fortnite Creative 2.0, a tool that allows users to craft their own virtual island game maps utilizing Fortnite assets, to devise an NFT-related game.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Leap Into Web3 for Nike with .SWOOSH</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This wouldn't be Nike's first foray into gaming. The company has been stepping up its efforts to merge its NFT unit, .SWOOSH, into traditional gaming. Just recently, on June 1, .SWOOSH announced its intention to incorporate its NFTs into games developed by EA Sports, a household name responsible for the incredibly successful FIFA soccer game franchise, among others. Although it's still not confirmed which EA Sports games will incorporate Nike NFTs, this latest hint seems to suggest that Nike's integration into the gaming world might be deeper than previously anticipated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although not yet confirmed, the probability of NFTs featuring in Airphoria is high, given .SWOOSH's involvement and Epic Games' known affinity for NFT gaming. If the speculations prove to be true, the move could provide a considerable opportunity for Web3 adoption amongst traditional gamers. Considering Fortnite's impressive player base of over 242.9 million active players in the past 30 days, as reported by Active Player, the potential impact could be monumental.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike has previously launched NFT sneakers on Polygon, as well as an earlier collaboration with RTFKT. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Why Blackrock Bitcoin spot ETF is a real worry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/why-blackrock-bitcoin-spot-etf-is-a-real-worry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:11:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/why-blackrock-bitcoin-spot-etf-is-a-real-worry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With Blackrock&rsquo;s recent spot ETF application many Bitcoincoiners are elated. However, should they be worried about this particular move by the $10 trillion asset manager?</p>

<p>&ldquo;I have not heard from any one client looking to buy a cryptocurrency at this time. Right now I can tell you that Worldwide, I have not heard from one client that said I need to be in this.</p>

<p>Larry Fink.</p>
<p>The Blackrock CEO did go on to say back in 2018 that his company would look back into crypto when it became more &ldquo;legitimised&rdquo;. Nearly 5 years later Blackrock is doing exactly that - but with crypto being singled out for extremely rough treatment from the SEC it could hardly be said that crypto has reached the legitimacy stage.</p>
<p>When such a massive and powerful institutional entity as Blackrock files an application for a Bitcoin ETF, when so many have failed, it might be guessed that there will have been some quiet conversations behind the scenes, and that some plan could be in place to exert control over the premier crypto asset.</p>
The Blackrock ESG commitment
<p>Larry Fink has said that he and his company are committed to pushing its ESG agenda.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;You have to force behaviours, and at Blackrock we are forcing behaviours&rdquo;</p>

<p>With Fink serving as a Trustee on the board of Klaus Schwab&rsquo;s World Economic Forum, you can be sure that this application for a Bitcoin Spot ETF will somehow play along with the ESG narrative.&nbsp;</p>
How Blackrock could potentially take control
<p>An extremely thought-provoking tweet by @anilsaidso posits how Blackrock could in one fail swoop take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A hidden gem in the BlackRock ETF filing.#GetForked https://t.co/tER6xxZPui pic.twitter.com/Qdt8BZ2OEZ</p>
&mdash; Anil  (@anilsaidso) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Hidden within the filing is what Blackrock would be able to do in the event of a Bitcoin hard fork. This is explosive beyond belief. Bitcoin has already been through hard forks in its history, and thus far the decentralised nature of Bitcoin has always won through, and forks of the original network have not been successful.</p>
<p>What Blackrock is contemplating in the event of a hard fork is that it would get to choose which fork to go with, thereby deciding the future of Bitcoin. And given its love for the ESG narrative, what if Blackrock itself or one of its &lsquo;associates&rsquo; proposed a PoS fork, and then all the institutions with backing of regulators and governments went with this fork and left the original PoW fork in its wake?</p>
Gold and silver were controlled 
<p>Government and institutions were able to use subterfuge to squash the price of gold and silver over many decades so that they would not detract from the power of the dollar. Big banks used massive short selling whenever the prices took off, and were able to build huge positions in the metals, especially J P Morgan.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is very similar to gold and silver in that it is sound money, meaning that it can&rsquo;t be debased by governments in order to backstop banks or pay for wars. Look for the Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF to be approved by an anti-Bitcoin SEC, and then watch what happens very closely.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Blackrock&rsquo;s recent spot ETF application many Bitcoincoiners are elated. However, should they be worried about this particular move by the $10 trillion asset manager?</p>

<p>&ldquo;I have not heard from any one client looking to buy a cryptocurrency at this time. Right now I can tell you that Worldwide, I have not heard from one client that said I need to be in this.</p>

<p>Larry Fink.</p>
<p>The Blackrock CEO did go on to say back in 2018 that his company would look back into crypto when it became more &ldquo;legitimised&rdquo;. Nearly 5 years later Blackrock is doing exactly that - but with crypto being singled out for extremely rough treatment from the SEC it could hardly be said that crypto has reached the legitimacy stage.</p>
<p>When such a massive and powerful institutional entity as Blackrock files an application for a Bitcoin ETF, when so many have failed, it might be guessed that there will have been some quiet conversations behind the scenes, and that some plan could be in place to exert control over the premier crypto asset.</p>
The Blackrock ESG commitment
<p>Larry Fink has said that he and his company are committed to pushing its ESG agenda.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;You have to force behaviours, and at Blackrock we are forcing behaviours&rdquo;</p>

<p>With Fink serving as a Trustee on the board of Klaus Schwab&rsquo;s World Economic Forum, you can be sure that this application for a Bitcoin Spot ETF will somehow play along with the ESG narrative.&nbsp;</p>
How Blackrock could potentially take control
<p>An extremely thought-provoking tweet by @anilsaidso posits how Blackrock could in one fail swoop take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A hidden gem in the BlackRock ETF filing.#GetForked https://t.co/tER6xxZPui pic.twitter.com/Qdt8BZ2OEZ</p>
&mdash; Anil  (@anilsaidso) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Hidden within the filing is what Blackrock would be able to do in the event of a Bitcoin hard fork. This is explosive beyond belief. Bitcoin has already been through hard forks in its history, and thus far the decentralised nature of Bitcoin has always won through, and forks of the original network have not been successful.</p>
<p>What Blackrock is contemplating in the event of a hard fork is that it would get to choose which fork to go with, thereby deciding the future of Bitcoin. And given its love for the ESG narrative, what if Blackrock itself or one of its &lsquo;associates&rsquo; proposed a PoS fork, and then all the institutions with backing of regulators and governments went with this fork and left the original PoW fork in its wake?</p>
Gold and silver were controlled 
<p>Government and institutions were able to use subterfuge to squash the price of gold and silver over many decades so that they would not detract from the power of the dollar. Big banks used massive short selling whenever the prices took off, and were able to build huge positions in the metals, especially J P Morgan.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is very similar to gold and silver in that it is sound money, meaning that it can&rsquo;t be debased by governments in order to backstop banks or pay for wars. Look for the Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF to be approved by an anti-Bitcoin SEC, and then watch what happens very closely.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wyre To Shut Down As Crypto Winter Claims Another Casualty]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wyre-to-shut-down-as-crypto-winter-claims-another-casualty</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wyre-to-shut-down-as-crypto-winter-claims-another-casualty</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations. It also noted that interested parties could begin inquiries about purchasing the firm&rsquo;s assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm cited challenges arising from the prolonged bear market and not due to the regulatory conditions prevailing in the US markets.&nbsp;</p>
Bear Market Claims Another Victim&nbsp;
<p>Wyre announced its decision to shutter operations in a tweet on Friday. The decision comes a few months after Bolt Financial canceled its planned $1.5 billion purchase of the crypto payments firm. Since the cancellation of the purchase, the digital asset markets have seen a number of high-profile bankruptcies, such as FTX, along with lawsuits against prominent exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, from The United States Securities and Exchange Commission. The company also stressed that the decision was not due to any direction from regulatory agencies.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After nearly a decade, Wyre is winding down. Due to market conditions, we made this decision to protect the best interest of our key stakeholders and customers. This decision is not due to any regulatory agency direction. Wyre continues to secure customer assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Wyre also stated that customers have until Friday, 14th July 2023, to withdraw their assets via the Wyre dashboard. If customers miss this date, Wyre has laid down a separate process to enable the recovery of assets left on the platform. According to Wyre&rsquo;s blog post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wyre continues to secure customer assets. If you have assets on the Wyre platform, you can continue to withdraw them via Wyre&rsquo;s dashboard until Friday, 14th July. After then, we will have a separate process to recover assets remaining on the platform. We will post details on the process on our website and blog.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Wyre team also seemed to suggest that the company&rsquo;s assets were up for sale and that interested parties could inquire about purchasing the firm or its assets.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you&rsquo;re interested in acquiring Wyre&rsquo;s or its subsidiaries&rsquo; assets, please reach out to 88 Partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Wyre&rsquo;s Troubled Year&nbsp;
<p>Wyre has been in the doldrums since Bolt Financial decided to cancel its planned purchase of the company for $1.5 billion in September 2022. A few months after the failed acquisition, more trouble began for the company as its fiat-to-crypto on-ramp solution provider Juno urged users to withdraw their crypto assets from the Juno platform and self custody them. Given the uncertainty surrounding its custodial partner, Wyre, Juno stated that such a step was necessary.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Juno as a platform doesn&rsquo;t custody crypto assets &amp; relies on our crypto partner for these services. Due to uncertainty with our crypto partner, we have taken preemptive action in the interest of our customers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The very next day, MetaMask also announced that it was ending support of the Wyre platform, citing several reports that the company was planning to shut down. MetaMask announced the news on its official Twitter handle, asking users not to use the Wyre service on the mobile aggregator.&nbsp;</p>
False Dawn&nbsp;
<p>A few days after MetaMask shuttered support for Wyre, the company announced the imposition of a 90% withdrawal limit for all its users. However, this limit was quickly removed following an announcement that Wyre had secured funding from an unnamed strategic partner. However, despite securing funding, Wyre still let go of 75 employees in January 2023. The announcement to mark the firm shutting down operations marks the end of Wyre after the company had explored several strategic options in a bid to stay afloat. The company had stated in January,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue, and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

A Growing List Of Bear Market Casualties&nbsp;
<p>Wyre is the latest in a growing list of crypto companies and blockchain firms that have buckled under the pressure of an unending bear market. Just in May alone, several firms, including Lightning Network payments platform BottlePay, NFT platform Terressa, crypto exchange HotBit, and Digital Currency Group&rsquo;s institutional trading platform TradeBlock, all shuttered operations thanks to the prolonged crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EmpireDAO also ended its tenancy at 190 Bowery in New York, giving further evidence of a market downturn. The crypto-exclusive co-working space was founded by Mike Fraietta, with its office building often touted as the WeWork of Web3. Fraietta stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tried every which way to get new sponsors, partnerships, and even crowdfunding. But we needed more help to sustain at 190 Bowery.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations. It also noted that interested parties could begin inquiries about purchasing the firm&rsquo;s assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm cited challenges arising from the prolonged bear market and not due to the regulatory conditions prevailing in the US markets.&nbsp;</p>
Bear Market Claims Another Victim&nbsp;
<p>Wyre announced its decision to shutter operations in a tweet on Friday. The decision comes a few months after Bolt Financial canceled its planned $1.5 billion purchase of the crypto payments firm. Since the cancellation of the purchase, the digital asset markets have seen a number of high-profile bankruptcies, such as FTX, along with lawsuits against prominent exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, from The United States Securities and Exchange Commission. The company also stressed that the decision was not due to any direction from regulatory agencies.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After nearly a decade, Wyre is winding down. Due to market conditions, we made this decision to protect the best interest of our key stakeholders and customers. This decision is not due to any regulatory agency direction. Wyre continues to secure customer assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Wyre also stated that customers have until Friday, 14th July 2023, to withdraw their assets via the Wyre dashboard. If customers miss this date, Wyre has laid down a separate process to enable the recovery of assets left on the platform. According to Wyre&rsquo;s blog post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wyre continues to secure customer assets. If you have assets on the Wyre platform, you can continue to withdraw them via Wyre&rsquo;s dashboard until Friday, 14th July. After then, we will have a separate process to recover assets remaining on the platform. We will post details on the process on our website and blog.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Wyre team also seemed to suggest that the company&rsquo;s assets were up for sale and that interested parties could inquire about purchasing the firm or its assets.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you&rsquo;re interested in acquiring Wyre&rsquo;s or its subsidiaries&rsquo; assets, please reach out to 88 Partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Wyre&rsquo;s Troubled Year&nbsp;
<p>Wyre has been in the doldrums since Bolt Financial decided to cancel its planned purchase of the company for $1.5 billion in September 2022. A few months after the failed acquisition, more trouble began for the company as its fiat-to-crypto on-ramp solution provider Juno urged users to withdraw their crypto assets from the Juno platform and self custody them. Given the uncertainty surrounding its custodial partner, Wyre, Juno stated that such a step was necessary.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Juno as a platform doesn&rsquo;t custody crypto assets &amp; relies on our crypto partner for these services. Due to uncertainty with our crypto partner, we have taken preemptive action in the interest of our customers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The very next day, MetaMask also announced that it was ending support of the Wyre platform, citing several reports that the company was planning to shut down. MetaMask announced the news on its official Twitter handle, asking users not to use the Wyre service on the mobile aggregator.&nbsp;</p>
False Dawn&nbsp;
<p>A few days after MetaMask shuttered support for Wyre, the company announced the imposition of a 90% withdrawal limit for all its users. However, this limit was quickly removed following an announcement that Wyre had secured funding from an unnamed strategic partner. However, despite securing funding, Wyre still let go of 75 employees in January 2023. The announcement to mark the firm shutting down operations marks the end of Wyre after the company had explored several strategic options in a bid to stay afloat. The company had stated in January,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue, and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

A Growing List Of Bear Market Casualties&nbsp;
<p>Wyre is the latest in a growing list of crypto companies and blockchain firms that have buckled under the pressure of an unending bear market. Just in May alone, several firms, including Lightning Network payments platform BottlePay, NFT platform Terressa, crypto exchange HotBit, and Digital Currency Group&rsquo;s institutional trading platform TradeBlock, all shuttered operations thanks to the prolonged crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EmpireDAO also ended its tenancy at 190 Bowery in New York, giving further evidence of a market downturn. The crypto-exclusive co-working space was founded by Mike Fraietta, with its office building often touted as the WeWork of Web3. Fraietta stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tried every which way to get new sponsors, partnerships, and even crowdfunding. But we needed more help to sustain at 190 Bowery.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Labs and Seoul Metropolitan Government Poised to Drive Blockchain Innovation at Seoul Web 3 Festival]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-and-seoul-metropolitan-government-poised-to-drive-blockchain-innovation-at-seoul-web-3-festival</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:50:58 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-and-seoul-metropolitan-government-poised-to-drive-blockchain-innovation-at-seoul-web-3-festival</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading Web3 venture fund LBank Labs is excited to announce its partnership with the prestigious Seoul Web 3.0 Festival, hosted by the Seoul Metropolitan Government, the Seoul Design Foundation and Baobab Partners.</p><p>The Seoul Web 3.0 Festival serves as a pivotal platform for industry leaders, innovators, and policymakers to explore the revolutionary potential of Web 3.0 and how the technology can be used for public services. LBank Labs is proud to contribute to this vital conversation by being the main partner of the festival and showcasing the cutting-edge projects it supports.</p><p>The festival will take place from July 31 to August 2 at the iconic Dongdaemun Design Plaza, renowned for its neofuturistic architecture. During the three-day event, representatives of mainstream blockchain projects in South Korea will be invited to discuss hot topics such as DeFi, NFTs, and Metaverse with the Seoul Municipal Government. The hosting of the Seoul Web3 Festival marks a new stage in the Korean blockchain ecosystem.</p><p>The event boasts an impressive lineup of attendees, including public figures such as Seoul Mayor Oh Se-hoon and prominent Korean policymakers. LBank Labs eagerly anticipates the opportunity to further engage with these esteemed guests, exchange ideas, and collaborate on future-focused initiatives that promote the widespread adoption of blockchain technology.</p><p>As the main sponsor and partner, LBank Labs will host an interactive party where visitors can engage with experts, explore innovative solutions, and learn more about the transformative power of blockchain technology. Additionally, LBank Labs will deliver insightful presentations and contribute to panel discussions, sharing valuable expertise and insights into the potential of Web 3.0.</p><p>LBank Labs' involvement at the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival underscores its commitment to fostering innovation and driving the adoption of blockchain technology. By partnering with the Seoul Metropolitan Government, LBank Labs aims to contribute to the growth of the blockchain ecosystem in South Korea and beyond.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading Web3 venture fund LBank Labs is excited to announce its partnership with the prestigious Seoul Web 3.0 Festival, hosted by the Seoul Metropolitan Government, the Seoul Design Foundation and Baobab Partners.</p><p>The Seoul Web 3.0 Festival serves as a pivotal platform for industry leaders, innovators, and policymakers to explore the revolutionary potential of Web 3.0 and how the technology can be used for public services. LBank Labs is proud to contribute to this vital conversation by being the main partner of the festival and showcasing the cutting-edge projects it supports.</p><p>The festival will take place from July 31 to August 2 at the iconic Dongdaemun Design Plaza, renowned for its neofuturistic architecture. During the three-day event, representatives of mainstream blockchain projects in South Korea will be invited to discuss hot topics such as DeFi, NFTs, and Metaverse with the Seoul Municipal Government. The hosting of the Seoul Web3 Festival marks a new stage in the Korean blockchain ecosystem.</p><p>The event boasts an impressive lineup of attendees, including public figures such as Seoul Mayor Oh Se-hoon and prominent Korean policymakers. LBank Labs eagerly anticipates the opportunity to further engage with these esteemed guests, exchange ideas, and collaborate on future-focused initiatives that promote the widespread adoption of blockchain technology.</p><p>As the main sponsor and partner, LBank Labs will host an interactive party where visitors can engage with experts, explore innovative solutions, and learn more about the transformative power of blockchain technology. Additionally, LBank Labs will deliver insightful presentations and contribute to panel discussions, sharing valuable expertise and insights into the potential of Web 3.0.</p><p>LBank Labs' involvement at the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival underscores its commitment to fostering innovation and driving the adoption of blockchain technology. By partnering with the Seoul Metropolitan Government, LBank Labs aims to contribute to the growth of the blockchain ecosystem in South Korea and beyond.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  25604 Selling Pressure - 17 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25604-selling-pressure-17-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25604-selling-pressure-17-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25604 Selling Pressure:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered selling pressure early in the Asian session as the pair tumbled to the 25143.24 area after technical selling pressure emerged around the 25604.52 level, a previous downside price objective linked to selling pressure in mid-May.&nbsp; &nbsp;The pair&rsquo;s depreciation slowed when BTC/USD tested the 61.8% retracement of the recent short-term appreciating range from 24750 to 25749.99.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 25915.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25347.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25604 Selling Pressure:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered selling pressure early in the Asian session as the pair tumbled to the 25143.24 area after technical selling pressure emerged around the 25604.52 level, a previous downside price objective linked to selling pressure in mid-May.&nbsp; &nbsp;The pair&rsquo;s depreciation slowed when BTC/USD tested the 61.8% retracement of the recent short-term appreciating range from 24750 to 25749.99.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 25915.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25347.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKX and McLaren Racing Host Panel on Technology in Sports and Film at Tribeca Festival]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-and-mclaren-racing-host-panel-on-technology-in-sports-and-film-at-tribeca-festival</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-and-mclaren-racing-host-panel-on-technology-in-sports-and-film-at-tribeca-festival</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York City, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>
<ul>
<li>Panelists included OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay</li>
</ul>
<p>From left to right: Director, producer, and screenwriter Stephen Kay; McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown; Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain; OKX CMO Haider Rafique; and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris discuss the power of technology in sports, film and crypto</p>
<p>OKX, a leading Web3 technology company, yesterday hosted a panel discussion with McLaren Racing at the Tribeca Festival titled, "Need for Speed: How Technology Powers Change in Sports, Movies, and Crypto," featuring OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris, and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay.</p>
<p>The panel, moderated by Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain, was held at the Tribeca Screening Room and focused on how technology has transformed various industries, including sports, entertainment, cryptocurrency and finance. During the discussion, the panelists emphasized the impact of innovation on speed, performance and efficiency across the different sectors.</p>
OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: &ldquo;We've achieved a lot together in just one year. The McLaren F1 team has a huge appetite to lean into Web3 and make its heritage more discoverable for younger generations, and we want to play a big role in making that a reality for them. There are incredible stories here that can motivate the next generation of drivers and fans to get involved with the sport and, in particular, celebrate McLaren's achievements on and off track. Our goal is to help McLaren transcend into this future and share what we are cooking together on our panel".
McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown said: &ldquo;This panel was a great opportunity to share the stage with our Primary Partner OKX, and discuss how technology can power change in our respective industries. In Formula 1, we constantly look to innovate and leverage technology to maximize our fan engagement opportunities. Partners like OKX can support us in these commitments, exploring how they can guide our Web3 strategy and make our sport ever-more exciting and accessible for the fans.&rdquo;
<p>OKX CMO Haider Rafique (left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (right)</p>
<p>McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown (in orange, left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (in orange, right) with OKX CMO Haider Rafique</p>
<p>Tribeca Festival 2023 is OKX&rsquo;s second consecutive year as the presenting sponsor. The company's multi-year partnership with Tribeca Festival aims to unlock new Web3 opportunities for creators, fans and talent. OKX also introduced the first-ever Tribeca Festival NFT pass for 2023 in January.</p>
<p>In May of last year, OKX and McLaren Racing announced a multi-year partnership that would make OKX a Primary Partner of the McLaren Formula 1 Team and McLaren Shadow esports team. Through this partnership, OKX supports the team&rsquo;s global fan experience, providing exciting opportunities and product innovations that bring fans closer to the action. OKX branding is featured on the McLaren cars, the helmets of McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, as well as the McLaren F1 and McLaren Shadow team kits.</p>
About OKX
<p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace and DEX.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX Web3, download our app or visit: okx.com/web3</p>
About McLaren Racing
<p>McLaren Racing was founded by racing driver Bruce McLaren 60 years ago in 1963. The team entered its first Formula 1 race in 1966. McLaren has since won 20 Formula 1 world championships, 183 Formula 1 grands prix, the Indianapolis 500 three times, and the Le Mans 24 Hours at its first attempt.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing competes across five racing series. In 2023, the team will compete in the FIA Formula 1 World Championship with McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, the NTT INDYCAR SERIES with Arrow McLaren drivers Pato O&rsquo;Ward, Felix Rosenqvist and Alexander Rossi, the ABB FIA Formula E World Championship with NEOM McLaren Formula E Team drivers Ren&eacute; Rast and Jake Hughes, and the Extreme E Championship with NEOM McLaren Extreme E Team drivers Emma Gilmour and Tanner Foust. The team also competes in the F1 Esports Pro Championship as McLaren Shadow, having won the 2022 Constructors&rsquo; and Drivers&rsquo; Championships.</p>
<p>McLaren is a champion for sustainability in the sport and a signatory to the UN Sports for Climate Action Commitment. It is committed to achieving net zero by 2040 and fostering a diverse and inclusive culture in the motorsport industry.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing &ndash; Official Website</p>
About the Tribeca Festival
<p>The Tribeca Festival, presented by OKX, brings artists and diverse audiences together to celebrate storytelling in all its forms, including film, TV, immersive, games, audio storytelling, music, and online work. With strong roots in independent film, Tribeca is a platform for creative expression and immersive entertainment. Tribeca champions emerging and established voices; discovers award-winning filmmakers and creators; curates innovative experiences; and introduces new technology and ideas through premieres, exhibitions, talks, and live performances.</p>
<p>The Festival was founded by Robert De Niro, Jane Rosenthal, and Craig Hatkoff in 2001 to spur the economic and cultural revitalization of lower Manhattan following the attacks on the World Trade Center. Tribeca will celebrate its 22nd year from June 7&ndash;18, 2023.</p>
<p>In 2019, James Murdoch&rsquo;s Lupa Systems, a private investment company with locations in New York and Mumbai, bought a majority stake in Tribeca Enterprises, bringing together Rosenthal, De Niro, and Murdoch to grow the enterprise.</p>
Disclaimer
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your risk tolerance and financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
Contact
<p>Pressmedia@okx.com</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York City, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>
<ul>
<li>Panelists included OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay</li>
</ul>
<p>From left to right: Director, producer, and screenwriter Stephen Kay; McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown; Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain; OKX CMO Haider Rafique; and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris discuss the power of technology in sports, film and crypto</p>
<p>OKX, a leading Web3 technology company, yesterday hosted a panel discussion with McLaren Racing at the Tribeca Festival titled, "Need for Speed: How Technology Powers Change in Sports, Movies, and Crypto," featuring OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris, and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay.</p>
<p>The panel, moderated by Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain, was held at the Tribeca Screening Room and focused on how technology has transformed various industries, including sports, entertainment, cryptocurrency and finance. During the discussion, the panelists emphasized the impact of innovation on speed, performance and efficiency across the different sectors.</p>
OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: &ldquo;We've achieved a lot together in just one year. The McLaren F1 team has a huge appetite to lean into Web3 and make its heritage more discoverable for younger generations, and we want to play a big role in making that a reality for them. There are incredible stories here that can motivate the next generation of drivers and fans to get involved with the sport and, in particular, celebrate McLaren's achievements on and off track. Our goal is to help McLaren transcend into this future and share what we are cooking together on our panel".
McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown said: &ldquo;This panel was a great opportunity to share the stage with our Primary Partner OKX, and discuss how technology can power change in our respective industries. In Formula 1, we constantly look to innovate and leverage technology to maximize our fan engagement opportunities. Partners like OKX can support us in these commitments, exploring how they can guide our Web3 strategy and make our sport ever-more exciting and accessible for the fans.&rdquo;
<p>OKX CMO Haider Rafique (left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (right)</p>
<p>McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown (in orange, left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (in orange, right) with OKX CMO Haider Rafique</p>
<p>Tribeca Festival 2023 is OKX&rsquo;s second consecutive year as the presenting sponsor. The company's multi-year partnership with Tribeca Festival aims to unlock new Web3 opportunities for creators, fans and talent. OKX also introduced the first-ever Tribeca Festival NFT pass for 2023 in January.</p>
<p>In May of last year, OKX and McLaren Racing announced a multi-year partnership that would make OKX a Primary Partner of the McLaren Formula 1 Team and McLaren Shadow esports team. Through this partnership, OKX supports the team&rsquo;s global fan experience, providing exciting opportunities and product innovations that bring fans closer to the action. OKX branding is featured on the McLaren cars, the helmets of McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, as well as the McLaren F1 and McLaren Shadow team kits.</p>
About OKX
<p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace and DEX.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX Web3, download our app or visit: okx.com/web3</p>
About McLaren Racing
<p>McLaren Racing was founded by racing driver Bruce McLaren 60 years ago in 1963. The team entered its first Formula 1 race in 1966. McLaren has since won 20 Formula 1 world championships, 183 Formula 1 grands prix, the Indianapolis 500 three times, and the Le Mans 24 Hours at its first attempt.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing competes across five racing series. In 2023, the team will compete in the FIA Formula 1 World Championship with McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, the NTT INDYCAR SERIES with Arrow McLaren drivers Pato O&rsquo;Ward, Felix Rosenqvist and Alexander Rossi, the ABB FIA Formula E World Championship with NEOM McLaren Formula E Team drivers Ren&eacute; Rast and Jake Hughes, and the Extreme E Championship with NEOM McLaren Extreme E Team drivers Emma Gilmour and Tanner Foust. The team also competes in the F1 Esports Pro Championship as McLaren Shadow, having won the 2022 Constructors&rsquo; and Drivers&rsquo; Championships.</p>
<p>McLaren is a champion for sustainability in the sport and a signatory to the UN Sports for Climate Action Commitment. It is committed to achieving net zero by 2040 and fostering a diverse and inclusive culture in the motorsport industry.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing &ndash; Official Website</p>
About the Tribeca Festival
<p>The Tribeca Festival, presented by OKX, brings artists and diverse audiences together to celebrate storytelling in all its forms, including film, TV, immersive, games, audio storytelling, music, and online work. With strong roots in independent film, Tribeca is a platform for creative expression and immersive entertainment. Tribeca champions emerging and established voices; discovers award-winning filmmakers and creators; curates innovative experiences; and introduces new technology and ideas through premieres, exhibitions, talks, and live performances.</p>
<p>The Festival was founded by Robert De Niro, Jane Rosenthal, and Craig Hatkoff in 2001 to spur the economic and cultural revitalization of lower Manhattan following the attacks on the World Trade Center. Tribeca will celebrate its 22nd year from June 7&ndash;18, 2023.</p>
<p>In 2019, James Murdoch&rsquo;s Lupa Systems, a private investment company with locations in New York and Mumbai, bought a majority stake in Tribeca Enterprises, bringing together Rosenthal, De Niro, and Murdoch to grow the enterprise.</p>
Disclaimer
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your risk tolerance and financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
Contact
<p>Pressmedia@okx.com</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Traders ask ChatGPT for price prediction: Binance coin, Bitcoin, Tradecurve]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-traders-ask-chatgpt-for-price-prediction-binance-coin-bitcoin-tradecurve</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-traders-ask-chatgpt-for-price-prediction-binance-coin-bitcoin-tradecurve</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of Artificial Intelligence, companies are consistently pushing for new technological advancements and investing millions towards creating the best possible chatbot that users can utilize to get the information they need with ease, and one of the most recent use cases has been making price predictions for the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency traders are now asking ChatGPT, the most popular AI-driven chatbot globally, to tell them everything they need to know surrounding the future value of Binance coin, Tradecurve, and Bitcoin during the current bear market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Asking ChatGPT About Binance coin
<p>According to ChatGPT, the price of Binance coin at the end of 2023 is difficult to predict with 100% accuracy; however, based on the current market conditions and historical price data, the AI is able to make some educated guesses as to how far it can climb.</p>
<p>On June 9, 2023, Binance coin traded at $259.21 per coin. This represents a lower point of value than the one Binance coin had at the start of the month, but there are factors that could impact its price in the future, including Binance's continued push towards creating new features and products, market demand, and overall regulatory compliance of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Binance coin at the end of 2023, according to some piece predictions made for the Binance coin, places it at a value of $465.85.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
The Answers ChatGPT Gave for Bitcoin
<p>The price of Bitcoin as of June 9, 2023, is at $26,607.05. Analysts went to ChatGPT to get accurate predictions about the future of Bitcoin. However, the AI did note that nothing can be predicted with 100% certainty.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The key factors that can affect the value of Bitcoin, according to ChatGPT, include the overall momentum of the market, mainstream adoption of the Bitcoin cryptocurrency, and the development of new, innovative features on top of the network or the creation of Layer-2 scaling solutions for it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin at the end of 2023 could see an increase, however, and based on estimates, BTC is expected to reach $65,000 by the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
What ChatGPT Thinks about The Performance of Tradecurve
<p>Investors and traders are also curious about new projects, and Tradecurve has stood out due to its popularity, appeal, and the freedom it provides investors as it does not require KYC checks whilst also having the lowest fees in the industry.</p>
<p>Tradecurve is a hybrid exchange that combines the best elements of CEXs and DEXs to provide a truly unique, decentralized experience that will enable anyone on a global scale access to markets that are otherwise unavailable to them due to banking restrictions or regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Each user of Tradecurve can effectively and effortlessly trade cryptocurrencies, as well as any other derivative, from one account while also maintaining privacy through the platform's DeFi capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is the utility token behind the platform, and it is currently undergoing Stage 3 of its presale, where it is offered at $0.015.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When asked about the future of the cryptocurrency, ChatGPT noted how it could climb to 100x at launch, bringing it to $1.5 in value, because of the increased demand for such a solution after heightened regulation of CEXs, and because of the fast sales of the TCRV tokens, where the team has already sold millions of tokens and can generate $20 million before the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of Artificial Intelligence, companies are consistently pushing for new technological advancements and investing millions towards creating the best possible chatbot that users can utilize to get the information they need with ease, and one of the most recent use cases has been making price predictions for the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency traders are now asking ChatGPT, the most popular AI-driven chatbot globally, to tell them everything they need to know surrounding the future value of Binance coin, Tradecurve, and Bitcoin during the current bear market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Asking ChatGPT About Binance coin
<p>According to ChatGPT, the price of Binance coin at the end of 2023 is difficult to predict with 100% accuracy; however, based on the current market conditions and historical price data, the AI is able to make some educated guesses as to how far it can climb.</p>
<p>On June 9, 2023, Binance coin traded at $259.21 per coin. This represents a lower point of value than the one Binance coin had at the start of the month, but there are factors that could impact its price in the future, including Binance's continued push towards creating new features and products, market demand, and overall regulatory compliance of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Binance coin at the end of 2023, according to some piece predictions made for the Binance coin, places it at a value of $465.85.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
The Answers ChatGPT Gave for Bitcoin
<p>The price of Bitcoin as of June 9, 2023, is at $26,607.05. Analysts went to ChatGPT to get accurate predictions about the future of Bitcoin. However, the AI did note that nothing can be predicted with 100% certainty.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The key factors that can affect the value of Bitcoin, according to ChatGPT, include the overall momentum of the market, mainstream adoption of the Bitcoin cryptocurrency, and the development of new, innovative features on top of the network or the creation of Layer-2 scaling solutions for it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin at the end of 2023 could see an increase, however, and based on estimates, BTC is expected to reach $65,000 by the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
What ChatGPT Thinks about The Performance of Tradecurve
<p>Investors and traders are also curious about new projects, and Tradecurve has stood out due to its popularity, appeal, and the freedom it provides investors as it does not require KYC checks whilst also having the lowest fees in the industry.</p>
<p>Tradecurve is a hybrid exchange that combines the best elements of CEXs and DEXs to provide a truly unique, decentralized experience that will enable anyone on a global scale access to markets that are otherwise unavailable to them due to banking restrictions or regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Each user of Tradecurve can effectively and effortlessly trade cryptocurrencies, as well as any other derivative, from one account while also maintaining privacy through the platform's DeFi capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is the utility token behind the platform, and it is currently undergoing Stage 3 of its presale, where it is offered at $0.015.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When asked about the future of the cryptocurrency, ChatGPT noted how it could climb to 100x at launch, bringing it to $1.5 in value, because of the increased demand for such a solution after heightened regulation of CEXs, and because of the fast sales of the TCRV tokens, where the team has already sold millions of tokens and can generate $20 million before the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will 10x Says Michael Saylor, This New Hybrid Exchange Plans to Overtake Binance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-will-10x-says-michael-saylor-this-new-hybrid-exchange-plans-to-overtake-binance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-will-10x-says-michael-saylor-this-new-hybrid-exchange-plans-to-overtake-binance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The popular Bitcoin investor and permabull, Michael Saylor, has released a new prediction for Bitcoin. Saylor has said that under the right conditions, the price of Bitcoin will jump by 10x to set a new trading high at $250,000. In other news, Tradecurve, a new hybrid exchange has outlined plans to overtake Binance as the number one crypto exchange, and some experts believe it is possible.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Michael Saylor has predicted a 10x price jump for Bitcoin, predicting the crypto will trade as high as $250,000 in the next bull run.</li>
<li>According to Saylor, regulatory clarity will be the catalyst for the next bull run.</li>
<li>While Binance suffers due to regulatory clarity, a new hybrid exchange has tapped into markets that could see it overtake the number one crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
Michael Saylor Predicts 10x Price Jump for Bitcoin (BTC)
<p>In an interview with Bloomberg, Michael Saylor, the co-founder of Microstrategy, an enterprise business intelligence provider, predicted that the price of Bitcoin could jump by 10x. In explaining the reasoning for his prediction, Saylor said regulatory clarity in the U.S. will drive the next Bitcoin rally.</p>
<p>The presence of regulatory clarity will encourage venture capitalists that have avoided cryptocurrencies to jump into the industry. He adds that the recent crackdown on many top crypto exchanges by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) would lay the groundwork for the next major Bitcoin bull run.</p>
<p>Congress is already working on a unified crypto regulatory framework and assigning crypto-specific roles to SEC and CFTC, meaning the next Bitcoin bull run couldn&rsquo;t be far away. If Saylor&rsquo;s prediction holds true, we would witness Bitcoin set a new all-time high at $250,000, beating its previous ATH at $68,789.</p>
<p></p>
Binance Has a New Challenger, And the Hybrid Exchange Could Overtake It
<p>On the journey to regulatory clarity for the cryptocurrency industry, the leading crypto exchange, Binance, has been caught in the web of the SEC. The crackdown on centralized exchanges has opened a window for the newer hybrid exchanges, which many crypto experts have called the future of crypto trading because they combine the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>One hybrid exchange, Tradecurve, has set out to challenge the dominance of Binance by incorporating into its platform trading features that Binance lack, including more trading options (forex and derivatives), negative balance protection, self-management of private keys, low latency ultra-fast order execution, and algorithmic trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By looking to offer wider assets for trading and features that will make for a seamless trading experience, Tradecurve plans to topple Binance as the number one crypto trading platform. With the current regulatory crackdown on Binance, many crypto analysts believe Tradecurve has a chance to steal market share from Binance to reduce its dominance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is on track to enact its plan, currently in the fourth presale phase expecting to raise $20 million to launch its platform. The project has enjoyed massive support from investors currently buying its native token, TCRV, at $0.018 per token.</p>
<p>Visit the links below to get more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The popular Bitcoin investor and permabull, Michael Saylor, has released a new prediction for Bitcoin. Saylor has said that under the right conditions, the price of Bitcoin will jump by 10x to set a new trading high at $250,000. In other news, Tradecurve, a new hybrid exchange has outlined plans to overtake Binance as the number one crypto exchange, and some experts believe it is possible.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Michael Saylor has predicted a 10x price jump for Bitcoin, predicting the crypto will trade as high as $250,000 in the next bull run.</li>
<li>According to Saylor, regulatory clarity will be the catalyst for the next bull run.</li>
<li>While Binance suffers due to regulatory clarity, a new hybrid exchange has tapped into markets that could see it overtake the number one crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
Michael Saylor Predicts 10x Price Jump for Bitcoin (BTC)
<p>In an interview with Bloomberg, Michael Saylor, the co-founder of Microstrategy, an enterprise business intelligence provider, predicted that the price of Bitcoin could jump by 10x. In explaining the reasoning for his prediction, Saylor said regulatory clarity in the U.S. will drive the next Bitcoin rally.</p>
<p>The presence of regulatory clarity will encourage venture capitalists that have avoided cryptocurrencies to jump into the industry. He adds that the recent crackdown on many top crypto exchanges by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) would lay the groundwork for the next major Bitcoin bull run.</p>
<p>Congress is already working on a unified crypto regulatory framework and assigning crypto-specific roles to SEC and CFTC, meaning the next Bitcoin bull run couldn&rsquo;t be far away. If Saylor&rsquo;s prediction holds true, we would witness Bitcoin set a new all-time high at $250,000, beating its previous ATH at $68,789.</p>
<p></p>
Binance Has a New Challenger, And the Hybrid Exchange Could Overtake It
<p>On the journey to regulatory clarity for the cryptocurrency industry, the leading crypto exchange, Binance, has been caught in the web of the SEC. The crackdown on centralized exchanges has opened a window for the newer hybrid exchanges, which many crypto experts have called the future of crypto trading because they combine the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>One hybrid exchange, Tradecurve, has set out to challenge the dominance of Binance by incorporating into its platform trading features that Binance lack, including more trading options (forex and derivatives), negative balance protection, self-management of private keys, low latency ultra-fast order execution, and algorithmic trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By looking to offer wider assets for trading and features that will make for a seamless trading experience, Tradecurve plans to topple Binance as the number one crypto trading platform. With the current regulatory crackdown on Binance, many crypto analysts believe Tradecurve has a chance to steal market share from Binance to reduce its dominance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is on track to enact its plan, currently in the fourth presale phase expecting to raise $20 million to launch its platform. The project has enjoyed massive support from investors currently buying its native token, TCRV, at $0.018 per token.</p>
<p>Visit the links below to get more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
