<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 May – Bitcoin SV, Lido DAO, SUI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-may-bitcoin-sv-lido-dao-sui.htm</link><description>In a surprising turn of events, Bitcoin experienced a significant drop earlier today, falling below the $27,000 mark to register an intraday low of $26,833. &lt;br /&gt;
This unexpected downturn occurred in the middle of the day and has countered the upward trend that followed the release of somewhat positive U.S. inflation data. &lt;br /&gt;
Considering the ongoing market volatility in the cryptocurrency market, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-may-bitcoin-sv-lido-dao-sui.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 May – Bitcoin SV, Lido DAO, SUI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>Bsv</category><category>Sponge</category><category>LDO</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>SUI</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bitcoin SV</category><category>Lido Dao</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Web3</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-may-bitcoin-sv-lido-dao-sui.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113592/274879/best-crypto-10-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="370480"/></item><item><title>Grayscale Seeks ETF Expansion Amid Ongoing Legal Battle over Spot Bitcoin Fund</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-seeks-etf-expansion-amid-ongoing-legal-battle-over-spot-bitcoin-fund.htm</link><description>In a sign of dedication to its efforts to launch a spot Bitcoin Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) in the US, Grayscale Investments is trying a new approach. &lt;br /&gt;
The digital asset manager, currently the world’s largest, announced on Wednesday the formation of a new trust, Grayscale Funds Trust. &lt;br /&gt;
The new Delaware statutory trust structure will allow Grayscale to independently manage its 1940 Act products as the firm continues to expand its ETF business, the company said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-seeks-etf-expansion-amid-ongoing-legal-battle-over-spot-bitcoin-fund.htm"&gt;Read More: Grayscale Seeks ETF Expansion Amid Ongoing Legal Battle over Spot Bitcoin Fund&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>GBTC</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-seeks-etf-expansion-amid-ongoing-legal-battle-over-spot-bitcoin-fund.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113593/274881/grayscale.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1361988"/></item><item><title>US House Lawmakers on Both Sides Seemingly Agree on Need for Crypto Legislation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-lawmakers-both-sides-seemingly-agree-need-for-crypto-legislation.htm</link><description>Lawmakers on both sides of the aisle seem to be reaching some sort of agreement on the need for legislation to regulate cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
Rep. French Hill, R-Ark., said his Democratic colleagues have told him they have supported “commonsense legislation for months.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-lawmakers-both-sides-seemingly-agree-need-for-crypto-legislation.htm"&gt;Read More: US House Lawmakers on Both Sides Seemingly Agree on Need for Crypto Legislation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Congress</category><category>Legislation</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-lawmakers-both-sides-seemingly-agree-need-for-crypto-legislation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113591/274878/white-house-ge254881e1-640.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="167122"/></item><item><title>Bitboy Token Prediction: Ben Price To Retrace After 1000% Rise, Whilst AiDoge and $SPONGE Pump</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitboy-token-prediction-ben-price-retrace-after-1000-rise-whilst-aidoge-sponge-pump.htm</link><description>The newly launched governance token, $BEN is a meme coin project designed for BitBboy’s Decentralized Autonomous community, Ben DAO.  &lt;br /&gt;
The token’s performance in the past two days before its public announcement represents prevalent price volatility in the coming days.  &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, the general meme coin frenzy in the crypto space due to the successes of AiDoge and SPONGE contributed to the spike of the BEN token. But its emergences have evoked mixed reactions. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitboy-token-prediction-ben-price-retrace-after-1000-rise-whilst-aidoge-sponge-pump.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitboy Token Prediction: Ben Price To Retrace After 1000% Rise, Whilst AiDoge and $SPONGE Pump&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitboy-token-prediction-ben-price-retrace-after-1000-rise-whilst-aidoge-sponge-pump.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113566/274830/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="256468"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk Meme Tweet Causes Milady NFT Price To Almost Double</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-meme-tweet-causes-milady-nft-price-double.htm</link><description>Twitter head Elon Musk caused a particular non-fungible token to spike on Wednesday after tweeting it out to his almost 140 million followers. &lt;br /&gt;
Musk tweeted a meme of the Milady NFT, which has since swelled in popularity.  &lt;br /&gt;
“There is no meme,” Musk tweeted on the image. “I love you.” &lt;br /&gt;
Milady Maker is a collection of 10,000 profile NFTS, according to marketplace OpenSea. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-meme-tweet-causes-milady-nft-price-double.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk Meme Tweet Causes Milady NFT Price To Almost Double&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>NFT</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-meme-tweet-causes-milady-nft-price-double.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113587/274863/screen-shot-2023-05-10-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1018951"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Inflation Rate Data is Announced – Will BTC Start Moving Up Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-will-btc-start-moving-up-now.htm</link><description>As the US inflation rate data has been released, the crypto community is eagerly awaiting the impact on the Bitcoin market.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the current state of the global economy, investors have turned to Bitcoin as a hedge against inflation.  &lt;br /&gt;
The announcement of the inflation rate is expected to have a significant effect on Bitcoin's price. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-will-btc-start-moving-up-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Inflation Rate Data is Announced – Will BTC Start Moving Up Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-inflation-rate-data-announced-will-btc-start-moving-up-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113579/274859/11-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526482"/></item><item><title>No Meme Token Launches, Pumps Up 700% Almost Instantly After Elon Musk Tweets There is No Meme Milady NFT</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/no-meme-token-launches-pumps-up-700-almost-instantly-after-elon-musk-tweets-there-no-meme-milady-nft.htm</link><description>The meme coin frenzy continues, with a new name suddenly making significant headway. &lt;br /&gt;
No Meme Token ($NOMEME), which was only launched around one hour ago, has already pumped more than 700% on Uniswap. &lt;br /&gt;
The token was launched in the wake of a tweet by Twitter, Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk, who shared a picture of a Milady Maker with the caption “There Is No Meme” and “I Love You”....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/no-meme-token-launches-pumps-up-700-almost-instantly-after-elon-musk-tweets-there-no-meme-milady-nft.htm"&gt;Read More: No Meme Token Launches, Pumps Up 700% Almost Instantly After Elon Musk Tweets There is No Meme Milady NFT&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>No Meme Token</category><category>NOMEME</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Milady Maker</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/no-meme-token-launches-pumps-up-700-almost-instantly-after-elon-musk-tweets-there-no-meme-milady-nft.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113585/274856/nomeme-token.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="194325"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Prices Crash Suddenly, Rumors of US Govt Holdings Being Sold-Off – What’s Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-crash-suddenly-rumors-of-us-govt-holdings-being-sold-off-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Speculation swirled on Wednesday on whether the US government's Bitcoin holdings were being sold off in the thousands. &lt;br /&gt;
In a tweet, Steven or @Dogetoshi, research director at The Block, found transactions labeled as “Gov: DOJ Confiscated funds.”  &lt;br /&gt;
It then seemed to be a user mistake. &lt;br /&gt;
Crypto veteran Adam Cochran echoed that and said that a user had the wallet tagged on their “own local end as Silkroad, so it wasn’t an Arkham alert that went out to traders/bots.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-crash-suddenly-rumors-of-us-govt-holdings-being-sold-off-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Prices Crash Suddenly, Rumors of US Govt Holdings Being Sold-Off – What’s Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Government</category><category>Silk Road</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-crash-suddenly-rumors-of-us-govt-holdings-being-sold-off-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113577/274852/pexels-pixabay-315788.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="206066"/></item><item><title>Bankrupt QuadrigaCX Exchange to Commence 'Interim Distribution' of Funds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-quadrigacx-exchange-commence-interim-distribution-of-funds.htm</link><description>The bankrupt Canadian crypto exchange QuadrigaCX is set to commence an “interim distribution” of funds to creditors, despite only a fraction of the missing funds being recovered. &lt;br /&gt;
“In the coming weeks, the Trustee intends to post a Notice to Affected Users providing details about the manner and procedure for the Interim Distribution and other related information,” a status update from law firm Miller Thomson said on Monday this week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-quadrigacx-exchange-commence-interim-distribution-of-funds.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankrupt QuadrigaCX Exchange to Commence 'Interim Distribution' of Funds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>QuadrigaCX</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-quadrigacx-exchange-commence-interim-distribution-of-funds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113545/274764/funds-distribution.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="215615"/></item><item><title>US Chamber of Commerce Backs Coinbase in Fight for Regulatory Clarity</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-chamber-of-commerce-backs-coinbase-fight-for-regulatory-clarity.htm</link><description>The US Chamber of Commerce backed Coinbase’s request for the US Securities and Exchange Commission to write rules for cryptocurrency in a recent court filing.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Chamber, which is the world’s largest business organization, said no one knows for certain which digital assets are securities under federal law....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-chamber-of-commerce-backs-coinbase-fight-for-regulatory-clarity.htm"&gt;Read More: US Chamber of Commerce Backs Coinbase in Fight for Regulatory Clarity&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Chamber of Commerce</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-chamber-of-commerce-backs-coinbase-fight-for-regulatory-clarity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113570/274846/jurisdiction-gc51c800ac-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120555"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Mike Novogratz's Galaxy Digital Crypto Firm Reports $134 Million Profit in Q1 2023 – Crypto Bull Market Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-crypto-firm-reports-134-million-profit-q1-2023-crypto-bull-market-back.htm</link><description>Crypto bull Mike Novogratz’s firm Galaxy Digital reported a profit of $134 million in the first quarter of this year, missing analysts’ expectations. &lt;br /&gt;
Galaxy’s earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter came in at $0.55, missing an estimate by analysts of $0.76....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-crypto-firm-reports-134-million-profit-q1-2023-crypto-bull-market-back.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Mike Novogratz's Galaxy Digital Crypto Firm Reports $134 Million Profit in Q1 2023 – Crypto Bull Market Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Mike Novogratz</category><category>Galaxy Digital</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mike-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-crypto-firm-reports-134-million-profit-q1-2023-crypto-bull-market-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113569/274837/mike-novogratz.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="60546"/></item><item><title>What the Latest US Inflation Numbers Mean for the Bitcoin (BTC) Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-latest-us-inflation-numbers-mean-for-bitcoin-btc-price.htm</link><description>The latest US Consumer Price Index (CPI) inflation numbers were just released and Bitcoin (BTC), which rallied at the time to hit session highs in the $28,300s, seemed to like it. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the latest CPI report, headline inflation fell to 4.9% YoY in April, its first sub-5.0% reading in over two years. &lt;br /&gt;
That was a tad below the median economist forecast for a 5.0% YoY reading....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-latest-us-inflation-numbers-mean-for-bitcoin-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: What the Latest US Inflation Numbers Mean for the Bitcoin (BTC) Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>CPI</category><category>Inflation</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-latest-us-inflation-numbers-mean-for-bitcoin-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113568/274835/btc-35.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2128274"/></item><item><title>$60 Million in USDT and MASK Token Sent from Crypto Exchange OKX to Alameda Research – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/60-million-usdt-mask-token-sent-from-crypto-exchange-okx-alameda-research-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>In a recent move, one of the leading digital asset exchange platforms, OKX, announced the transfer of substantial funds to Alameda Research.  &lt;br /&gt;
The transfer involves around $60 million worth of USDT (Tether) and MASK tokens. &lt;br /&gt;
Based on the report from a crypto analytics platform, Arkham Intelligence, the transfer from OKX took place on May 9. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/60-million-usdt-mask-token-sent-from-crypto-exchange-okx-alameda-research-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: $60 Million in USDT and MASK Token Sent from Crypto Exchange OKX to Alameda Research – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/60-million-usdt-mask-token-sent-from-crypto-exchange-okx-alameda-research-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113550/274810/ftx.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99818"/></item><item><title>Green Recycle-2-Earn Crypto Project Ecoterra’s Presale on Fire, Nears $3.5 Million as 10% Price Rise Approaches</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-recycle-2-earn-crypto-project-ecoterras-presale-on-fire-nears-35-million-as-10-price-rise-approaches.htm</link><description>Green Recycle-to-earn (R2E) crypto project Ecoterra’s presale is on fire, with sales of $ECOTERRA nearing $3.5 million as investors rush to get in ahead of a 10% price rise. &lt;br /&gt;
With Ecoterra’s presale having only crossed the $3 million mark around five days ago, that means the environmentally friendly Web3 start-up has been raking in around $100,000 per day....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/green-recycle-2-earn-crypto-project-ecoterras-presale-on-fire-nears-35-million-as-10-price-rise-approaches.htm"&gt;Read More: Green Recycle-2-Earn Crypto Project Ecoterra’s Presale on Fire, Nears $3.5 Million as 10% Price Rise Approaches&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-recycle-2-earn-crypto-project-ecoterras-presale-on-fire-nears-35-million-as-10-price-rise-approaches.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113540/274736/unnamed-20.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="798884"/></item><item><title>PayPal's Crypto Holdings Approach $1 Billion, Primarily in Bitcoin and Ether</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypals-crypto-holdings-approach-1-billion-primarily-bitcoin-ether.htm</link><description>PayPal has disclosed that it holds nearly $1 billion in cryptocurrencies on its balance sheet, mainly consisting of BTC and ETH.  &lt;br /&gt;
In its latest quarterly financial performance report, the financial payments giant revealed that it holds $943 million worth of customer assets in bitcoin, ether, bitcoin cash, and litecoin, which marks an increase of $339 million from the end of last year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paypals-crypto-holdings-approach-1-billion-primarily-bitcoin-ether.htm"&gt;Read More: PayPal's Crypto Holdings Approach $1 Billion, Primarily in Bitcoin and Ether&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypals-crypto-holdings-approach-1-billion-primarily-bitcoin-ether.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113546/274771/143208e76a-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="38219"/></item><item><title>Crypto Self-Regulatory Organization Plan Floated in US House Hearing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-self-regulatory-organization-plan-floated-in-us-house-hearing.htm</link><description>US lawmakers drifted the idea of regulating cryptocurrency through a self-regulatory organization putting both the Securities and Exchange Commission and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission in charge. &lt;br /&gt;
Rep. Stephen Lynch, D-Mass., asked former CFTC Chair Timothy Massad what measures would be necessary given talks that regulatory jurisdiction should be given to the CFTC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-self-regulatory-organization-plan-floated-in-us-house-hearing.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Self-Regulatory Organization Plan Floated in US House Hearing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Congress</category><category>Self Regulation</category><category>Self-Regulatory Organization</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-self-regulatory-organization-plan-floated-in-us-house-hearing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113554/274800/united-states-gdfa254efe-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="232372"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as Meme Coin Mania Pushes Gas Fees to 12 Month High – Is ETH Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-mania-pushes-gas-fees-12-month-high-eth-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>Ether (ETH), the cryptocurrency that powers the smart-contract-enabled Ethereum blockchain, was last up a little over 1.0% on Wednesday in the $1,870 area. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency derived a small intra-day boost from US Consumer Price Index inflation data that came in broadly in line with expectations at still-hot levels, but at the same time boosted expectations that the Fed’s tightening cycle has already concluded....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-mania-pushes-gas-fees-12-month-high-eth-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as Meme Coin Mania Pushes Gas Fees to 12 Month High – Is ETH Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-mania-pushes-gas-fees-12-month-high-eth-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113555/274799/eth-6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6975908"/></item><item><title>Meme Coin Top Performer $SPONGE Price to Explode – Lists on MEXC Exchange Thursday, Plus Another CEX Announcement</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-top-performer-sponge-price-explode-mexc-lists-thursday-plus-another-exchange-announcement.htm</link><description>Wednesday May 10th 2023 – Insurgent meme coin $SPONGE lists on MEXC Global tomorrow, plus a listing announcement from one as yet unnamed exchange, in its bid to flip Pepe. &lt;br /&gt;
Seychelles-based MEXC Global joins a lengthening roll call of exchanges listing $SPONGE.  &lt;br /&gt;
Trading of $SPONGE on the eighth-ranked exchange, according to data site CoinGecko, begins tomorrow Thursday, May 11th, at 10:00 UTC. &lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile, $SPONGE trading starts on MEXC on the same date and time....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-top-performer-sponge-price-explode-mexc-lists-thursday-plus-another-exchange-announcement.htm"&gt;Read More: Meme Coin Top Performer $SPONGE Price to Explode – Lists on MEXC Exchange Thursday, Plus Another CEX Announcement&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-coin-top-performer-sponge-price-explode-mexc-lists-thursday-plus-another-exchange-announcement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113549/274791/unnamed-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="60496"/></item><item><title>Binance NFT Marketplace Expands Offerings, Welcomes Bitcoin NFTs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-nft-marketplace-expands-offerings-welcomes-bitcoin-nfts.htm</link><description>Binance's NFT marketplace has revealed plans to support Bitcoin Ordinals later this month, expanding its ecosystem and creating new opportunities for NFT traders and collectors. &lt;br /&gt;
Although the exchange has not announced a specific launch date, the move is expected to occur soon. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance NFT marketplace currently supports NFTs on BNB Chain, Ethereum, and Polygon....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-nft-marketplace-expands-offerings-welcomes-bitcoin-nfts.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance NFT Marketplace Expands Offerings, Welcomes Bitcoin NFTs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-nft-marketplace-expands-offerings-welcomes-bitcoin-nfts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113541/274749/nft-g5d02b03fb-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="242742"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Twitter Hacker Extradited to US, Coinbase Employee Sentenced to Two Years in Prison, Binance Launches VIP Capital Connect Service</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-twitter-hacker-extradited-to-us-coinbase-employee-sentenced-to-two-years-in-prison-binance-launches-vip-capital-connect-service.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-twitter-hacker-extradited-to-us-coinbase-employee-sentenced-to-two-years-in-prison-binance-launches-vip-capital-connect-service.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Twitter Hacker Extradited to US, Coinbase Employee Sentenced to Two Years in Prison, Binance Launches VIP Capital Connect Service&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Banking</category><category>Xapo</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Unstoppable Domains</category><category>Mining</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Legal</category><category>Twitter</category><category>Hack</category><category>Court</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Vietnam</category><category>Crime</category><category>Binance</category><category>EU</category><category>USA</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-twitter-hacker-extradited-to-us-coinbase-employee-sentenced-to-two-years-in-prison-binance-launches-vip-capital-connect-service.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113510/274659/adobestock-wavebreakmedia.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="84084"/></item></channel></rss>
