<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now August 16 – SEI, THORChain, Toncoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency markets fell on Wednesday, with total market cap dropping by around $16 billion to around $1.1 trillion, Bitcoin (BTC) dropping 1.5% to around $28,700 and Ether (ETH) dropping 1.1% to just above $1,800, where it is now finding support from its 200DMA. &lt;br /&gt;
Downward moves in the crypto market come amid macro headwinds, with US stock markets falling while long-dated US government bond yields and the US dollar rise in wake of the latest Fed minutes release....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now August 16 – SEI, THORChain, Toncoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sei blockchain</category><category>SEI</category><category>Toncoin</category><category>TON</category><category>THORChain</category><category>RUNE</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-august-16-sei-thorchain-toncoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122643/324346/best-crypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Developers Launch Shibarium, Ushering In New Era of Growth for SHIB Ecosystem</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu developers have launched their highly anticipated, purpose-built Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Shibarium, ushering in a new era of growth for one of the crypto industry’s largest decentralized communities. &lt;br /&gt;
The launch announcement was made at the Blockchain Futurist Conference/ETH Toronto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Developers Launch Shibarium, Ushering In New Era of Growth for SHIB Ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Shibarium</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Ethereum layer-2</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-developers-launch-shibarium-ushering-new-era-of-growth-for-shib-ecosystem.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122634/324342/adobestock-468262659-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4483045"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Tumble and BTC Falls to $29,000 – Here are Key Levels to Watch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</link><description>The volatile nature of the cryptocurrency market is once again underscored as Bitcoin, the foremost digital currency, witnesses a significant drop, plummeting to levels around $29,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst an overall tumble in crypto prices, the immediate trajectory and stability of Bitcoin remain the subjects of fervent debate. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Tumble and BTC Falls to $29,000 – Here are Key Levels to Watch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-crypto-prices-tumble-btc-falls-29000-here-are-key-levels-watch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122633/324341/16-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="490072"/></item><item><title>Cat Coin, Shibarium Token Pumping on Uniswap - Are They Scams? Best Meme Coin Alternatives</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm</link><description>A BNB blockchain-based meme coin called Cat (CAT) is has pumped up over 100% on Wednesday, while another meme coin called Shibarium Token (SHIBARIUM) is up over 130%. &lt;br /&gt;
The former’s latest rally has pushed its market cap back to the north of $1 million, with over $2.5 million in trading volumes coming in in the last 24 hours alone. &lt;br /&gt;
CAT now has nearly 12,000 holders, impressive stuff....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm"&gt;Read More: Cat Coin, Shibarium Token Pumping on Uniswap - Are They Scams? Best Meme Coin Alternatives&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shibie</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cat-coin-shibarium-token-pumping-on-uniswap-are-they-scams-best-meme-coin-alternatives.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122632/324331/shibie.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="214151"/></item><item><title>The FBI Seizes Nearly $2 Million Of Digital Assets In Three Months, New Filings Reveal</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fbi-seizes-nearly-2-million-of-digital-assets-three-months-new-filings-reveal.htm</link><description>The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) seized digital assets worth $1.7 million from March to May in the United States. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the filing, the Federal law enforcement agency seized Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), USD Tether (USDT), Monero (XMR), and DAI in its ongoing efforts to curb unlawful activities. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fbi-seizes-nearly-2-million-of-digital-assets-three-months-new-filings-reveal.htm"&gt;Read More: The FBI Seizes Nearly $2 Million Of Digital Assets In Three Months, New Filings Reveal&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FBI</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>SEIZE</category><category>$2 Million</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fbi-seizes-nearly-2-million-of-digital-assets-three-months-new-filings-reveal.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122629/324326/adobestock-kristina-blokh.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1204612"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Secures Approval to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Trading for US Customers</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-secures-approval-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-trading-for-us-customers.htm</link><description>Coinbase, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange, has recently received the green light from the National Futures Association (NFA) to extend its services to include investment opportunities in cryptocurrency futures for eligible clients within the United States. &lt;br /&gt;
On August 16, Coinbase proudly announced that it had been granted official authorization to function as a Futures Commission Merchant (FCM) platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-secures-approval-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-trading-for-us-customers.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Secures Approval to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Trading for US Customers&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>CFTC</category><category>NFA</category><category>FCM&lt; Futures Commission Merchant</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-secures-approval-launch-bitcoin-ether-futures-trading-for-us-customers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122626/324317/coinbase-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="708345"/></item><item><title>Former FTX Executive Invokes Fifth Amendment Right, Remains Silent in Trial – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-invokes-fifth-amendment-right-remains-silent-trial-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Ryan Salame, a former executive of now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX, has declined to testify about his involvement in an alleged illegal campaign donation scheme.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a motion filed by U.S. federal prosecutors on Monday, Salame's attorney has said that, if subpoenaed, he intends to invoke his Fifth Amendment right....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-invokes-fifth-amendment-right-remains-silent-trial-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Former FTX Executive Invokes Fifth Amendment Right, Remains Silent in Trial – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Ryan Salame</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-invokes-fifth-amendment-right-remains-silent-trial-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122608/324286/b8402f706581cf173c4f428ea.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="120581"/></item><item><title>Tokens Highlighted in Binance and Coinbase SEC Lawsuits See Surge in Trading – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tokens-highlighted-binance-coinbase-sec-lawsuits-see-surge-trading-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Around two months after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed lawsuits against major exchanges Binance.US and Coinbase, targeting 19 cryptocurrencies that were designated as unregistered securities, the same tokens are showing signs of recovery. &lt;br /&gt;
Following the allegations, the combined market value of the 19 tokens dropped by roughly $20 billion, but trading volume for these tokens has later increased, data compiled by CCData showed....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tokens-highlighted-binance-coinbase-sec-lawsuits-see-surge-trading-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Tokens Highlighted in Binance and Coinbase SEC Lawsuits See Surge in Trading – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tokens-highlighted-binance-coinbase-sec-lawsuits-see-surge-trading-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122596/324268/recovery.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="139968"/></item><item><title>FDIC's Annual Risk Report Embraces Crypto as a Significant Banking Concern</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fdics-annual-risk-report-embraces-crypto-as-significant-banking-concern.htm</link><description>Crypto assets present “novel and complex risks” to the banking sector that are “difficult to fully assess,” according to the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC)’s 2023 Risk Review for the banking sector. &lt;br /&gt;
The report – published earlier this month – named “crypto-asset risk” among five categories of risk banks are faced with today. The others include credit risk, market risk, operational risk, and climate-related financial risk....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fdics-annual-risk-report-embraces-crypto-as-significant-banking-concern.htm"&gt;Read More: FDIC's Annual Risk Report Embraces Crypto as a Significant Banking Concern&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fdics-annual-risk-report-embraces-crypto-as-significant-banking-concern.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122624/324311/adobestock-317381100.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="230907"/></item><item><title>Dubai Fines Co-Founders of Failed Three Arrows Capital Over New Exchange OPNX</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-fines-co-founders-of-failed-three-arrows-capital-over-new-exchange-opnx.htm</link><description>Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) has slapped failed 3AC co-founders with a massive $2.7 million fine against their new crypto project OPNX. &lt;br /&gt;
Crypto exchange OPNX, co-founded by Kyle Davies and Su Zhu who established the now-defunct hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), has apparently not paid the fine of AED10 million ($2.7 million) which was imposed by VARA in May for a market offense....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-fines-co-founders-of-failed-three-arrows-capital-over-new-exchange-opnx.htm"&gt;Read More: Dubai Fines Co-Founders of Failed Three Arrows Capital Over New Exchange OPNX&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-fines-co-founders-of-failed-three-arrows-capital-over-new-exchange-opnx.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122620/324306/burj-khalifa-2212978-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="245061"/></item><item><title>Crypto Custodian Ledger Lets Users Buy Digital Assets In New PayPal Integration</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm</link><description>Crypto hardware wallet, Ledger has announced a new PayPal integration that allows its users to buy Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH).  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a joint announcement by the companies on Aug 16, Ledger Live software become fully integrated with verified PayPal users in the United States with no extra verification....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Custodian Ledger Lets Users Buy Digital Assets In New PayPal Integration&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ledger</category><category>PayPal</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Hardware wallet</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122612/324297/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103701"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Stellar Buys Minority Stake in MoneyGram, Adidas and BAPE Reveal Limited Sneakers Auctioned via NFT Passes, Three Key Silvergate Execs Set to Leave the Company</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Stellar Buys Minority Stake in MoneyGram, Adidas and BAPE Reveal Limited Sneakers Auctioned via NFT Passes, Three Key Silvergate Execs Set to Leave the Company&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Investment</category><category>Stellar</category><category>Moneygram</category><category>NFT</category><category>Silvergate</category><category>SEC</category><category>Uzbekistan</category><category>Banking</category><category>mastercard</category><category>Moonpay</category><category>Payments</category><category>Ireland</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SIX</category><category>SDX</category><category>Security</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122587/324261/screenshot-2023-08-16-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="319017"/></item><item><title>New Crypto Lobbyist Group Emerges in Washington, Seeks to Allay Misconceptions in the Sector</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency miners are getting a dedicated mining lobbyist group tasked with dispelling fears around the activity among citizens and policymakers. &lt;br /&gt;
The group, the Digital Energy Council was unveiled on Aug 15 and will now open up discussions with policymakers in Washington on the sustainability of crypto mining whilst advancing key policies to spark growth in the sector....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm"&gt;Read More: New Crypto Lobbyist Group Emerges in Washington, Seeks to Allay Misconceptions in the Sector&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Miner</category><category>Lobbyist Group</category><category>Washington</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122599/324274/bitcoin-gf8a75ed9e-1280-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293858"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Startup Nova Labs Introduces Affordable $5 Phone Plan – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>Blockchain startup Nova Labs has announced the launch of a new phone plan that offers users unlimited text, talk, and data at just $5 per month. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Tuesday press release, Nova Labs said that the plan will initially be available only to residents of Miami or those who have received an invitation to access the product....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Startup Nova Labs Introduces Affordable $5 Phone Plan – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Nova Labs</category><category>Telecommunication</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122588/324240/iphone-500291-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227848"/></item><item><title>Singapore Court to Adjudicate DeFiance Capital's $140 Million Dispute with 3AC Liquidators</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm</link><description>A judge in Singapore has decided that a $140 million legal dispute between bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital’s (3AC) liquidators and investment firm DeFiance Capital will be heard in the city-state, against the will of the liquidators. &lt;br /&gt;
The disagreement between the parties center around assets managed by DeFiance Capital, an independently run firm that was within the 3AC corporate structure....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm"&gt;Read More: Singapore Court to Adjudicate DeFiance Capital's $140 Million Dispute with 3AC Liquidators&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>3AC</category><category>DeFiance Capital</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122591/324255/3ac.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="141215"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy THORChain? RUNE Price Blasts Up 60% and LPX Token Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>In a magnificent display, leading decentralized liquidity and trading protocol THORhain (RUNE) has blasted up a shocking +60% - yet, as traders race to get in on the action, many are asking is it too late to buy THORChain? &lt;br /&gt;
The pump comes amid a favourable time in THORchain tokenomics, with large swathes of supply currently in circulation and the slow onset of deflationary dynamics afoot....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy THORChain? RUNE Price Blasts Up 60% and LPX Token Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122589/324254/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="375523"/></item><item><title>Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun's Huobi-Linked Exchange WhiteBIT Raises Concerns Over Its Lending Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm</link><description>An obscure exchange with connections to Justin Sun, WhiteBIT, has sparked concerns after advertising a staggering Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of 24.8% to users depositing Tether (USDT) for a year on its lending platform, Protos reported.  &lt;br /&gt;
This rate is five times higher than the average USD money market rate, a glaring red flag for potential investors. &lt;br /&gt;
WhiteBIT's association with Justin Sun, a well-known figure in the cryptocurrency industry, raises further suspicion. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun's Huobi-Linked Exchange WhiteBIT Raises Concerns Over Its Lending Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Justin Sun</category><category>Huobi</category><category>USDD</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122586/324237/justin-sun.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="140116"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as Tokenized Version of Bitcoin Prepares to Launch on SOL Blockchain – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Solana (SOL) has dived by 6% today, with the altcoin's fall to $23.39 coming as the cryptocurrency market as a whole drops by 1.5% in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
This means SOL has lost 5% in a week and 15% in a month, with today's selloff largely the result of speculation that the SEC is delay all of its decisions regarding Bitcoin ETF applications until 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as Tokenized Version of Bitcoin Prepares to Launch on SOL Blockchain – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122581/324236/solana-price-prediction-a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1159021"/></item><item><title>ApeCoin is Going to Zero as APE Price Drops 10% in 24 Hours While New Meme Coin Sonik Goes Viral – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>As altcoin markets continue to take a hit, ApeCoin (APE) has fallen -10% back below the 20DMA in a tumultuous rejection from trendline resistance, leaving some fearful BAYC bagholders to question whether ApeCoin is going to zero. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes following a catastrophic year for ApeCoin, which has bled-out -93.5% since the all-time high on April 28 2022 - leaving APE price reeling in a tight descendant trading channel since the start of this summer....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: ApeCoin is Going to Zero as APE Price Drops 10% in 24 Hours While New Meme Coin Sonik Goes Viral – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122578/324232/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="911562"/></item><item><title>PayPal Halts Crypto Sales in U.K. Until 2024 to Comply With New FCA Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm</link><description>Online payment giant PayPal said it will temporarily pause crypto buying services in the UK to comply with the recent new rules for marketing cryptoassets enacted by the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). &lt;br /&gt;
In a message to its customers on Tuesday, PayPal said that the crypto sales would pause effective 1 October 2023 and the service will be re-enabled in early 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: PayPal Halts Crypto Sales in U.K. Until 2024 to Comply With New FCA Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122557/324183/pexels-brett-jordan-5437587.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="4379393"/></item></channel></rss>
