<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 21:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Russia Partners With Iran to Release a Stablecoin Backed by Gold (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/russia-partners-with-iran-to-release-a-stablecoin-backed-by-gold-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Iran]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233444</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/stablecoin_iran_Russia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/stablecoin_iran_Russia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Russia's government and Iran's central bank could supposedly team up and create a stablecoin called "the token of the Persian Gulf region."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Russian government and the Central Bank of Iran are reportedly mulling a partnership to create a new stablecoin that can facilitate cross-border settlements.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The token will be pegged to the valuation of gold.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Mutual Operation</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.vedomosti.ru/economics/articles/2023/01/16/959100-rossiya-i-iran-nachali-prorabotku-obschego-steiblkoina" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the Russian media outlet Vedomosti, the local authorities could collaborate with Iran&#8217;s central bank to launch a new crypto asset called &#8220;the token of the Persian Gulf region.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Assuming it sees the light of day, it will replace fiat currencies such as the dollar, the euro, the ruble, and others in foreign trade transactions. Alexander Brazhnikov &#8211; Executive Director of the Russian Association of the Crypto Industry and Blockchain &#8211; said the coin will be backed by gold and will be employed in a special economic zone in Astrakhan.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The two nations recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.marineinsight.com/shipping-news/iran-and-russia-jointly-sign-deal-to-build-a-vessel-for-caspian-sea-port/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">signed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a contract to facilitate trade through a transportation system in the Caspian Sea, with the northern tip of the network being the Russian town of Astrakhan.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Anton Tkachev &#8211; a member of the Duma Committee on Information Policy &#8211; confirmed the rumors about the creation of the new stablecoin. However, he specified that such a move could be actively discussed only when Russia&#8217;s government implements an appropriate regulatory framework on its local crypto sector.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Anatoly Aksakov &#8211; Chairman of the State Duma Committee on the Financial Markets &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.vedomosti.ru/finance/news/2022/12/05/953772-v-gosdume-poobeschali" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the end of 2022 that the authorities will apply such rules by the end of 2023:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I can assure everyone that we will definitely have crypto as a legal product next year, there will definitely be legislation&#8230; I can only say unequivocally that it cannot be used in the Russian Federation as a means of payment for internal settlements.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Iran and Russia Share Similar Views on Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Russia, specifically its central bank, has not displayed the most friendly stance on the digital asset industry. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russias-central-bank-reportedly-proposes-a-total-crypto-ban/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">proposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a total ban on all crypto endeavors, but the Finance Ministry later </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russia-finance-ministry-proposes-to-regulate-crypto-instead-of-banning-it/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">softened</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the tone to &#8220;just&#8221; implementing regulations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmakers have been trying to establish a &#8220;national&#8221; cryptocurrency platform based on the Moscow Exchange standards for months. As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russia-inches-closer-to-launching-a-national-crypto-exchange-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in November, the authorities also discussed this with market participants and now await the approval of the Ministry of Finance and the Bank of Russia.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One area where Russia wants to concentrate on is bitcoin mining. President Vladimir Putin </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/putin-crypto-mining-could-provide-russia-with-competitive-advantages/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year that he sees potential in it:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Although, of course, we also have certain competitive advantages here, especially in the so-called mining. I mean the surplus of electricity and the well-trained personnel available in the country.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Central Bank of the Islamic Republic of Iran has also been quite negative on crypto, prohibiting domestic banks and financial institutions from dealing with it in 2018. The government </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/iran-doubles-down-on-its-war-against-illegal-crypto-miners-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">declared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> war on illicit bitcoin miners while also pausing even the legal operators to preserve the stability of the national electricity system. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/russia-partners-with-iran-to-release-a-stablecoin-backed-by-gold-report/" rel="nofollow">Russia Partners With Iran to Release a Stablecoin Backed by Gold (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet The House Republican Who Could Decide Crypto&#8217;s Future</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/meet-the-house-republican-who-could-decide-cryptos-future/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233303</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[House Republicans are launching a cryptocurrency subcommittee. Let's have a look. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While crypto prices rallied last week, the public learned House Republicans are forming a cryptocurrency subcommittee. The announcement may spell the beginning of the end of U.S. regulatory ambiguity on blockchain and digital assets.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Strange, isn&#8217;t it? Each man&#8217;s life touches so many other lives. And when he isn&#8217;t around, he leaves an awful hole, doesn&#8217;t he?&#8221; — Clarence, &#8220;It&#8217;s A Wonderful Life&#8221; (1946 Christmas drama about a banking panic).</p></blockquote>
<h2>Addressing a Big Hole</h2>
<p>Rep. Patrick McHenry, a Republican from North Carolina&#8217;s delegation, <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/01/12/mchenry-reveals-house-crypto-panel-names-subcommittee-chairs-00077667" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said Thursday</a> he&#8217;s planning to create the new crypto subcommittee.</p>
<p>He says it will address &#8220;a big hole in how we structure the committee&#8221; to reckon with crypto. McHenry was referring to the House Financial Services Committee, for which he is the incoming chair for the 118th U.S. Congress:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’ve got to respond for oversight and policymaking on a new asset class.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The announcement of a new House crypto panel coincided with a massive crypto price bull run. Over $600 million in BTC shorts were liquidated as the Bitcoin price rallied to $21,000. The overall crypto market cap ballooned to $1 trillion <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-taps-1-trillion-as-solana-polkadot-explode-double-digits/" data-wpel-link="internal">as altcoins posted double-digit gains</a>.</p>
<p>After a year-long roll to ever-lower support levels, the cryptocurrency exchange market has finally shown some spirit. Maybe all it needed was a little broad-based consumer confidence and the hope of some regulatory clarity.</p>
<p>After the fall of FTX in November, the Republican McHenry joined with Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters (CA) to call for a bipartisan crypto bill.</p>
<p>Following a series of devastating <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-lesson-in-alameda-ftx-about-government-regulation-and-crypto-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">insolvencies among various crypto startups</a>, consumers and investors may welcome congressional rulemaking. It could also clear up the future of many projects by resolving the turf war among U.S. regulators.</p>
<p>For example, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-seeks-formal-deal-with-the-cftc-for-crypto-regulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">the SEC has been pushing</a> for control over the regulation of crypto. But the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-chair-reiterates-bitcoin-and-ether-are-commodities/" data-wpel-link="internal">Commodity Futures Trading Commission says</a> Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) are commodities.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-233434" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover.jpg" alt="mchenry_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mchenry_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Meet The House Republican Who Could Decide Crypto&#8217;s Future</h2>
<p>A rule issued by legislation from the Republican Congress might not mean burdens for the crypto industry. It certainly could, for instance, if Bitcoin were defined by law as security. But it might not go that way.</p>
<p>A year ago, the Republican financial services chair <a href="https://twitter.com/PatrickMcHenry/status/1468636724720984067" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Congress must fully understand these innovative new technologies, like #crypto. We don&#8217;t need knee-jerk reactions by lawmakers to regulate out of fear of the unknown.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>McHenry <a href="https://financialservices.house.gov/news/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=408215" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">has also encouraged</a> policymakers to question whether they are taking cryptocurrency seriously and understand it well enough to even make sensible propositions about it:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Let’s be clear, this technology is already regulated. The question for policymakers is whether you know enough about this technology, which is neither fish nor fowl, to have a serious debate.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>One indication that new rules from the Republican-led crypto subcommittee might not be onerous is McHenry&#8217;s position on payday loan regulations. <a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/payday-loan-lenders-high-interest-loans-cfpb/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">He supported</a> a 2020 Trump-era Republican rule change to relax compliance burdens for payday lenders issuing high-interest loans.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.opensecrets.org/members-of-congress/patrick-mchenry/summary?cid=N00026627" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">His top contributors are</a> Alphabet Inc, a tech titan; Signature Bank, a New York commercial banking giant; and MetLife, Inc., an insurance company. There is a lot of overlap there with the concerns and economics of the crypto business.</p>
<p>Whatever happens next, crypto and traditional finance markets will be watching and strategizing about their futures.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/meet-the-house-republican-who-could-decide-cryptos-future/" rel="nofollow">Meet The House Republican Who Could Decide Crypto&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>After Losing Coins, Bitcoin Core Dev Starts to Doubt Self-Custody</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/after-losing-coins-bitcoin-core-dev-starts-to-doubt-self-custody/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233537</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One of Bitcoin’s most prolific developers thinks Bitcoin lacks any reliable storage solutions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Core developer Luke Dashjr is having doubts about the safety of Bitcoin’s existing storage solutions after his personal wallet was drained of over $4 million in coins last month.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The programmer suggested that his practice for storing his coins was well in excess of “standard practices,” and yet he was still successfully robbed. </span></p>
<h2>Is Bitcoin Safe?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Monday, Dashjr responded to a fellow Bitcoiner on Twitter who asked how others would spend their money if they woke up one day to $30 million in their bank account. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Some of Bitcoin’s greatest devotees – including MicroStrategy’s executive chairman  Michael Saylor – might champion a 100% Bitcoin allocation. However, Dashjr advocated a (relatively) modest approach: “Maybe 1000 BTC or so, if I could find a way to keep it safe,” he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1614864603715878916" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">replied</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, suggesting real estate as a potentially safer alternative.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On December 31st, Dashjr </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-core-developer-loses-3-5m-in-btc-in-a-supposed-exploit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">lost</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> his entire stash of over 200 BTC to a hacker who, according to the developer, compromised his PGP (pretty good privacy) key. A PGP key is an encryption program providing cryptographic privacy and authentication for sensitive files – such as a Bitcoin private key. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A private key is a digital signature required to send a Bitcoin transaction from its associated wallet. Most experts recommend keeping one’s personal keys in “cold storage” – disconnected from the internet entirely – as a foolproof way of protecting one’s Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yet Dashjr suggested otherwise. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Standard practices are obviously insecure,” he said. “My security was far in excess of standard practices, and I still got compromised.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Cold Storage</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The developer </span><a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1614961413222547456" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">claims</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the addresses from which his Bitcoin were stolen were in fact cold storage addresses. He is not entirely sure that using a ColdCard, a reputable hardware wallet, would have </span><a href="https://twitter.com/LukeDashjr/status/1614944863497162753" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">protected</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> his funds. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Dashjr is still unaware of how his funds were stolen or at least hasn’t disclosed such details publicly. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Adam Back – one of Bitcoin’s earliest contributors who collaborated with Satoshi Nakamoto, </span><a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us/status/1615067345080422400" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">believes</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Dashjr was targeted through his home network and had his machines compromised. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others had a harsher critique of Dashjr, with Bitcoiners like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hodlonaut-prevails-in-lawsuit-against-self-described-satoshi-craig-wright/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Holdonaut</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> accusing him of spreading misinformation about the ease with which Bitcoin can be secured. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I’m just having a big issue with him saying it’s not possible to store bitcoin securely,” he said over Twitter. “Seed phrase on paper/metal doesn’t care about the compromised home network.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-losing-coins-bitcoin-core-dev-starts-to-doubt-self-custody/" rel="nofollow">After Losing Coins, Bitcoin Core Dev Starts to Doubt Self-Custody</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index Rises to &#8216;Neutral&#8217; for the First Time in 9 Months</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-fear-and-greed-index-rises-to-neutral-for-the-first-time-in-9-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 20:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233406</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Neutral.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Neutral.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Index stopped at 52 yesterday (January 15), which was its highest point in the last nine months.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index &#8211; a metric that determines the community&#8217;s general sentiment on the primary cryptocurrency &#8211; spiked to a state of &#8220;Neutral&#8221; for the first time in nearly nine months.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The increase comes as a result of BTC&#8217;s positive start in 2023.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At Last, out of the &#8216;Fear&#8217; Zone</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index tracks multiple segments, including price volatility, social media comments, surveys, and others, to display the momentary investor sentiment toward the leading digital asset. It provides results between 0 (&#8220;Extreme Fear&#8221;) to 100 (&#8220;Extreme Greed&#8221;).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Index </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pointed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at 52 yesterday (January 15), meaning it was in &#8220;Neutral&#8221; territory for the first time since April 5, 2022. It was either in the &#8220;Fear&#8221; or &#8220;Extreme Fear&#8221; zones during the past nine months, prompted by the prolonged bear market and the adverse events that surrounded the cryptocurrency industry (<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Terra crash</a>, 3AC&#8217;s bankruptcy, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">the collapse of FTX</a>, and many more).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The main reason for the recent surge could be bitcoin&#8217;s price increase. The asset has added approximately 25% to its USD value since the start of the year, currently trading at around $20,800. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/market-watch-solana-soars-5-bitcoin-marked-10-week-high-above-21k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hit</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> almost $21,500 earlier today (January 16)- a 10-week high. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the promising results, though, the Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index has now returned to the state of &#8220;Fear,&#8221; dropping to 45. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entire digital asset sector has seen moments of revival over the last several days, with the global crypto market cap <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-taps-1-trillion-as-solana-polkadot-explode-double-digits/" data-wpel-link="internal">touching</a> the $1 trillion mark during the weekend (on CoinGecko). </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bull Run on the Horizon?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The last time bitcoin started the year that well was at the beginning of 2021, which prompted some analysts, such as Glassnode&#8217;s James Check, to envision the end of the prolonged bear market. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal">noted</a> that the two leading cryptocurrencies by market cap &#8211; bitcoin and ether &#8211; have seen little volatility in the past few weeks. Such periods historically lead to &#8220;explosive market moves:&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It really is quite remarkable, and there are very few instances in history where bitcoin and any digital asset really goes to sleep to this level on a volatility framework.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin&#8217;s price was relatively flat between December 2018 and March 2019, hovering around $3,500. In April, though, it started a rally that lasted until July (when BTC was worth nearly $12,000). </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-fear-and-greed-index-rises-to-neutral-for-the-first-time-in-9-months/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index Rises to &#8216;Neutral&#8217; for the First Time in 9 Months</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Martin Luther King Jr. Day: How Bitcoin Makes The Dream Happen (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/happy-birthday-mlk-how-bitcoin-makes-the-dream-happen-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232814</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[MLK was famous for fighting racial discrimination and for his "I Have A Dream" speech. Today is his birthday.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almost sixty years after MLK gave the speech, crypto embodies <a href="https://www.marshall.edu/onemarshallu/i-have-a-dream/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Dr. King&#8217;s dream</a>. It makes a dream much like his substantial and available to us in code and computer network design.</p>
<h2>How Bitcoin Currency Is About The Same Dream As MLK</h2>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I was a drum major for justice, peace, and righteousness.&#8221; -MLK</p></blockquote>
<p>Bitcoin is a technology united around equal and open access to financial opportunity and infrastructure. Crypto is designed to make prejudice irrelevant and discrimination impossible because of or over its networks.</p>
<p>The agnosticism of the valuable working elements of the network to the user is the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocurrencies-increase-in-popularity-among-lgbtq-and-black-americans/" data-wpel-link="internal">pride of crypto</a>. One could imagine MLK happy about its development.</p>
<p>Moreover, the idea of a financial intermediary that does not need to interact with any of the identifying information of the user to work for them was one of the early hopes of the Bitcoin community. This recalls the hope of MLK and his supporters that this information would not be used to discriminate.</p>
<p>Since 2009, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-for-beginners/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin created a system</a> that respects universal human rights to use basic banking services. It&#8217;s something MLK could really appreciate if he were still alive today.</p>
<p>Bitcoin does not judge anyone by the color of their skin. But it&#8217;s even more radical than Martin Luther King&#8217;s dream speech. It doesn&#8217;t judge anyone by the content of their character, either.</p>
<p>Bitcoin doesn&#8217;t need to know about that to work. Bitcoin is there for anyone to use.</p>
<p>It doesn&#8217;t ask where you live. It doesn&#8217;t ask what your credit history is before working as advertised. Furthermore, you don&#8217;t have to wait to be approved by another human who might be too busy to get to you to use Bitcoin.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s how Bitcoin helps make the dream of financial easement and non-discrimination happen.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233440" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233440" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233440" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover.jpg" alt="mlkjr_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/mlkjr_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233440" class="wp-caption-text">Martin Luther King: Source: NPR</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Parallels Between Bitcoin and Dr. King&#8217;s I Have A Dream Speech</h2>
<p>Like MLK&#8217;s 1963 Lincoln Memorial Address, Bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-is-superior-to-all-other-payment-networks-strike-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">has aimed to be</a> &#8220;the greatest demonstration for freedom&#8221; in the history of nations.</p>
<p>The problems MLK identified as their cause for grievance were segregation, discrimination, disenfranchisement, and alienation. This was happening to African Americans in 1963 on the centennial of the Emancipation Proclamation ending slavery.</p>
<p>Bitcoin exists to address these same problems that persist today in the global financial system. It is interesting to wonder what MLK would think about the technology if he were alive today.</p>
<p>It exists to solve the crisis of the unbanked. MLK might be interested to know how many <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/unbanked-americans-use-cryptocurrency-for-payments-and-transfers-fed-survey-finds/" data-wpel-link="internal">unbanked Americans today have</a> already used crypto.</p>
<p>It exists to end unequal or seriously unsatisfactory access to lending and banking services. It offers a way around fiat currencies of corrupt governments with perilously confiscatory inflationary schemes and discrimination based on sex, race, class, religion, caste, and political affiliation.</p>
<p>MLK said the March on Washington was to cash a check for the United States&#8217; promise of unalienable rights. Bitcoin &#8211;  this is distributed computer network architecture that encodes your cashed checks as your inalienable rights when you produce your private key to make a request to the network for your funds.</p>
<p>MLK continues on with his banking analogy in the speech so it&#8217;s very relevant to wish him a happy birthday and examine the parallels between the ideals of his speech and what crypto has started to accomplish.</p>
<p><em>Featured image courtesy of NPR</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/happy-birthday-mlk-how-bitcoin-makes-the-dream-happen-opinion/" rel="nofollow">Martin Luther King Jr. Day: How Bitcoin Makes The Dream Happen (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Ethereum Liquid Staking and Why It Is Crucial As Shanghai Upgrade Approaches?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ethereum-liquid-staking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 16:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233411</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum Liquid Staking protocols have been soaring in value since the start of 2023 as the Shanghai upgrade inches closer. Here's why.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum is the largest smart contract platform in the industry, and it underwent a major shift by transitioning to a new consensus algorithm in 2022.</p>
<p>What is commonly referred to as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">The Merge</a> saw the network abandon Proof of Work and transition to Proof of Stake in pursuit of fulfilling its broader roadmap towards scalability, decentralization, and security.</p>
<p><strong>Quick Navigation</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><a href="#limits">Limitations of Self-Staking</a></li>
<li><a href="#what">What is Ethereum Liquid Staking?</a></li>
<li><a href="#top3">Top 3 Ethereum Liquid Staking Protocols: Lido, Rocket Pool, Ankr</a></li>
<li><a href="#dif">Liquid Staking vs. Exchange Staking: What’s the Difference?</a></li>
<li><a href="#top3">Top 3 Ethereum Liquid Staking Protocols: Lido, Rocket Pool, Ankr</a></li>
<li><a href="#why">Why Ethereum Liquid Staking Coins Surge?</a></li>
</ul>
<p>With the introduction of Proof of Stake on the Beacon chain a while back, users were able to deposit 32 ETH to become full validators of the network.</p>
<p>This is part of Ethereum’s core components &#8211; namely, decentralization and transparency. In essence, users across the world are able to maintain the network and uphold it by running their own validator nodes.</p>
<p>However, this, in itself, also brought up a few limitations. Let’s have a look at some of them when it comes to self-staking.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-232432" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1.jpg" alt="ethereum_cover (1)" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2 id="limits">Limitations of Self-Staking</h2>
<p>Those who wish to become full validators are facing some notable drawbacks. For instance, they’re unable to move the minimum required amount (32 ETH), making it entirely illiquid for the time the user wishes to remain a full validator.</p>
<p>Users who stake their ETH to the Beacon depositor contract in a bid to secure the network are not allowed to withdraw their ETH until this functionality is enabled. The core developers of Ethereum said that this will become possible with the Shanghai update. It is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/liquid-staking-platforms-surging-ahead-of-ethereum-shanghai-upgrade/" data-wpel-link="internal">expected</a> to hit the public testnet in February and potentially the mainnet in March.</p>
<p><em>Learn more about the Shanghai update in our </em><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/talking-ethereum-2-0-with-consensys-pm-matt-nelson-when-can-eth-validators-unstake/" data-wpel-link="internal"><em>podcast</em></a><em> with ConsenSys product manager Matt Nelson. </em></p>
<p>It’s important to note that there is currently around 16 million ETH worth somewhere close to $25 billion (at current prices) locked in the contract. As opposed to this considerable limitation, liquid staking platforms offer an alternative.</p>
<h2 id="what">What is Ethereum Liquid Staking?</h2>
<p>Ethereum liquid staking is a concept that’s been around for quite some time but picked up speed at the beginning of 2023 when the majority of platforms that offer these capabilities saw tremendous growth.</p>
<p>In essence, liquid staking is an alternative to locking up a user’s stake. In doing so, it allows users to stake whatever amount of ETH they want and unstake it without the requirement of this capability being enabled on the mainnet (e.g., before the Shanghai upgrade).</p>
<p>This is carried out through the issuance of a tokenized version of the funds being staked &#8211; some sort of a derivative. It can be transferred, stored, traded, spent, or even locked, as one would with a regular token.</p>
<p>The way it works is quite simple. A user would deposit ETH to a third-party platform. The platform would deposit the ETh to the Beacon depositor contract for them (by running their own validators). In return, the protocol would mint a representative ETH, which the user can withdraw, trade, stake, and whatnot.</p>
<p>There are a few benefits to Ethereum Liquid Staking, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>No risk of long-term holding</li>
<li>Availability of deposited tokens</li>
<li>Yield similar to that of locked ETH staking</li>
</ul>
<p>The upcoming Shanghai upgrade has pushed the Ethereum Liquid Staking narrative considerably, and most of the platforms that offer services of the kind saw their native cryptocurrencies skyrocket since the beginning of 2023.</p>
<p>That said, let’s have a quick look at some of the most popular Ethereum Liquid Staking protocols.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-233412" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover.jpg" alt="ethereum_liquid_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ethereum_liquid_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2 id="top3">Top 3 Ethereum Liquid Staking Protocols</h2>
<h3>Lido</h3>
<p>Lido is the largest protocol for Ethereum Liquid Staking by means of both total market capitalization and the total value locked ($7.68 billion at the time of this writing) on its platform.</p>
<p>When users stake ETH with Lido, they receive an alternative token called stETH which represents their stake in a 1:1 ratio. The tokens are minted upon deposit and are subsequently burned when they are redeemed.</p>
<p>The stETH token balances are issued 1:1 to the ETH that is staked by Lido. The stETH token balances are also updated daily when the oracle reports the change in the total stake.</p>
<p>The native cryptocurrency of Lido is called LDO.</p>
<h3>Rocket Pool</h3>
<p>At the time of this writing, Rocket Pool is the second-largest Ethereum Liquid Staking protocol by means of total value locked on its platform (around $800 million.)</p>
<p>Similarly to Lido, users are able to stake their ETH at Rocket Pool and receive an alternative token that’s called rETH.</p>
<p>The minimum deposit is 0.01 ETH, there is no limit as to how much users can stake, and they are allowed to continue staking and withdraw as they see fit.</p>
<p>The native cryptocurrency of Rocket Pool is called RPL.</p>
<h3>Ankr</h3>
<p>Ankr Protocol is next in line in terms of total value of ETH locked on its platform. At the time of this writing, it’s around $153 million.</p>
<p>The alternative token that the protocol issues is called ankrETH. Similarly to the other platforms, users are able to withdraw whenever they want to and take part in various DeFi farms using the ankrETH tokens.</p>
<h2 id="dif">Liquid Staking vs. Exchange Staking: What’s the Difference?</h2>
<p>Some exchanges, such as Coinbase and Binance also allow users to deposit ETH and stake it toward the Beacon depositor contract and earn rewards.</p>
<p>What is more, they also issue their own ETH tokens that users can withdraw and trade as they see fit. With Binance, for instance, the token is called BETH, and users can trade it against USDT whenever they want to. The main thing to consider is that you need to have BETH in your account to be eligible for the staking yield.</p>
<p>Another important consideration is that these are centralized counterparties, and, as such, they keep custody of your tokens &#8211; in this case, the ETH alternatives. Therefore, all drawbacks and limitations to holding your crypto on an exchange apply, with all the benefits too.</p>
<h2 id="why">Why Ethereum Liquid Staking Coins Surge?</h2>
<p>As mentioned in the beginning of the guide, almost all protocols that provide Ethereum liquid staking capabilities saw the prices of their native cryptocurrencies soar in value since the start of 2023.</p>
<p>For example, LDO is up over 100% in the past 30 days. ANKR is up around 45% in the past 14 days. Frax Shares (FXS) is up over 100% in the last two weeks. Rocket Pool’s RPL token is up around 70% in the last month. Other Ethereum liquid staking coins, such as StakeWise (SWISE) Stafi (FIS), and others, are also up similar percentages.</p>
<p>The consensus seems to be that traders are expecting the upcoming Shanghai upgrade for Ethereum to be quite beneficial for these platforms. The reason is that over 15 million ETH will be unlocked and users will seek liquid alternatives where they would stake their ETH. And since these protocols provide some clear advantages, the current narrative is that Shanghai will propel the demand for their services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ethereum-liquid-staking/" rel="nofollow">What is Ethereum Liquid Staking and Why It Is Crucial As Shanghai Upgrade Approaches?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nexo Turmoil Causing Tension in Bulgarian Parliament</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nexo-turmoil-causing-tension-in-bulgarian-parliament/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 16:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nexo]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233382</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Nexo_Bulgaria.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Nexo_Bulgaria.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Nexo drama has prompted political tension in Bulgaria after it was revealed that firm employees had donated to one of the parties.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The scandal around the cryptocurrency lending platform Nexo has triggered a massive verbal fight between the leading political parties in Bulgaria. GERB (the party that ruled between 2009 and 2021) alleged Democratic Bulgaria and We Continue the Change of having close ties with the distressed entity and even receiving significant donations from it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the contrary, numerous MPs claimed that members of GERB have intentionally launched such attacks against their rivals to prevent them from forming an acting government.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nexo Creates Huge Drama in Bulgaria</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The platform that allows users to earn interest on crypto deposits has had a rough start to the year after the Bulgarian authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nexo-bulgarian-offices-reportedly-raided-by-authorities/" data-wpel-link="internal">raided</a> its local offices. The operation was part of a probe into suspected tax crimes and money laundering.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The investigation quickly turned into one of the main topics in the Eastern European country, while the leading political parties used it as an opportunity to hurt each other&#8217;s reputation.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Boiko Borisov (PM of the nation between 2009 and 2021) and other members of his GERB party </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dariknews.bg/novini/bylgariia/borisov-za-nexo-naglostta-na-hristo-ivanov-i-drugite-e-bezgranichna-2336140" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> five employees of Nexo donated 20,000 BGN each to Democratic Bulgaria (a major rival of the former ruling organization) in October 2021. It was disclosed that two more workers of the crypto platform followed suit, giving away the same amount days later.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">GERB went even further, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://bnr.bg/horizont/post/101763726/gerb-proveravat-dali-pp-e-bila-finansirana-ot-lica-svarzani-s-nexo" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to check whether Nexo has financed the political campaign of &#8220;We Continue the Change&#8221; (the party that won the elections in 2021 and stayed at the helm until June last year). Borisov&#8217;s organization and other members of Bulgaria&#8217;s political elite also claimed that the former Finance Minister Asen Vasilev was part of Nexo&#8217;s inner circle and acted on behalf of the company.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Vasilev </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bulgaria-won-t-waver-on-euro-adoption-finance-chief-says-1.1711244" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year that the government has been exploring options to embrace a crypto payment mechanism &#8220;in the short to medium term.&#8221; He revealed the ruling body will partner with the central bank and &#8220;industry players&#8221; on the move (without particularly mentioning Nexo).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reaction to the Accusations</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Members of We Continue the Change were quick to refute the allegations, claiming the scandal is one of GERB&#8217;s PR actions against its opposition. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MP Kalina Konstantinova </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dariknews.bg/novini/bylgariia/konstantinova-skandalyt-s-nexo-e-edna-ot-piar-akciite-na-prokuraturata-i-gerb-2336186" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">believes</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the prosecution launched the Nexo investigation at the exact time when President Rumen Radev was about to give Democratic Bulgaria (a close ally of We Continue the Change) a mandate to form a government and thus leave GERB out of the equation.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;But I think people can see past the facade that is meant to distract from the important subject. Namely, the formation of a cabinet and the consideration of one of the most important anti-corruption laws, the one on control over the chief prosecutor,&#8221; she added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Democratic Bulgaria&#8217;s leader &#8211; Hristo Ivanov &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://epicenter.bg/article/Hristo-Ivanov--Nyama-da-vrashtame-darenieto-na-Nexo/305547/2/0" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">admitted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that his party received donations from Nexo employees. However, he sees nothing wrong with that, stating the transactions were publicly registered and reported to the Audit Office. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This means telling the people who gave this money, the entire Bulgarian community that donated, that there is something wrong with it,&#8221; he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ivanov shared Konstantinova&#8217;s stance that the prosecutors&#8217; efforts against Nexo came at the right time when Democratic Bulgaria was about to obtain the chance to establish a cabinet and enforce major judiciary reforms:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;How exactly was Thursday chosen in the week in which the third term is to be served, and it is clear that we, in the third term, will try to resolve the issue of the status of the attorney general. Let there not be some propaganda exploitation of an otherwise real investigation here.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">What About Asen Vasilev?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former Finance Minister </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.flashnews.bg/sled-skandala-s-nexo-asen-vasilev-se-poyavi-otreche-pp-da-ima-dareniya-ot-kriptobankata/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">rejected</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the rumors that he had close relations with Nexo and that the platform financially backed We Continue the Change. The allegations that Vasilev was hiding on an unknown island were also refuted as he talked in front of journalists in the center of Bulgaria&#8217;s capital &#8211; Sofia.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dnes.dir.bg/politika/asen-vasilev-za-aferata-nekso-mediyna-dimka-razsledvanite-shte-osadyat-balgariya" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">described</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Nexo saga as a &#8220;big media smoke,&#8221; predicting that the accused executives of the cryptocurrency platform could sue Bulgaria for undermining its reputation:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The final effect of these actions, what will happen, is most likely that Bulgaria will be condemned by those whose interests have been damaged, whom the prosecution is attacking, and that we will have to pay compensation from the budget.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nexo has previously claimed that the prosecutors&#8217; actions are against the law, vowing to take the case to court. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/Nexo/status/1613477470732173314" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">asserted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that it complied with all anti-money laundering policies, but some watchdogs have adopted the &#8220;kick first, ask questions later approach.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nexo-turmoil-causing-tension-in-bulgarian-parliament/" rel="nofollow">Nexo Turmoil Causing Tension in Bulgarian Parliament</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Taps $21K But is it Time for a Correction? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-taps-21k-but-is-it-time-for-a-correction-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 16:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233479</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price has gained significant bullish momentum and recovered from the drop caused by the FTX fallout. Yet, it has reached a robust resistance, and if the bulls push the price above it, a mid-term uptrend will become possible. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Bitcoin&#8217;s price continued its rally after overtaking the 50 [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has gained significant bullish momentum and recovered from the drop caused by the FTX fallout. Yet, it has reached a robust resistance, and if the bulls push the price above it, a mid-term uptrend will become possible.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3><strong>The Daily Chart</strong></h3>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price continued its rally after overtaking the 50 and 100-day moving averages. It has also surpassed the wedge&#8217;s upper trendline reaching a decisive resistance level with considerable momentum. Currently, the market faces the prior major pivot, a critical resistance level of roughly $21.5K.</p>
<p>If Bitcoin successfully surpasses the $21.5K level, the demand will be more likely to return to the market, and a new rally toward higher price levels may take place. In case of a breakout, the $25K price level will be the next barrier on Bitcoin&#8217;s path. Yet, the price has been surging impulsively, and it could enter a consolidation stage before the next impulsive rally.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233483" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233483" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-233483 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1601231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-Daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233483" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>In the 4-hour timeframe, it is evident that the price has fully recovered from the FTX crash and reached its prior major daily pivot at $21.5K. Major pivots are crucial levels in classic price action patterns, and moving above them could be a bullish sign of an uptrend.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the price has formed a double-top reversal pattern, a well-known bearish signal, and if it gets rejected, a leg down will be possible. Hence, considering the importance of this region, the upcoming price action should decide Bitcoin&#8217;s path in the mid-term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233484" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233484" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-233484 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1601232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233484" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-Chain Analysis</h2>
<p>By<strong>: </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><strong>Edris</strong></a></p>
<h3>Bitcoin Miners Position Index</h3>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s miners, who may be the most critical players in the network as they provide security and validate transactions, also play a crucial part in the market when it comes to supply and demand. Miners have large bags of BTC, and their selling or hodling affects the asset&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Over the last few months, miners have been distributing rather than accumulating or hodling, as the Bitcoin plunge has put pressure on most of them, forcing their hand to sell their coins to cover their costs of operation and with the recent surge in price, they chose to sell to the strength again.</p>
<p>This behavior is clearly visible on the Miners Position Index with a considerable spike and is very similar to April 2022, when Bitcoin was trading around the $46K mark and then began to fall rapidly. So, investors should be cautious as the bear market may still continue since the recent selling pressure could also lead to another crash in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233482" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233482" style="width: 1280px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-233482 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023.jpeg" alt="btc_miners_positions_index_chart_160123" width="1280" height="805" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023.jpeg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023-300x189.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023-1024x644.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023-768x483.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-MPI-Jan-16-2023-50x31.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233482" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-taps-21k-but-is-it-time-for-a-correction-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Taps $21K But is it Time for a Correction? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Su Zhu and Kyle Davies Raising $25M for a Crypto Exchange: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/su-zhu-and-kyle-davies-raising-25m-for-a-crypto-exchange-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233450</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Zu_Shu-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Zu_Shu-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The duo is best known as the co-founders of a defunct crypto hedge fund. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The two people behind the now-bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital are reportedly planning to launch a new exchange and want to raise $25 million from investors.</p>
<p>The name of the new project will be GTX and will have a somewhat controversial relation to FTX.</p>
<ul>
<li>Citing two pitch desks, The Block <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/202589/3ac-zhu-davies-new-crypto-exchange?utm_source=onecryptofeed&amp;utm_medium=social" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> that GTX&#8217;s name stems from the idea that &#8220;G comes after F,&#8221; in a clear affiliation with the failed crypto exchange. Recall that Su Zhu had multiple <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-drama-goes-on-sbf-and-zhu-su-trade-blows-over-alleged-media-control/" data-wpel-link="internal">comments</a> on FTX&#8217;s debacle and SBF&#8217;s actions at the time.</li>
<li>The $25 million Zhu and Davies are looking to raise now should help them launch the new exchange that will focus on trading in crypto bankruptcy claims.</li>
<li>The report also noted that the FTX creditors will transfer their claims on the former SBF-led exchange to GTX upon its launch.</li>
<li>3AC, once one of the largest crypto hedge funds, was among the first domino pieces to fall after the Terra ecosystem collapse last summer. Both founders have since been rather quiet on social media while also failing to cooperate with law enforcement agencies, according to some reports.</li>
<li>Zhu and Davies, however, refuted these rumors but were recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founders-su-zhu-kyle-davies-subpoenaed-in-bankruptcy-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">subpoenaed</a> in the bankruptcy case.</li>
<li>They began to address the community more frequently in the past several weeks, often times <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founder-zhu-su-accuses-dcg-of-being-criminally-fraudulent/" data-wpel-link="internal">blasting</a> other struggling crypto companies, such as Digital Currency Group.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/su-zhu-and-kyle-davies-raising-25m-for-a-crypto-exchange-report/" rel="nofollow">Su Zhu and Kyle Davies Raising $25M for a Crypto Exchange: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SOL Explodes 60% Weekly But How High Can it Reach? (Solana Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sol-explodes-60-weekly-but-how-high-can-it-reach-solana-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233415</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solana&#8217;s price doubled since the end of December, and bulls continue to be in control of the price action. Key Support levels: $20 Key Resistance levels: $27 SOL has managed to fully recover most of the drop that started in November 2022. At this rate, buyers seem eager to return its price back to pre-FTX [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Solana&#8217;s price doubled since the end of December, and bulls continue to be in control of the price action.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $20</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $27</strong></p>
<p>SOL has managed to fully recover most of the drop that started in November 2022. At this rate, buyers seem eager to return its price back to pre-FTX collapse levels soon.</p>
<p>To maintain this positive momentum, the cryptocurrency will have to break the key resistance at $27. Sellers continue to be absent, but if they return, then the key support is found at $20.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233417" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233417" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233417" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-18-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233417" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume:</strong> The buying volume is making higher highs. This is bullish. As long as it continues, there is no looking back for buyers.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI almost reached 90 points. While this shows buy pressure is high, it also serves as a warning that this level of momentum is hard to maintain for long.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD is bullish, but the histogram appears to turn flat. This may signal that buyers are losing strength.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233416" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233416" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233416" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-16_16-02-38-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233416" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SOL is bullish.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SOL Price</h2>
<p>Such parabolic moves are known to bring an equally powerful retrace. Therefore, buyers need to be on guard because, at any moment, the price could quickly reverse course and put sellers in charge. It&#8217;s important to remain vigilant.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sol-explodes-60-weekly-but-how-high-can-it-reach-solana-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">SOL Explodes 60% Weekly But How High Can it Reach? (Solana Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
