<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 21:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Sued for Insider Trading With Dogecoin Using &#8220;Publicity Stunts&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-sued-for-insider-trading-with-dogecoin-using-publicity-stunts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253649</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ElonMusk2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ElonMusk2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s tweets often influence Dogecoin’s price, but allegations from investors suggest that Musk traded around his social media activity. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tesla boss Elon Musk is guilty of insider trading against his followers using Dogecoin (DOGE), alleged memecoin investors in a court filing against the tech entrepreneur on Wednesday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The accusations are a follow-up to a $258 billion class action lawsuit filed by the same group in June 2022, accusing Musk and his companies of causing hundreds of billions in losses for Dogecoin holders.   </span></p>
<h2>Elon Musk Dogecoin Agenda</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per the </span><a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.581639/gov.uscourts.nysd.581639.74.1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">amended filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in a Manhattan federal court on May 31, Elon Musk engaged in “a deliberate course of carnival barking market manipulation,” through a “publicity circus” intended to pump Dogecoin’s price. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">These stunts include his </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sell-the-news-dogecoin-drops-20-after-elon-musk-snl/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">public appearances</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and social media activity hyping up  Dogecoin dating back to April 2019. These stunts boosted Dogecoin’s price by 36,000% to $0.70+ by May 2021. Today, DOGE trades 90% down from that high. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Musk’s pretense that promotion of Dogecoin was just well-meaning fun—not meant to be taken seriously—is not credible,” read the filing, labeling the tycoon an “apex predator,” and his millions of Twitter followers as prey. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The lawsuit noted that numerous studies have already demonstrated the effect of Elon Musk’s tweets on the price of Dogecoin. Indeed, Musk’s announcements that he would begin </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-spikes-15-as-elon-musk-says-spacex-will-soon-accept-it-for-merch-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">accepting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Dogecoin at SpaceX in 2021, and his </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-skyrockets-22-as-elon-musk-visited-twitter-hq-ahead-of-purchase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">visit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to Twitter HQ after taking over the company last year, have each contributed to DOGE’s changing price. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Musk exercised his influence again by changing Twitter’s blue bird logo to a picture of the Doge meme’s Shiba Inu for three days, helping </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-explodes-25-after-elon-musk-changes-twitter-icon-to-doge-meme/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pump</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the coin’s price by 30%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing added that Musk and Tesla traded profitably around the billionaire’s “intended moves,” citing blockchain records as evidence. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Specifically, the lawsuit claims to have tracked down a wallet address – DH5ya – allegedly belonged to Musk, and became the largest single holder of Dogecoin by February 2021. That wallet then sold millions of dollars worth of Dogecoin at multiple times throughout April 2021.</span></p>
<h2>Securities Fraud?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A key part of the lawsuit is the presupposition that Dogecoin is an unregistered security under existing standards from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Musk was founded by Dogecoin creators Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer back in 2013 – but they have remained uninvolved in the development of the project for years. Markus himself often jokes with Elon Musk on Twitter, both of whom often provide lighthearted commentary about crypto over Twitter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When the original lawsuit was filed last year, Musk’s lawyers said the lawsuit was fanciful. “There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for, or funny pictures about, a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion,&#8221; they said.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-sued-for-insider-trading-with-dogecoin-using-publicity-stunts/" rel="nofollow">Elon Musk Sued for Insider Trading With Dogecoin Using &#8220;Publicity Stunts&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Contracts for Institutional Investors on June 5 </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-launch-bitcoin-and-ether-futures-contracts-for-institutional-investors-on-june-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253535</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/coinbase_bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/coinbase_bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The move marks a shift in Coinbase’s focus away from retail trade, an area of increased regulatory scrutiny in recent months. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Popular crypto exchange Coinbase will launch Bitcoin and Ethereum futures contracts for institutional investors on June 5, the company said on its website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company will launch these products through CFTC-regulated Coinbase Derivative Exchange, promising lower fees than other US-regulated derivatives exchanges. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTI and ETI for Institutional Investors </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span></h2>
<p>Coinbase has partnered with leading FCMs (Futures Commission Merchants), brokers, and front-end providers to enable institutional clients seamless access to these contracts.</p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“The Coinbase Bitcoin (BTI) and Coinbase Ether (ETI) futures contracts will be accessible through leading third-party institutional futures commission merchants (FCMs) and brokers,” the <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-will-launch-institutional-sized-bitcoin-and" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a> said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To help investors manage their portfolios effectively, BTI and ETI will be available in 1 Bitcoin and 10 Ether contracts.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decision to launch these futures contracts followed the release of nano bitcoin (BIT) and nano Ether (ET) contracts earlier. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“With the launch of these institutional-sized USD-settled contracts, we look to empower institutional participants with greater precision in managing crypto exposure, expressing directional views, or tracking Bitcoin and Ether returns in a capital-efficient way,” Coinbase said. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase Looking Beyond US</span></h2>
<p>Over the past two months, Coinbase was in the news for exploring friendlier jurisdictions for its entire range of offerings. As part of this endeavor, it secured a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">license</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in Bermuda, where a crypto regulation has been in place since 2018.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Based in Bermuda, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> the Coinbase International Exchange for non-US institutional investors, a derivatives exchange offering perpetual futures contracts. Furthermore, Coinbase is believed to evaluate options in European Union and the UK for setting its base.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Although Coinbase says it’s committed to the US, its disillusionment with the world’s largest crypto market came recently when the regulators signaled that they might investigate the company’s staking services, calling them unregulated securities.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Coinbase has <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/we-asked-the-sec-for-reasonable-crypto-rules-for-americans-we-got-legal" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">refuted</a> these claims, the regulatory scrutiny of crypto firms in the US has become more intense in the past few months, especially after FTX’s collapse. With the prolonged downturn keeping crypto firms under check, big entities like Coinbase must look beyond the US to retain their leadership position in the crypto business. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-launch-bitcoin-and-ether-futures-contracts-for-institutional-investors-on-june-5/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Contracts for Institutional Investors on June 5 </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As the Meme Coin Craze Shows No Signs of Slowing Down, Here Are 3 Tokens That Could Explode Next</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-meme-coin-craze-shows-no-signs-of-slowing-down-here-are-3-tokens-that-could-explode-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253614</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin market has taken a hit in recent weeks, with most tokens suffering double-digit value drops. Investors are now looking elsewhere for returns potential, given the current state of meme coin stalwarts like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. However, despite this red wave, several tokens are withstanding the tide and producing stellar results – [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin market has taken a hit in recent weeks, with most tokens suffering double-digit value drops.</p>
<p>Investors are now looking elsewhere for returns potential, given the current state of meme coin stalwarts like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>
<p>However, despite this red wave, several tokens are withstanding the tide and producing stellar results – providing a glimmer of hope for meme coin enthusiasts.</p>
<h2>Waning Enthusiasm Hits the Meme Coin Market Hard</h2>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap reveals that total meme coin trading volume is down by 17% over the past day – highlighting the lack of excitement around these crypto assets.</p>
<p>Individual trading volumes are down across the board, with the main culprits being $DOGE, $SHIB, $PEPE, and $FLOKI. All four of these tokens have seen waning interest over the past week – with $DOGE being the only one providing signs of a reversal.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253617" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2-300x99.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Meme coins seem to be following the market trajectory set by big players like Bitcoin and Ethereum. Both of these coins have posted losses in the past few days, dragging down their peers.</p>
<p>Moreover, the buzz around the meme coin niche has mostly faded with the dramatic fall of popular tokens like $PEPE and $WOJAK.</p>
<p>Investors in these coins have opted to cash in rather than wait for price to bounce back – leading to the dramatic value drops experienced in recent weeks.</p>
<p>Finally, there has also been an evident lack of innovation within the space since the breakthrough of Pepe in mid-April. Although many copycat coins have entered the fray, none were able to match Pepe&#8217;s impact, prompting investors to return to more established cryptos.</p>
<p>All told, these factors paint a bleak picture for the meme coin niche in the short term.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Ignites Hope After Raising $2.7 Million</h2>
<p>Fortunately, several projects have begun to gain traction over the past week – with investors hopeful that they can spark the meme coin market back into life.</p>
<p>Leading the way in this regard is<a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a>, a brand-new meme coin from the creators of the ultra-successful Wall St Bulls NFT collection.</p>
<p>In 2021, this NFT collection made headlines when it sold out all 10,000 pieces in 32 minutes and raised $2.5 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">According</a> to OpenSea, 1,864 ETH worth of these NFTs have been traded since the collection launched – equating to over $3.5 million based on today’s exchange rate.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253618" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="305" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This collection&#8217;s incredible success led to the formation of a colossal community around Wall Street Memes, evidenced by the 523,000+ “degens” that follow the official Instagram account.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; community benefits from an indirect link to the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">WallStreetBets subreddit</a>. This subreddit played a significant role in the GameStop short squeeze, a market-rocking event two years ago</p>
<p>Now, Wall Street Memes&#8217; team is looking to give back to the community by launching the $WSM token – allowing holders to benefit as the community grows.</p>
<p>Early investors can now <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">buy $WSM tokens</a> through the Wall Street Memes presale, which has raised over $2.7 million in just one week.</p>
<p>Clearly, Wall Street Memes stands as a beacon of potential amidst the current meme coin gloom – making it an exciting time to be a $WSM investor.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>AiDoge Redefining Meme Coin Landscape After Selling Out $15m Presale</h2>
<p>Another meme coin that’s still making headway amidst the current market turmoil is<a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> AiDoge ($AI)</a>.</p>
<p>As its name suggests, AiDoge is an innovative meme coin that blends artificial intelligence (AI) concepts with a Doge-like theme – creating a unique and intriguing proposition for meme coin enthusiasts.</p>
<p>AiDoge’s flagship feature is its groundbreaking meme generator, which uses cutting-edge AI algorithms to create hilarious images using text-based prompts.</p>
<p>AiDoge users can easily capitalize on trending topics by instantly uploading these images to social media sites like Reddit and Twitter.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253619" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2-300x122.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Per the project’s <a href="https://aidoge.com/assets/documents/Aidoge_Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, users can also earn tokenized rewards by uploading their memes to AiDoge’s public wall, where they will be voted on by other community members.</p>
<p>Central to the AiDoge ecosystem is $AI – the project’s native transactional token.</p>
<p>Users must buy $AI to use the meme generator, although many eager investors opted to purchase tokens through the project’s presale phase to gain financial exposure to AiDoge’s growth.</p>
<p>This led to AiDoge’s presale hitting its funding target of $14.9 million – although the development team is offering one final chance for investors to get involved before $AI is listed on major exchanges on June 19.</p>
<p>Investors can <a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">buy $AI</a> through the project&#8217;s website for $0.0000336, which will be the token&#8217;s official listing price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Website</strong></a></p>
<h2>Baby Doge Coin Acts as Beacon of Resilience for Investors</h2>
<p>Lastly, Baby Doge Coin is also performing remarkably well, making it one of the few meme coins to post gains in the past week.</p>
<p>Per CoinGecko, Baby Doge Coin is up by 0.5% over the past seven days. Although this is a minor value increase, it’s a far cry from the sharp price drops experienced by most projects in the meme coin niche.</p>
<p>Moreover, $BABYDOGE is now the fifth-largest meme coin in the world, according to CoinMarketCap, boasting a market cap of nearly $300 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253620" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="281" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-300x140.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Naturally, most of the hype surrounding Baby Doge Coin is fuelled by its branding. Although it has no direct link to the Dogecoin project, many meme coin investors are opting to purchase tokens to capitalize on the association with $DOGE.</p>
<p>However, Baby Doge Coin is distinguishing itself with a focus on real-world utility. The project offers a custom-built DEX that allows community members to swap any token on the Binance Smart Chain.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the steady performance and rise in market cap of $BABYDOGE indicate that it&#8217;s captured the attention of meme coin lovers – making it an intriguing contender within the market.</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-meme-coin-craze-shows-no-signs-of-slowing-down-here-are-3-tokens-that-could-explode-next/" rel="nofollow">As the Meme Coin Craze Shows No Signs of Slowing Down, Here Are 3 Tokens That Could Explode Next</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Scam Token &#8216;OPENAI&#8217; Promoted On OpenAI CTO&#8217;s Twitter Account</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/scam-token-openai-promoted-on-openai-ctos-twitter-account/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253632</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ChatGPT_Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ChatGPT_Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The ChatGPT creators did not launch a crypto token, despite brief claims from a company executive’s Twitter page.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Twitter account belonging to OpenAI CTO Mira Murati was hacked on Thursday, and used to promote a scam crypto token supposedly backed by the company. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The tweet stayed online for roughly an hour, garnering 80,000 views from platform users before being taken down. </span></p>
<h2>Another Scam AI Token</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The hacker promoted a fraudulent airdrop for ‘OPENAI’ token, described as a “groundbreaking token driven by artificial intelligence-based language models.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Mira Murati’s (CTO at <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@OpenAI</a>) account has been hacked and is being used to promote crypto scams. The tweet is gaining 1k+ impressions per minute. <a href="https://t.co/VekeRV1xDT" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/VekeRV1xDT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Max Rdlb (@maxrdlb) <a href="https://twitter.com/maxrdlb/status/1664441810201219072?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">The tweet provided a link to a well-edited phishing website that appeared like a direct copy of an actual project called </span><a href="https://www.chaingpt.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">ChainGPT</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – an AI chatbot for crypto and blockchain information. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The copied version, however, included some minor tweaks – such as a prompt for visitors to connect their crypto wallet. Reports suggest that the site lured investors into transaction signing requests, with which the hacker could transfer NFTs and ERC-20 tokens from the victim’s wallet. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The fake tweet from Murati’s account used restricted replies, making it more difficult for followers to warn readers that the post was fraudulent. Though it’s now removed, Murati has not released any clarifying statement from her account. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to </span><a href="https://twitter.com/realScamSniffer/status/1664579191352987649" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Scam Sniffer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the hack was perpetrated by a repeat offender in the art of phishing scams named “Pink Drainer.” Netting $110,000 from this particular hack, the scammer has already drained $1.8 million from over 500 victims since May 30.</span></p>
<h2>Twitter-Based Crypto Scams</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto Twitter is notorious for phishing scams perpetrated using spam bots, which frequently clog reply sections for notable industry influencers. Elon Musk promised to remedy the issue partially through Twitter’s new verification program.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many such scams work by impersonating high-profile personalities. One of the most famous scams occurred in July 2020, when over 130 prominent accounts including Elon Musk, Joe Biden, Barrack Obama, and others were </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/breaking-down-twitters-hack-blaming-bitcoin-hidden-messages-and-insiders/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">hacked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, inviting users to send BTC to a certain address, and promising a 2:1 return. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Social media scams of the like have worked before: A fake Michael Saylor </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-worth-1-1-million-sent-to-a-confirmed-michael-saylor-giveaway-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">phishing scam</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> netted the perpetrator over $1.1 million from a victim in January 2022, on-chain data showed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We report them every 15 minutes and they are taken down after a few hours, but the scammers just launch more,” said Saylor at the time.  </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/scam-token-openai-promoted-on-openai-ctos-twitter-account/" rel="nofollow">Scam Token &#8216;OPENAI&#8217; Promoted On OpenAI CTO&#8217;s Twitter Account</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto and Fiat Stored on Apps Might Not Be Insured by The FDIC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-and-fiat-stored-on-apps-might-not-be-insured-by-the-fdic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 18:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253540</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FDIC-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/FDIC-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the CFPB, funds and assets stored on mobile apps may not benefit from deposit protection in case of bankruptcy.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a report recently published by the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) of America, regulators warn that crypto and fiat held on mobile apps may not actually benefit from the FDIC’s policy of insuring up to $250k per depositor.</p>
<h2>Non-Bank Services Not Covered</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.consumerfinance.gov/data-research/research-reports/issue-spotlight-analysis-of-deposit-insurance-coverage-on-funds-stored-through-payment-apps/full-report/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, an unfortunate consequence of the rise of payment services and apps such as PayPal or Venmo is that consumers are often given the impression that in the event of the platform going bankrupt, the government will reimburse user funds stuck with these services.</p>
<p>However, this is not the case. For funds to be reimbursed by the FDIC or NCUA, they would have to be deposited at an FDIC or NCUA-insured bank. Plenty of payment services do not hold user funds in escrow at one of these banks. Often, these payment services invest user funds into stocks and bonds as a way of generating profit in order to keep the service free or low-cost for the end user.</p>
<p>The report notes that this aspect is often <a href="https://www.consumerfinance.gov/data-research/research-reports/issue-spotlight-analysis-of-deposit-insurance-coverage-on-funds-stored-through-payment-apps/full-report/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">obfuscated</a> by the TOUs of the payment platforms.</p>
<h2>Platforms Not Obliged to Report Deposits</h2>
<p>Another key difference between payment services and banks is that the banks are required by federal law to provide detailed information on customer deposits to the FDIC and other regulators. Payment services, on the other hand, have no such requirement.</p>
<blockquote><p>“While the core service of nonbank payment platforms is to provide a mechanism to send funds from one person to another, these apps also facilitate a growing set of related financial products and services, including offering debit cards, credit cards, BNPL loans, international remittances, and crypto asset transactions. [&#8230;] While banks and credit unions are required to provide detailed information on their total deposits on a regular basis, these entities currently have no such requirement under federal law.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Although the importance of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/9-must-tips-securing-crypto-wallet/" data-wpel-link="internal">self-custody</a> is repeatedly reinforced to the crypto community, the failure of FTX – which was explicitly named in the report – has also prompted the CFPB to remind consumers that they may be left high and dry if they do not secure their own assets.</p>
<p>Despite the good deals some services offer when buying crypto, always remember to practice self-custody when it comes to your crypto stash.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of History</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-and-fiat-stored-on-apps-might-not-be-insured-by-the-fdic/" rel="nofollow">Crypto and Fiat Stored on Apps Might Not Be Insured by The FDIC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Wins No Matter What the Fed Does: Arthur Hayes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wins-no-matter-what-the-fed-does-arthur-hayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 17:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253606</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto essayist believes Bitcoin’s bull market will fully begin by late 2023, irrespective of the central bank’s actions. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Will the Federal Reserve stop raising interest rates next month? For Bitcoin investors, the answer may not actually matter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes, Bitcoin’s price and inflation will rise in tandem precisely because of hawkish central bank policy – contrary to what modern monetary theory would suggest. </span></p>
<h2>How Rising Rates Will Increase Inflation</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a Thursday </span><a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/patience-is-beautiful/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">blog post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> titled “Patience is Beautiful,” Hayes outlined why the economy’s ever-expanding debt-to-GDP ratio will cause traditional economic “laws” to “break down.” This includes the idea that rising interest rates cause the money supply and inflation to fall. He writes:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Regardless of which path the Fed chooses, be it to hike or cut rates, they will accelerate inflation and catalyze a general rush for the exits from the parasitic fiat monetary financial system.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Data from </span><a href="https://www.usdebtclock.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">US Debt Clock</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows that the United States government is currently $31.8 trillion in debt. That’s a far cry from the nation’s $26.4 trillion GDP and its relatively meager $4.6 trillion yearly tax revenue. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">President Joe Biden and House Speaker Kevin McCarthy recently unveiled a draft bill to avert an incoming </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-happen-to-bitcoin-if-the-us-debt-ceiling-cracks-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">debt crisis</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> after the nation reached its $31.4 trillion debt limit in January. The deal would suspend the debt ceiling entirely until 2025, but require a number of cost-cutting measures to ensure it doesn’t spiral out of hand until then. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hayes predicted that the debt ceiling will indeed be lifted sometime this summer, at which point the US Treasury “must issue trillions of dollars worth of debt.” This would drive up interest rates on short-term government debt, incentivizing bank depositors to withdraw their holdings en masse as they are incentivized to lend to the government, rather than the bank. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As such, the Federal Reserve will be forced to cut rates, making banks profitable again, but causing inflation to spike as a consequence. Alternatively, the Fed could keep raising rates – but this would only incentivize more bank failures, which will be paid off by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation with more money printing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Gold, Bitcoin, AI tech stocks, etc. will all be beneficiaries of this “wealth” that is printed by the government and handed out as interest,” Hayes said. </span></p>
<h2>Stay Patient, Says Hayes</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the short term, Hayes said he expects Bitcoin to hold firm – but that a bull market will likely begin in the late third/early fourth quarter of the year. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Money printing, yield curve control, bank failures, etc. will all come to pass,” he wrote. “Between now and then, chill the fuck out… “Because come this fall, you better be strapped into your trading spaceship, ready for liftoff.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last month, Hayes </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-bitmex-head-arthur-hayes-predicts-no-all-time-high-for-bitcoin-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> he doesn’t expect Bitcoin to rise to a new all-time high ($70,000) before the end of the year, but that 2024 is “gonna be a good year.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">His opinion mirrors that of the on-chain market analysis firm CryptoQuant, which told CryptoPotato in April that institutional investors are </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-intend-to-buy-bitcoin-in-late-2023-interview-with-cryptoquant/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">eyeing Bitcoin</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for later this year. A new all-time high, they said, could be reached by Q2 2024. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wins-no-matter-what-the-fed-does-arthur-hayes/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Wins No Matter What the Fed Does: Arthur Hayes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Leads With 11% Gains, Bitcoin Struggles With $27K, Injective (INJ) Explodes: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-leads-with-11-gains-bitcoin-struggles-with-27k-injective-inj-explodes-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253549</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple is the best performer from the large-cap cryptocurrencies over the past seven days, but Injective (NJ) stole the show altogether.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past seven days saw the cryptocurrency market increase, but it wasn&#8217;t something particularly considerable. Bitcoin remained rather stagnant and managed an increase of slightly more than one percent. However, there were those who exploded and led the market&#8217;s recovery. Namely, XRP. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<p>Starting with the BTC price &#8211; it wasn&#8217;t very impressive during the last week. In fact, the primary cryptocurrency only booked an increase of slightly more than one percent and is currently unable to convincingly claim the $27K level. The week saw some volatility when BTC soared above $28K, but the buyers were unable to maintain the pressure, and sellers ultimately took over, pushing the price back to where it&#8217;s currently trading.</p>
<p>With Ripple&#8217;s XRP, though &#8211; it was a different story. The cryptocurrency exploded by over 11% in the past seven days. It seems that investors are starting to price in a potential victory for Ripple in the case against the Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p>But this wasn&#8217;t even the most impressive performance of the week.</p>
<p>Injective (INJ) is this week&#8217;s top performer. It&#8217;s up a whopping 25% in a market that&#8217;s otherwise rather uncertain. The altcoin has been one of the best performers throughout the year.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, the week was also important for stablecoins. USDC launched on Arbitrum, while Tether announced that it will launch a sustainable Bitcoin mining operation in the country of Uruguay.</p>
<p>In an interesting bit, we also pinned the two most popular AI-based chatbots &#8211; ChatGPT and Google&#8217;s Bard &#8211; against each other. We <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-ethereum-flip-bitcoin-we-put-chatgpt-and-googles-bard-against-each-other/" data-wpel-link="internal">asked</a> both of them if Ethereum will flip Bitcoin, and their answers were quite entertaining.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth noting that one more crypto heavyweight is considering expanding outside of the United States. Gemini is considering the UAE as a new destination as the regulatory environment in the US isn&#8217;t getting any better.</p>
<p>All in all, the week was relatively productive in terms of price developments, and the market seems to be moving out of its recent slumber. That said, it&#8217;s important to see how the next few weeks will turn out and if the positive sentiment will continue growing.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,182B | 24H Vol: $36B | BTC Dominance: 44.1%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $26,922 (+1.2%) | ETH: $1,881 (+3%) | BNB: $304 (-0.6%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253596" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" alt="xrp_mu_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>What Would Happen to Bitcoin If The US Debt Ceiling Cracks (Opinion). </strong>Despite the fact that an initial deal was reached, the issues surrounding the US debt are still a growing concern among investors. Here&#8217;s a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-happen-to-bitcoin-if-the-us-debt-ceiling-cracks-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">thought</a> on what could happen to BTC if the debt ceiling cracks.</p>
<p><strong>Tether to Launch Sustainable Bitcoin Mining Operations in Uruguay. </strong>Tether, the issuer of the largest stablecoin &#8211; USDT, will be launching sustainable Bitcoin mining operations in the country of Uruguay. The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-to-launch-sustainable-bitcoin-mining-operations-in-uruguay/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> this on May 30th.</p>
<p><strong>USDC Stablecoin to Be Launched Natively on Layer 2 Scaling Solution Arbitrum. </strong>The USDC stablecoin will be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-stablecoin-to-be-launched-natively-on-layer-2-scaling-solution-arbitrum/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> natively on Arbitrum. The latter is a layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum. The stablecoin will be considered the official version of USDC for the Arbitrum ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Gemini Eyes UAE Expansion Amid US Uncertainty, Crypto.com Gets MPI License in Singapore. </strong>Gemini is also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/" data-wpel-link="internal">considering</a> expansion outside of the US. In particular, the platform is looking at UAE. The reason seems to be the growing regulatory burden and uncertainty in the US.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Mining Difficulty Exceeds 50T for the First Time. </strong>Bitcoin&#8217;s mining difficulty achieved an all-time high. The latest difficulty adjustment <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-exceeds-50t-for-the-first-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">happened</a> on May 31st and added 3.4% to the total mining difficulty.</p>
<p><strong>Will Ethereum Flip Bitcoin? We Put ChatGPT and Google’s Bard Against Each Other. </strong>In an interesting debate, we pinned two of the most popular AIs against each other. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-ethereum-flip-bitcoin-we-put-chatgpt-and-googles-bard-against-each-other/" data-wpel-link="internal">Here&#8217;s</a> what ChatGPT and Google&#8217;s Bard think on whether Ethereum will flip Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Litecoin – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-jun-2-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-ltc/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-leads-with-11-gains-bitcoin-struggles-with-27k-injective-inj-explodes-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">Ripple Leads With 11% Gains, Bitcoin Struggles With $27K, Injective (INJ) Explodes: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz Says Crypto is Lackadaisical Right Now &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mike-novogratz-says-crypto-is-lackadaisical-right-now-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 12:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253560</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/MikeNovogratz-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/MikeNovogratz-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Galaxy Digital boss believes crypto adoption is still on the rise despite declining interest from institutional investors in the industry. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Novogratz, the founder and CEO of Galaxy Digital, believes the crypto space is lackadaisical right now due to low participation from institutional investors.</p>
<p>During an <a href="https://youtu.be/nj51qbQ_VSs" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with CNBC, the American investor said the market lacks enthusiasm as most of the recent activities in the space are coming from retail buyers while large-scale players are withdrawing.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Quite frankly, crypto is lackadaisical, I&#8217;d say. There&#8217;s a constant bid from retail. We&#8217;re seeing it through all the platforms, and there&#8217;s not a lot of institutional excitement right now and so the dog days of summer started early in crypto. Does it make me thrilled? That&#8217;s just the reality,&#8221; Novogratz said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Lack of Enthusiasm From Institutional Investors</h2>
<p>Novogratz&#8217;s statement <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-133-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-d1962cf39cea" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">resounds</a> a May 31 report from CoinShares on weekly crypto asset flows, which disclosed that digital asset investment products saw outflows of $39 million from institutional investors for the sixth consecutive week, totaling $272 million.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutional-crypto-funds-see-5th-consecutive-week-of-outflows-coinshares/" data-wpel-link="internal">remained</a> the focus of the outflows, with a total of $11 million, while Ethereum lost $5.9 million in outflows. Algorand, Litecoin, and Uniswap funds also saw outflows of $8 million, $500,000, and $200,000, respectively.</p>
<p>The U.S. led the flows, with Germany and Switzerland following closely behind. Altogether, 0.8% of assets under management left the crypto market last week.</p>
<h2>Adoption Still On the Rise</h2>
<p>Despite the declining institutional adoption, Novogratz noted that &#8220;interesting&#8221; things are still happening in the crypto space. The Galaxy Digital CEO pointed out the growing adoption of cryptocurrencies in Asia, particularly in Hong Kong and China.</p>
<p>The largest Chinese social media app, WeChat, recently enabled Bitcoin price quote indexes in its search queries. The platform&#8217;s 1.3 billion users can now access the digital asset&#8217;s price quotes despite the current <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peoples-bank-of-china-with-a-broader-crackdown-on-bitcoin-and-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">crypto ban</a> in the country.</p>
<p>In addition, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-confirms-crypto-commitment-at-web3-conference-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Hong Kong</a> now allows retail crypto trading through regulated exchanges. The Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium has approved the top 30 cryptocurrencies by market cap for listing to enable easy reviews and compliance from the exchanges.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There&#8217;s a couple of things that happened today which are pretty interesting. WeChat just enabled Bitcoin and crypto trading on the biggest single platform in the world. That&#8217;s a pretty big deal. Hong Kong is officially allowing crypto trading for retail customers through regulated exchanges for the first time, and so we&#8217;re seeing Asian adoption,&#8221; Novogratz added.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mike-novogratz-says-crypto-is-lackadaisical-right-now-heres-why/" rel="nofollow">Mike Novogratz Says Crypto is Lackadaisical Right Now &#8211; Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Centralized Crypto Exchange S-Trade Delivers Simplicity and Security</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-centralized-crypto-exchange-s-trade-delivers-simplicity-and-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 12:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253581</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1200630_-_4_1685690140NXDES1UDdU.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1200630_-_4_1685690140NXDES1UDdU.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, June 2nd, 2023] S-Trade, a new crypto exchange with a range of innovative features, has launched with the goal of simplifying digital asset trading. It provides solutions catered to a wide range of traders, including those who favor a hands-on approach as well as those who prefer to use trading [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, June 2nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://s-trade.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">S-Trade</a>, a new crypto exchange with a range of innovative features, has launched with the goal of simplifying digital asset trading. It provides solutions catered to a wide range of traders, including those who favor a hands-on approach as well as those who prefer to use trading bots.</p>
<p>S-Trade is a centralized cryptocurrency exchange where users can buy, sell and store digital assets, as well as access more than 100 trading pairs and 24 fiat assets. The exchange offers a full suite of robust trading features, including secure deposits/withdrawals; crypto loans; margin trading; options; futures contracts; new token listings; dual currency options; and trading bots.</p>
<p>A service token plays an important role in the S-Trade ecosystem. It can be used to pay for services as well as a tool for hedging risks during a drop in the market. Holders of the exchange’s token can also enjoy other benefits such as participation in the exchange’s cashback system; participation in voting; reduced fees; personalized offers and increased affiliate rates.</p>
<p>S-Trade incorporates low trading fees, which reduce further when traders make use of the exchange’s native token. There’s also an automated trading facility that can increase efficiency and maximize profits. S-Trade’s ready-to-use trading bots can be customized to meet the goals of each user. These are simple and intuitive to set up, so they’re a perfect way for crypto newbies to start making money without any prior trading knowledge.</p>
<p>Other services offered by S-Trade include the ability to participate in staking and crypto lending, replenishing the liquidity pool, and receiving interest on profits.</p>
<p>S-Trade’s mission is to provide users with all the necessary tools and services for managing and interacting with any digital asset, as well as to make engaging with cryptocurrency understandable for everyone. It aims to achieve this by providing a simple, easy-to-use interface and offering proprietary tech and features that allow users to copy trades.</p>
<h2>About S-Trade</h2>
<p>S-Trade mission To provide users with all the necessary tools and products for managing digital assets. We strive to make the interaction with cryptocurrencies simple and understandable for everyone. The convenience of users and the security of their assets are the priority of S-Trade.</p>
<p><a href="https://s-trade.com/about-us" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/STrade_Exchange" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-centralized-crypto-exchange-s-trade-delivers-simplicity-and-security/" rel="nofollow">New Centralized Crypto Exchange S-Trade Delivers Simplicity and Security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DPAT Raises Private Funding To Enhance Web3.0 Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253566</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Image_6_1200x720_16856963850g8ESLMpnA.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Image_6_1200x720_16856963850g8ESLMpnA.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Accra, Ghana, June 2nd, 2023] DPAT, the first Web3 crowdsourcing platform designed to connect investors with real estate and infrastructure opportunities in major African cities, has announced the launch of its highly anticipated updated roadmap and revamped website. Positioning itself as a bridge to new emerging economies, the Ethereum-backed Web3 investment platform [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Accra, Ghana, June 2nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://dpatoken.io/?utm_source=syndicated&amp;utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_campaign=private_funding&amp;utm_id=dpat" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>DPAT</strong></a><strong>, the first Web3 </strong>crowdsourcing platform designed to connect investors with real estate and infrastructure opportunities in major African cities, has announced the launch of its highly anticipated updated roadmap and revamped website.</p>
<p>Positioning itself as a bridge to new emerging economies, the Ethereum-backed Web3 investment platform is set to attract investors, crypto advocates, and entrepreneurs alike by offering a say in what gets built, by whom, and for who in markets where they believe success is only lacking the right type of funding.</p>
<p>The road map for the Direct Property Africa Token (DPAT) project demonstrates its scope and endurance. Initially, focusing on 15 cities in 12 countries to establish systems, processes, and legal precedents. The project team will reinvest the funds received to support the ongoing development of custom solutions such as a seamless marketplace checkout and simple developer onboarding processes.</p>
<blockquote><p>Project Lead for DPAT, Mustafa A said: “The feedback from our community matters to us, and we have taken that into account. We continue to build applications with the end user in mind and revamping our website and processes to provide an enhanced user experience is a sign of things to come.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Beyond the new website built to make it easier to navigate and access project information, the marketplace will help developers smoothly list their projects and engage with their community by offering rewards and equity-based NFTs to swiftly raise capital at prices that are competitive with banks and other traditional lenders. To further show its support to the African real estate industry, DPAT will work closely with agents and developers in project cities to increase knowledge, simplicity, and security through the implementation and integration of Web3 technology to digitize and update current business models.</p>
<p>The project is currently in its presale phase and shortly after completion in August, Direct Property Africa will roll out the NFT crowdsourcing marketplace and increase its core team. DPAT will initially launch on Uniswap and list on tier 1 centralized exchanges a few weeks later. With an ambitious road map, DPAT is on track to disrupt how developers finance projects and the community access African assets. All while showcasing a different side and image of the continent.</p>
<h2>About Direct Property Africa Token (DPAT)</h2>
<p>Direct Property Africa is a Web3 real estate and infrastructure ecosystem, including a crowdsourcing marketplace for local developers to raise funding for projects in major African cities like Cape Town, Lagos, and Accra with fractional ownership using asset-backed equity NFTs. DPAT is the utility token of the Direct Property Africa ecosystem offering rewards and privileges to holders.</p>
<p>Learn more about Direct Property Africa Token at <a href="https://dpatoken.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://dpatoken.io/</a></p>
<p>Join the conversation on DPATs <a href="https://discord.gg/u2dgVqUYun" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a>, <a href="https://t.me/dpatokencommunity" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> and follow on <a href="https://twitter.com/dpatoken" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> for latest project updates.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dpat-raises-private-funding-to-enhance-web3-0-ecosystem/" rel="nofollow">DPAT Raises Private Funding To Enhance Web3.0 Ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
