<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 02:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Acquires Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-acquires-indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 02:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229446</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/binance-tokocrypto.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/binance-tokocrypto.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This latest move makes it possible for Binance to operate legally in Indonesia after being banned by its authorities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto winter is proving to be unbearable for some, but other businesses enjoy the cold weather. Binance is taking advantage of the current market conditions to expand into the Asian market by acquiring its third licensed crypto exchange.</p>
<p>This Dec. 19, Binance confirmed that it became the majority shareholder of Indonesian cryptocurrency exchange Tokocrypto, appointing a new CEO following the resignation of Pang Xue Kai, its founder and now former CEO.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.cnbcindonesia.com/tech/20221219165022-37-398232/binance-caplok-tokocrypto-tunjuk-ceo-baru" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by CNBC Indonesia, Binance plans to acquire all of Tokocrypto&#8217;s shares in a phased manner to operate legally in the country, as the exchange has all regulatory permits from the Commodity Futures Trading Regulatory Agency (BAPPEBTI).</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that Binance has been investing in Tokocrypto since 2020, so it had a long and close relationship with the Indonesian exchange.</p>
<h2>The Best Outcome for Tokyocrypto</h2>
<p>Pang Xue Kai, who will become a member of Tokocrypto&#8217;s Board of Commissioners, praised Binance&#8217;s acquisition, stating that the Asian giant has contributed a lot to helping Tokocrypto enter the Indonesian digital market.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Tokocrypto came from our idea more than four years ago and I am very proud to see every growth, achievement and contribution that the company has made to advance Indonesia&#8217;s digital economy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Pang Xue Kai added that this decision was &#8220;carefully&#8221; made with the future of the exchange in mind to take advantage of all the growth opportunities Binance can offer to build an additional physical trading platform for crypto assets.</p>
<p>Yudhono Rawis, Tokocrypto&#8217;s interim CEO, regretted that they had to downsize the company&#8217;s team but stressed that it was the best decision in order to overcome the challenging macroeconomic conditions affecting the global market.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It is regrettable that we have had to reduce the size of the company to ensure we remain in a good position to cope with the uncertain macroeconomic conditions and we extend our sincerest apologies to the affected employees.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance Expands Into the Asian Market</h2>
<p>Binance is branching out into the Asian market by acquiring other crypto exchanges, avoiding the tedious licensing processes that have recently become more demanding following the bankruptcy of several crypto exchanges and investment funds, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-arrows-capital-ordered-into-liquidation-by-a-birtish-virgin-islands-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">Three Arrows Capital</a>, Voyager Digital, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX</a>, and Alameda Research, among many others.</p>
<p>In July 2021, the Malaysian Securities Commission banned Binance from operating in the country. Still, in March this year, CZ&#8217;s exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-returns-to-malaysia-with-strategic-investment-in-mx-global/" data-wpel-link="internal">acquired Mx Global,</a> a business registered in Malaysia, allowing Binance to run in that country legally.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-strengthens-japanese-presence-acquires-a-locally-regulated-exchange/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by CryptoPotato, Binance&#8217;s most recent acquisition in Asia was Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC), a Japanese exchange regulated by Japan&#8217;s Financial Services Agency (FSA). Japan also<a href="https://www.fsa.go.jp/policy/virtual_currency02/Binance2_keikokushilyo.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> banned Binance</a> four years ago.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-acquires-indonesian-exchange-tokyocrypto/" rel="nofollow">Binance Acquires Indonesian Exchange Tokyocrypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alexander Hoeptner With Details on BitMEX Wrongful Termination Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alexander-hoeptner-with-details-on-bitmex-wrongful-termination-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMEX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229389</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/alex-hoeptner.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/alex-hoeptner.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The court filing argued that Höptner's termination was "wholly wrongful and without basis."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The court filing argued that Höptner&#8217;s termination was &#8220;wholly wrongful and without basis.&#8221;</p>
<p>Former BitMEX Chief Alexander Höptner has sued his former employer for $3.4 million for breach of agreement and wrongful termination. This includes $2.4 million for his second-year bonus and smaller amounts for remaining wages, relocation expenses, and housing.</p>
<p>The claim, filed by Höptner&#8217;s legal representatives &#8211; Kelvin Chia Partnership &#8211; with Singapore&#8217;s High Court, alleges BitMEX of conducting a &#8220;baseless&#8221; internal investigation against him to avoid payment of salaries and bonuses.</p>
<ul>
<li>The investigation in question is centered primarily around his several relocations to Hong Kong, Singapore, and Germany.</li>
<li>The ousted CEO said that he was accused of misappropriating company funds. The filing stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There were no objections and/or concerns raised as to the Claimant’s relocation and/or the costs that was to be incurred by the HDR Group in respect of the same.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>However, Höptner was informed by BitMEX that the company might not pay his second-year bonus or reimburse for his relocation as a result of an &#8220;extensive cost-cutting and restructuring program that involved numerous layoffs.&#8221;</li>
<li>However, BitMEX co-founders Arthur Hayes and Samuel Reed allegedly launched an investigation into his expenses in late September, according to the court filing.</li>
<li>The following month, the derivatives platform informed the exec of his termination in a letter citing the investigation accusing him of &#8220;dishonestly misappropriate some $230,000 of the Group&#8217;s funds to fund his personal and unauthorized relocation from Hong Kong to Germany.&#8221;</li>
<li>These allegations barred Höptner from being entitled to any further payments.</li>
<li>It was earlier <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitmex-ceo-alexander-hoptner-steps-down-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that the exec stepped down as the CEO less than two years after replacing Hayes. His role was later filled in by Stephan Lutz.</li>
<li><em>CryptoPotato </em>received commentary on behalf of the former executive:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>After being brought on board in late 2020, in partnership with my executive team and the board, I developed an aggressive strategy to scale and diversify the company. We were very much on track, which made the actions of the founders even more confusing to me. I honestly think that no matter how well my team and I delivered, the founders would have always found a way to reinsert themselves into the day-to-day operations of the company.</p>
<p>At the direction of the founders and the board, I put my life on hold to relocate multiple times as required by the company. I’m disappointed that it has gotten to the point that legal proceedings are necessary, but I’ve been left with no choice.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alexander-hoeptner-with-details-on-bitmex-wrongful-termination-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">Alexander Hoeptner With Details on BitMEX Wrongful Termination Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>If People Withdrew Everything from Binance US, We Would Still Have Millions in Assets, CEO Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/if-people-withdrew-everything-from-binance-us-we-would-still-have-millions-in-assets-ceo-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 22:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229436</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Binance_US_Lawsuit.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Binance_US_Lawsuit.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance US said customer assets are backed 1:1, and that the company is subject to regular audits. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance US chief Brian Shroder assured his followers on Monday that his exchange is prepared to process every last withdraw customer withdrawal – unlike certain competitors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">He also expanded on his company’s successful bid to purchase Voyager’s assets worth $1.02 billion and bring an end to the defunct crypto lender’s bankruptcy proceedings as soon as possible. </span></p>
<h2>Replacing FTX US</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a <a href="https://twitter.com/BrianShroder/status/1604825059813920770" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter thread</a> on Monday, Shroder confirmed that Voyager’s 3.5 million customers will soon be able to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-agrees-to-buy-voyager-digital-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">access their funds</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on the Binance US platform. Customers have been unable to access their accounts since July, although the company received court approval to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-digital-given-green-light-to-return-customer-funds-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">return</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> some funds to investors the following month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Shroder, their bid will not involve liquidating customers&#8217; digital assets for cash, allowing to retain their crypto. He added that the company always maintains 1:1 reserves on customer deposits, is subject to regular audits, does not offer margin trading or engage in proprietary trading, and holds no corporate debt. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Binance.US is well capitalized: our assets exceed our liabilities,” he wrote. “All of our customers could withdraw their assets tomorrow, which is their right &amp; we would still have hundreds of millions of current assets.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to FTX’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">bankruptcy lawyer</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the rival exchange went insolvent due to engaging in many of the activities Shroder listed – including margin trading with customer assets at Alameda Research. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While its former boss, Sam Bankman-Fried, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-says-ftx-us-should-be-solvent-unsure-why-withdrawals-not-enabled/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claims</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> FTX US is still entirely solvent, the exchange was included in the bankruptcy proceedings. That left Voyager absent the previous winner of the bid for its assets, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-us-wins-bid-to-acquire-bankrupt-lender-voyagers-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">valued</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> at $1.4 billion in October. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We will do everything in our power to speed up the legal and court approval process,” continued Shroder. “Current target, pending court approvals, is to provide users access to their assets in March, 2023.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance VS Binance US</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As with FTX US, Binance US purports to operate independently from its international variant. Its claim to regular audits contrasts with those of Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, who has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-on-audits-ftx-the-2-1-billion-sbf-buyout-in-2021-and-recent-withdrawal-spree/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claimed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that audits are difficult to come by for crypto firms. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Binance underwent a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-crypto-com-auditor-mazars-group-pauzes-work-with-crypto-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">proof of reserves</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> analysis this month, the firm responsible abandoned its crypto services last week due to misunderstandings about what their reports were being publicly presented. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Monday, Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ceo-will-consider-massive-share-buyback-if-sec-lawsuit-fails/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">denied</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the idea that crypto exchanges can’t secure audits if they try to. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/if-people-withdrew-everything-from-binance-us-we-would-still-have-millions-in-assets-ceo-says/" rel="nofollow">If People Withdrew Everything from Binance US, We Would Still Have Millions in Assets, CEO Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The United States Might Need to Ban Crypto, Says Banking Committee Chief</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-united-states-might-need-to-ban-crypto-says-banking-committee-chief/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 20:35:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Ban]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229428</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/gettyimages-1196885365-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/gettyimages-1196885365-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Senator Sherrod Brown thinks banning crypto could be an option for addressing all of the technology’s related risks. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">U.S. Senator and chairman of the Senate Banking Committee, Sherrod Brown (D-OH), spoke on Sunday about what actions regulators need to take after the implosion of FTX. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">He suggested that crypto may be something that “ought to be banned” if not for the risk of sending the industry offshore. </span></p>
<h2>Banning Crypto</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Speaking with NBC’s Chuck Todd on </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gzqJahHvhsY&amp;list=PL0tDb4jw6kPzzvIBrLUGHUkVkj3oIz-eY&amp;index=3&amp;ab_channel=NBCNews" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><i><span style="font-weight: 400">Meet the Press</span></i></a><i><span style="font-weight: 400">, </span></i><span style="font-weight: 400">Brown agreed that Sam Bankman-Fried – FTX’s former and disgraced boss – used political favor and donations to create an illusion of credibility around himself, presenting a flaw within the current political system. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, he claimed the FTX collapse represents just one large part of the dangers of crypto, which includes Ponzi schemes, poor consumer protections, and national security threats. Among those threats are “Korean cybercriminals,” “drug trafficking,” “human trafficking,” and terrorist financing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Brown said he’d already asked the secretary of the Treasury to conduct a government-wide assessment of crypto involving various regulatory agencies. He noted that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been particularly aggressive, but that legislative action may also be necessary. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I’ve spent much of the last year and a half in this job… trying to educate the public about crypto and the dangers that it presents to our security as a nation, and to consumers that get hoodwinked by it,” he said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Thus far, the Biden administration has agreed to take a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pitches-for-regulation-and-strict-oversight-of-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">regulatory approach</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to the crypto industry, pursuing “responsible innovation” as its top priority for the space. Despite his doubts over much of the industry, Federal Reserve chairman Jerome Powell has clarified that he has “no intention to ban” crypto. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Todd asked Brown if he thought the regulatory approach may be giving an inappropriate green light to a technology that ought to be banned entirely. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I share that thought,” said Brown, stressing the need for agencies to unite on getting crypto under control. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We want them to do what they need to do at the same time – maybe banning it, although banning it is very difficult because it will go offshore, and who knows how that will work,” he said. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Sending Crypto Abroad</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto’s flag bearers frequently note the dangers of sending crypto abroad when speaking against overly strict and imposing regulations. Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-coinbase-wont-end-up-like-ftx-brian-armstrong/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">thinks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> this is primarily what allowed the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">FTX fraud</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to grow to such a substantial size. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We should continue to work with policymakers to create sensible regulation for centralized exchanges/custodians in each market (as we’ve been doing for some time), but then we need to see a level playing field enforced, which hasn’t happened to date,” he said in November.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance, which operates overseas, is currently the largest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume. Concerns about Binance’s opaque operations have inflated over the past month, especially after its proof of reserves partner </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-crypto-com-auditor-mazars-group-pauzes-work-with-crypto-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">called it quits</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> after releasing its first report on the exchange’s Bitcoin holdings.</span></p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of Politico</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-united-states-might-need-to-ban-crypto-says-banking-committee-chief/" rel="nofollow">The United States Might Need to Ban Crypto, Says Banking Committee Chief</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>For the First Time in Four Years, These Ethereum Whales Transfer Over $27M Worth of ETH</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/for-the-first-time-in-four-years-these-ethereum-whales-transfer-over-27m-worth-of-eth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229366</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ETHWhales.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ETHWhales.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[On-chain data suggested that the ETH tokens reportedly originated from Genesis and Poloniex.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the incessant bear market, whales appear to be waking up from their slumber to move their ETH holdings that were untouched for about four years.</p>
<p>According to the blockchain security company<a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1604701035314180096" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Peckshield Alert</a>, large amounts of ETH were transferred on December 18th by two addresses that have remained dormant since October 2018.</p>
<h2>Dormant ETH Wakes Up</h2>
<p>22,982 ETH, which is worth approximately $27.2 million at current prices, were moved to two new addresses.</p>
<p>The emergence of old wallets from hibernation typically arouses more public interest, especially if it&#8217;s linked with troubled entities.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, in addition to ETH transfers, bankrupt crypto lender Three Arrows Capital (3AC) also <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1604658942897926145" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">moved</a> a sizable chunk of ETH on December 19. The tokens in question &#8211; 2,000 ETH worth around $2.38 million &#8211; were withdrawn from Binance, while the embattled company&#8217;s address still holds 6,595 ETH worth nearly $7.85 million.</p>
<p>The latest development comes on the heels of significant price corrections in the market. Ethereum, for one, has shed over 20% of its gains seen since the past month dragging its price to a previous support level. After forming a local top at $1,352 last week, sellers took control to catalyze another leg down to $1,184.</p>
<h2>Demand for Ethereum</h2>
<p>2022 has been monumental for the Ethereum network (despite being disastrous for the overall crypto market). The much-hyped <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Merge,</a> which introduced staked ETH as an out-and-out cryptocurrency-native yield-bearing instrument, managed to eclipse other collateralized yield-bearing services. Nansen&#8217;s recent <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/research/an-on-chain-look-at-ethereums-liquid-staking-landscape" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> highlighted the significant demand for liquid Ethereum staking solutions as the cryptocurrency continued to be staked across several platforms in the months following the shift to proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus.</p>
<p>While stETH saw over 127% increase in average daily trading volume since the upgrade, there have been very few material changes in ETH&#8217;s price. However, some big price action may be expected as the network anticipates another hard fork, called &#8220;Shanghai,&#8221; slated for March 2023 release.</p>
<p>The next phase in Ethereum&#8217;s pipeline is the introduction of sharding &#8211; a feature that is expected to significantly ramp up transaction throughput.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/for-the-first-time-in-four-years-these-ethereum-whales-transfer-over-27m-worth-of-eth/" rel="nofollow">For the First Time in Four Years, These Ethereum Whales Transfer Over $27M Worth of ETH</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Falls 3% Daily but Is a Retest of $0.3 Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-falls-3-daily-but-is-a-retest-of-0-3-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 17:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229400</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s recent price action has been particularly rough following a convincing rejection from a key resistance level. The cryptocurrency is currently dropping toward the bulls&#8217; last resort as risk assets stumble. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the daily chart, the price has failed to move back above the significant $0.43 resistance level [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s recent price action has been particularly rough following a convincing rejection from a key resistance level. The cryptocurrency is currently dropping toward the bulls&#8217; last resort as risk assets stumble.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price has failed to move back above the significant $0.43 resistance level and is currently falling rapidly.</p>
<p>The 50-day and 200-day moving average lines, which also provided additional resistance around the $0.43 level, are now on the verge of a bearish cross, as the former is seemingly bound to drop below the latter soon.</p>
<p>All signs are pointing to a potential retest of the $0.3 support level, which could be the last hope for a bullish turnaround.</p>
<p>However, if the above-mentioned support level also crumbles, a further crash could be expected in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229402" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229402" style="width: 2428px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229402 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" alt="xrp_price_chart_191201" width="2428" height="1500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022.jpeg 2428w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-300x185.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-1024x633.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-768x474.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-1536x949.jpeg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-2048x1265.jpeg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-Daily-Dec-19-2022-50x31.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2428px) 100vw, 2428px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229402" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The large bearish flag was broken to the downside earlier, and the price has been declining as a result.</p>
<p>From a classical price action standpoint, a retest of the $0.3 support level looks imminent. However, the RSI indicator is currently showcasing a clear bullish divergence in this timeframe. This could hint at a probable pullback toward the lower trendline of the pattern in the short term.</p>
<p>Whether this pullback occurs or not remains to be seen, but the bearish momentum and the overall market structure both increase the likelihood of a drop-down to the $0.3 level in the near future.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229401" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229401" style="width: 2428px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-229401 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022.jpeg" alt="xrp_price_chart_191202" width="2428" height="1500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022.jpeg 2428w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-300x185.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-1024x633.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-768x474.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-1536x949.jpeg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-2048x1265.jpeg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT-4H-Dec-19-2022-50x31.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2428px) 100vw, 2428px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229401" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-falls-3-daily-but-is-a-retest-of-0-3-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Falls 3% Daily but Is a Retest of $0.3 Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale CEO Will Consider Massive Share Buyback if SEC Lawsuit Fails</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ceo-will-consider-massive-share-buyback-if-sec-lawsuit-fails/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229415</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/GrayscaleSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/GrayscaleSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Grayscale has a backup plan for shoring up GBTC if the fund can’t transition into a Bitcoin spot ETF. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale may consider a 20% tender offer on GBTC shares if its bid to convert into a Bitcoin spot ETF ultimately fails, said CEO Michael Sonnenshein to investors on Monday.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an interview on the same day, the executive also commented on the FTX’s collapse, the crypto bear market, and the state of Binance.</span></p>
<h2>Shoring Up GBTC</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Potato/status/1604834703122567172" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">conversation</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with CNBC, Sonnenshein acknowledged that the industry is going through a “crypto winter,” which will produce more “regulation” and “consolidation” on the other side.</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We’ve seen time and again bad actors get weeded out of the ecosystem, and crypto emerges more resilient and even stronger each time we see these types of events,” he said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The crypto winter has been rough on Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) – a popular investment vehicle for gaining exposure to the price of Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Not only has the value of its Bitcoin holdings declined substantially, but the discount between the market price of GBTC shares and the company’s net asset value has grown </span><a href="https://ycharts.com/companies/GBTC/discount_or_premium_to_nav" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">wider than ever</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to nearly 50%. In other words, while Grayscale holds $15.42 in Bitcoin per share, those shares only trade for $7.91 at writing time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale’s current structure doesn’t allow for shares to be easily redeemed for Bitcoin, which allows for the value discrepancy, to begin with. That’s why the firm seeks to convert its fund into a spot ETF – which would bring share value to par with its underlying Bitcoin, and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-holds-private-meeting-with-sec-discussing-bitcoin-spot-etf-transition/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">create massive value</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for investors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As such, the company is currently suing the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for rejecting its conversion attempts at every turn. It has received multiple amicus briefs in its support – including from </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-amicus-brief-to-support-grayscale-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-lawsuit-against-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The SEC recently submitted its reply brief, and we are currently drafting our </span><span style="font-weight: 400">response to the SEC, which is due January 13, 2023 – with final written briefs </span><span style="font-weight: 400">due on February 3, 2023,” </span><a href="https://grayscale.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022-End-of-Year-Investor-Letter.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">explained</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Sonnenshein in a letter to investors. “Shortly thereafter, a three-judge panel will be selected to hear oral arguments and rule on the case.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Should the courts not rule in Grayscale’s favor, Sonnenshein said that Grayscale would explore “other options” for returning value to investors. One method could be to include a tender offer for up to 20% of outstanding GBTC shares – however, this would require relief from the SEC.</span></p>
<h2>What’s Up With Binance?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CNBC also asked Sonnenshein for his thoughts on Binance and the state of its financials. CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) was interviewed by the same panel last week, and was unable to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-on-audits-ftx-the-2-1-billion-sbf-buyout-in-2021-and-recent-withdrawal-spree/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">clearly state</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> if Binance could handle a $2 billion clawback resulting from FTX’s bankruptcy proceedings. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Binance received a proof of reserves audit earlier this month from Mazars Group, the company </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-crypto-com-auditor-mazars-group-pauzes-work-with-crypto-clients/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">paused</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> its services to crypto firms shortly after due to concerns about how their reports were publicly understood. Binance and other firms, like Tether, have often claimed that audits are difficult to come by in the digital asset space. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Sonnenshein, however, rejected that idea. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We’ve had audited financials of our investment products – Bitcoin, Ethereum… those have all been audited going back to 2013, 2014,” he said. “I reject the premise that it’s hard to get audited financials done.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ceo-will-consider-massive-share-buyback-if-sec-lawsuit-fails/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale CEO Will Consider Massive Share Buyback if SEC Lawsuit Fails</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Agrees to Buy Voyager Digital Assets</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-agrees-to-buy-voyager-digital-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 13:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229388</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance US will be buying the assets of Voyager. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance US has entered into an agreement with Voyager Digital to acquire its assets. The bid from the cryptocurrency exchange also means that there&#8217;s a path for Voyager customer funds to be unlocked &#8220;as soon as possible.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>CryptoPotato <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-confirms-binance-us-will-bid-again-for-voyager-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier in November that CZ had confirmed that Binance US will be bidding for the assets of Voyager.</li>
<li>Today, in an <a href="https://blog.binance.us/voyager-binance-us/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">official announcement</a>, Voyager confirmed that the exchange will acquire its assets:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“Our bid is a reflection of our guiding principle that customers should come first.  Our goal is simple: return users their cryptocurrencies on the fastest timeline possible. [&#8230;] We hope our selection brings to an end a painful bankruptcy process which saw customers unfairly dragged into it at no fault of their own. Upon close of the deal, users will be able to seamlessly access their digital assets on the Binance.US platform where they will continue to receive future disbursements from the Voyager estate.” &#8211; Said Brian Shroder, CEO and President at Binance US.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-agrees-to-buy-voyager-digital-assets/" rel="nofollow">Binance US Agrees to Buy Voyager Digital Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medieval Empires (MEE) Will Be Listed on MEXC December 19</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/medieval-empires-mee-will-be-listed-on-mexc-december-19/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 12:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229375</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr2.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr2.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Medieval Empires will be listed on MEXC Global on December 19 ,12:00 (UTC). Users are able to trade its native token MEE(MEE/USDT).Along with the listing,MEXC launched a deposit MEE to share a 1,000 MX rewards campaign. Medieval Empires is an elaborate, multi-player online strategy game set in what is [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</p>
<p><a href="https://www.medievalempires.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Medieval Empires</a> will be listed on <a href="https://www.mexc.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">MEXC</a> Global on December 19 ,12:00 (UTC). Users are able to trade its native token MEE(MEE/USDT).Along with the listing,MEXC launched a <a href="https://support.mexc.com/hc/en-001/articles/13600945437593--Initial-Listing-MEXC-Will-List-Medieval-Empires-MEE-in-Assessment-Zone-Deposit-to-Share-1-000-MX-Rewards-" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">deposit MEE to share a 1,000 MX rewards</a> campaign.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr32.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-229376" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr32.png" alt="" width="602" height="339" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr32.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr32-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/medival-pr32-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Medieval Empires is an elaborate, multi-player online strategy game set in what is now modern-day Turkey during the late 13th century. Featuring internationally acclaimed actor, Engin Altan Düzyatan as Kayi Tribe leader Ertuğrul Gazi, the game aims to provide a state-of-the-art Web 3.0 experience to the fans of the character/actor, gamers as well as blockchain and crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p>The game is set in a passive PvE area and starts with players building towns while trading, fighting, and forging alliances.Medieval Empires offers several outstanding features,including multiplayer online strategy,play-to-own gameplay,persistent online world,community battles,physical &amp; digital NFTs with utility and massive historic battles.</p>
<p>The land will play an integral part in the gameplay and the game economy, with numerous benefits for landowners.There are 6 tiers of land.They launched a land sale in September 2022. This exclusive feature allows users the first opportunity to enter the immersive world of Medieval Empires.</p>
<p>Recently, Medieval Empires raised $2.1 million in the first seed round. Led by some of the key opinion leaders in the space such as  Evan Luthra, James Crypto Guru, Satoshi Stacker, Crypto King, and Davinci Jeremie,the successful funding round lays the foundation for Medieval Empowers to lead the mainstream adoption of blockchain gaming.</p>
<p>Medieval Empires, has partnered with Polygon Studios, an ecosystem builder owned and operated by Polygon, the leading Ethereum scaling solution onboarding millions to Web3. As part of the strategic collaboration, Medieval Empires is being built on the Polygon blockchain, allowing its players to enjoy an exciting Web3 gaming experience.</p>
<p>The team behind Medieval Empires is highly competent and vastly experienced in the fields of game development and blockchain technology.The project is backed by Carl Runefelt, better known in the crypto community as The Moon. Other notable advisors to the project include Scott McCarthy, former CMO at Illuvium, as well as Justin Edwards, former COO of Decentraland.</p>
<p>According to public information,MEXC is one of the world&#8217;s Top 10 cryptocurrency trading platform. The core products include spot trading, leveraged ETF, futures, NFT Index, etc. MEXC supports more than 1,700 cryptocurrency transactions.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/press-releases/four-years-of-deep-cultivation-mexc-perpetual-futures-liquidity-ranks-no-1" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">press release</a> on Cointelegraph, in September this year, the liquidity of the MEXC’s Futures reached first place in the world, which is a conclusion based on analyzing the transaction data of the top 50 currencies ranked by market value. Just at the beginning of December 2022, the MEXC Futures business also achieved significant growth, and the average daily transaction volume increased by 1,200%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/medieval-empires-mee-will-be-listed-on-mexc-december-19/" rel="nofollow">Medieval Empires (MEE) Will Be Listed on MEXC December 19</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chiliz’s Latest Series of Fan Tokens Are Listed on MEXC for the Secondary Market Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chilizs-latest-series-of-fan-tokens-are-listed-on-mexc-for-the-secondary-market-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 12:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229367</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-pr33.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-pr33.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Recently, Socios.com, Chiliz’s fan token creator, and several football clubs launched the latest fan tokens. These tokens collectively had their initial launch on the cryptocurrency trading platform MEXC to expand their scale in the secondary market. There are 16 clubs that launched fan tokens, including Everton FC Fan Token, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</p>
<p>Recently, Socios.com, Chiliz’s fan token creator, and several football clubs launched the latest fan tokens. These tokens collectively had their initial launch on the cryptocurrency trading platform MEXC to expand their scale in the secondary market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mexc-pr2222.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-229370" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mexc-pr2222.png" alt="" width="602" height="339" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mexc-pr2222.png 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mexc-pr2222-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/mexc-pr2222-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>There are 16 clubs that launched fan tokens, including Everton FC Fan Token, Crystal Palace FT, Leeds United FT, Arsenal Fan Token Atlético Mineiro FT, etc.</p>
<p>According to the data on December 14, Arsenal fan token AFC, AS Monaco fan token ASM, FC Barcelona FT fan token BAR, and Aston Villa FT fan token AVL, reached the highest gain of 272%, 200%, 126%, 240%, respectively after being listed on MEXC.</p>
<p>In fact, fan tokens are social tokens in sports, entertainment, and other fields resulting from the rise of the NFT in 2021. Fans hold tokens of relevant clubs or teams and will have the opportunity to obtain signed jerseys, NFT rewards, VIP seats, and participate in voting, club activities, etc. Among them, Chiliz, the entertainment and sports infrastructure provider based on blockchain technology, has collaborated with many well-known clubs to launch fan tokens. These include Juventus fan token JUV, AC Milan fan token ACM, etc.</p>
<p>In this cryptocurrency bear market, fan tokens have become the only sector that experienced an overall boom in the second half of this year, as a result of the World Cup in Qatar. Three months before the World Cup, Binance and MEXC, the two major trading platforms, took the lead in launching the fan token zone. Both platforms have listed fan tokens of relevant clubs or national teams.</p>
<p>According to public information, MEXC is not only the first trading platform to launch fan tokens, but also has more than 30 fan tokens listed, making it the trading platform with the largest number of listed fan tokens at present.</p>
<p>During this World Cup, different fan tokens have also shown different price performances as the game progresses. ARG, the fan token of the Argentine national team, which has won two World Cups, began to rebound from its bottom on December 9 and reached an 87% gain on the 13th. It was especially after Argentina defeated Croatia 3-0 and advanced to the final, that ARG hit the highest gain of 46.1% on MEXC.</p>
<h2>About MEXC</h2>
<p>MEXC is the world&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency trading platform, providing one-stop cryptocurrency trading services for spot, ETF, futures, Staking, NFT Index, and more. MEXC currently serves more than 10 million users worldwide and embraces the philosophy of &#8220;Users first, MEXC&#8217;s Changing for you&#8221;. Visit the <a href="https://www.mexc.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">website</a> and get more information.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chilizs-latest-series-of-fan-tokens-are-listed-on-mexc-for-the-secondary-market-expansion/" rel="nofollow">Chiliz’s Latest Series of Fan Tokens Are Listed on MEXC for the Secondary Market Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
