<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 04:18:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Proposes New Ecosystem Council]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-proposes-new-ecosystem-council</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-ecosystem-council-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-proposes-new-ecosystem-council</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon, the renowned Ethereum scaling solution, recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This proposal, revolving around the establishment of an "Ecosystem Council," will redefine how system smart contracts within the Polygon environment are managed and upgraded. This proposal indicates the continuous efforts by Polygon to strike a perfect balance between community-driven governance and efficient decision-making in a decentralized network.</p>
A New System for Decentralized Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">System smart contracts represent a fundamental element of the blockchain infrastructure. They can directly or indirectly influence user funds and the infrastructure's functioning. A crucial aspect of these contracts is their upgradeability, which allows seamless migration to improved versions under specific circumstances. The importance of this feature is evident in various Layer 2 (L2) solutions, such as Optimism, Arbitrum, and zkSync, where an efficient means of patching bugs and upgrading pivotal architecture components is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the proposal, the Ecosystem Council would comprise technically proficient and value-aligned individuals, elected and removable by the community. This council will be responsible for performing timelock-limited upgrades to system smart contracts across Polygon networks, such as Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For example, in the case of non-emergency or routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the timelock as usual. On the other hand, if there is a perceived threat to user funds due to potential vulnerabilities in smart contracts, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect assets. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polygon community will be empowered with three competencies: the election and removal of Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit an Emergency State, and the power to veto any upgrade proposed by the Ecosystem Council. This model is expected to increase community engagement while retaining a level of control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
The Ecosystem Council: Balancing Efficiency and Decentralization
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposed model suggests the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a group consisting of reputable, technically adept, and value-aligned individuals. These individuals would be democratically elected by the community and could also be removed by them. The council's primary role would be to perform timelock-limited upgrades to the system's smart contracts across the Polygon networks, including the Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The governance model will allow the council to handle both routine and sensitive proposals. In the case of routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the standard timelock protocol. However, if a potential vulnerability poses a risk to user funds, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect the funds. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To maintain a balance between efficiency and community engagement, Polygon proposes empowering the community with several competencies. These include the power to elect and remove Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit the Emergency State, and the authority to veto any upgrade proposed and scheduled by the Ecosystem Council. By bestowing the community with these powers, Polygon hopes to increase the overall community engagement while maintaining a level of centralized control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
Navigating the Transition: Inviting Community Input
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the proposed model promises improved governance and security, its rollout must be gradual and well planned, especially considering the live nature of the blockchain. To ensure a seamless transition, the Polygon team is inviting its community to participate in the process, providing feedback, and assisting in answering open questions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The community is particularly encouraged to contribute ideas regarding incentivizing participation in the model and establishing a robust and secure voting mechanism. Decisions around these aspects, like the general design principles, voting power proxy, and architecture, will be crucial to the model's success. The team is also considering the use of the $MATIC token as a voting power proxy, which would provide broad ecosystem inclusion and legitimize the Ecosystem Council.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Polygon's proposed Ecosystem Council represents an exciting step towards more robust, efficient, and community-driven governance of system smart contracts. By integrating elements of both centralized and decentralized decision-making, the model aims to bring the best of both worlds to the Polygon network. This move could help Polygon maintain its reputation as a leading Layer 2 solution, offering an improved governance framework that values efficiency, security, and community inclusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon, the renowned Ethereum scaling solution, recently proposed a new decentralized governance model aimed at enhancing its network's security, upgradeability, and robustness.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This proposal, revolving around the establishment of an "Ecosystem Council," will redefine how system smart contracts within the Polygon environment are managed and upgraded. This proposal indicates the continuous efforts by Polygon to strike a perfect balance between community-driven governance and efficient decision-making in a decentralized network.</p>
A New System for Decentralized Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">System smart contracts represent a fundamental element of the blockchain infrastructure. They can directly or indirectly influence user funds and the infrastructure's functioning. A crucial aspect of these contracts is their upgradeability, which allows seamless migration to improved versions under specific circumstances. The importance of this feature is evident in various Layer 2 (L2) solutions, such as Optimism, Arbitrum, and zkSync, where an efficient means of patching bugs and upgrading pivotal architecture components is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the proposal, the Ecosystem Council would comprise technically proficient and value-aligned individuals, elected and removable by the community. This council will be responsible for performing timelock-limited upgrades to system smart contracts across Polygon networks, such as Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For example, in the case of non-emergency or routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the timelock as usual. On the other hand, if there is a perceived threat to user funds due to potential vulnerabilities in smart contracts, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect assets. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polygon community will be empowered with three competencies: the election and removal of Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit an Emergency State, and the power to veto any upgrade proposed by the Ecosystem Council. This model is expected to increase community engagement while retaining a level of control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
The Ecosystem Council: Balancing Efficiency and Decentralization
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposed model suggests the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a group consisting of reputable, technically adept, and value-aligned individuals. These individuals would be democratically elected by the community and could also be removed by them. The council's primary role would be to perform timelock-limited upgrades to the system's smart contracts across the Polygon networks, including the Polygon PoS and zkEVM.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The governance model will allow the council to handle both routine and sensitive proposals. In the case of routine proposals, the council will make a proposal and proceed with the standard timelock protocol. However, if a potential vulnerability poses a risk to user funds, the council will enact an Emergency State, freezing transactions to protect the funds. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To maintain a balance between efficiency and community engagement, Polygon proposes empowering the community with several competencies. These include the power to elect and remove Ecosystem Council members, the ability to exit the Emergency State, and the authority to veto any upgrade proposed and scheduled by the Ecosystem Council. By bestowing the community with these powers, Polygon hopes to increase the overall community engagement while maintaining a level of centralized control to prevent malicious activities.</p>
Navigating the Transition: Inviting Community Input
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the proposed model promises improved governance and security, its rollout must be gradual and well planned, especially considering the live nature of the blockchain. To ensure a seamless transition, the Polygon team is inviting its community to participate in the process, providing feedback, and assisting in answering open questions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The community is particularly encouraged to contribute ideas regarding incentivizing participation in the model and establishing a robust and secure voting mechanism. Decisions around these aspects, like the general design principles, voting power proxy, and architecture, will be crucial to the model's success. The team is also considering the use of the $MATIC token as a voting power proxy, which would provide broad ecosystem inclusion and legitimize the Ecosystem Council.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Polygon's proposed Ecosystem Council represents an exciting step towards more robust, efficient, and community-driven governance of system smart contracts. By integrating elements of both centralized and decentralized decision-making, the model aims to bring the best of both worlds to the Polygon network. This move could help Polygon maintain its reputation as a leading Layer 2 solution, offering an improved governance framework that values efficiency, security, and community inclusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Price Prediction: LTC Halving Draws Close; Uwerx (WERX) Bullish Run Continues as Listing Nears]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/litecoin-ltc-price-prediction-ltc-halving-draws-close-uwerx-werx-bullish-run-continues-as-listing-nears</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5807.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/litecoin-ltc-price-prediction-ltc-halving-draws-close-uwerx-werx-bullish-run-continues-as-listing-nears</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the countdown to the Litecoin (LTC) halving event begins, the crypto community eagerly awaits the potential price implications of this significant milestone. Simultaneously, the market is enthusiastic as Uwerx approaches its highly anticipated listing.</p>
<p>In this article, we delve into the Litecoin (LTC) price prediction and the bullish momentum surrounding Uwerx, providing valuable insights to navigate these exciting developments. </p>
<p class="s8">Litecoin (LTC): Price Prediction</p>
<p>Revolutionizing digital payments, Litecoin (LTC) leverages blockchain technology to ensure swift, secure, and cost-effective transactions. </p>
<p>While sharing similarities with Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC) distinguishes itself with unique attributes like a different hashing algorithm, rapid block transaction times, and a capped maximum supply.</p>
<p>Presently valued at $91.15, Litecoin (LTC) boasts a market cap of $6,652,668,844, firmly establishing its position as a significant contender in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Industry analysts anticipate promising growth for Litecoin (LTC), envisioning a potential value of $153 by Q4 2024, reflecting its upward trajectory and future potential. </p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Fueling the Freelance Revolution with Unparalleled Backing</p>
<p>Boasting an impressive tally of over 5,500 sign-ups, a thriving Twitter following surpassing 1,600, and a vibrant Telegram community exceeding 1,600 members, Uwerx has amassed remarkable interest and unwavering support. Such fervent backing is a testament to the platform's tremendous potential for success. Brace yourself for the dawn of a groundbreaking era in freelancing.</p>
<p>Uwerx is preparing for a fascinating Test Airdrop, receiving resounding support of 98.2% in a Twitter poll. This happens on July 31st &nbsp;as the presale concludes, marking the highly anticipated occasion.</p>
<p>Responding to the community's demands, Uwerx is swiftly implementing a 25-year token lock, endorsed by 82.8% of voters. This strategic move ensures enduring stability and security, solidifying Uwerx's unwavering commitment to its valued investors.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Accelerating through Presale Stages, Unleashing Limitless Potential</p>
<p>Embark on an exhilarating journey with Uwerx as its presale rapidly advances through Stage 5, offering a captivating WERX token price of $0.041 with a juicy bonus on orders of 15%. This extraordinary opportunity awaits those seeking to join Uwerx'svoyage of growth and triumph.</p>
<p>Witness the extraordinary pace of Uwerx's presale stages, where Stage 1 to Stage 4 achieved an impressive completion in a short time. These remarkable achievements showcase the unwavering enthusiasm and unwavering confidence surrounding Uwerx'srevolutionary vision.</p>
<p>Setting a groundbreaking precedent, Uwerx distinguishes itself from industry giants by introducing a minimal transaction fee of just 1%, an exceptional contrast to the burdensome charges of 10% by Upwork and 20% by Fiverr. This revolutionary fee structure brings forth equity, benefiting freelancers and clients and fostering a harmonious and thriving ecosystem.</p>
<p>Reinforcing its commitment to security and trust, Uwerxundergoes comprehensive audits by the esteemed SolidProofand InterFi Network, ensuring unparalleled integrity and reliability. These rigorous evaluations provide users with unwavering assurance, establishing Uwerx as a platform built on transparency and accountability.</p>
<p>Emphasizing transparency and autonomy, Uwerx plans to renounce its contracts upon readiness for centralized exchange listings, solidifying its commitment to a decentralized future. Additionally, the platform's commitment to fairness is further reinforced by reducing taxes to zero, enabling an environment of equal opportunities and independence.</p>
<p>Introducing the revolutionary Uwerx Vault, an impregnable storage solution for WERX tokens. Users can securely store their tokens within the vault and engage in staking and unlocking rewards based on platform variables. This groundbreaking feature amplifies active participation and fosters an engaged community within the dynamic Uwerx ecosystem.</p>
<p>Uwerx's imminent listing on CoinSniper and its forthcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st propels its visibility and accessibility to new heights. These strategic listings broaden Uwerx's horizons, opening abundant avenues for users to immerse themselves in the platform and actively contribute to its exponential growth. Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey with Uwerx, where limitless potential awaits.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX) Nears Beta Platform Launch: Empowering Users through Testing and Feedback</p>
<p>The wait is over! Uwerx has made its Alpha platform available to the public, ushering in a new era of possibilities. But guess what? Uwerx isn't one to rest on its laurels. With the Beta platform on the horizon, the future's looking brighter than ever.</p>
<p>With impressive progress, an unwaveringly supportive community, and an ambitious roadmap, Uwerx emerges as a trailblazer, spearheading the revolution in the freelance industry. Its distinct approach and exclusive attributes offer a compelling investment opportunity that astute investors should consider seizing to maximize their gains. </p>
<p>More update on the Alpha platform has been released as PDFs again. Included is a total of TEN pages, ranging from Signing Up, Logging In, Forgot password, Freelancer or Client initiation, Initial step of Job Creation and initial step of Finding Talent, My activity page, Hiring dashboard page, Job creation process page(s). There&rsquo;s also more to come in during the week!</p>
<p>Share your design suggestions, feedback, thoughts, and recommendations by emailing feedback@uwerx.network. Your contribution will help shape the future of Uwerx. Unleash your potential with Uwerx as it forges ahead, fueled by innovation and user-centricity.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the countdown to the Litecoin (LTC) halving event begins, the crypto community eagerly awaits the potential price implications of this significant milestone. Simultaneously, the market is enthusiastic as Uwerx approaches its highly anticipated listing.</p>
<p>In this article, we delve into the Litecoin (LTC) price prediction and the bullish momentum surrounding Uwerx, providing valuable insights to navigate these exciting developments. </p>
<p class="s8">Litecoin (LTC): Price Prediction</p>
<p>Revolutionizing digital payments, Litecoin (LTC) leverages blockchain technology to ensure swift, secure, and cost-effective transactions. </p>
<p>While sharing similarities with Bitcoin (BTC), Litecoin (LTC) distinguishes itself with unique attributes like a different hashing algorithm, rapid block transaction times, and a capped maximum supply.</p>
<p>Presently valued at $91.15, Litecoin (LTC) boasts a market cap of $6,652,668,844, firmly establishing its position as a significant contender in the cryptocurrency market. </p>
<p>Industry analysts anticipate promising growth for Litecoin (LTC), envisioning a potential value of $153 by Q4 2024, reflecting its upward trajectory and future potential. </p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Fueling the Freelance Revolution with Unparalleled Backing</p>
<p>Boasting an impressive tally of over 5,500 sign-ups, a thriving Twitter following surpassing 1,600, and a vibrant Telegram community exceeding 1,600 members, Uwerx has amassed remarkable interest and unwavering support. Such fervent backing is a testament to the platform's tremendous potential for success. Brace yourself for the dawn of a groundbreaking era in freelancing.</p>
<p>Uwerx is preparing for a fascinating Test Airdrop, receiving resounding support of 98.2% in a Twitter poll. This happens on July 31st &nbsp;as the presale concludes, marking the highly anticipated occasion.</p>
<p>Responding to the community's demands, Uwerx is swiftly implementing a 25-year token lock, endorsed by 82.8% of voters. This strategic move ensures enduring stability and security, solidifying Uwerx's unwavering commitment to its valued investors.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX): Accelerating through Presale Stages, Unleashing Limitless Potential</p>
<p>Embark on an exhilarating journey with Uwerx as its presale rapidly advances through Stage 5, offering a captivating WERX token price of $0.041 with a juicy bonus on orders of 15%. This extraordinary opportunity awaits those seeking to join Uwerx'svoyage of growth and triumph.</p>
<p>Witness the extraordinary pace of Uwerx's presale stages, where Stage 1 to Stage 4 achieved an impressive completion in a short time. These remarkable achievements showcase the unwavering enthusiasm and unwavering confidence surrounding Uwerx'srevolutionary vision.</p>
<p>Setting a groundbreaking precedent, Uwerx distinguishes itself from industry giants by introducing a minimal transaction fee of just 1%, an exceptional contrast to the burdensome charges of 10% by Upwork and 20% by Fiverr. This revolutionary fee structure brings forth equity, benefiting freelancers and clients and fostering a harmonious and thriving ecosystem.</p>
<p>Reinforcing its commitment to security and trust, Uwerxundergoes comprehensive audits by the esteemed SolidProofand InterFi Network, ensuring unparalleled integrity and reliability. These rigorous evaluations provide users with unwavering assurance, establishing Uwerx as a platform built on transparency and accountability.</p>
<p>Emphasizing transparency and autonomy, Uwerx plans to renounce its contracts upon readiness for centralized exchange listings, solidifying its commitment to a decentralized future. Additionally, the platform's commitment to fairness is further reinforced by reducing taxes to zero, enabling an environment of equal opportunities and independence.</p>
<p>Introducing the revolutionary Uwerx Vault, an impregnable storage solution for WERX tokens. Users can securely store their tokens within the vault and engage in staking and unlocking rewards based on platform variables. This groundbreaking feature amplifies active participation and fosters an engaged community within the dynamic Uwerx ecosystem.</p>
<p>Uwerx's imminent listing on CoinSniper and its forthcoming listing on Uniswap by August 1st propels its visibility and accessibility to new heights. These strategic listings broaden Uwerx's horizons, opening abundant avenues for users to immerse themselves in the platform and actively contribute to its exponential growth. Prepare to embark on an extraordinary journey with Uwerx, where limitless potential awaits.</p>
<p class="s8">Uwerx (WERX) Nears Beta Platform Launch: Empowering Users through Testing and Feedback</p>
<p>The wait is over! Uwerx has made its Alpha platform available to the public, ushering in a new era of possibilities. But guess what? Uwerx isn't one to rest on its laurels. With the Beta platform on the horizon, the future's looking brighter than ever.</p>
<p>With impressive progress, an unwaveringly supportive community, and an ambitious roadmap, Uwerx emerges as a trailblazer, spearheading the revolution in the freelance industry. Its distinct approach and exclusive attributes offer a compelling investment opportunity that astute investors should consider seizing to maximize their gains. </p>
<p>More update on the Alpha platform has been released as PDFs again. Included is a total of TEN pages, ranging from Signing Up, Logging In, Forgot password, Freelancer or Client initiation, Initial step of Job Creation and initial step of Finding Talent, My activity page, Hiring dashboard page, Job creation process page(s). There&rsquo;s also more to come in during the week!</p>
<p>Share your design suggestions, feedback, thoughts, and recommendations by emailing feedback@uwerx.network. Your contribution will help shape the future of Uwerx. Unleash your potential with Uwerx as it forges ahead, fueled by innovation and user-centricity.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Join the presale and take advantage of the 15% bonus!</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Discover InQubeta, The 50x Crypto Powering The Future of AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/discover-inqubeta-the-50x-crypto-powering-the-future-of-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-5806.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/discover-inqubeta-the-50x-crypto-powering-the-future-of-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">InQubeta, an innovative AI technology startup, is revolutionizing the landscape of artificial intelligence. With its groundbreaking solutions and visionary approach, InQubeta is at the forefront of transforming industries and unlocking the true potential of AI. </p>
<p class="s5">As we delve into the world of InQubeta, we embark on a captivating journey that showcases the magic of this remarkable platform and its potential to shape the future.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta Is Powered By Its Unique Token QUBE</p>
<p class="s5">At the core of InQubeta lies its native token, QUBE. This token serves as the gateway to an ecosystem where AI and blockchain converge. With its deflationary nature, QUBE offers a unique investment opportunity for crypto enthusiasts looking to diversify their portfolios. InQubeta has implemented a buy and sell tax mechanism that allocates 2% of transactions to a burn wallet and directs 5% to a dedicated reward pool. This deflationary model not only encourages long-term holding but also creates a scarcity effect that could potentially drive the value of QUBE upward over time.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, QUBE plays a pivotal role in the InQubetaecosystem, extending its utility beyond a mere investment vehicle. By leveraging QUBE on the InQubeta NFT marketplace, investors gain access to fractional investment opportunities in AI startups. The platform introduces innovative reward and equity-based NFTs, providing a seamless and efficient investment process. Powered by blockchain technology, this marketplace ensures transparency, security, and democratization, enabling investors of all backgrounds to participate in the AI revolution.</p>
<p class="s5">The transformative power of InQubeta extends beyond financial gains. QUBE serves as a governance token, empowering holders to participate in the decision-making processes of the platform actively. </p>
<p class="s5">Through a decentralized governance model, QUBE holders can propose ideas, engage in discussions, and cast votes on crucial matters that shape the future of InQubeta. This inclusive approach fosters a strong community and aligns the project's interests with those of its stakeholders, ensuring a collective effort in driving InQubeta's success.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta&rsquo;s Presale Surpasses $400,000 Milestone</p>
<p class="s5">As the InQubeta journey unfolds, investors are met with an enticing opportunity: the ongoing presale of QUBE tokens. This presale has already surpassed the impressive milestone of $400,000, highlighting the immense interest and support behind InQubeta's vision. By participating in the presale, investors can secure their stake in the future of AI and position themselves for potential exponential growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Joining the InQubeta presale is straightforward and accessible. With a minimum investment requirement that allows for wider participation, investors can contribute to the growth of this groundbreaking project. The presale accepts popular cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and USDT, ensuring a seamless investment process for all. The presale also allows you to purchase QUBE tokens with credit or debit cards.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">Don&rsquo;t Miss Out On InQubeta</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta is redefining the way we perceive and interact with artificial intelligence, unlocking new possibilities and paving the way for transformative advancements. The successful start to the presale, is a testament to the widespread enthusiasm and confidence in InQubeta's vision.</p>
<p class="s5">The combination of InQubeta's innovative solutions, the deflationary nature of QUBE, and the growing demand for AI technologies set the stage for a promising future for QUBE token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">Investing in QUBE tokens during the presale is not just an investment in the future of AI; it is an opportunity to be part of a revolutionary movement. With the potential for a 50x growth, according to industry experts, investing in QUBE today could yield significant returns in the future. Seize this moment, join the InQubeta presale, and be part of the magic reshaping the artificial intelligence world. The future awaits, and InQubeta is leading the way.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p>https://inqubeta.ai</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">InQubeta, an innovative AI technology startup, is revolutionizing the landscape of artificial intelligence. With its groundbreaking solutions and visionary approach, InQubeta is at the forefront of transforming industries and unlocking the true potential of AI. </p>
<p class="s5">As we delve into the world of InQubeta, we embark on a captivating journey that showcases the magic of this remarkable platform and its potential to shape the future.</p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta Is Powered By Its Unique Token QUBE</p>
<p class="s5">At the core of InQubeta lies its native token, QUBE. This token serves as the gateway to an ecosystem where AI and blockchain converge. With its deflationary nature, QUBE offers a unique investment opportunity for crypto enthusiasts looking to diversify their portfolios. InQubeta has implemented a buy and sell tax mechanism that allocates 2% of transactions to a burn wallet and directs 5% to a dedicated reward pool. This deflationary model not only encourages long-term holding but also creates a scarcity effect that could potentially drive the value of QUBE upward over time.</p>
<p class="s5">Moreover, QUBE plays a pivotal role in the InQubetaecosystem, extending its utility beyond a mere investment vehicle. By leveraging QUBE on the InQubeta NFT marketplace, investors gain access to fractional investment opportunities in AI startups. The platform introduces innovative reward and equity-based NFTs, providing a seamless and efficient investment process. Powered by blockchain technology, this marketplace ensures transparency, security, and democratization, enabling investors of all backgrounds to participate in the AI revolution.</p>
<p class="s5">The transformative power of InQubeta extends beyond financial gains. QUBE serves as a governance token, empowering holders to participate in the decision-making processes of the platform actively. </p>
<p class="s5">Through a decentralized governance model, QUBE holders can propose ideas, engage in discussions, and cast votes on crucial matters that shape the future of InQubeta. This inclusive approach fosters a strong community and aligns the project's interests with those of its stakeholders, ensuring a collective effort in driving InQubeta's success.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">InQubeta&rsquo;s Presale Surpasses $400,000 Milestone</p>
<p class="s5">As the InQubeta journey unfolds, investors are met with an enticing opportunity: the ongoing presale of QUBE tokens. This presale has already surpassed the impressive milestone of $400,000, highlighting the immense interest and support behind InQubeta's vision. By participating in the presale, investors can secure their stake in the future of AI and position themselves for potential exponential growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Joining the InQubeta presale is straightforward and accessible. With a minimum investment requirement that allows for wider participation, investors can contribute to the growth of this groundbreaking project. The presale accepts popular cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, and USDT, ensuring a seamless investment process for all. The presale also allows you to purchase QUBE tokens with credit or debit cards.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s8">Don&rsquo;t Miss Out On InQubeta</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta is redefining the way we perceive and interact with artificial intelligence, unlocking new possibilities and paving the way for transformative advancements. The successful start to the presale, is a testament to the widespread enthusiasm and confidence in InQubeta's vision.</p>
<p class="s5">The combination of InQubeta's innovative solutions, the deflationary nature of QUBE, and the growing demand for AI technologies set the stage for a promising future for QUBE token holders.</p>
<p class="s5">Investing in QUBE tokens during the presale is not just an investment in the future of AI; it is an opportunity to be part of a revolutionary movement. With the potential for a 50x growth, according to industry experts, investing in QUBE today could yield significant returns in the future. Seize this moment, join the InQubeta presale, and be part of the magic reshaping the artificial intelligence world. The future awaits, and InQubeta is leading the way.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p>https://inqubeta.ai</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  26587 Target Absorbed - 18 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-26587-target-absorbed-18-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-26587-target-absorbed-18-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Absorbs 26587 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 18 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Significant Stops were also elected above the 26587.57 area during the climb, an upside price objective associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26661.17 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25913.83.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Absorbs 26587 Target:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 18 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent gains early in the Asian session as the pair reached the 26783.20 area after Stops were elected above the 26611.97 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 28473.93 to 24750.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 27051, 27595, and 27677 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; Significant Stops were also elected above the 26587.57 area during the climb, an upside price objective associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 24750 and 25143.24 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;The technical significance of these levels was confirmed when buying pressure emerged around the 26165 area during a pullback, just above another upside price objective around the 26153 area.&nbsp; Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, and 22025 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26661.17 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25913.83.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tether Responds to Account Deactivation Controversy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/tether-responds-to-account-deactivation-controversy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-responds-to-controversy-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/tether-responds-to-account-deactivation-controversy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to information released by the New York Attorney General (NYAG), Tether, the issuer of leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">While reasons for the individual account terminations remain undisclosed, the named entities included MoonPay, BlockFi, CMS Holdings, and Galois Capital.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Responding to the unfolding situation, Tether indicated its reluctance to comment on specific customer relationships, noting that each party had undergone stringent compliance checks both during onboarding and throughout their relationship, in line with Tether's compliance policies.</p>
NYAG Investigation and Tether's Commitment to Transparency
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the NYAG investigation wrapped up in early 2021, some of the documents in question extend until June of that year. These documents were collected during the NYAG's probe into Tether and sister company Bitfinex over the alleged misappropriation of $850 million. During this investigation, iFinex, the parent company of both entities, requested an extension to produce the required financial documents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Following a settlement that included an $18.5 million penalty and the cessation of trading in New York, media outlets and Coinbase sought the public disclosure of Tether&rsquo;s initial quarterly report under the Freedom of Information Act. However, Tether opposed this motion, citing the need to protect its customers' confidential data.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite Tether's objections, the NYAG granted media outlets access to the documents, leading to the revelation about the deacttivation of numerous company accounts. </p>
Tether's Stance on Transparency and Risk Management
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether remains adamant about its commitment to transparency while prioritizing its customers' privacy and security. Following the settlement with the NYAG, Tether has diligently completed its quarterly reporting obligations, affirming its commitment to openness and transparency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, Tether claims that it takes pride in its meticulous development of risk metrics and processes, enabling its investment and financial teams to thoroughly assess the risk tied to the company's financial interactions. Tether has continually demonstrated its commitment to sustaining its business objectives while adhering to a robust risk management culture.</p>
Tether's Reserves and Commercial Papers
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether's dedication to maintaining the highest standards is evident in its transparent dealings regarding its lending program and reserves. Tether's reserves have proven to be extremely liquid, high-quality, and readily available to support any size of redemption, demonstrated by the repayment of US$7 billion in 48 hours in 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the released documents, Tether has consistently maintained an A2 or better rating for the majority of its commercial papers, and none of its past statements have undergone any changes. This commitment to upholding the highest standards has been echoed in the company's dedication to accountability and its unwavering risk management culture. The firm, however, has been severely criticized over past decisions, especially in the case of blocking an MEV Validator as a security response.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether says that while media outlets have rushed to present this information to readers, Tether remains committed to its users, as well as for the benefit of the the broader crypto community. The company is keen to provide a factual point of reference about the disclosed materials, and it continues to cooperate with law enforcement, having assisted in over 150 investigations across four continents in the past 18 months. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to information released by the New York Attorney General (NYAG), Tether, the issuer of leading stablecoin USDT, reportedly deactivated around 29 accounts tied to significant players in the cryptocurrency sphere in 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">While reasons for the individual account terminations remain undisclosed, the named entities included MoonPay, BlockFi, CMS Holdings, and Galois Capital.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Responding to the unfolding situation, Tether indicated its reluctance to comment on specific customer relationships, noting that each party had undergone stringent compliance checks both during onboarding and throughout their relationship, in line with Tether's compliance policies.</p>
NYAG Investigation and Tether's Commitment to Transparency
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the NYAG investigation wrapped up in early 2021, some of the documents in question extend until June of that year. These documents were collected during the NYAG's probe into Tether and sister company Bitfinex over the alleged misappropriation of $850 million. During this investigation, iFinex, the parent company of both entities, requested an extension to produce the required financial documents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Following a settlement that included an $18.5 million penalty and the cessation of trading in New York, media outlets and Coinbase sought the public disclosure of Tether&rsquo;s initial quarterly report under the Freedom of Information Act. However, Tether opposed this motion, citing the need to protect its customers' confidential data.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite Tether's objections, the NYAG granted media outlets access to the documents, leading to the revelation about the deacttivation of numerous company accounts. </p>
Tether's Stance on Transparency and Risk Management
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether remains adamant about its commitment to transparency while prioritizing its customers' privacy and security. Following the settlement with the NYAG, Tether has diligently completed its quarterly reporting obligations, affirming its commitment to openness and transparency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Notably, Tether claims that it takes pride in its meticulous development of risk metrics and processes, enabling its investment and financial teams to thoroughly assess the risk tied to the company's financial interactions. Tether has continually demonstrated its commitment to sustaining its business objectives while adhering to a robust risk management culture.</p>
Tether's Reserves and Commercial Papers
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether's dedication to maintaining the highest standards is evident in its transparent dealings regarding its lending program and reserves. Tether's reserves have proven to be extremely liquid, high-quality, and readily available to support any size of redemption, demonstrated by the repayment of US$7 billion in 48 hours in 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the released documents, Tether has consistently maintained an A2 or better rating for the majority of its commercial papers, and none of its past statements have undergone any changes. This commitment to upholding the highest standards has been echoed in the company's dedication to accountability and its unwavering risk management culture. The firm, however, has been severely criticized over past decisions, especially in the case of blocking an MEV Validator as a security response.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Tether says that while media outlets have rushed to present this information to readers, Tether remains committed to its users, as well as for the benefit of the the broader crypto community. The company is keen to provide a factual point of reference about the disclosed materials, and it continues to cooperate with law enforcement, having assisted in over 150 investigations across four continents in the past 18 months. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap Aligns with Wormhole and Axelar for Cross-Chain Bridging]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uniswap-aligns-with-wormhole-and-axelar-for-cross-chain-bridging</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-cross-chain-bridging-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 14:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uniswap-aligns-with-wormhole-and-axelar-for-cross-chain-bridging</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These selections are the result of a comprehensive analysis conducted by Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee, which evaluated a range of potential protocols. The proposed changes are also aligned to the protocol's recent disclosure of its plans for V4.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Diving Deep into the Decision</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee scrutinized multiple contenders, namely Wormhole, Celer, DeBridge, LayerZero, Axelar, and Multichain (CRP). Each of these was rigorously assessed for its proficiency in facilitating cross-chain governance. Out of the competition, Wormhole and Axelar emerged victorious, with the committee endorsing these two for utilization across all cross-chain deployments.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the committee puts it, both Wormhole and Axelar have demonstrated their aptness in managing governance messaging for potential cross-chain deployments. They, however, advised the community to persistently review these and other bridge providers, bearing in mind the dynamics of the industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cross-Chain Governance and Its Implications</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The fundamental application for Uniswap DAO's cross-chain bridge lies in its ability to relay governance messages from Ethereum to other chains for execution. All Uniswap deployment proposals undertake a formal voting procedure on Ethereum. Any upgrades for deployments on alternate chains are then communicated via a cross-chain messaging protocol.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Wormhole and Axelar have gained the committee's approval, this doesn't entirely exclude other bridges. The report also pointed out that those deemed unsuitable for Uniswap's present cross-chain governance needs might still satisfy the prerequisites of other protocols and applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Vulnerabilities and Controversies: The Story of Cross-Chain Bridges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The controversy around cross-chain bridges in the Web3 sphere is nothing new. In 2022, these bridging protocols proved to be a weak spot, with hackers successfully exploiting them and causing billions in losses. As per data from Rekt, four out of the top five most expensive DeFi breaches targeted bridges, resulting in an aggregated loss of over $2.1 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to these vulnerabilities, Uniswap has formed its Cross-Chain Bridge Assessment Committee to aid governance delegates and the Uniswap community in making well-informed decisions regarding cross-chain bridging protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Committee's evaluations covered more than 130 assessment questions for each protocol, taking into account their ability to ensure "safety, liveness, and censorship resistance". Looking ahead, Celer and DeBridge might be reassessed despite their current shortcomings in slashing mechanisms and security assurances. The report was notably critical of Multichain for its lack of transparency and ineffective deterrents to prevent validator collusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To underscore the context, Uniswap has over $5.9 billion locked in its protocol as of May 2023, with daily transaction volume frequently exceeding $1 billion. Given these figures, Uniswap's choice of Wormhole and Axelar could have significant implications for both the involved protocols and Uniswap's ongoing cross-chain operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap recently disclosed its preferred choice for handling non-Ethereum deployments in its cross-chain bridging operations: Wormhole and Axelar.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These selections are the result of a comprehensive analysis conducted by Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee, which evaluated a range of potential protocols. The proposed changes are also aligned to the protocol's recent disclosure of its plans for V4.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Diving Deep into the Decision</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's Bridge Assessment Committee scrutinized multiple contenders, namely Wormhole, Celer, DeBridge, LayerZero, Axelar, and Multichain (CRP). Each of these was rigorously assessed for its proficiency in facilitating cross-chain governance. Out of the competition, Wormhole and Axelar emerged victorious, with the committee endorsing these two for utilization across all cross-chain deployments.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the committee puts it, both Wormhole and Axelar have demonstrated their aptness in managing governance messaging for potential cross-chain deployments. They, however, advised the community to persistently review these and other bridge providers, bearing in mind the dynamics of the industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cross-Chain Governance and Its Implications</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The fundamental application for Uniswap DAO's cross-chain bridge lies in its ability to relay governance messages from Ethereum to other chains for execution. All Uniswap deployment proposals undertake a formal voting procedure on Ethereum. Any upgrades for deployments on alternate chains are then communicated via a cross-chain messaging protocol.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Wormhole and Axelar have gained the committee's approval, this doesn't entirely exclude other bridges. The report also pointed out that those deemed unsuitable for Uniswap's present cross-chain governance needs might still satisfy the prerequisites of other protocols and applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Vulnerabilities and Controversies: The Story of Cross-Chain Bridges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The controversy around cross-chain bridges in the Web3 sphere is nothing new. In 2022, these bridging protocols proved to be a weak spot, with hackers successfully exploiting them and causing billions in losses. As per data from Rekt, four out of the top five most expensive DeFi breaches targeted bridges, resulting in an aggregated loss of over $2.1 billion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to these vulnerabilities, Uniswap has formed its Cross-Chain Bridge Assessment Committee to aid governance delegates and the Uniswap community in making well-informed decisions regarding cross-chain bridging protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Committee's evaluations covered more than 130 assessment questions for each protocol, taking into account their ability to ensure "safety, liveness, and censorship resistance". Looking ahead, Celer and DeBridge might be reassessed despite their current shortcomings in slashing mechanisms and security assurances. The report was notably critical of Multichain for its lack of transparency and ineffective deterrents to prevent validator collusion.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To underscore the context, Uniswap has over $5.9 billion locked in its protocol as of May 2023, with daily transaction volume frequently exceeding $1 billion. Given these figures, Uniswap's choice of Wormhole and Axelar could have significant implications for both the involved protocols and Uniswap's ongoing cross-chain operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Nike Teases Airphoria NFT Collab With Fortnite and Unreal Engine]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/nike-teases-airphoria-nft-collab-with-fortnite-and-unreal-engine</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nike-dotswoosh-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/nike-teases-airphoria-nft-collab-with-fortnite-and-unreal-engine</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike, a titan in the world of footwear and apparel, has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move: introducing a collection of sneaker nonfungible tokens (NFTs) in Fortnite, the massively popular online game developed by Epic Games.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Rumors of Airphoria: A Possible Revolution in the Gaming Industry</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a series of June 16 social media posts, Nike teased an event set for June 20, which they termed the "ultimate Sneakerhunt". A promotional video showcased the logos of both Fortnite and Nike's Air Max amidst floating clouds. As the video transitions, it unveils the name of this intriguing venture, 'Airphoria', ending with a display of Nike's Web3 platform .SWOOSH logo alongside that of Epic Games' Unreal Engine.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">On 6.20 the ultimate Sneakerhunt begins. AirphoriaAirphoria pic.twitter.com/QgMyA1uXRT</p>
&mdash; Nike (@Nike) June 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">However, specific details remain elusive. Members of the NFT community have begun to speculate that Nike might have employed Fortnite Creative 2.0, a tool that allows users to craft their own virtual island game maps utilizing Fortnite assets, to devise an NFT-related game.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Leap Into Web3 for Nike with .SWOOSH</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This wouldn't be Nike's first foray into gaming. The company has been stepping up its efforts to merge its NFT unit, .SWOOSH, into traditional gaming. Just recently, on June 1, .SWOOSH announced its intention to incorporate its NFTs into games developed by EA Sports, a household name responsible for the incredibly successful FIFA soccer game franchise, among others. Although it's still not confirmed which EA Sports games will incorporate Nike NFTs, this latest hint seems to suggest that Nike's integration into the gaming world might be deeper than previously anticipated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although not yet confirmed, the probability of NFTs featuring in Airphoria is high, given .SWOOSH's involvement and Epic Games' known affinity for NFT gaming. If the speculations prove to be true, the move could provide a considerable opportunity for Web3 adoption amongst traditional gamers. Considering Fortnite's impressive player base of over 242.9 million active players in the past 30 days, as reported by Active Player, the potential impact could be monumental.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike has previously launched NFT sneakers on Polygon, as well as an earlier collaboration with RTFKT. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike, a titan in the world of footwear and apparel, has started dropping hints about a potentially massive move: introducing a collection of sneaker nonfungible tokens (NFTs) in Fortnite, the massively popular online game developed by Epic Games.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Rumors of Airphoria: A Possible Revolution in the Gaming Industry</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">In a series of June 16 social media posts, Nike teased an event set for June 20, which they termed the "ultimate Sneakerhunt". A promotional video showcased the logos of both Fortnite and Nike's Air Max amidst floating clouds. As the video transitions, it unveils the name of this intriguing venture, 'Airphoria', ending with a display of Nike's Web3 platform .SWOOSH logo alongside that of Epic Games' Unreal Engine.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">On 6.20 the ultimate Sneakerhunt begins. AirphoriaAirphoria pic.twitter.com/QgMyA1uXRT</p>
&mdash; Nike (@Nike) June 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">However, specific details remain elusive. Members of the NFT community have begun to speculate that Nike might have employed Fortnite Creative 2.0, a tool that allows users to craft their own virtual island game maps utilizing Fortnite assets, to devise an NFT-related game.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Leap Into Web3 for Nike with .SWOOSH</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This wouldn't be Nike's first foray into gaming. The company has been stepping up its efforts to merge its NFT unit, .SWOOSH, into traditional gaming. Just recently, on June 1, .SWOOSH announced its intention to incorporate its NFTs into games developed by EA Sports, a household name responsible for the incredibly successful FIFA soccer game franchise, among others. Although it's still not confirmed which EA Sports games will incorporate Nike NFTs, this latest hint seems to suggest that Nike's integration into the gaming world might be deeper than previously anticipated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although not yet confirmed, the probability of NFTs featuring in Airphoria is high, given .SWOOSH's involvement and Epic Games' known affinity for NFT gaming. If the speculations prove to be true, the move could provide a considerable opportunity for Web3 adoption amongst traditional gamers. Considering Fortnite's impressive player base of over 242.9 million active players in the past 30 days, as reported by Active Player, the potential impact could be monumental.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Nike has previously launched NFT sneakers on Polygon, as well as an earlier collaboration with RTFKT. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Why Blackrock Bitcoin spot ETF is a real worry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/why-blackrock-bitcoin-spot-etf-is-a-real-worry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/black.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:11:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/why-blackrock-bitcoin-spot-etf-is-a-real-worry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With Blackrock&rsquo;s recent spot ETF application many Bitcoincoiners are elated. However, should they be worried about this particular move by the $10 trillion asset manager?</p>

<p>&ldquo;I have not heard from any one client looking to buy a cryptocurrency at this time. Right now I can tell you that Worldwide, I have not heard from one client that said I need to be in this.</p>

<p>Larry Fink.</p>
<p>The Blackrock CEO did go on to say back in 2018 that his company would look back into crypto when it became more &ldquo;legitimised&rdquo;. Nearly 5 years later Blackrock is doing exactly that - but with crypto being singled out for extremely rough treatment from the SEC it could hardly be said that crypto has reached the legitimacy stage.</p>
<p>When such a massive and powerful institutional entity as Blackrock files an application for a Bitcoin ETF, when so many have failed, it might be guessed that there will have been some quiet conversations behind the scenes, and that some plan could be in place to exert control over the premier crypto asset.</p>
The Blackrock ESG commitment
<p>Larry Fink has said that he and his company are committed to pushing its ESG agenda.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;You have to force behaviours, and at Blackrock we are forcing behaviours&rdquo;</p>

<p>With Fink serving as a Trustee on the board of Klaus Schwab&rsquo;s World Economic Forum, you can be sure that this application for a Bitcoin Spot ETF will somehow play along with the ESG narrative.&nbsp;</p>
How Blackrock could potentially take control
<p>An extremely thought-provoking tweet by @anilsaidso posits how Blackrock could in one fail swoop take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A hidden gem in the BlackRock ETF filing.#GetForked https://t.co/tER6xxZPui pic.twitter.com/Qdt8BZ2OEZ</p>
&mdash; Anil  (@anilsaidso) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Hidden within the filing is what Blackrock would be able to do in the event of a Bitcoin hard fork. This is explosive beyond belief. Bitcoin has already been through hard forks in its history, and thus far the decentralised nature of Bitcoin has always won through, and forks of the original network have not been successful.</p>
<p>What Blackrock is contemplating in the event of a hard fork is that it would get to choose which fork to go with, thereby deciding the future of Bitcoin. And given its love for the ESG narrative, what if Blackrock itself or one of its &lsquo;associates&rsquo; proposed a PoS fork, and then all the institutions with backing of regulators and governments went with this fork and left the original PoW fork in its wake?</p>
Gold and silver were controlled 
<p>Government and institutions were able to use subterfuge to squash the price of gold and silver over many decades so that they would not detract from the power of the dollar. Big banks used massive short selling whenever the prices took off, and were able to build huge positions in the metals, especially J P Morgan.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is very similar to gold and silver in that it is sound money, meaning that it can&rsquo;t be debased by governments in order to backstop banks or pay for wars. Look for the Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF to be approved by an anti-Bitcoin SEC, and then watch what happens very closely.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With Blackrock&rsquo;s recent spot ETF application many Bitcoincoiners are elated. However, should they be worried about this particular move by the $10 trillion asset manager?</p>

<p>&ldquo;I have not heard from any one client looking to buy a cryptocurrency at this time. Right now I can tell you that Worldwide, I have not heard from one client that said I need to be in this.</p>

<p>Larry Fink.</p>
<p>The Blackrock CEO did go on to say back in 2018 that his company would look back into crypto when it became more &ldquo;legitimised&rdquo;. Nearly 5 years later Blackrock is doing exactly that - but with crypto being singled out for extremely rough treatment from the SEC it could hardly be said that crypto has reached the legitimacy stage.</p>
<p>When such a massive and powerful institutional entity as Blackrock files an application for a Bitcoin ETF, when so many have failed, it might be guessed that there will have been some quiet conversations behind the scenes, and that some plan could be in place to exert control over the premier crypto asset.</p>
The Blackrock ESG commitment
<p>Larry Fink has said that he and his company are committed to pushing its ESG agenda.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;You have to force behaviours, and at Blackrock we are forcing behaviours&rdquo;</p>

<p>With Fink serving as a Trustee on the board of Klaus Schwab&rsquo;s World Economic Forum, you can be sure that this application for a Bitcoin Spot ETF will somehow play along with the ESG narrative.&nbsp;</p>
How Blackrock could potentially take control
<p>An extremely thought-provoking tweet by @anilsaidso posits how Blackrock could in one fail swoop take control of Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A hidden gem in the BlackRock ETF filing.#GetForked https://t.co/tER6xxZPui pic.twitter.com/Qdt8BZ2OEZ</p>
&mdash; Anil  (@anilsaidso) June 15, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Hidden within the filing is what Blackrock would be able to do in the event of a Bitcoin hard fork. This is explosive beyond belief. Bitcoin has already been through hard forks in its history, and thus far the decentralised nature of Bitcoin has always won through, and forks of the original network have not been successful.</p>
<p>What Blackrock is contemplating in the event of a hard fork is that it would get to choose which fork to go with, thereby deciding the future of Bitcoin. And given its love for the ESG narrative, what if Blackrock itself or one of its &lsquo;associates&rsquo; proposed a PoS fork, and then all the institutions with backing of regulators and governments went with this fork and left the original PoW fork in its wake?</p>
Gold and silver were controlled 
<p>Government and institutions were able to use subterfuge to squash the price of gold and silver over many decades so that they would not detract from the power of the dollar. Big banks used massive short selling whenever the prices took off, and were able to build huge positions in the metals, especially J P Morgan.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is very similar to gold and silver in that it is sound money, meaning that it can&rsquo;t be debased by governments in order to backstop banks or pay for wars. Look for the Blackrock Bitcoin Spot ETF to be approved by an anti-Bitcoin SEC, and then watch what happens very closely.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wyre To Shut Down As Crypto Winter Claims Another Casualty]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wyre-to-shut-down-as-crypto-winter-claims-another-casualty</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 08:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wyre-to-shut-down-as-crypto-winter-claims-another-casualty</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations. It also noted that interested parties could begin inquiries about purchasing the firm&rsquo;s assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm cited challenges arising from the prolonged bear market and not due to the regulatory conditions prevailing in the US markets.&nbsp;</p>
Bear Market Claims Another Victim&nbsp;
<p>Wyre announced its decision to shutter operations in a tweet on Friday. The decision comes a few months after Bolt Financial canceled its planned $1.5 billion purchase of the crypto payments firm. Since the cancellation of the purchase, the digital asset markets have seen a number of high-profile bankruptcies, such as FTX, along with lawsuits against prominent exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, from The United States Securities and Exchange Commission. The company also stressed that the decision was not due to any direction from regulatory agencies.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After nearly a decade, Wyre is winding down. Due to market conditions, we made this decision to protect the best interest of our key stakeholders and customers. This decision is not due to any regulatory agency direction. Wyre continues to secure customer assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Wyre also stated that customers have until Friday, 14th July 2023, to withdraw their assets via the Wyre dashboard. If customers miss this date, Wyre has laid down a separate process to enable the recovery of assets left on the platform. According to Wyre&rsquo;s blog post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wyre continues to secure customer assets. If you have assets on the Wyre platform, you can continue to withdraw them via Wyre&rsquo;s dashboard until Friday, 14th July. After then, we will have a separate process to recover assets remaining on the platform. We will post details on the process on our website and blog.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Wyre team also seemed to suggest that the company&rsquo;s assets were up for sale and that interested parties could inquire about purchasing the firm or its assets.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you&rsquo;re interested in acquiring Wyre&rsquo;s or its subsidiaries&rsquo; assets, please reach out to 88 Partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Wyre&rsquo;s Troubled Year&nbsp;
<p>Wyre has been in the doldrums since Bolt Financial decided to cancel its planned purchase of the company for $1.5 billion in September 2022. A few months after the failed acquisition, more trouble began for the company as its fiat-to-crypto on-ramp solution provider Juno urged users to withdraw their crypto assets from the Juno platform and self custody them. Given the uncertainty surrounding its custodial partner, Wyre, Juno stated that such a step was necessary.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Juno as a platform doesn&rsquo;t custody crypto assets &amp; relies on our crypto partner for these services. Due to uncertainty with our crypto partner, we have taken preemptive action in the interest of our customers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The very next day, MetaMask also announced that it was ending support of the Wyre platform, citing several reports that the company was planning to shut down. MetaMask announced the news on its official Twitter handle, asking users not to use the Wyre service on the mobile aggregator.&nbsp;</p>
False Dawn&nbsp;
<p>A few days after MetaMask shuttered support for Wyre, the company announced the imposition of a 90% withdrawal limit for all its users. However, this limit was quickly removed following an announcement that Wyre had secured funding from an unnamed strategic partner. However, despite securing funding, Wyre still let go of 75 employees in January 2023. The announcement to mark the firm shutting down operations marks the end of Wyre after the company had explored several strategic options in a bid to stay afloat. The company had stated in January,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue, and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

A Growing List Of Bear Market Casualties&nbsp;
<p>Wyre is the latest in a growing list of crypto companies and blockchain firms that have buckled under the pressure of an unending bear market. Just in May alone, several firms, including Lightning Network payments platform BottlePay, NFT platform Terressa, crypto exchange HotBit, and Digital Currency Group&rsquo;s institutional trading platform TradeBlock, all shuttered operations thanks to the prolonged crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EmpireDAO also ended its tenancy at 190 Bowery in New York, giving further evidence of a market downturn. The crypto-exclusive co-working space was founded by Mike Fraietta, with its office building often touted as the WeWork of Web3. Fraietta stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tried every which way to get new sponsors, partnerships, and even crowdfunding. But we needed more help to sustain at 190 Bowery.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco-based crypto payments firm Wyre has announced that it has begun the process of winding down its operations. It also noted that interested parties could begin inquiries about purchasing the firm&rsquo;s assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The firm cited challenges arising from the prolonged bear market and not due to the regulatory conditions prevailing in the US markets.&nbsp;</p>
Bear Market Claims Another Victim&nbsp;
<p>Wyre announced its decision to shutter operations in a tweet on Friday. The decision comes a few months after Bolt Financial canceled its planned $1.5 billion purchase of the crypto payments firm. Since the cancellation of the purchase, the digital asset markets have seen a number of high-profile bankruptcies, such as FTX, along with lawsuits against prominent exchanges, including Coinbase and Binance, from The United States Securities and Exchange Commission. The company also stressed that the decision was not due to any direction from regulatory agencies.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;After nearly a decade, Wyre is winding down. Due to market conditions, we made this decision to protect the best interest of our key stakeholders and customers. This decision is not due to any regulatory agency direction. Wyre continues to secure customer assets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Wyre also stated that customers have until Friday, 14th July 2023, to withdraw their assets via the Wyre dashboard. If customers miss this date, Wyre has laid down a separate process to enable the recovery of assets left on the platform. According to Wyre&rsquo;s blog post,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Wyre continues to secure customer assets. If you have assets on the Wyre platform, you can continue to withdraw them via Wyre&rsquo;s dashboard until Friday, 14th July. After then, we will have a separate process to recover assets remaining on the platform. We will post details on the process on our website and blog.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Wyre team also seemed to suggest that the company&rsquo;s assets were up for sale and that interested parties could inquire about purchasing the firm or its assets.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you&rsquo;re interested in acquiring Wyre&rsquo;s or its subsidiaries&rsquo; assets, please reach out to 88 Partners.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Wyre&rsquo;s Troubled Year&nbsp;
<p>Wyre has been in the doldrums since Bolt Financial decided to cancel its planned purchase of the company for $1.5 billion in September 2022. A few months after the failed acquisition, more trouble began for the company as its fiat-to-crypto on-ramp solution provider Juno urged users to withdraw their crypto assets from the Juno platform and self custody them. Given the uncertainty surrounding its custodial partner, Wyre, Juno stated that such a step was necessary.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Juno as a platform doesn&rsquo;t custody crypto assets &amp; relies on our crypto partner for these services. Due to uncertainty with our crypto partner, we have taken preemptive action in the interest of our customers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The very next day, MetaMask also announced that it was ending support of the Wyre platform, citing several reports that the company was planning to shut down. MetaMask announced the news on its official Twitter handle, asking users not to use the Wyre service on the mobile aggregator.&nbsp;</p>
False Dawn&nbsp;
<p>A few days after MetaMask shuttered support for Wyre, the company announced the imposition of a 90% withdrawal limit for all its users. However, this limit was quickly removed following an announcement that Wyre had secured funding from an unnamed strategic partner. However, despite securing funding, Wyre still let go of 75 employees in January 2023. The announcement to mark the firm shutting down operations marks the end of Wyre after the company had explored several strategic options in a bid to stay afloat. The company had stated in January,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue, and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

A Growing List Of Bear Market Casualties&nbsp;
<p>Wyre is the latest in a growing list of crypto companies and blockchain firms that have buckled under the pressure of an unending bear market. Just in May alone, several firms, including Lightning Network payments platform BottlePay, NFT platform Terressa, crypto exchange HotBit, and Digital Currency Group&rsquo;s institutional trading platform TradeBlock, all shuttered operations thanks to the prolonged crypto winter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>EmpireDAO also ended its tenancy at 190 Bowery in New York, giving further evidence of a market downturn. The crypto-exclusive co-working space was founded by Mike Fraietta, with its office building often touted as the WeWork of Web3. Fraietta stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We tried every which way to get new sponsors, partnerships, and even crowdfunding. But we needed more help to sustain at 190 Bowery.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Labs and Seoul Metropolitan Government Poised to Drive Blockchain Innovation at Seoul Web 3 Festival]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-and-seoul-metropolitan-government-poised-to-drive-blockchain-innovation-at-seoul-web-3-festival</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_3_7732570265_1686939758pXSAVRTbnQ.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:50:58 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-and-seoul-metropolitan-government-poised-to-drive-blockchain-innovation-at-seoul-web-3-festival</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading Web3 venture fund LBank Labs is excited to announce its partnership with the prestigious Seoul Web 3.0 Festival, hosted by the Seoul Metropolitan Government, the Seoul Design Foundation and Baobab Partners.</p><p>The Seoul Web 3.0 Festival serves as a pivotal platform for industry leaders, innovators, and policymakers to explore the revolutionary potential of Web 3.0 and how the technology can be used for public services. LBank Labs is proud to contribute to this vital conversation by being the main partner of the festival and showcasing the cutting-edge projects it supports.</p><p>The festival will take place from July 31 to August 2 at the iconic Dongdaemun Design Plaza, renowned for its neofuturistic architecture. During the three-day event, representatives of mainstream blockchain projects in South Korea will be invited to discuss hot topics such as DeFi, NFTs, and Metaverse with the Seoul Municipal Government. The hosting of the Seoul Web3 Festival marks a new stage in the Korean blockchain ecosystem.</p><p>The event boasts an impressive lineup of attendees, including public figures such as Seoul Mayor Oh Se-hoon and prominent Korean policymakers. LBank Labs eagerly anticipates the opportunity to further engage with these esteemed guests, exchange ideas, and collaborate on future-focused initiatives that promote the widespread adoption of blockchain technology.</p><p>As the main sponsor and partner, LBank Labs will host an interactive party where visitors can engage with experts, explore innovative solutions, and learn more about the transformative power of blockchain technology. Additionally, LBank Labs will deliver insightful presentations and contribute to panel discussions, sharing valuable expertise and insights into the potential of Web 3.0.</p><p>LBank Labs' involvement at the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival underscores its commitment to fostering innovation and driving the adoption of blockchain technology. By partnering with the Seoul Metropolitan Government, LBank Labs aims to contribute to the growth of the blockchain ecosystem in South Korea and beyond.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Leading Web3 venture fund LBank Labs is excited to announce its partnership with the prestigious Seoul Web 3.0 Festival, hosted by the Seoul Metropolitan Government, the Seoul Design Foundation and Baobab Partners.</p><p>The Seoul Web 3.0 Festival serves as a pivotal platform for industry leaders, innovators, and policymakers to explore the revolutionary potential of Web 3.0 and how the technology can be used for public services. LBank Labs is proud to contribute to this vital conversation by being the main partner of the festival and showcasing the cutting-edge projects it supports.</p><p>The festival will take place from July 31 to August 2 at the iconic Dongdaemun Design Plaza, renowned for its neofuturistic architecture. During the three-day event, representatives of mainstream blockchain projects in South Korea will be invited to discuss hot topics such as DeFi, NFTs, and Metaverse with the Seoul Municipal Government. The hosting of the Seoul Web3 Festival marks a new stage in the Korean blockchain ecosystem.</p><p>The event boasts an impressive lineup of attendees, including public figures such as Seoul Mayor Oh Se-hoon and prominent Korean policymakers. LBank Labs eagerly anticipates the opportunity to further engage with these esteemed guests, exchange ideas, and collaborate on future-focused initiatives that promote the widespread adoption of blockchain technology.</p><p>As the main sponsor and partner, LBank Labs will host an interactive party where visitors can engage with experts, explore innovative solutions, and learn more about the transformative power of blockchain technology. Additionally, LBank Labs will deliver insightful presentations and contribute to panel discussions, sharing valuable expertise and insights into the potential of Web 3.0.</p><p>LBank Labs' involvement at the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival underscores its commitment to fostering innovation and driving the adoption of blockchain technology. By partnering with the Seoul Metropolitan Government, LBank Labs aims to contribute to the growth of the blockchain ecosystem in South Korea and beyond.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrency.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  25604 Selling Pressure - 17 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25604-selling-pressure-17-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-june-2023-720-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-25604-selling-pressure-17-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25604 Selling Pressure:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered selling pressure early in the Asian session as the pair tumbled to the 25143.24 area after technical selling pressure emerged around the 25604.52 level, a previous downside price objective linked to selling pressure in mid-May.&nbsp; &nbsp;The pair&rsquo;s depreciation slowed when BTC/USD tested the 61.8% retracement of the recent short-term appreciating range from 24750 to 25749.99.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 25915.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25347.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD 25604 Selling Pressure:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered selling pressure early in the Asian session as the pair tumbled to the 25143.24 area after technical selling pressure emerged around the 25604.52 level, a previous downside price objective linked to selling pressure in mid-May.&nbsp; &nbsp;The pair&rsquo;s depreciation slowed when BTC/USD tested the 61.8% retracement of the recent short-term appreciating range from 24750 to 25749.99.&nbsp; Large Stops are cited below the 24660 and 24568 levels, and bears are eyeing the 23196.08 area as a significant downside price objective.&nbsp; Above the market, Stops are cited above the 26544, 26912, 27281, 27737, and 27805 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Below the market, downside price objectives include the 25323.24 and 24680.87 levels.&nbsp; Notably, the 25309.26 area represents the 50% retracement of the appreciating range from 19568.52 to 30825.30.&nbsp; Stops are also cited below major retracement levels linked to the 19568.52 and 15460 levels, including the 25094, 23954, 23255, 22278, 22025, 21415, 19139, and 18796 areas.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 27528, 27737, 27805, 28200, 28473, and 28873 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 25915.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 25347.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKX and McLaren Racing Host Panel on Technology in Sports and Film at Tribeca Festival]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-and-mclaren-racing-host-panel-on-technology-in-sports-and-film-at-tribeca-festival</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blog-1600x844-8-16867035833jj2v7butl.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-and-mclaren-racing-host-panel-on-technology-in-sports-and-film-at-tribeca-festival</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York City, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>
<ul>
<li>Panelists included OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay</li>
</ul>
<p>From left to right: Director, producer, and screenwriter Stephen Kay; McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown; Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain; OKX CMO Haider Rafique; and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris discuss the power of technology in sports, film and crypto</p>
<p>OKX, a leading Web3 technology company, yesterday hosted a panel discussion with McLaren Racing at the Tribeca Festival titled, "Need for Speed: How Technology Powers Change in Sports, Movies, and Crypto," featuring OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris, and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay.</p>
<p>The panel, moderated by Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain, was held at the Tribeca Screening Room and focused on how technology has transformed various industries, including sports, entertainment, cryptocurrency and finance. During the discussion, the panelists emphasized the impact of innovation on speed, performance and efficiency across the different sectors.</p>
OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: &ldquo;We've achieved a lot together in just one year. The McLaren F1 team has a huge appetite to lean into Web3 and make its heritage more discoverable for younger generations, and we want to play a big role in making that a reality for them. There are incredible stories here that can motivate the next generation of drivers and fans to get involved with the sport and, in particular, celebrate McLaren's achievements on and off track. Our goal is to help McLaren transcend into this future and share what we are cooking together on our panel".
McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown said: &ldquo;This panel was a great opportunity to share the stage with our Primary Partner OKX, and discuss how technology can power change in our respective industries. In Formula 1, we constantly look to innovate and leverage technology to maximize our fan engagement opportunities. Partners like OKX can support us in these commitments, exploring how they can guide our Web3 strategy and make our sport ever-more exciting and accessible for the fans.&rdquo;
<p>OKX CMO Haider Rafique (left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (right)</p>
<p>McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown (in orange, left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (in orange, right) with OKX CMO Haider Rafique</p>
<p>Tribeca Festival 2023 is OKX&rsquo;s second consecutive year as the presenting sponsor. The company's multi-year partnership with Tribeca Festival aims to unlock new Web3 opportunities for creators, fans and talent. OKX also introduced the first-ever Tribeca Festival NFT pass for 2023 in January.</p>
<p>In May of last year, OKX and McLaren Racing announced a multi-year partnership that would make OKX a Primary Partner of the McLaren Formula 1 Team and McLaren Shadow esports team. Through this partnership, OKX supports the team&rsquo;s global fan experience, providing exciting opportunities and product innovations that bring fans closer to the action. OKX branding is featured on the McLaren cars, the helmets of McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, as well as the McLaren F1 and McLaren Shadow team kits.</p>
About OKX
<p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace and DEX.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX Web3, download our app or visit: okx.com/web3</p>
About McLaren Racing
<p>McLaren Racing was founded by racing driver Bruce McLaren 60 years ago in 1963. The team entered its first Formula 1 race in 1966. McLaren has since won 20 Formula 1 world championships, 183 Formula 1 grands prix, the Indianapolis 500 three times, and the Le Mans 24 Hours at its first attempt.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing competes across five racing series. In 2023, the team will compete in the FIA Formula 1 World Championship with McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, the NTT INDYCAR SERIES with Arrow McLaren drivers Pato O&rsquo;Ward, Felix Rosenqvist and Alexander Rossi, the ABB FIA Formula E World Championship with NEOM McLaren Formula E Team drivers Ren&eacute; Rast and Jake Hughes, and the Extreme E Championship with NEOM McLaren Extreme E Team drivers Emma Gilmour and Tanner Foust. The team also competes in the F1 Esports Pro Championship as McLaren Shadow, having won the 2022 Constructors&rsquo; and Drivers&rsquo; Championships.</p>
<p>McLaren is a champion for sustainability in the sport and a signatory to the UN Sports for Climate Action Commitment. It is committed to achieving net zero by 2040 and fostering a diverse and inclusive culture in the motorsport industry.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing &ndash; Official Website</p>
About the Tribeca Festival
<p>The Tribeca Festival, presented by OKX, brings artists and diverse audiences together to celebrate storytelling in all its forms, including film, TV, immersive, games, audio storytelling, music, and online work. With strong roots in independent film, Tribeca is a platform for creative expression and immersive entertainment. Tribeca champions emerging and established voices; discovers award-winning filmmakers and creators; curates innovative experiences; and introduces new technology and ideas through premieres, exhibitions, talks, and live performances.</p>
<p>The Festival was founded by Robert De Niro, Jane Rosenthal, and Craig Hatkoff in 2001 to spur the economic and cultural revitalization of lower Manhattan following the attacks on the World Trade Center. Tribeca will celebrate its 22nd year from June 7&ndash;18, 2023.</p>
<p>In 2019, James Murdoch&rsquo;s Lupa Systems, a private investment company with locations in New York and Mumbai, bought a majority stake in Tribeca Enterprises, bringing together Rosenthal, De Niro, and Murdoch to grow the enterprise.</p>
Disclaimer
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your risk tolerance and financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
Contact
<p>Pressmedia@okx.com</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York City, New York, June 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p>
<ul>
<li>Panelists included OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay</li>
</ul>
<p>From left to right: Director, producer, and screenwriter Stephen Kay; McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown; Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain; OKX CMO Haider Rafique; and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris discuss the power of technology in sports, film and crypto</p>
<p>OKX, a leading Web3 technology company, yesterday hosted a panel discussion with McLaren Racing at the Tribeca Festival titled, "Need for Speed: How Technology Powers Change in Sports, Movies, and Crypto," featuring OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique, McLaren Racing Chief Executive Officer Zak Brown, McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris, and director, producer and screenwriter Stephen Kay.</p>
<p>The panel, moderated by Emmy-nominated filmmaker and Webby Awards Founder Tiffany Shlain, was held at the Tribeca Screening Room and focused on how technology has transformed various industries, including sports, entertainment, cryptocurrency and finance. During the discussion, the panelists emphasized the impact of innovation on speed, performance and efficiency across the different sectors.</p>
OKX Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique said: &ldquo;We've achieved a lot together in just one year. The McLaren F1 team has a huge appetite to lean into Web3 and make its heritage more discoverable for younger generations, and we want to play a big role in making that a reality for them. There are incredible stories here that can motivate the next generation of drivers and fans to get involved with the sport and, in particular, celebrate McLaren's achievements on and off track. Our goal is to help McLaren transcend into this future and share what we are cooking together on our panel".
McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown said: &ldquo;This panel was a great opportunity to share the stage with our Primary Partner OKX, and discuss how technology can power change in our respective industries. In Formula 1, we constantly look to innovate and leverage technology to maximize our fan engagement opportunities. Partners like OKX can support us in these commitments, exploring how they can guide our Web3 strategy and make our sport ever-more exciting and accessible for the fans.&rdquo;
<p>OKX CMO Haider Rafique (left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (right)</p>
<p>McLaren Racing CEO Zak Brown (in orange, left) and McLaren F1 Driver Lando Norris (in orange, right) with OKX CMO Haider Rafique</p>
<p>Tribeca Festival 2023 is OKX&rsquo;s second consecutive year as the presenting sponsor. The company's multi-year partnership with Tribeca Festival aims to unlock new Web3 opportunities for creators, fans and talent. OKX also introduced the first-ever Tribeca Festival NFT pass for 2023 in January.</p>
<p>In May of last year, OKX and McLaren Racing announced a multi-year partnership that would make OKX a Primary Partner of the McLaren Formula 1 Team and McLaren Shadow esports team. Through this partnership, OKX supports the team&rsquo;s global fan experience, providing exciting opportunities and product innovations that bring fans closer to the action. OKX branding is featured on the McLaren cars, the helmets of McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, as well as the McLaren F1 and McLaren Shadow team kits.</p>
About OKX
<p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace and DEX.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX Web3, download our app or visit: okx.com/web3</p>
About McLaren Racing
<p>McLaren Racing was founded by racing driver Bruce McLaren 60 years ago in 1963. The team entered its first Formula 1 race in 1966. McLaren has since won 20 Formula 1 world championships, 183 Formula 1 grands prix, the Indianapolis 500 three times, and the Le Mans 24 Hours at its first attempt.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing competes across five racing series. In 2023, the team will compete in the FIA Formula 1 World Championship with McLaren F1 drivers Lando Norris and Oscar Piastri, the NTT INDYCAR SERIES with Arrow McLaren drivers Pato O&rsquo;Ward, Felix Rosenqvist and Alexander Rossi, the ABB FIA Formula E World Championship with NEOM McLaren Formula E Team drivers Ren&eacute; Rast and Jake Hughes, and the Extreme E Championship with NEOM McLaren Extreme E Team drivers Emma Gilmour and Tanner Foust. The team also competes in the F1 Esports Pro Championship as McLaren Shadow, having won the 2022 Constructors&rsquo; and Drivers&rsquo; Championships.</p>
<p>McLaren is a champion for sustainability in the sport and a signatory to the UN Sports for Climate Action Commitment. It is committed to achieving net zero by 2040 and fostering a diverse and inclusive culture in the motorsport industry.</p>
<p>McLaren Racing &ndash; Official Website</p>
About the Tribeca Festival
<p>The Tribeca Festival, presented by OKX, brings artists and diverse audiences together to celebrate storytelling in all its forms, including film, TV, immersive, games, audio storytelling, music, and online work. With strong roots in independent film, Tribeca is a platform for creative expression and immersive entertainment. Tribeca champions emerging and established voices; discovers award-winning filmmakers and creators; curates innovative experiences; and introduces new technology and ideas through premieres, exhibitions, talks, and live performances.</p>
<p>The Festival was founded by Robert De Niro, Jane Rosenthal, and Craig Hatkoff in 2001 to spur the economic and cultural revitalization of lower Manhattan following the attacks on the World Trade Center. Tribeca will celebrate its 22nd year from June 7&ndash;18, 2023.</p>
<p>In 2019, James Murdoch&rsquo;s Lupa Systems, a private investment company with locations in New York and Mumbai, bought a majority stake in Tribeca Enterprises, bringing together Rosenthal, De Niro, and Murdoch to grow the enterprise.</p>
Disclaimer
<p>This announcement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not intended to provide any investment, tax, or legal advice, nor should it be considered an offer to purchase, sell, or hold digital assets. Digital assets, including stablecoins, involve a high degree of risk, can fluctuate greatly, and can even become worthless. You should carefully consider whether trading or holding digital assets is suitable for you in light of your risk tolerance and financial condition. Please consult your legal/tax/investment professional for questions about your specific circumstances.</p>
Contact
<p>Pressmedia@okx.com</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Traders ask ChatGPT for price prediction: Binance coin, Bitcoin, Tradecurve]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-traders-ask-chatgpt-for-price-prediction-binance-coin-bitcoin-tradecurve</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-83.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-traders-ask-chatgpt-for-price-prediction-binance-coin-bitcoin-tradecurve</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of Artificial Intelligence, companies are consistently pushing for new technological advancements and investing millions towards creating the best possible chatbot that users can utilize to get the information they need with ease, and one of the most recent use cases has been making price predictions for the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency traders are now asking ChatGPT, the most popular AI-driven chatbot globally, to tell them everything they need to know surrounding the future value of Binance coin, Tradecurve, and Bitcoin during the current bear market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Asking ChatGPT About Binance coin
<p>According to ChatGPT, the price of Binance coin at the end of 2023 is difficult to predict with 100% accuracy; however, based on the current market conditions and historical price data, the AI is able to make some educated guesses as to how far it can climb.</p>
<p>On June 9, 2023, Binance coin traded at $259.21 per coin. This represents a lower point of value than the one Binance coin had at the start of the month, but there are factors that could impact its price in the future, including Binance's continued push towards creating new features and products, market demand, and overall regulatory compliance of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Binance coin at the end of 2023, according to some piece predictions made for the Binance coin, places it at a value of $465.85.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
The Answers ChatGPT Gave for Bitcoin
<p>The price of Bitcoin as of June 9, 2023, is at $26,607.05. Analysts went to ChatGPT to get accurate predictions about the future of Bitcoin. However, the AI did note that nothing can be predicted with 100% certainty.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The key factors that can affect the value of Bitcoin, according to ChatGPT, include the overall momentum of the market, mainstream adoption of the Bitcoin cryptocurrency, and the development of new, innovative features on top of the network or the creation of Layer-2 scaling solutions for it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin at the end of 2023 could see an increase, however, and based on estimates, BTC is expected to reach $65,000 by the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
What ChatGPT Thinks about The Performance of Tradecurve
<p>Investors and traders are also curious about new projects, and Tradecurve has stood out due to its popularity, appeal, and the freedom it provides investors as it does not require KYC checks whilst also having the lowest fees in the industry.</p>
<p>Tradecurve is a hybrid exchange that combines the best elements of CEXs and DEXs to provide a truly unique, decentralized experience that will enable anyone on a global scale access to markets that are otherwise unavailable to them due to banking restrictions or regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Each user of Tradecurve can effectively and effortlessly trade cryptocurrencies, as well as any other derivative, from one account while also maintaining privacy through the platform's DeFi capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is the utility token behind the platform, and it is currently undergoing Stage 3 of its presale, where it is offered at $0.015.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When asked about the future of the cryptocurrency, ChatGPT noted how it could climb to 100x at launch, bringing it to $1.5 in value, because of the increased demand for such a solution after heightened regulation of CEXs, and because of the fast sales of the TCRV tokens, where the team has already sold millions of tokens and can generate $20 million before the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of Artificial Intelligence, companies are consistently pushing for new technological advancements and investing millions towards creating the best possible chatbot that users can utilize to get the information they need with ease, and one of the most recent use cases has been making price predictions for the crypto market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency traders are now asking ChatGPT, the most popular AI-driven chatbot globally, to tell them everything they need to know surrounding the future value of Binance coin, Tradecurve, and Bitcoin during the current bear market.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Asking ChatGPT About Binance coin
<p>According to ChatGPT, the price of Binance coin at the end of 2023 is difficult to predict with 100% accuracy; however, based on the current market conditions and historical price data, the AI is able to make some educated guesses as to how far it can climb.</p>
<p>On June 9, 2023, Binance coin traded at $259.21 per coin. This represents a lower point of value than the one Binance coin had at the start of the month, but there are factors that could impact its price in the future, including Binance's continued push towards creating new features and products, market demand, and overall regulatory compliance of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Binance coin at the end of 2023, according to some piece predictions made for the Binance coin, places it at a value of $465.85.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
The Answers ChatGPT Gave for Bitcoin
<p>The price of Bitcoin as of June 9, 2023, is at $26,607.05. Analysts went to ChatGPT to get accurate predictions about the future of Bitcoin. However, the AI did note that nothing can be predicted with 100% certainty.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The key factors that can affect the value of Bitcoin, according to ChatGPT, include the overall momentum of the market, mainstream adoption of the Bitcoin cryptocurrency, and the development of new, innovative features on top of the network or the creation of Layer-2 scaling solutions for it.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Bitcoin at the end of 2023 could see an increase, however, and based on estimates, BTC is expected to reach $65,000 by the end of the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
What ChatGPT Thinks about The Performance of Tradecurve
<p>Investors and traders are also curious about new projects, and Tradecurve has stood out due to its popularity, appeal, and the freedom it provides investors as it does not require KYC checks whilst also having the lowest fees in the industry.</p>
<p>Tradecurve is a hybrid exchange that combines the best elements of CEXs and DEXs to provide a truly unique, decentralized experience that will enable anyone on a global scale access to markets that are otherwise unavailable to them due to banking restrictions or regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Each user of Tradecurve can effectively and effortlessly trade cryptocurrencies, as well as any other derivative, from one account while also maintaining privacy through the platform's DeFi capabilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is the utility token behind the platform, and it is currently undergoing Stage 3 of its presale, where it is offered at $0.015.&nbsp;</p>
<p>When asked about the future of the cryptocurrency, ChatGPT noted how it could climb to 100x at launch, bringing it to $1.5 in value, because of the increased demand for such a solution after heightened regulation of CEXs, and because of the fast sales of the TCRV tokens, where the team has already sold millions of tokens and can generate $20 million before the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV token below:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will 10x Says Michael Saylor, This New Hybrid Exchange Plans to Overtake Binance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-will-10x-says-michael-saylor-this-new-hybrid-exchange-plans-to-overtake-binance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-84.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-will-10x-says-michael-saylor-this-new-hybrid-exchange-plans-to-overtake-binance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The popular Bitcoin investor and permabull, Michael Saylor, has released a new prediction for Bitcoin. Saylor has said that under the right conditions, the price of Bitcoin will jump by 10x to set a new trading high at $250,000. In other news, Tradecurve, a new hybrid exchange has outlined plans to overtake Binance as the number one crypto exchange, and some experts believe it is possible.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Michael Saylor has predicted a 10x price jump for Bitcoin, predicting the crypto will trade as high as $250,000 in the next bull run.</li>
<li>According to Saylor, regulatory clarity will be the catalyst for the next bull run.</li>
<li>While Binance suffers due to regulatory clarity, a new hybrid exchange has tapped into markets that could see it overtake the number one crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
Michael Saylor Predicts 10x Price Jump for Bitcoin (BTC)
<p>In an interview with Bloomberg, Michael Saylor, the co-founder of Microstrategy, an enterprise business intelligence provider, predicted that the price of Bitcoin could jump by 10x. In explaining the reasoning for his prediction, Saylor said regulatory clarity in the U.S. will drive the next Bitcoin rally.</p>
<p>The presence of regulatory clarity will encourage venture capitalists that have avoided cryptocurrencies to jump into the industry. He adds that the recent crackdown on many top crypto exchanges by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) would lay the groundwork for the next major Bitcoin bull run.</p>
<p>Congress is already working on a unified crypto regulatory framework and assigning crypto-specific roles to SEC and CFTC, meaning the next Bitcoin bull run couldn&rsquo;t be far away. If Saylor&rsquo;s prediction holds true, we would witness Bitcoin set a new all-time high at $250,000, beating its previous ATH at $68,789.</p>
<p></p>
Binance Has a New Challenger, And the Hybrid Exchange Could Overtake It
<p>On the journey to regulatory clarity for the cryptocurrency industry, the leading crypto exchange, Binance, has been caught in the web of the SEC. The crackdown on centralized exchanges has opened a window for the newer hybrid exchanges, which many crypto experts have called the future of crypto trading because they combine the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>One hybrid exchange, Tradecurve, has set out to challenge the dominance of Binance by incorporating into its platform trading features that Binance lack, including more trading options (forex and derivatives), negative balance protection, self-management of private keys, low latency ultra-fast order execution, and algorithmic trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By looking to offer wider assets for trading and features that will make for a seamless trading experience, Tradecurve plans to topple Binance as the number one crypto trading platform. With the current regulatory crackdown on Binance, many crypto analysts believe Tradecurve has a chance to steal market share from Binance to reduce its dominance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is on track to enact its plan, currently in the fourth presale phase expecting to raise $20 million to launch its platform. The project has enjoyed massive support from investors currently buying its native token, TCRV, at $0.018 per token.</p>
<p>Visit the links below to get more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The popular Bitcoin investor and permabull, Michael Saylor, has released a new prediction for Bitcoin. Saylor has said that under the right conditions, the price of Bitcoin will jump by 10x to set a new trading high at $250,000. In other news, Tradecurve, a new hybrid exchange has outlined plans to overtake Binance as the number one crypto exchange, and some experts believe it is possible.&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>Michael Saylor has predicted a 10x price jump for Bitcoin, predicting the crypto will trade as high as $250,000 in the next bull run.</li>
<li>According to Saylor, regulatory clarity will be the catalyst for the next bull run.</li>
<li>While Binance suffers due to regulatory clarity, a new hybrid exchange has tapped into markets that could see it overtake the number one crypto exchange.</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
Michael Saylor Predicts 10x Price Jump for Bitcoin (BTC)
<p>In an interview with Bloomberg, Michael Saylor, the co-founder of Microstrategy, an enterprise business intelligence provider, predicted that the price of Bitcoin could jump by 10x. In explaining the reasoning for his prediction, Saylor said regulatory clarity in the U.S. will drive the next Bitcoin rally.</p>
<p>The presence of regulatory clarity will encourage venture capitalists that have avoided cryptocurrencies to jump into the industry. He adds that the recent crackdown on many top crypto exchanges by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) would lay the groundwork for the next major Bitcoin bull run.</p>
<p>Congress is already working on a unified crypto regulatory framework and assigning crypto-specific roles to SEC and CFTC, meaning the next Bitcoin bull run couldn&rsquo;t be far away. If Saylor&rsquo;s prediction holds true, we would witness Bitcoin set a new all-time high at $250,000, beating its previous ATH at $68,789.</p>
<p></p>
Binance Has a New Challenger, And the Hybrid Exchange Could Overtake It
<p>On the journey to regulatory clarity for the cryptocurrency industry, the leading crypto exchange, Binance, has been caught in the web of the SEC. The crackdown on centralized exchanges has opened a window for the newer hybrid exchanges, which many crypto experts have called the future of crypto trading because they combine the best features of centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>One hybrid exchange, Tradecurve, has set out to challenge the dominance of Binance by incorporating into its platform trading features that Binance lack, including more trading options (forex and derivatives), negative balance protection, self-management of private keys, low latency ultra-fast order execution, and algorithmic trading.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By looking to offer wider assets for trading and features that will make for a seamless trading experience, Tradecurve plans to topple Binance as the number one crypto trading platform. With the current regulatory crackdown on Binance, many crypto analysts believe Tradecurve has a chance to steal market share from Binance to reduce its dominance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is on track to enact its plan, currently in the fourth presale phase expecting to raise $20 million to launch its platform. The project has enjoyed massive support from investors currently buying its native token, TCRV, at $0.018 per token.</p>
<p>Visit the links below to get more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token:</p>
<p>Click Here For the Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Frax Finance Unveils Plans For Its Ethereum L2]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/frax-finance-unveils-plans-for-its-ethereum-l2</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/frax-finance-fraxchain-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/frax-finance-fraxchain-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/frax-finance-fraxchain-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/frax-finance-unveils-plans-for-its-ethereum-l2</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Frax Finance, creators of one of the most innovative decentralized stablecoins and DeFi-focused stablecoin infrastructure, has unveiled its plans to roll out an Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain, aptly named Fraxchain. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The objective is simple but ambitious: to cultivate a smart contract platform with an unwavering focus on decentralized finance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Frax Protocol: A Trio of Stablecoins and Integrated Subprotocols</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Frax Protocol represents a pioneering development in the crypto world. At its core, it issues three distinct decentralized stablecoins: FRAX, a USD pegged asset; the Frax Price Index (FPI) stablecoin, which uniquely ties its value to a basket of consumer goods, creating a new unit of account independent of national currencies; and FraxEther (frxETH), a stablecoin pegged to ETH, designed to replace WETH in smart contracts. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Complementing these stablecoins, the protocol also houses three subprotocols: Fraxlend, Fraxswap, and Fraxferry. Fraxswap, the first Automated Market Maker (AMM) using time-weighted average market maker orders, helps in rebalancing collateral, minting/redemptions, adjusting stablecoin supply, and deploying protocol-owned liquidity on-chain. Fraxlend creates a lending market for Frax-based stablecoins, allowing the origination of debt, bespoke non-custodial loans, and the incorporation of collateral assets into the Frax Finance economy. Lastly, Fraxferry enables the transfer of Frax Protocol tokens across multiple blockchains. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Frax Share (FXS) serves as the primary governance token across the Frax ecosystem, accruing fees, revenue, and excess collateral value. An additional governance token, FPIS, is specific to the FPI and shares its value capture with FXS holders. A Gauge Rewards System allows the community to propose rewards for strategies that integrate Frax-based stablecoins. The fixed, halving annual FXS emissions flow to different gauges based on veFXS staker votes.</p>
Frax Finance Sets Sights on Layer 2 with Fraxchain
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain, a project by the makers of the Frax stablecoin, is set to strengthen the hold of decentralized finance in the blockchain landscape. &ldquo;Fraxchain marks the zenith of the entire Frax ecosystem and mirrors the traction and usage we&rsquo;ve attained,&rdquo; Frax founder Sam Kazemian explains.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Glimpse into the Fraxchain Framework</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The slated release date for this network is by the end of this calendar year. The network's governance will hinge on the holders of Frax Shares (FXS) tokens. The modus operandi of the network includes leveraging the Frax stablecoin and Frax Ether, the project's liquid staking derivative, for transaction fees. What's more, the fees garnered by the roll-up network could partially be burned or funneled back to the Ethereum mainnet, to be dispersed among stakers of the FXS governance token, Kazemian outlined. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain hinges on a Layer 2 rollup model. In this arrangement, it will publish state roots to the Ethereum mainnet for securing the network. The rollup network will also incorporate decentralized sequencers&mdash;these nodes order transactions into batches in a rollup network. Any entity can operate them, as long as they secure the nod via a governance vote. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kazemian further elaborated on this feature:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Fraxchain proposes a solution where sequencer roles can be auctioned off and rotated, creating a decentralized sequencer base. If a sequencer is forced to shut down, Fraxchain would allow the next elected sequencer to pick up from where the previous one left off,&rdquo; he explained. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain: By the Numbers</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As per the numbers, Frax's ecosystem has made a significant mark on the world of crypto. As of this writing, the total supply of Frax stands at over $1.23 billion, while Frax Shares (FXS) have a market cap exceeding $371 million. The Frax stablecoin is listed on major exchanges and is integrated into numerous DeFi platforms, while FXS token is used for governance decisions, further cementing its position in the decentralized finance space.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Fraxchain encapsulates the pivotal move of Frax Finance to fortify its position in the DeFi world. It will be interesting to monitor the progress of this Layer 2 solution, with an eye on the continued growth and traction of the Frax ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Frax Finance, creators of one of the most innovative decentralized stablecoins and DeFi-focused stablecoin infrastructure, has unveiled its plans to roll out an Ethereum Layer 2 blockchain, aptly named Fraxchain. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The objective is simple but ambitious: to cultivate a smart contract platform with an unwavering focus on decentralized finance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Frax Protocol: A Trio of Stablecoins and Integrated Subprotocols</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Frax Protocol represents a pioneering development in the crypto world. At its core, it issues three distinct decentralized stablecoins: FRAX, a USD pegged asset; the Frax Price Index (FPI) stablecoin, which uniquely ties its value to a basket of consumer goods, creating a new unit of account independent of national currencies; and FraxEther (frxETH), a stablecoin pegged to ETH, designed to replace WETH in smart contracts. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Complementing these stablecoins, the protocol also houses three subprotocols: Fraxlend, Fraxswap, and Fraxferry. Fraxswap, the first Automated Market Maker (AMM) using time-weighted average market maker orders, helps in rebalancing collateral, minting/redemptions, adjusting stablecoin supply, and deploying protocol-owned liquidity on-chain. Fraxlend creates a lending market for Frax-based stablecoins, allowing the origination of debt, bespoke non-custodial loans, and the incorporation of collateral assets into the Frax Finance economy. Lastly, Fraxferry enables the transfer of Frax Protocol tokens across multiple blockchains. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Frax Share (FXS) serves as the primary governance token across the Frax ecosystem, accruing fees, revenue, and excess collateral value. An additional governance token, FPIS, is specific to the FPI and shares its value capture with FXS holders. A Gauge Rewards System allows the community to propose rewards for strategies that integrate Frax-based stablecoins. The fixed, halving annual FXS emissions flow to different gauges based on veFXS staker votes.</p>
Frax Finance Sets Sights on Layer 2 with Fraxchain
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain, a project by the makers of the Frax stablecoin, is set to strengthen the hold of decentralized finance in the blockchain landscape. &ldquo;Fraxchain marks the zenith of the entire Frax ecosystem and mirrors the traction and usage we&rsquo;ve attained,&rdquo; Frax founder Sam Kazemian explains.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Glimpse into the Fraxchain Framework</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The slated release date for this network is by the end of this calendar year. The network's governance will hinge on the holders of Frax Shares (FXS) tokens. The modus operandi of the network includes leveraging the Frax stablecoin and Frax Ether, the project's liquid staking derivative, for transaction fees. What's more, the fees garnered by the roll-up network could partially be burned or funneled back to the Ethereum mainnet, to be dispersed among stakers of the FXS governance token, Kazemian outlined. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain hinges on a Layer 2 rollup model. In this arrangement, it will publish state roots to the Ethereum mainnet for securing the network. The rollup network will also incorporate decentralized sequencers&mdash;these nodes order transactions into batches in a rollup network. Any entity can operate them, as long as they secure the nod via a governance vote. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kazemian further elaborated on this feature:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Fraxchain proposes a solution where sequencer roles can be auctioned off and rotated, creating a decentralized sequencer base. If a sequencer is forced to shut down, Fraxchain would allow the next elected sequencer to pick up from where the previous one left off,&rdquo; he explained. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Fraxchain: By the Numbers</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As per the numbers, Frax's ecosystem has made a significant mark on the world of crypto. As of this writing, the total supply of Frax stands at over $1.23 billion, while Frax Shares (FXS) have a market cap exceeding $371 million. The Frax stablecoin is listed on major exchanges and is integrated into numerous DeFi platforms, while FXS token is used for governance decisions, further cementing its position in the decentralized finance space.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Fraxchain encapsulates the pivotal move of Frax Finance to fortify its position in the DeFi world. It will be interesting to monitor the progress of this Layer 2 solution, with an eye on the continued growth and traction of the Frax ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Price Analysis: Uwerx (WERX) Reaches Summit; Bleak DOGE Social Sentiment Raises Questions About Price Reversal]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/dogecoin-doge-price-analysis-uwerx-werx-reaches-summit-bleak-doge-social-sentiment-raises-questions-about-price-reversal</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-16-at-145340.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-16-at-145340.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-16-at-145340.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/dogecoin-doge-price-analysis-uwerx-werx-reaches-summit-bleak-doge-social-sentiment-raises-questions-about-price-reversal</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) joins the list of several other tokens caught up in the price drops due to the recent US Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s (SEC) lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto analysts study the charts to see what this means for the meme coin while also discovering a new token, rising against all odds&mdash;Uwerx.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This article explores what the SEC lawsuit could mean for Dogecoin (DOGE) while exploring the unique benefits Uwerx has to offer its users.&nbsp;</p>
Dogecoin (DOGE): The Fate of the Meme Coin
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE), like several other tokens, has been caught in the SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase. While several media platforms spread uncertainty and fear regarding Dogecoin (DOGE), crypto analysts take a different approach to the token&rsquo;s price predictions.</p>
<p>Most media outlets have communicated that the recent sell-offs and price drops in Dogecoin (DOGE) forewarn investors of an even bleaker future. But crypto analysts have stated that the sell-offs and price drops were not driven by long-term traders but by short-term investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to industry experts, the fate of Dogecoin (DOGE) in the crypto market is less bleak than media outlets will lead most to believe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Today, Dogecoin (DOGE) sells at $0.061421, with a live market cap of $8,554,931,776. Dogecoin&rsquo;s (DOGE) market supply is presently at 139,736,336,384 DOGE. Due to market sentiments, Dogecoin (DOGE) is predicted to reach $0.092 by 2024.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): A Brighter Future
<p>Uwerx is positioned to be the leading freelance platform globally. Uwerx is set to be different and preferable compared to other freelancing platforms. Considering Uwerx&rsquo;s increasing numbers, one might state that Uwerx is already meeting its goals.</p>
<p>With over 6,200 sign-ups on the Uwerx platform, over 1,600 followers on Twitter, and over 1,600 subscribers to the Telegram community, the Uwerx platform is growing beyond all expectations. While other platforms might take this as a sign to work less hard, the Uwerx team remains unrelenting. With the current listing on CoinSniper and the scheduled Uwerx listing on Uniswap by the 1st of August, the Uwerx Team is doing all it can to ensure that Uwerx reaches its target audience.</p>
<p>The confidence of the Uwerx team in expanding its reach can be traced to several factors. Firstly, Uwerx has successfully passed its audit approval by InterFi Network and SolidProof. This implies that the platform is excellent by all standards in the industry. In addition, Uwerx is set to only offer a 1% transaction fee, a very affordable fee compared to Upwork and Fiverr&rsquo;s 10 and 20%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx will also be offering its users incentivization and gamification features to serve as more motivation for their work. Uwerx will also put a 25-year liquidity lock in place for its tokens. Uwerx team tokens are included in the mix as team tokens have already been locked for nine months, further assuring Uwerx users of the security and stability of their tokens. Once Uwerx is unveiled on the 4th of August, 2023, contract ownerships will be renounced, thus eliminating the likelihood of scams and fraud.</p>
<p>The Uwerx Vault has now been unveiled, allowing Uwerx users to store their tokens securely, just like staking, as they get rewarded dependent on the variables existing within the platform. The&nbsp; Alpha platform has also been unveiled, and Uwerx will soon be transitioning from the Alpha Platform to the Beta platform, allowing Uwerx users to test the platform for themselves. The Uwerx team encourages users to send their feedback via email to the Uwerx team at feedback@uwerx.network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the 31st of July, 2023, when Uwerx&rsquo;s presale ends, WERX token holders will receive their tokens in a 6-week vesting period. Uwerx will also carry out a Test Airdrop when the Uwerx presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale: Beyond the Stars
<p>The Uwerx team has been in awe of Uwerx&rsquo;s incredible growth and sell-out of its presale. The first four stages of Uwerx&rsquo;s presale were all sold out in a very short time. The Uwerx team has also had to modify the critical token allocations due to the high demands for Uwerx.</p>
<p>WERX tokens sell at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus on all purchases. Considering that Uwerx will be launched officially on the 4th of August, this price is bound to increase soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click on any of the links to purchase your WERX tokens at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus on your purchases.</p>
<p>Presale:&nbsp; invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin (DOGE) joins the list of several other tokens caught up in the price drops due to the recent US Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s (SEC) lawsuit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto analysts study the charts to see what this means for the meme coin while also discovering a new token, rising against all odds&mdash;Uwerx.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This article explores what the SEC lawsuit could mean for Dogecoin (DOGE) while exploring the unique benefits Uwerx has to offer its users.&nbsp;</p>
Dogecoin (DOGE): The Fate of the Meme Coin
<p>Dogecoin (DOGE), like several other tokens, has been caught in the SEC lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase. While several media platforms spread uncertainty and fear regarding Dogecoin (DOGE), crypto analysts take a different approach to the token&rsquo;s price predictions.</p>
<p>Most media outlets have communicated that the recent sell-offs and price drops in Dogecoin (DOGE) forewarn investors of an even bleaker future. But crypto analysts have stated that the sell-offs and price drops were not driven by long-term traders but by short-term investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to industry experts, the fate of Dogecoin (DOGE) in the crypto market is less bleak than media outlets will lead most to believe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Today, Dogecoin (DOGE) sells at $0.061421, with a live market cap of $8,554,931,776. Dogecoin&rsquo;s (DOGE) market supply is presently at 139,736,336,384 DOGE. Due to market sentiments, Dogecoin (DOGE) is predicted to reach $0.092 by 2024.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): A Brighter Future
<p>Uwerx is positioned to be the leading freelance platform globally. Uwerx is set to be different and preferable compared to other freelancing platforms. Considering Uwerx&rsquo;s increasing numbers, one might state that Uwerx is already meeting its goals.</p>
<p>With over 6,200 sign-ups on the Uwerx platform, over 1,600 followers on Twitter, and over 1,600 subscribers to the Telegram community, the Uwerx platform is growing beyond all expectations. While other platforms might take this as a sign to work less hard, the Uwerx team remains unrelenting. With the current listing on CoinSniper and the scheduled Uwerx listing on Uniswap by the 1st of August, the Uwerx Team is doing all it can to ensure that Uwerx reaches its target audience.</p>
<p>The confidence of the Uwerx team in expanding its reach can be traced to several factors. Firstly, Uwerx has successfully passed its audit approval by InterFi Network and SolidProof. This implies that the platform is excellent by all standards in the industry. In addition, Uwerx is set to only offer a 1% transaction fee, a very affordable fee compared to Upwork and Fiverr&rsquo;s 10 and 20%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx will also be offering its users incentivization and gamification features to serve as more motivation for their work. Uwerx will also put a 25-year liquidity lock in place for its tokens. Uwerx team tokens are included in the mix as team tokens have already been locked for nine months, further assuring Uwerx users of the security and stability of their tokens. Once Uwerx is unveiled on the 4th of August, 2023, contract ownerships will be renounced, thus eliminating the likelihood of scams and fraud.</p>
<p>The Uwerx Vault has now been unveiled, allowing Uwerx users to store their tokens securely, just like staking, as they get rewarded dependent on the variables existing within the platform. The&nbsp; Alpha platform has also been unveiled, and Uwerx will soon be transitioning from the Alpha Platform to the Beta platform, allowing Uwerx users to test the platform for themselves. The Uwerx team encourages users to send their feedback via email to the Uwerx team at feedback@uwerx.network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the 31st of July, 2023, when Uwerx&rsquo;s presale ends, WERX token holders will receive their tokens in a 6-week vesting period. Uwerx will also carry out a Test Airdrop when the Uwerx presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
Uwerx (WERX) Presale: Beyond the Stars
<p>The Uwerx team has been in awe of Uwerx&rsquo;s incredible growth and sell-out of its presale. The first four stages of Uwerx&rsquo;s presale were all sold out in a very short time. The Uwerx team has also had to modify the critical token allocations due to the high demands for Uwerx.</p>
<p>WERX tokens sell at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus on all purchases. Considering that Uwerx will be launched officially on the 4th of August, this price is bound to increase soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click on any of the links to purchase your WERX tokens at $0.041 per token with a 15% bonus on your purchases.</p>
<p>Presale:&nbsp; invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[France's AMF Turns On Binance: Investigations Underway Since 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/france-amf-turns-on-binance-investigations-underway-since-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-amf-investigation-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-amf-investigation-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-amf-investigation-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/france-amf-turns-on-binance-investigations-underway-since-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance, the world's largest crypto exchange with roughly 62 million users, is reportedly under scrutiny from French financial regulatory authorities.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to a breaking report from Le Monde, investigations into the exchange's activities were to have been underway since at least the early quarter of 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The inquest, led by the judicial investigation service of finance and under the specialized interregional jurisdiction of Paris, has brought into question the exchange's adherence to legal norms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Reportedly, the focus of the probe revolves around "acts of illegal exercise of the function of service provider on digital assets (PSAN), and acts of aggravated money laundering." Particularly, the exchange is being examined for its participation in investment operations, concealment, and conversion - all purportedly carried out by offenders that generated profits.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Offhand, however, these allegations appear to be more a matter of misinterpretation and miscommunication withe the regulatory body than a wilful abandonment of due diligence from the side of Binance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance Commits To KYC Procedures</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Simultaneously, questions have been raised about Binance's commitment to 'Know Your Customer' (KYC) procedures, a regulatory framework meant to curb money laundering activities. Reports suggest that Binance may not have been fully compliant with these protocols, leading to further speculation about the exchange's operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To further complicate matters, it's alleged that Binance had been offering services to French customers without obtaining an appropriate operating license. Regulations enacted in 2019 require crypto exchanges to gain the approval of the Financial Markets Authority (AMF) to legally operate in France. Binance commenced operations in France in 2020 but purportedly only secured AMF approval in May 2022, fueling further controversy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to the claims, a Binance spokesperson maintained that the company cooperates with global law enforcement and abides by all local laws. However, they refrained from commenting on specifics about the investigation.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Binance invests considerable time and resources into cooperating with law enforcement globally. We abide by all laws in France, just as we do in every other market we operate," the exchange said in a tweet thread responding to reportage on the matter.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">To clarify:In France, on-site visits by regulators and inspectors, are part of regulatory obligations to which all financial institutions must adhere. We had an on-site visit last week by the relevant authorities. Binance, as always, was fully collaborative and we met our&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Binance (@binance) June 16, 2023


<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance: Between Compliance and Current Charges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This French investigation comes amidst Binance facing litigation in the United States. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has brought forward 13 charges against the crypto exchange's U.S. subsidiary and CEO Changpeng Zhao. Recent reportage also indicate that Binance.US has also cut off staff amid the ongoing legal troubles.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These revelations underscore the challenging terrain for Binance, as well as for similar platforms such as Coinbase. As of mid-2022, the SEC stated that out of the 62 million users on Binance globally, only 25 million had filled in KYC documents. This implies a substantial proportion of users on the platform are operating without the requisite KYC documentation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. Note: This story is currently developing and CryptoDaily will update this article with relevant information when available and as the matter unfolds.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Binance, the world's largest crypto exchange with roughly 62 million users, is reportedly under scrutiny from French financial regulatory authorities.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to a breaking report from Le Monde, investigations into the exchange's activities were to have been underway since at least the early quarter of 2022.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The inquest, led by the judicial investigation service of finance and under the specialized interregional jurisdiction of Paris, has brought into question the exchange's adherence to legal norms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Reportedly, the focus of the probe revolves around "acts of illegal exercise of the function of service provider on digital assets (PSAN), and acts of aggravated money laundering." Particularly, the exchange is being examined for its participation in investment operations, concealment, and conversion - all purportedly carried out by offenders that generated profits.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Offhand, however, these allegations appear to be more a matter of misinterpretation and miscommunication withe the regulatory body than a wilful abandonment of due diligence from the side of Binance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance Commits To KYC Procedures</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Simultaneously, questions have been raised about Binance's commitment to 'Know Your Customer' (KYC) procedures, a regulatory framework meant to curb money laundering activities. Reports suggest that Binance may not have been fully compliant with these protocols, leading to further speculation about the exchange's operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To further complicate matters, it's alleged that Binance had been offering services to French customers without obtaining an appropriate operating license. Regulations enacted in 2019 require crypto exchanges to gain the approval of the Financial Markets Authority (AMF) to legally operate in France. Binance commenced operations in France in 2020 but purportedly only secured AMF approval in May 2022, fueling further controversy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In response to the claims, a Binance spokesperson maintained that the company cooperates with global law enforcement and abides by all local laws. However, they refrained from commenting on specifics about the investigation.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Binance invests considerable time and resources into cooperating with law enforcement globally. We abide by all laws in France, just as we do in every other market we operate," the exchange said in a tweet thread responding to reportage on the matter.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">To clarify:In France, on-site visits by regulators and inspectors, are part of regulatory obligations to which all financial institutions must adhere. We had an on-site visit last week by the relevant authorities. Binance, as always, was fully collaborative and we met our&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Binance (@binance) June 16, 2023


<p class="md-end-block md-p">Binance: Between Compliance and Current Charges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This French investigation comes amidst Binance facing litigation in the United States. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has brought forward 13 charges against the crypto exchange's U.S. subsidiary and CEO Changpeng Zhao. Recent reportage also indicate that Binance.US has also cut off staff amid the ongoing legal troubles.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These revelations underscore the challenging terrain for Binance, as well as for similar platforms such as Coinbase. As of mid-2022, the SEC stated that out of the 62 million users on Binance globally, only 25 million had filled in KYC documents. This implies a substantial proportion of users on the platform are operating without the requisite KYC documentation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. Note: This story is currently developing and CryptoDaily will update this article with relevant information when available and as the matter unfolds.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance.US Cuts Staff Amid SEC Lawsuits]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binanceus-cuts-staff-amid-sec-lawsuits</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-us-cz-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binanceus-cuts-staff-amid-sec-lawsuits</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate conducted a round of layoffs after the SEC charged the exchange with securities violations last week. </p>
<p>Crypto giant Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate, Binance.US, has reportedly laid off some of its staff after the Securities and Exchange Commission sued the exchange with securities violations and sought a temporary restraining order to freeze the exchange&rsquo;s assets.</p>
<p>Reuters reports that around 50 people, or 10%, have been laid off. Sources say employees in the exchange&rsquo;s legal, compliance, and risk departments have been dismissed.</p>
<p>Media outlet CoinDesk cites documents in which Binance.US management described the SEC as a &ldquo;politically motivated regulator&rdquo; that forced the company to become a &ldquo;crypto-only exchange.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The documents read:</p>

<p>As part of this transition, and because of our preparation for a multi-year and very costly litigation process, the Board has asked Management to shrink the size of our teams across the company and reduce our burn rate.</p>

<p>Adding:</p>

<p>Unlike every other US crypto company, we have been working to avoid this scenario, but circumstances have now shifted. This was a very hard decision &ndash; one that we didn&rsquo;t take lightly. We are sad to see our colleagues depart, but we wish them the best and will do what we can to assist them in this transition.</p>

Binance.US Suspends USD Deposits and Withdrawals
<p>Last week, the SEC sued Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao, accusing the exchange of allegedly mishandling customer funds and lying to investors and regulators about its operations.</p>
<p>The next day, the agency filed a motion for a temporary restraining order to freeze the assets of two of Binance&rsquo;s US units.</p>
<p>Days after the SEC filed suit against Binance and requested to freeze Binance.US&rsquo;s assets, the exchange announced that it was suspending US dollar deposits, and its banking partners were preparing to halt fiat withdrawals from June 13.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate conducted a round of layoffs after the SEC charged the exchange with securities violations last week. </p>
<p>Crypto giant Binance&rsquo;s US affiliate, Binance.US, has reportedly laid off some of its staff after the Securities and Exchange Commission sued the exchange with securities violations and sought a temporary restraining order to freeze the exchange&rsquo;s assets.</p>
<p>Reuters reports that around 50 people, or 10%, have been laid off. Sources say employees in the exchange&rsquo;s legal, compliance, and risk departments have been dismissed.</p>
<p>Media outlet CoinDesk cites documents in which Binance.US management described the SEC as a &ldquo;politically motivated regulator&rdquo; that forced the company to become a &ldquo;crypto-only exchange.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The documents read:</p>

<p>As part of this transition, and because of our preparation for a multi-year and very costly litigation process, the Board has asked Management to shrink the size of our teams across the company and reduce our burn rate.</p>

<p>Adding:</p>

<p>Unlike every other US crypto company, we have been working to avoid this scenario, but circumstances have now shifted. This was a very hard decision &ndash; one that we didn&rsquo;t take lightly. We are sad to see our colleagues depart, but we wish them the best and will do what we can to assist them in this transition.</p>

Binance.US Suspends USD Deposits and Withdrawals
<p>Last week, the SEC sued Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao, accusing the exchange of allegedly mishandling customer funds and lying to investors and regulators about its operations.</p>
<p>The next day, the agency filed a motion for a temporary restraining order to freeze the assets of two of Binance&rsquo;s US units.</p>
<p>Days after the SEC filed suit against Binance and requested to freeze Binance.US&rsquo;s assets, the exchange announced that it was suspending US dollar deposits, and its banking partners were preparing to halt fiat withdrawals from June 13.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[MineLab.bz Revolutionizes Cloud Cryptocurrency Mining with AI Optimization, Delivering Daily Returns of up to 3%]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/minelabbz-revolutionizes-cloud-cryptocurrency-mining-with-ai-optimization-delivering-daily-returns-of-up-to-3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-1-1200x900.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-1-1200x900.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-1-1200x900.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/minelabbz-revolutionizes-cloud-cryptocurrency-mining-with-ai-optimization-delivering-daily-returns-of-up-to-3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom - MineLab Limited, a leading cryptocurrency cloud mining company, is proud to announce the launch of MineLab.bz, a cutting-edge platform that utilizes artificial intelligence (AI) to revolutionize the mining process and deliver substantial daily returns to its users.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency mining has traditionally been a complex and resource-intensive process, requiring specialized hardware and significant energy consumption. MineLab.bz changes the game by leveraging AI technology to optimize mining operations, significantly improving efficiency and profitability.</p>
<p>Through its advanced AI algorithms, MineLab.bz optimizes mining strategies in real-time, taking into account factors such as network difficulty, coin prices, and market trends. This dynamic approach allows for the identification of the most profitable coins to mine at any given moment, ensuring maximum returns for users.</p>

<p>"We are excited to introduce MineLab.bz to the cryptocurrency mining industry," said Alfie Hutchinson, CEO of MineLab Limited. "Our platform represents a paradigm shift in cloud mining, combining the power of AI with the potential of cryptocurrencies. We aim to provide a user-friendly, secure, and highly profitable solution for individuals and businesses looking to participate in cryptocurrency mining."</p>

<p></p>
<p>MineLab.bz offers users the opportunity to join their cloud mining network and start earning daily returns of up to 3%. The platform caters to both experienced miners and newcomers, providing a streamlined and user-friendly interface that requires no technical expertise. Users can easily create an account, deposit funds, and begin mining within minutes.</p>
<p>To ensure the utmost security, MineLab.bz implements state-of-the-art encryption protocols and multi-factor authentication, safeguarding users' investments and personal information. Additionally, the platform is backed by a team of experienced professionals in the fields of cryptocurrency, blockchain, and AI, dedicated to providing excellent customer support.</p>
<p>As a London-based company, MineLab Limited is committed to upholding the highest standards of transparency and regulatory compliance. The company operates in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, further enhancing trust and confidence in its services.</p>
<p>For more information about MineLab.bz and to start earning daily returns through cloud cryptocurrency mining, please visit https://www.minelab.bz.</p>
About MineLab Limited
<p>MineLab Limited is a leading cloud cryptocurrency mining company based in London, United Kingdom. The company leverages artificial intelligence to optimize the mining process and deliver substantial daily returns to its users. With a commitment to transparency, security, and innovation, MineLab Limited aims to redefine the cloud mining industry and empower individuals and businesses to participate in the cryptocurrency revolution.</p>
<p>Media Contact:</p>
<p>Jennifer Thompson</p>
<p>Public Relations Manager</p>
<p>MineLab Limited</p>
<p>Email: press@minelab.bz</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom - MineLab Limited, a leading cryptocurrency cloud mining company, is proud to announce the launch of MineLab.bz, a cutting-edge platform that utilizes artificial intelligence (AI) to revolutionize the mining process and deliver substantial daily returns to its users.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency mining has traditionally been a complex and resource-intensive process, requiring specialized hardware and significant energy consumption. MineLab.bz changes the game by leveraging AI technology to optimize mining operations, significantly improving efficiency and profitability.</p>
<p>Through its advanced AI algorithms, MineLab.bz optimizes mining strategies in real-time, taking into account factors such as network difficulty, coin prices, and market trends. This dynamic approach allows for the identification of the most profitable coins to mine at any given moment, ensuring maximum returns for users.</p>

<p>"We are excited to introduce MineLab.bz to the cryptocurrency mining industry," said Alfie Hutchinson, CEO of MineLab Limited. "Our platform represents a paradigm shift in cloud mining, combining the power of AI with the potential of cryptocurrencies. We aim to provide a user-friendly, secure, and highly profitable solution for individuals and businesses looking to participate in cryptocurrency mining."</p>

<p></p>
<p>MineLab.bz offers users the opportunity to join their cloud mining network and start earning daily returns of up to 3%. The platform caters to both experienced miners and newcomers, providing a streamlined and user-friendly interface that requires no technical expertise. Users can easily create an account, deposit funds, and begin mining within minutes.</p>
<p>To ensure the utmost security, MineLab.bz implements state-of-the-art encryption protocols and multi-factor authentication, safeguarding users' investments and personal information. Additionally, the platform is backed by a team of experienced professionals in the fields of cryptocurrency, blockchain, and AI, dedicated to providing excellent customer support.</p>
<p>As a London-based company, MineLab Limited is committed to upholding the highest standards of transparency and regulatory compliance. The company operates in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, further enhancing trust and confidence in its services.</p>
<p>For more information about MineLab.bz and to start earning daily returns through cloud cryptocurrency mining, please visit https://www.minelab.bz.</p>
About MineLab Limited
<p>MineLab Limited is a leading cloud cryptocurrency mining company based in London, United Kingdom. The company leverages artificial intelligence to optimize the mining process and deliver substantial daily returns to its users. With a commitment to transparency, security, and innovation, MineLab Limited aims to redefine the cloud mining industry and empower individuals and businesses to participate in the cryptocurrency revolution.</p>
<p>Media Contact:</p>
<p>Jennifer Thompson</p>
<p>Public Relations Manager</p>
<p>MineLab Limited</p>
<p>Email: press@minelab.bz</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[WIN NFT HERO Coming Soon to the APENFT Launchpad with Limited Release of the New HERO Mystery Box]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/win-nft-hero-coming-soon-to-the-apenft-launchpad-with-limited-release-of-the-new-hero-mystery-box</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686913383XXqJfKzbhl.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686913383XXqJfKzbhl.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/image1_1686913383XXqJfKzbhl.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:09:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/win-nft-hero-coming-soon-to-the-apenft-launchpad-with-limited-release-of-the-new-hero-mystery-box</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>WIN NFT HERO, a strategy game built on Tron, has been garnering a lot of attention. Following the official launch of the game&rsquo;s v2.0 and the new HERO system in April 2023, WIN NFT HERO officially launched v2.1 with an open beta test on June 1. Along with that news, an official announcement was made that the S1 Million Dollar Season event will be launched on June 15.</p><p>According to the official announcement, WIN NFT HERO S1 season game scenario is a PvP points tournament. Only players with 3N and above quality heroes can participate. WIN NFT HERO's S1 season event includes an abundance of $NFT, $WIN, $WNH and high-quality NFT rewards.</p><p>New players who want to participate in the WIN NFT HERO S1 season must first obtain a HERO NFT. The cost of the WIN NFT HERO depends upon what version it is. There are 5 qualities to choose from, ranging from low to high: N (green), R (blue), SR (purple), SSR (orange), and UR (red). The higher the quality of the HERO, the stronger the HERO is.&nbsp;</p><p>Currently, the WIN NFT HERO game contains a total of 58 heroes in 11 lineups, 19 of which are new heroes added when v2.0 was launched. Since the new heroes have different attributes, skills, bond effects, etc., players with new heroes will be able to experiment with more strategic combinations as well as have a greater advantage in matchmaking.</p><p>To celebrate the upcoming S1 season and help players achieve better scores, WIN NFT HERO announced that a new Hero Mystery Box sale will go live on APENFT Launchpad on June 16, 2023. 200 Hero Mystery Boxes will be available, priced at 10 USDD per box. Each box will include five new heroes, distributed according to the rarity.</p><p>These limited v2.1 HERO Mystery Boxes are exclusive to the APENFT Launchpad. As the S1 season approaches, expect these highly scarce new HERO NFTs to be even more popular.</p><p></p><p>About WIN NFT HERO</p><p>WIN NFT HERO is a "GameFi + NFT" strategy game, built on the TRON blockchain. It offers all kinds of heroes, equipment, and other NFT in-game assets for individual players to enjoy as they play, earn, and collect.</p><p>WIN NFT HERO requires players to match different strategic formations according to hero attributes in order to win on the battlefield. The goal of WIN NFT HERO is simple &ndash; to unite players around the world through blockchain gaming with a shared economy that transcends real world values. This &ldquo;GameFi + NFT&rdquo; game provides players with an unprecedented experience in immersive entertainment.</p><p>Learn more about WIN NFT HERO at their:</p><p>Website&#65306;https://www.winnfthero.io/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/winnfthero</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/WINNFTHEROEN</p><p>Discord: https://discord.gg/j9jsQKXq8M</p><p>Media Contact</p><p>Jane Ho</p><p>product@winnfthero.io</p><p></p><p>About APENFT Marketplace</p><p>APENFT Marketplace is an NFT trading platform native to the TRON blockchain, launched by the APENFT Foundation, with additional support from the world&rsquo;s largest distributed storage system BitTorrent File System (BTFS). It provides a range of NFT-related services, including NFT minting, trading, and creation. By converting more artworks as NFTs and bringing more GameFi projects on the blockchain, APENFT Marketplace not only makes art unique and eternal but also boosts transparency in the exchange and transmission. With higher speed and zero transaction fees, APENFT Marketplace helps boost a more diverse ecosystem and a stronger community.</p><p>The APENFT utility token ($NFT) is the official governance token issued by the APENFT Foundation. It is a decentralized digital asset that is backed by TRC-20 protocols, and serves as proof of rights on APENFT. With the designation of TRON as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, $NFT has been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country effective on October 7th, 2022. Currently, $NFT is traded on over 27 CEXs and DEXs including OKX, Huobi, KuCoin, Bybit, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and SunSwap.</p><p>Learn more about APENFT at their:</p><p>Website: https://apenft.io/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/apenftorg</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/apenftEN</p><p>Discord: https://discord.gg/Hq8GETYTrD</p><p></p>ContactLorna Hecontact@apenft.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, June 16th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>WIN NFT HERO, a strategy game built on Tron, has been garnering a lot of attention. Following the official launch of the game&rsquo;s v2.0 and the new HERO system in April 2023, WIN NFT HERO officially launched v2.1 with an open beta test on June 1. Along with that news, an official announcement was made that the S1 Million Dollar Season event will be launched on June 15.</p><p>According to the official announcement, WIN NFT HERO S1 season game scenario is a PvP points tournament. Only players with 3N and above quality heroes can participate. WIN NFT HERO's S1 season event includes an abundance of $NFT, $WIN, $WNH and high-quality NFT rewards.</p><p>New players who want to participate in the WIN NFT HERO S1 season must first obtain a HERO NFT. The cost of the WIN NFT HERO depends upon what version it is. There are 5 qualities to choose from, ranging from low to high: N (green), R (blue), SR (purple), SSR (orange), and UR (red). The higher the quality of the HERO, the stronger the HERO is.&nbsp;</p><p>Currently, the WIN NFT HERO game contains a total of 58 heroes in 11 lineups, 19 of which are new heroes added when v2.0 was launched. Since the new heroes have different attributes, skills, bond effects, etc., players with new heroes will be able to experiment with more strategic combinations as well as have a greater advantage in matchmaking.</p><p>To celebrate the upcoming S1 season and help players achieve better scores, WIN NFT HERO announced that a new Hero Mystery Box sale will go live on APENFT Launchpad on June 16, 2023. 200 Hero Mystery Boxes will be available, priced at 10 USDD per box. Each box will include five new heroes, distributed according to the rarity.</p><p>These limited v2.1 HERO Mystery Boxes are exclusive to the APENFT Launchpad. As the S1 season approaches, expect these highly scarce new HERO NFTs to be even more popular.</p><p></p><p>About WIN NFT HERO</p><p>WIN NFT HERO is a "GameFi + NFT" strategy game, built on the TRON blockchain. It offers all kinds of heroes, equipment, and other NFT in-game assets for individual players to enjoy as they play, earn, and collect.</p><p>WIN NFT HERO requires players to match different strategic formations according to hero attributes in order to win on the battlefield. The goal of WIN NFT HERO is simple &ndash; to unite players around the world through blockchain gaming with a shared economy that transcends real world values. This &ldquo;GameFi + NFT&rdquo; game provides players with an unprecedented experience in immersive entertainment.</p><p>Learn more about WIN NFT HERO at their:</p><p>Website&#65306;https://www.winnfthero.io/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/winnfthero</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/WINNFTHEROEN</p><p>Discord: https://discord.gg/j9jsQKXq8M</p><p>Media Contact</p><p>Jane Ho</p><p>product@winnfthero.io</p><p></p><p>About APENFT Marketplace</p><p>APENFT Marketplace is an NFT trading platform native to the TRON blockchain, launched by the APENFT Foundation, with additional support from the world&rsquo;s largest distributed storage system BitTorrent File System (BTFS). It provides a range of NFT-related services, including NFT minting, trading, and creation. By converting more artworks as NFTs and bringing more GameFi projects on the blockchain, APENFT Marketplace not only makes art unique and eternal but also boosts transparency in the exchange and transmission. With higher speed and zero transaction fees, APENFT Marketplace helps boost a more diverse ecosystem and a stronger community.</p><p>The APENFT utility token ($NFT) is the official governance token issued by the APENFT Foundation. It is a decentralized digital asset that is backed by TRC-20 protocols, and serves as proof of rights on APENFT. With the designation of TRON as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, $NFT has been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country effective on October 7th, 2022. Currently, $NFT is traded on over 27 CEXs and DEXs including OKX, Huobi, KuCoin, Bybit, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and SunSwap.</p><p>Learn more about APENFT at their:</p><p>Website: https://apenft.io/</p><p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/apenftorg</p><p>Telegram: https://t.me/apenftEN</p><p>Discord: https://discord.gg/Hq8GETYTrD</p><p></p>ContactLorna Hecontact@apenft.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
