<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 01:16:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Transaction Fees Surge to 2-year Highs – Where Next for the BTC Price?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transaction-fees-surge-to-2-year-highs-where-next-for-the-btc-price.htm</link><description>The mean fee to conduct a transaction on the Bitcoin network just shot to its highest level in nearly two years, as per data presented by crypto on-chain analytics firm Glassnode. &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, the average transaction fee clocked in at 0.00032814 BTC, up more than ten-fold from a dip to 0.00003161 on the 23rd of April. &lt;br /&gt;
At the current Bitcoin price of around $29,600, that implies a transaction fee of nearly $10....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transaction-fees-surge-to-2-year-highs-where-next-for-the-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Transaction Fees Surge to 2-year Highs – Where Next for the BTC Price?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Transactions</category><category>BRC-20</category><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 01:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-transaction-fees-surge-to-2-year-highs-where-next-for-the-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113148/273882/btc-10.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131590"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Turns Green for The Month – Is the Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-turns-green-for-month-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin (BTC) turns green for the month, investors and traders are speculating whether the bear market is finally over.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this price prediction, we will explore Bitcoin price predictions and analyze the factors driving the recent positive momentum, assessing if this marks the end of the prolonged bearish trend. &lt;br /&gt;
The US Dollar (USD) experienced significant changes in key economic indicators. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-turns-green-for-month-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Turns Green for The Month – Is the Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-turns-green-for-month-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113079/273674/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="989495"/></item><item><title>US DOJ Investigating Binance’s Involvement With Possible Russian Sanctions Violations: Bloomberg</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-investigating-binances-involvement-with-possible-russian-sanctions-violations-bloomberg.htm</link><description>The US Justice Department is investigating whether Binance Holdings Ltd. was illegally used to let Russians skirt US sanctions and move money through the cryptocurrency exchange, according to a report from Bloomberg News. &lt;br /&gt;
The Justice Department’s national security division is looking into whether Binance or company officials acted improperly regarding sanctions related to Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, Bloomberg said, citing people familiar with the matter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-investigating-binances-involvement-with-possible-russian-sanctions-violations-bloomberg.htm"&gt;Read More: US DOJ Investigating Binance’s Involvement With Possible Russian Sanctions Violations: Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Sanctions</category><category>Russian</category><category>Russia</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 21:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-investigating-binances-involvement-with-possible-russian-sanctions-violations-bloomberg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113145/273856/binance-logo-g2ddcf0aaa-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="113229"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today 5 May – Flow, Internet Computer, Casper Network</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-5-may-flow-internet-computer-casper-network.htm</link><description>The United States Bureau of Labor Statistics recently disclosed favorable data on the nation's employment landscape today, setting stocks and the crypto markets up for a minor rally throughout the day. &lt;br /&gt;
The April figures revealed an addition of 185,000 jobs, accompanied by a 3.4% rise in unemployment. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this developing macroeconomic backdrop, what are the biggest crypto gainers today?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-5-may-flow-internet-computer-casper-network.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today 5 May – Flow, Internet Computer, Casper Network&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>FLOW</category><category>Sponge</category><category>ICP</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>CSPR</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Internet Computer</category><category>Casper Network</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Spongebob</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>memes</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-5-may-flow-internet-computer-casper-network.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113143/273840/iggest-crypto-gainers-tod.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="328905"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Forecast as Whale Activity Shows Huge Buy Orders Filling Up – What Do They Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-whale-activity-shows-huge-buy-orders-filling-up-what-do-they-know.htm</link><description>Cardano (ADA) was last changing hands in the low $0.39s and as such remains marooned well within this week’s $0.38-$0.40ish ranges. &lt;br /&gt;
Cardano’s lack of volatility is surprising given that crypto and broader financial markets have been substantially roiled by Wednesday’s Fed meeting on Friday’s US jobs report....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-whale-activity-shows-huge-buy-orders-filling-up-what-do-they-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Forecast as Whale Activity Shows Huge Buy Orders Filling Up – What Do They Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>ADA</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Ecoterra</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-whale-activity-shows-huge-buy-orders-filling-up-what-do-they-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113142/273837/ada-2.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="135477"/></item><item><title>Major Media Outlets Seek Release of 9 Million FTX Customer Names Despite Scam Fears – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-media-outlets-seek-release-of-9-million-ftx-customer-names-despite-scam-fears-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Major media outlets such as The New York Times, The Financial Times, and Bloomberg have asked the court in FTX’s bankruptcy case to hand over a list containing the names of millions of FTX customers. &lt;br /&gt;
In total, the lists the media outlets are asking to get access to contains the names of some 9 million FTX customers and creditors who lost their money when the exchange filed for bankruptcy in November last year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-media-outlets-seek-release-of-9-million-ftx-customer-names-despite-scam-fears-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Major Media Outlets Seek Release of 9 Million FTX Customer Names Despite Scam Fears – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-media-outlets-seek-release-of-9-million-ftx-customer-names-despite-scam-fears-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113124/273731/ftx-court-case.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="82794"/></item><item><title>Sen. Warren Plans To Reintroduce Crypto Bill To Crack Down on National Security Risks</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sen-warren-plans-reintroduce-crypto-bill-crack-down-national-security-risks.htm</link><description>Democratic Sen. Elizabeth Warren has plans to reintroduce a cryptocurrency bill to crack down on money laundering and terrorist financing.  &lt;br /&gt;
The long-standing crypto critic said she planned to reintroduce that legislation during a Senate Armed Services Committee hearing on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sen-warren-plans-reintroduce-crypto-bill-crack-down-national-security-risks.htm"&gt;Read More: Sen. Warren Plans To Reintroduce Crypto Bill To Crack Down on National Security Risks&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Elizabeth Warren</category><category>National Security</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Policy</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sen-warren-plans-reintroduce-crypto-bill-crack-down-national-security-risks.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113139/273832/screen-shot-2023-05-05-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="451869"/></item><item><title>What's Next for Crypto Prices as US Regional Banks Take a Hit? – yPredict Tool Makes AI Price Predictions Easy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-as-us-regional-banks-take-hit-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm</link><description>The US banking sector is in the midst of a crisis, and the government's efforts have been insufficient, and some would even say damaging. &lt;br /&gt;
As regional banks face financial headwinds, the cryptocurrency market is on the lookout for ripple effects. &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst the crisis, yPredict's presale has received much attention for its AI-powered price predictions platform that can help predict market moves in both calm and volatile markets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-as-us-regional-banks-take-hit-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm"&gt;Read More: What's Next for Crypto Prices as US Regional Banks Take a Hit? – yPredict Tool Makes AI Price Predictions Easy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>US banking crisis</category><category>First Republic Bank</category><category>Financial Crisis</category><category>J.P. Morgan Chase</category><category>Ai Price Prediction</category><category>AI</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>FDIC</category><category>Pacwest</category><category>Western Alliance</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Crypto Total Marketcap</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-as-us-regional-banks-take-hit-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113122/273742/adobestock-549672609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="602943"/></item><item><title>Solana Founder Unfazed by FTX Troubles and Growing Blockchain Competition – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-founder-unfazed-by-ftx-troubles-growing-blockchain-competition-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Solana Labs founder Anatoly Yakovenko remains confident about the prospects of the Solana blockchain amid increasing competition from other emerging blockchain networks.  &lt;br /&gt;
At least six blockchain networks are set to launch soon, with Scroll, Linea, and the Coinbase-backed Base projects already gaining popularity among developers, potentially affecting market share for existing networks like Solana. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-founder-unfazed-by-ftx-troubles-growing-blockchain-competition-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Founder Unfazed by FTX Troubles and Growing Blockchain Competition – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Anatoly Yakovenko</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-founder-unfazed-by-ftx-troubles-growing-blockchain-competition-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113081/273681/f584725c05.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="88039"/></item><item><title>NY Attorney General Proposes Bill To Rein In Cryptocurrency Industry</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-proposes-bill-rein-cryptocurrency-industry.htm</link><description>New York Attorney General Letitia James proposed legislation that would require refunds of customers and audits of cryptocurrency exchanges in her latest move to rein in the industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
James’ program bill proposes the “strongest and most comprehensive set of regulations on cryptocurrency in the nation,” according to a statement released by her office on Friday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-proposes-bill-rein-cryptocurrency-industry.htm"&gt;Read More: NY Attorney General Proposes Bill To Rein In Cryptocurrency Industry&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Letitia James</category><category>New York Attorney General</category><category>Exchanges</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Policy</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-proposes-bill-rein-cryptocurrency-industry.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113129/273755/pexels-jeffrey-czum-2760856.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="147178"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Voyager Might Start Fund Distribution in ‘Few Weeks’, Jack Dorsey’s Cash App Posts $2.16B in BTC Revenue for Q1, UK Continues Crypto ATM Crackdown</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-voyager-might-start-fund-distribution-few-weeks-jack-dorseys-cash-app-posts-216b-btc-revenue-for-q1-uk-continues-crypto-atm-crackdown.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-voyager-might-start-fund-distribution-few-weeks-jack-dorseys-cash-app-posts-216b-btc-revenue-for-q1-uk-continues-crypto-atm-crackdown.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Voyager Might Start Fund Distribution in ‘Few Weeks’, Jack Dorsey’s Cash App Posts $2.16B in BTC Revenue for Q1, UK Continues Crypto ATM Crackdown&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Voyager Digital</category><category>Legal</category><category>block</category><category>Cash App</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Investment</category><category>Regulation</category><category>USA</category><category>UK</category><category>FCA</category><category>Kenya</category><category>Tax</category><category>NFT</category><category>AI</category><category>Zimbabwe</category><category>Banking</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Europe</category><category>Square</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-voyager-might-start-fund-distribution-few-weeks-jack-dorseys-cash-app-posts-216b-btc-revenue-for-q1-uk-continues-crypto-atm-crackdown.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113095/273696/adobestock-syda-productions-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="104057"/></item><item><title>Nigerian Government Greenlights Policy to Foster Blockchain-Based Economy – Details</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerian-government-greenlights-policy-to-foster-blockchain-based-economy-details.htm</link><description>Nigeria's Federal Executive Council has approved a national blockchain policy in a recent meeting. &lt;br /&gt;
This policy will enable the country to develop a proper regulatory framework for blockchain adoption.  &lt;br /&gt;
Nigeria is one of the nations whose citizens have an avid interest in cryptocurrencies.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, crypto transactions involving traditional banks are considered illegal in the region due to a controversial ban....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerian-government-greenlights-policy-to-foster-blockchain-based-economy-details.htm"&gt;Read More: Nigerian Government Greenlights Policy to Foster Blockchain-Based Economy – Details&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerian-government-greenlights-policy-to-foster-blockchain-based-economy-details.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113114/273719/analytics-g5baa42f4d-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="235958"/></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud and Avalanche Collaborate to Enable Metaverse Deployment on Blockchain</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/alibaba-cloud-avalanche-collaborate-enable-metaverse-deployment-blockchain.htm</link><description>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing subsidiary of Alibaba Group, has joined forces with Avalanche, a smart contract layer-1 blockchain platform, to launch a metaverse on the blockchain. &lt;br /&gt;
The partnership aims to bring new possibilities to the metaverse world by creating decentralized, secure, and scalable virtual worlds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/alibaba-cloud-avalanche-collaborate-enable-metaverse-deployment-blockchain.htm"&gt;Read More: Alibaba Cloud and Avalanche Collaborate to Enable Metaverse Deployment on Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/alibaba-cloud-avalanche-collaborate-enable-metaverse-deployment-blockchain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113112/273717/metaverse-gc101ae895-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="242391"/></item><item><title>Steve Curran, CEO of Burn Ghost Games, on Play-to-Earn Gaming, and Why Some Games Go Viral | Ep. 227</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-curran-ceo-of-burn-ghost-games-on-play-earn-gaming-and-why-some-games-go-viral-ep-227.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Steve Curran, CEO and Co-Founder of Burn Ghost Games, talks about the future of P2E gaming, the power of casual gaming, and how video games are the biggest use case for Web3....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-curran-ceo-of-burn-ghost-games-on-play-earn-gaming-and-why-some-games-go-viral-ep-227.htm"&gt;Read More: Steve Curran, CEO of Burn Ghost Games, on Play-to-Earn Gaming, and Why Some Games Go Viral | Ep. 227&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-curran-ceo-of-burn-ghost-games-on-play-earn-gaming-and-why-some-games-go-viral-ep-227.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113097/273698/steve-curran-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="125964"/></item><item><title>UK Regulator Descends Upon Illegal Crypto ATMs in Latest Raid</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-regulator-descends-upon-illegal-crypto-atms-latest-raid.htm</link><description>The UK’s financial regulator, along with local police, descended upon illegally operated cryptocurrency automatic teller machines (ATMs) as part of a continued crackdown. &lt;br /&gt;
The Financial Conduct Authority inspected sites in Exeter, Nottingham and Sheffield to stop the illegal activity, the regulator said in a statement on Friday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-regulator-descends-upon-illegal-crypto-atms-latest-raid.htm"&gt;Read More: UK Regulator Descends Upon Illegal Crypto ATMs in Latest Raid&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>ATM</category><category>FCA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Crime</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-regulator-descends-upon-illegal-crypto-atms-latest-raid.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113104/273708/fca-reception-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="92316"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Faces Existential Risk as SEC Increases Scrutiny on Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-faces-existential-risk-as-sec-increases-scrutiny-crypto.htm</link><description>The US-based crypto exchange Coinbase is facing an “existential risk” as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues its crackdown on the crypto industry, a financial analyst has warned. &lt;br /&gt;
The warning from the analyst followed renewed concerns among Coinbase investors that tokens listed on the exchange could be considered securities under SEC rules, a change in classification that would bring a host of new regulatory requirements with it, Bloomberg reported on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-faces-existential-risk-as-sec-increases-scrutiny-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Faces Existential Risk as SEC Increases Scrutiny on Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-faces-existential-risk-as-sec-increases-scrutiny-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113098/273700/brian-armstrong.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="24649"/></item><item><title>Crypto Regulation Halts Growth of S Korean Web3 Unicorns, Warns Professor</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-regulation-halts-growth-of-s-korean-web3-unicorns-warns-professor.htm</link><description>A leading South Korean professor says that restrictive crypto laws are stopping Web3 unicorns from growing in the nation. &lt;br /&gt;
The expert also claimed that banks and other financial market players should be allowed to move more freely in the crypto market. &lt;br /&gt;
According to EDaily, the Web3 comments came from Hoseo University Professor Kim Hyeong-joong, who also serves as the President of the Fintech Society. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at a Web 3.0 policy seminar this week, Kim said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-regulation-halts-growth-of-s-korean-web3-unicorns-warns-professor.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Regulation Halts Growth of S Korean Web3 Unicorns, Warns Professor&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Web3</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-regulation-halts-growth-of-s-korean-web3-unicorns-warns-professor.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113093/273691/adobestock-484339390.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="650631"/></item><item><title>Banking Giant BNP Paribas to Launch China CBDC Wallet Platform – A Boost for the Digital Yuan?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/banking-giant-bnp-paribas-launch-china-cbdc-wallet-platform-boost-for-digital-yuan.htm</link><description>The Chinese arm of the French banking titan BNP Paribas announced it will launch a digital yuan wallet management platform, in another boost for China’s central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per Shanghai Securities Net, BNP Paribas China will be teaming up with the state-owned commercial bank, the Bank of China, for the project. &lt;br /&gt;
The French bank will launch a platform that links with the Bank of China’s own digital yuan ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/banking-giant-bnp-paribas-launch-china-cbdc-wallet-platform-boost-for-digital-yuan.htm"&gt;Read More: Banking Giant BNP Paribas to Launch China CBDC Wallet Platform – A Boost for the Digital Yuan?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bank</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/banking-giant-bnp-paribas-launch-china-cbdc-wallet-platform-boost-for-digital-yuan.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113069/273647/adobestock-572377668-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="272910"/></item><item><title>Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 700% in 7 Days – Can PEPE Overtake Dogecoin and Shiba Inu?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-700-7-days-can-pepe-overtake-dogecoin-shiba-inu.htm</link><description>The price of Pepe Coin (PEPE) has jumped by more than 65% in the past 24 hours, with its surge to $0.00000213 marking a 700% gain in the past week. &lt;br /&gt;
This makes PEPE the best-performing top-100 cryptocurrency (by market cap) by quite some margin, with most coins down in the past 24 hours and week. &lt;br /&gt;
And given its sheer, value-defying momentum at the moment, PEPE has every chance of overtaking Dogecoin and Shiba Inu as the market's biggest meme token....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-700-7-days-can-pepe-overtake-dogecoin-shiba-inu.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 700% in 7 Days – Can PEPE Overtake Dogecoin and Shiba Inu?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-700-7-days-can-pepe-overtake-dogecoin-shiba-inu.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113061/273648/pepe-price-prediction-as-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1493316"/></item><item><title>Binance Addresses Compliance Concerns, Claims Robust Measures in Place to Prevent Terrorism Financing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-addresses-compliance-concerns-claims-robust-measures-place-prevent-terrorism-financing.htm</link><description>Leading cryptocurrency exchange Binance has responded to a Reuters report that raised questions about its compliance policies for preventing and tackling cryptocurrency-based financing of terrorism.  &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange said it takes the issue very seriously and is not aware of any exchange, or other financial institution, that does more today to keep bad actors off their platform than Binance, the platform said in a Friday blog post. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-addresses-compliance-concerns-claims-robust-measures-place-prevent-terrorism-financing.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Addresses Compliance Concerns, Claims Robust Measures in Place to Prevent Terrorism Financing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>law</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Israel</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 09:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-addresses-compliance-concerns-claims-robust-measures-place-prevent-terrorism-financing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113067/273641/adobestock-photo-gonzo-1-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="30135"/></item></channel></rss>
