<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>US Lawmakers To Hold Digital Asset Spot Market Hearing Next Week</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-hold-digital-asset-spot-market-hearing-next-week.htm</link><description>US lawmakers are slated to discuss digital asset spot markets during a congressional hearing next week. &lt;br /&gt;
The House Agriculture Committee will hold a hearing on June 6 titled “The Future of Digital Assets: Providing Clarity for Digital Asset Spot Markets.” &lt;br /&gt;
The committee has jurisdiction over the Commodity Futures Trading Commission and has begun an effort to work with the House Financial Services Committee, which has oversight over the Securities and Exchange Commission. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-hold-digital-asset-spot-market-hearing-next-week.htm"&gt;Read More: US Lawmakers To Hold Digital Asset Spot Market Hearing Next Week&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-hold-digital-asset-spot-market-hearing-next-week.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115524/278461/washington-dc-ge6f6ffb63-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161889"/></item><item><title>Japanese Stablecoin Ban Lifted, Banks Prepare Move</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-stablecoin-ban-lifted-banks-prepare-move.htm</link><description>Japanese firms can now issue stablecoins, after a long-awaited piece of legislation came into effect today. &lt;br /&gt;
The revised Payment Services Act was promulgated at midnight on June 1, 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
Under the terms of the act, all token-issuing firms must be able to prove they have the underlying assets that back their coins. &lt;br /&gt;
And only regulated banks, fund transfer service providers, trust companies, and other financial industry firms can issue these coins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-stablecoin-ban-lifted-banks-prepare-move.htm"&gt;Read More: Japanese Stablecoin Ban Lifted, Banks Prepare Move&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Japan</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-stablecoin-ban-lifted-banks-prepare-move.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115549/278510/adobestock-418889525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="417851"/></item><item><title>How Will Bitcoin Perform in June? Here Is What History Tells Us</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-will-bitcoin-perform-june-here-what-history-tells-us.htm</link><description>Bitcoin is on course to close May down a little over 7%, marking the first negative month for the world’s largest cryptocurrency since last December. &lt;br /&gt;
The drop would also mark BTC’s worst month since the collapse of cryptocurrency exchange FTX triggered a 16% price drop last November. &lt;br /&gt;
But a 7% drop in May is an improvement on its May 2021 and 2022 performances, when Bitcoin lost 35.38% and 15.56% respectively....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/how-will-bitcoin-perform-june-here-what-history-tells-us.htm"&gt;Read More: How Will Bitcoin Perform in June? Here Is What History Tells Us&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Price</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-will-bitcoin-perform-june-here-what-history-tells-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115561/278554/btc-6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="255668"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 31 May – Solana, The Graph, Filecoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-31-may-solana-graph-filecoin.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has been affected this week by uncertainty surrounding the U.S. debt ceiling vote and potential interest rate hikes. &lt;br /&gt;
While legislation to raise the debt ceiling and cut government spending was introduced in the House of Representatives on Tuesday, the market remains on edge due to the bill's unclear fate until it is voted upon. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of the growing concerns regarding this macroeconomic development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-31-may-solana-graph-filecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 31 May – Solana, The Graph, Filecoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>WSM</category><category>SOL</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>GRT</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>FIL</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Solana</category><category>The Graph</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Web3</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible token</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Freelance Work</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Coca-Cola</category><category>Evian</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-31-may-solana-graph-filecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115558/278547/best-crypto-31-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="253760"/></item><item><title>US Senator Warren Calls Out Crypto’s Role in Fentanyl Transactions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senator-warren-calls-out-cryptos-role-fentanyl-transactions.htm</link><description>US Sen. Elizabeth Warren called out cryptocurrency’s role in fentanyl drug transactions and pushed for her bill to combat money laundering during a congressional hearing on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
The Massachusetts Democrat, and longstanding crypto critic, said her bill, the Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act, will close loopholes “in our anti-money laundering rules and cuts off drugs suppliers and cartels from using crypto to fuel their illegal business.” ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senator-warren-calls-out-cryptos-role-fentanyl-transactions.htm"&gt;Read More: US Senator Warren Calls Out Crypto’s Role in Fentanyl Transactions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Fentanyl</category><category>Elizabeth Warren</category><category>Treasury</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senator-warren-calls-out-cryptos-role-fentanyl-transactions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115559/278552/screen-shot-2023-05-31-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="471767"/></item><item><title>Coinbase: Embracing Crypto Could Determine Future of U.S. National Security</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-embracing-crypto-could-determine-future-of-us-national-security.htm</link><description>Amid heightened regulatory uncertainty and anti-crypto sentiment in the United States, a leading US-based cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase, has linked crypto to national security. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm noted in a lengthy blog post that the US must embrace crypto to facilitate national security. &lt;br /&gt;
The May 30 article discussed the impact of embracing new technologies on security and world leadership. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-embracing-crypto-could-determine-future-of-us-national-security.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase: Embracing Crypto Could Determine Future of U.S. National Security&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-embracing-crypto-could-determine-future-of-us-national-security.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115552/278522/future-gd752f6d4d-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="461141"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces Off $27,000 Support Level – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-off-27000-support-level-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>In the world of cryptocurrency, Bitcoin has once again captured the attention of traders and investors as it makes significant moves in the market.  &lt;br /&gt;
After testing the crucial support level of $27,000, BTC has managed to bounce back, sparking speculation about its next target. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-off-27000-support-level-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces Off $27,000 Support Level – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-off-27000-support-level-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115503/278372/31-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480917"/></item><item><title>US Government's Push for FTX Inquiry Reaches Court of Appeals – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-governments-push-for-ftx-inquiry-reaches-court-of-appeals-heres-latest.htm</link><description>The US Government’s push for an independent inquiry of the now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX was on Tuesday referred to the U.S. Third Circuit Court of Appeals. &lt;br /&gt;
The ruling, made by Delaware District Judge Colm F. Connolly, argued that the question of whether the case should be referred to the appeals court was not up to the judge to decide....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-governments-push-for-ftx-inquiry-reaches-court-of-appeals-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: US Government's Push for FTX Inquiry Reaches Court of Appeals – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-governments-push-for-ftx-inquiry-reaches-court-of-appeals-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115543/278499/ftx.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="85472"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts 30% of Staff Amid Market Slump</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-nansen-cuts-30-of-staff-amid-market-slump.htm</link><description>Blockchain analytics firm Nansen is cutting 30% of its staff, the company’s CEO Alex Svanevik announced via Twitter on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Svanevik said that the decision to reduce the company’s cost base, which is “too high relative to where the company is today”, was based on the fact that Nansen had scaled too fast in recent years, and also blamed “brutal” conditions in crypto markets. &lt;br /&gt;
Nansen was founded in 2020 and, according to LinkedIn, employs between 50 and 200 people....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-nansen-cuts-30-of-staff-amid-market-slump.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Analytics Firm Nansen Cuts 30% of Staff Amid Market Slump&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Nansen</category><category>Crypto Winter</category><category>Layoffs</category><category>Market Slump</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-analytics-firm-nansen-cuts-30-of-staff-amid-market-slump.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115551/278517/nansen.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227918"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Bears Eye Retest of YTD Lows – Here's Where LUNC is Heading Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-bears-eye-retest-of-ytd-lows-heres-where-lunc-heading-now.htm</link><description>Things aren’t looking good for Terra Luna Classic (LUNC). &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency, which powers the original Terra blockchain that experienced catastrophe after its associated algorithmic “stablecoin” UST lost its 1:1 per to the US dollar last May, was last trading around 3% lower on Wednesday in the $0.000084 area....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-bears-eye-retest-of-ytd-lows-heres-where-lunc-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Bears Eye Retest of YTD Lows – Here's Where LUNC is Heading Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-bears-eye-retest-of-ytd-lows-heres-where-lunc-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115548/278509/lunc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="382447"/></item><item><title>Render Network's RNDR Token Outperforms Broader Crypto Market, Mirrors Tech Stocks as NVIDIA Hits $1 Trillion Market Cap</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/render-networks-rndr-token-outperforms-broader-crypto-market-mirrors-tech-stocks-as-nvidia-hits-1-trillion-market-cap.htm</link><description>The decentralized GPU-based rendering solutions provider Render Network’s native RNDR token has seen a wave of interest over the past month as the narrative around artificial intelligence (AI) continues to strengthen. &lt;br /&gt;
In the past 30 days, the token has outperformed the broader crypto market, instead following tech stocks such as Nvidia higher as major cryptos like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) have seen falling or stagnant prices....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/render-networks-rndr-token-outperforms-broader-crypto-market-mirrors-tech-stocks-as-nvidia-hits-1-trillion-market-cap.htm"&gt;Read More: Render Network's RNDR Token Outperforms Broader Crypto Market, Mirrors Tech Stocks as NVIDIA Hits $1 Trillion Market Cap&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Render Network</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/render-networks-rndr-token-outperforms-broader-crypto-market-mirrors-tech-stocks-as-nvidia-hits-1-trillion-market-cap.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115499/278350/ai.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="220215"/></item><item><title>Bybit Joins Binance in Exit from Canadian Crypto Market – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bybit-joins-binance-exit-from-canadian-crypto-market-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Bybit has announced plans to exit Canada, citing growing regulatory scrutiny in the country.  &lt;br /&gt;
"In light of recent regulatory development, Bybit has made the difficult but necessary decision to pause the availability of our products and services," the crypto platform said in a Tuesday blog post....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bybit-joins-binance-exit-from-canadian-crypto-market-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Bybit Joins Binance in Exit from Canadian Crypto Market – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ByBit</category><category>Canada</category><category>Binance</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bybit-joins-binance-exit-from-canadian-crypto-market-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115529/278480/dfc7521ec5e09a95ea7d641cb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="19998"/></item><item><title>New Presale Token Mooky Launches with Community-Driven Crypto Project to Help Protect the Environment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-presale-token-mooky-launches-with-community-driven-crypto-project-to-help-protect-the-environment.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com. &lt;br /&gt;
While multiple meme coins are coming up and offering huge returns to investors, Mooky aims to reward investors while conducting good deeds to help the environment. This community-driven cryptocurrency project will give back to charities by raising funds through $MOOK, the native token. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-presale-token-mooky-launches-with-community-driven-crypto-project-to-help-protect-the-environment.htm"&gt;Read More: New Presale Token Mooky Launches with Community-Driven Crypto Project to Help Protect the Environment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-presale-token-mooky-launches-with-community-driven-crypto-project-to-help-protect-the-environment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115510/278398/mooky-img.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="693768"/></item><item><title>Binance Chief Communications Officer Responds to Reports on Job Cuts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-chief-communications-officer-responds-reports-job-cuts.htm</link><description>Binance’s chief communications officer denied that the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange is cutting 20 percent of its staff, following news reports about the job cuts on Wednesday morning.  &lt;br /&gt;
Binance’s Patrick Hillmann retweeted a post from independent journalist Colin Wu, who had reported that layoffs in June were expected to be about 20 percent....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-chief-communications-officer-responds-reports-job-cuts.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Chief Communications Officer Responds to Reports on Job Cuts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Exchanges</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-chief-communications-officer-responds-reports-job-cuts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115537/278494/screen-shot-2023-05-31-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="610596"/></item><item><title>Leading Web3 Play-to-Earn Platform Battle Infinity Secures Huge $3.5 Million Investment from Top VC Firm as Major Product Launches Approach – Time to Buy IBAT?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-web3-play-earn-platform-battle-infinity-secures-huge-35-million-investment-from-top-vc-firm-as-major-product-launches-approach-time-to-buy-ibat.htm</link><description>Tuesday, 30th May - Web3 play-to-earn (P2E) gaming metaverse platform Battle Infinity just secured a massive strategic investment from a top venture capital (VC) investment firm. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitgert Ventures will invest a huge $3.5 million into Battle Infinity to help fund the development of its blockchain-powered gaming ecosystem, which is already generating huge hype in web3 circles....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-web3-play-earn-platform-battle-infinity-secures-huge-35-million-investment-from-top-vc-firm-as-major-product-launches-approach-time-to-buy-ibat.htm"&gt;Read More: Leading Web3 Play-to-Earn Platform Battle Infinity Secures Huge $3.5 Million Investment from Top VC Firm as Major Product Launches Approach – Time to Buy IBAT?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-web3-play-earn-platform-battle-infinity-secures-huge-35-million-investment-from-top-vc-firm-as-major-product-launches-approach-time-to-buy-ibat.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115533/278483/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="439399"/></item><item><title>DAO Maker Price is Going to Zero and Crypto Whales are Stacking Launchpad XYZ as a Better Alternative– What Do They Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dao-maker-going-zero-crypto-whales-are-stacking-launchpad-xyz-as-better-alternative-what-do-they-know.htm</link><description>The DAO Maker (DAO) price has been caught in a downward spiral since falling below its 100-day moving average on May 13.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, certain signals suggest the sell-off may be nearing an end and a reversal could be on the horizon. &lt;br /&gt;
The DAO Maker price is currently trading at $1.153, down by 0.58% so far today as the bearish trend persists.  &lt;br /&gt;
DAO is still trailing below its 20-day EMA and 50-day EMA which are at $1.305 and $1.394 respectively....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dao-maker-going-zero-crypto-whales-are-stacking-launchpad-xyz-as-better-alternative-what-do-they-know.htm"&gt;Read More: DAO Maker Price is Going to Zero and Crypto Whales are Stacking Launchpad XYZ as a Better Alternative– What Do They Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DAO Maker</category><category>DAO</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>Web3</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Crypto Wallet</category><category>NFT</category><category>Digital Assets</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Play To Earn Games</category><category>P2E</category><category>Crypto Gaming</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>DEX</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Decentralized Autonomous Organization</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dao-maker-going-zero-crypto-whales-are-stacking-launchpad-xyz-as-better-alternative-what-do-they-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115528/278470/05-31-23-cn-dao-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="614299"/></item><item><title>Hong Kong and UAE Central Banks Join Forces on Crypto Regulations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-uae-central-banks-join-forces-crypto-regulations.htm</link><description>Both Hong Kong and the United Arab Emirates (UAE) have strengthened ties after their respective central banks (CBUAE) and monetary authorities (HKMA) agreed to join forces on crypto regulation earlier this week. &lt;br /&gt;
The parties held a meeting in Abu Dhabi on Monday to “enhance collaboration between the financial services sectors of the two jurisdictions,” according to a press release from the HKMA published yesterday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-uae-central-banks-join-forces-crypto-regulations.htm"&gt;Read More: Hong Kong and UAE Central Banks Join Forces on Crypto Regulations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-uae-central-banks-join-forces-crypto-regulations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115518/278433/pexels-gije-cho-16865479.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="281871"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Xapo Integrates USDT Payment Rails, Police Reportedly Detains Trust Reserve Core Team, Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Recommends All Banks Adopt Blockchain &amp; AI</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-xapo-integrates-usdt-payment-rails-police-reportedly-detains-trust-reserve-core-team-reserve-bank-of-india-deputy-governor-recommends-all-banks-adopt-blockchain-ai.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-xapo-integrates-usdt-payment-rails-police-reportedly-detains-trust-reserve-core-team-reserve-bank-of-india-deputy-governor-recommends-all-banks-adopt-blockchain-ai.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Xapo Integrates USDT Payment Rails, Police Reportedly Detains Trust Reserve Core Team, Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Recommends All Banks Adopt Blockchain &amp; AI&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>India</category><category>Reserve Bank of India</category><category>AI</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Payments</category><category>China</category><category>stablecoins</category><category>Legal</category><category>Police</category><category>Binance</category><category>Banking</category><category>Japan</category><category>SBI Group</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>UAE</category><category>El Salvador</category><category>Saifedean Ammous</category><category>Tether</category><category>Mining</category><category>Uruguay</category><category>Xapo</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-xapo-integrates-usdt-payment-rails-police-reportedly-detains-trust-reserve-core-team-reserve-bank-of-india-deputy-governor-recommends-all-banks-adopt-blockchain-ai.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115480/278342/adobestock-ownza-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="150205"/></item><item><title>Green Crypto Coin Ecoterra Raises $4.5 Million as Investors Shift to Eco Friendly Blockchain Platforms – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-coin-ecoterra-raises-45-million-as-investors-shift-eco-friendly-blockchain-platforms-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>Blockchain technology and environmental sustainability may seem like unlikely partners, but Ecoterra ($ECOTERRA), the rising star of crypto presales, is proving otherwise. &lt;br /&gt;
In a ground-breaking move, ecoterra is using the transformative power of blockchain to wage an all-out war on climate change and resource wastage....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-coin-ecoterra-raises-45-million-as-investors-shift-eco-friendly-blockchain-platforms-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Green Crypto Coin Ecoterra Raises $4.5 Million as Investors Shift to Eco Friendly Blockchain Platforms – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/green-crypto-coin-ecoterra-raises-45-million-as-investors-shift-eco-friendly-blockchain-platforms-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115508/278379/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="521307"/></item><item><title>Trust Reserve Stablecoin Team Detained in China: PANews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trust-reserve-stablecoin-team-detained-china-panews.htm</link><description>A Trust Reserve stablecoin team was detained by police in China on May 29, according to PANews.  &lt;br /&gt;
The news outlet reported that the team “had been taken away by the police and detained, and the family members of some employees had been notified.” &lt;br /&gt;
The office in Shanghai was vacant and had a seal of “Judicial Seizure, Strictly No Vandalism,” on it, according to PaNews. &lt;br /&gt;
Trust Reserve had products including stablecoin CNHC and the Hong Kong dollar stablecoin HKDC. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trust-reserve-stablecoin-team-detained-china-panews.htm"&gt;Read More: Trust Reserve Stablecoin Team Detained in China: PANews&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>China</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Arrest</category><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/trust-reserve-stablecoin-team-detained-china-panews.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115504/278361/pexels-aboodi-vesakaran-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="35305"/></item></channel></rss>
