<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 06:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hong Kong Dollar Stablecoin to Compete with USDT and USDC Proposed: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-dollar-stablecoin-to-compete-with-usdt-and-usdc-proposed-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 06:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258696</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/hong_kong_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/hong_kong_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hong Kong is wasting no time since it opened its doors to the crypto industry last month. A recent proposal is for the creation of an HKD stablecoin to compete with USD-denominated ones.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 4, the Vice President of Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, Cai Wensheng, penned a proposal for an HKD stablecoin. The policy proposal was also made by Wang Yang, Lei Zhibin, and Wen Yizhou but was not endorsed by the Hong Kong government.</p>
<p>The academics have a vision for a local currency stablecoin that competes against industry-dominant Tether (USDT) and Circle (USDC).</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A Proposal for Hong Kong to Issue a Hong Kong Dollar Stablecoin to Compete with USDT/USDC</p>
<p>By Vice President of Hong Kong University of Science and Technology and Chairman of Meitu</p>
<p>Read more: <a href="https://t.co/pCTxkqMLM7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/pCTxkqMLM7</a></p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1676207017705484289?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Hong Kong Govt Stablecoin Preferred</h2>
<p>According to Chinese journalist Wu Blockchain, the <a href="https://wublock.substack.com/p/a-proposal-for-hong-kong-to-issue" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">proposal</a> for the issuance of an HKD stablecoin would help to solidify Hong Kong’s leadership in the blockchain sector.</p>
<p>Other reasons justifying the proposal include propelling the local currency, enhancing transaction efficiency, reducing transaction costs, improving current payment systems, and “further strengthening Hong Kong’s fintech capabilities.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“Moreover, the Hong Kong Dollar stablecoin can enhance the efficiency and inclusiveness of Hong Kong’s financial system; its stability, freedom of exchange, high security, openness, and cross-border liquidity can support a wider range of financial innovations.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The proposal noted that the government’s current plan is limited by allowing and encouraging private institutions to issue HKD stablecoins.</p>
<p>“This measure is too conservative,” they said, because it doesn’t align with the government’s ambitions to promote the digital economy.</p>
<p>Therefore, the academics suggest the government issues a stablecoin called HKDG backed by Hong Kong’s foreign exchange reserves which were around US$430 billion as of March 2023.</p>
<p>A local stablecoin would also help with de-dollarization, they said.</p>
<p>However, any central bank-issued asset would be highly controlled and potentially used as a surveillance tool as it is in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/china-will-dominate-global-digital-finance-warns-coinbase-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">China</a>, which has oversight over Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Hong Kong launched new regulations for virtual asset service providers last month and is now working on establishing a regulatory framework for stablecoins.</p>
<h2>Asia Rushing to Regulate</h2>
<p>Hong Kong is currently leading the way on crypto regulations in the region, but other Asian countries are catching up.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/japan-eases-crypto-tax-requirements-to-entice-fintech-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">Japan</a> has ramped up its crypto regulations and KYC policies as it competes to become a regional digital asset hub.</p>
<p>South Korea passed the Virtual Asset User Protection Act last week, and Singapore’s central bank has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-requires-crypto-companies-to-hold-customer-funds-in-a-trust-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">proposed</a> new crypto exchange rules to keep customer assets in trust.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-dollar-stablecoin-to-compete-with-usdt-and-usdc-proposed-report/" rel="nofollow">Hong Kong Dollar Stablecoin to Compete with USDT and USDC Proposed: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager’s Creditors Charged $5.2M By Law Firm in Latest Bill, Adds up to $16.5M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/voyagers-creditors-charged-5-2m-by-law-firm-in-latest-bill-adds-up-to-16-5m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 04:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258570</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Voyager_Loan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Voyager_Loan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The law firm was formally engaged in September 2022 for the period extending from July 2022 to May 2023.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Creditors of bankrupt crypto lending platform Voyager Digital will pay more than $5 million for the third interim fee period, which ended in mid-May.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In total, McDermott Will &amp; Emery has charged the Voyager creditors’ group roughly $16.5 million for its services for less than a year.</span></p>
<h2>Legal Expenses</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">McDermott Will &amp; Emery, the law firm that represents the Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors in the bankruptcy case of cryptocurrency platform Voyager Digital Holding Inc., has billed the creditors’ group $5.17 million for the third interim fee period of 1 March 2023 and 18 May 2023. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For the entire fee period from 22 July 2022 to 18 May 2023, the law firm has <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x193/11753/PLEADINGS/1175307042380000000001.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">billed</a> the creditors’ group $16.48 million. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Initially, $11.2 million was earmarked to be paid to the law firm for its services. So far, the creditors’ group has paid out $8.9 million. A big part of the bill &#8211; $1 million &#8211; accrued on planning and disclosure settlement. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Discussing sale options, meeting buyers, and examining objections were significant in this part of the work. And it mostly involved Voyager’s sale to FTX.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Failed Deals </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After filing for bankruptcy, Voyager Digital was close to being acquired twice. In October, FTX won the bid to buy it for $1.4 billion, piping Binance in the race. However, the creditors opposed the deal as it included a clause that provided <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/creditors-oppose-immunity-from-future-bankruptcy-lawsuits-plans-for-voyager-execs/" data-wpel-link="internal">immunity</a>, or “broad releases,” from future bankruptcy lawsuits for top Voyager executives. Subsequently, FTX landed in a liquidity crisis leading it to file for bankruptcy.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After suffering huge losses due to its exposure to Singapore-headquartered hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), Voyager Digital filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In April, Binance.US <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-pulls-out-of-1-billion-asset-purchase-deal-with-voyager/" data-wpel-link="internal">pulled out</a> of a $ 1-billion deal to purchase Voyager’s assets following issues with local regulators. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“While our hope throughout this process was to help Voyager’s customers access their crypto in kind, the hostile and uncertain regulatory climate in the United States has introduced an unpredictable operating environment impacting the entire American business community,” Binance’s US affiliate said in a statement. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyagers-creditors-charged-5-2m-by-law-firm-in-latest-bill-adds-up-to-16-5m/" rel="nofollow">Voyager’s Creditors Charged $5.2M By Law Firm in Latest Bill, Adds up to $16.5M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>TON Foundation Unveils Encrypted Messenger to Enhance User Security</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ton-foundation-unveils-encrypted-messenger-to-enhance-user-security/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 23:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telegram]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258413</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TON_Network.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/TON_Network.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[TON users will able to retain the ability to send messages via the decentralized blockchain in an event of "apocalypse," according to a core dev. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The TON Foundation &#8211; the non-profit association behind The Open Network (TON) &#8211; announced the integration of messenger encryption on the network. The move aims to enhance user privacy by deploying necessary safeguards in a text sent with a transaction.</p>
<p>The new feature uses end-to-end encryption. This essentially guarantees that only the sender and recipient are able to view the message, thereby improving levels of security for TON&#8217;s user base.</p>
<h2>Enhancing User Privacy</h2>
<p>According to the official update shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the network fee for delivering an encrypted message via TON is around 0.006 Toncoin (TON) per transaction. The low price is expected to make the service accessible all across the chain&#8217;s increasing user base.</p>
<p>Commenting on the latest addition, TON Foundation&#8217;s core developer Anatoly Makosov said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Now this popular feature &#8211; which is not available on most other blockchains &#8211; is available with full encryption. Even in the event of an apocalypse and the failure of conventional messenger servers, you will retain the ability to send messages via the decentralized TON blockchain. Rest assured that these messages will be reliably delivered and safeguarded through encryption.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Several crypto wallets, as well as standard web and desktop wallets (Windows, MacOS, Linux), have already added support for the encryption feature, the statement by the foundation revealed. Meanwhile, the encryption for messages will be available in upcoming updates for TON mobile wallets and the Tonkeeper wallet.</p>
<h2>TON&#8217;s Evolution</h2>
<p>TON &#8211; which happens to be a layer-1 blockchain previously created by Telegram &#8211; had a much turbulent start. The project has been run as a community-led, open-source project after Telegram&#8217;s abandonment a few years back. Since then, the TON Foundation has managed to ink several partnerships.</p>
<p>As part of the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/telegram-to-receive-10m-for-ton-blockchain-effort/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnership</a> with DWF Labs, the blockchain industry market maker invested $10 million towards TON&#8217;s development last November.</p>
<p>DWF Labs is reportedly slated to participate in an estimated 50 seed investment rounds scheduled over a few months. The focus of the funding rounds will be to accelerate the scaling of the TON ecosystem as well as its associated projects.</p>
<p>More recently, TON <a href="https://twitter.com/ton_blockchain/status/1660652193123389443" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">unveiled</a> a $25 million fund dubbed &#8220;TON Accelerator Program,&#8221; which aims to invest between $50,000 and $250,000 per project and be accompanied by partnerships and mentorships from TON&#8217;s staff.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ton-foundation-unveils-encrypted-messenger-to-enhance-user-security/" rel="nofollow">TON Foundation Unveils Encrypted Messenger to Enhance User Security</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will The SEC Approve A Bitcoin Spot ETF In 2023? Lawyer Breaks Down The Odds</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-sec-approve-a-bitcoin-spot-etf-in-2023-lawyer-breaks-down-the-odds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 22:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258679</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There are two main avenues to get a Bitcoin spot ETF through the SEC - but neither may be likely to work. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The fate of Bitcoin’s price throughout the rest of the year largely lies in the answer to one question: Will a Bitcoin spot ETF be approved in the United States?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Joe Carlasare – a commercial litigator supporting Bitcoin – tweeted on Monday that he gives such a product a 30-40% chance of launching inside of a year. He later spoke with </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400"> to explain how he arrived at those numbers. </span></p>
<h2>The Trouble With Grayscale’s Lawsuit</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Carlasare, the market’s best bet at launching a spot ETF remains with Grayscale’s lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As the owners of the world’s largest Bitcoin fund, Grayscale sued the regulator last year for denying its ETF application in an “arbitrary and capricious” manner, despite approving multiple similar products in the form of Bitcoin futures ETFs. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The case went to its first oral hearing in March, during which judges seemed more sympathetic to Grayscale’s arguments than the SEC’s. This spurred certain analysts including Bloomberg’s Elliot Z. Stein to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-has-70-odds-of-winning-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-analyst/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">assign</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> 70% odds to Grayscale’s victory, thus boosting the odds of a spot ETF approval by the end of the year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Carlasare, however, refuses to be so optimistic – especially as a Grayscale victory won’t necessarily lead to a spot ETF.<br />
</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">For what seems like the 100th time, my personal view is that the probability of success in approving a spot bitcoin ETF in the near term (inside of a year) is still 30-40% —- which I consider to be fairly good odds.</p>
<p>I strongly reject the view that approval is highly probable… <a href="https://t.co/fAuNJ9pkhh" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/fAuNJ9pkhh</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Joe Carlasare (@JoeCarlasare) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeCarlasare/status/1675975751630290944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The hard part about handicapping the Grayscale v SEC suit is that a “win” may just mean the court of appeals directs the SEC to revisit their decision,” explained the lawyer to </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400"> via DM. “In other words, the Court could just send the case back for further proceeding and assessment in front of the SEC .”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>BlackRock’s SSA With Coinbase</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A review by the SEC has inevitably meant rejection for every applicant with a similar product thus far. Nevertheless, the market is optimistic that a filing last month from BlackRock – the world’s largest asset manager – can get through, given the firm’s phenomenal </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">success rate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against the SEC with past applications. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The SEC called BlackRock and Fidelity’s filings “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">inadequate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">” last Friday for failing to share a specific spot Bitcoin exchange with which their respective exchanges, NASDAQ and CBOE, would form a surveillance sharing agreement (SSA). Both firms have already refiled, clarifying that their planned SSA will be with </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-stock-surges-12-as-blackrock-names-it-as-surveillance-partner/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Coinbase is the largest Bitcoin exchange in the United States, Carlasare fears the platform doesn’t represent a market of “sufficient size,” as the SEC requests. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Sufficient size is somewhat ambiguous, but they have said it has to be a market large enough so that a person or firm attempting to manipulate the Bitcoin spot market would need to necessarily trade on that platform,” he explained. “If you apply that to the SSA with Coinbase, one can conclude that’s not going to satisfy [the] SEC, especially where the majority of spot trading volume is outside the U.S.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Overall, Carlasare gives Grayscale 50% odds of victory against the SEC in its lawsuit, and Coinbase 40% odds of being the “secret sauce” needed to get BlackRock’s ETF approved. He considers both sets of odds “optimistic.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-sec-approve-a-bitcoin-spot-etf-in-2023-lawyer-breaks-down-the-odds/" rel="nofollow">Will The SEC Approve A Bitcoin Spot ETF In 2023? Lawyer Breaks Down The Odds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s How Much of BTC&#8217;s Circulating Supply Is Owned by Long-Term Holders: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-of-btcs-circulating-supply-is-owned-by-long-term-holders-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 22:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258587</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The current amount held by LTHs is just 20,000 BTC shy of the all-time high of 14.49 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to data provided by Glassnode, long-term holders currently hold almost 14.5M bitcoin (BTC). LTHs have been on a gradual accumulation spree in the past year and a half despite the prolonged bear market. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Blockchain analytics firm CryptoQuant has recently revealed that institutional investors (hedge funds, pension funds, commercial banks, insurance companies, and more) have also shown an increasing appetite for holding the primary cryptocurrency in the long run.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">So Close to the ATH</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Glassnode&#8217;s figures </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1675842010261979137" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that BTC investors willing to hold the asset for the long term have purchased a significant amount between April and early July 2023. The largest crypto asset has performed quite well during those months, as it recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-posts-2-consecutive-green-quarters-for-the-first-time-since-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">closed</a> its second consecutive quarter in the green for the first time since 2021.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Long-term holders also showed rising interest in BTC between September 2022 and the end of the year. Moreover, their accumulation efforts continued even during<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the FTX meltdown</a> in November, which shook the entire crypto industry to its core. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In fact, other market participants, such as those holding less than 1 BTC (described as &#8220;shrimps&#8221;) and those with no more than 10 BTC (&#8220;crabs&#8221;), also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-spike-in-bitcoin-accumulation-from-retail-investors-after-ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">bought</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> significant amounts of bitcoin shortly after the collapse of the once-prominent cryptocurrency exchange. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Overall, long-term holders have amassed a total of 1.01M BTC over the past 602 days and now possess 14.47M BTC (around 75% of the circulating supply). The figure is just 20K BTC less than the all-time high.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that long-term holders were even more aggressive during the bull run in 2021. They accumulated over 2.4M BTC between April and November 2021, when bitcoin&#8217;s USD valuation was considerably higher than now, peaking at almost $70,000.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_258594" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-258594" style="width: 695px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-258594" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-scaled.jpg" alt="Long-Term BTC Holders" width="695" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-300x173.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-1024x590.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-768x442.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-1536x885.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-2048x1179.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Glassnode-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 695px) 100vw, 695px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-258594" class="wp-caption-text">Long-Term BTC Holders, Source: Glassnode</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Institutional Investors Are Also Flocking</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutional-bitcoin-btc-accumulation-sees-exponential-increase-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> by CryptoQuant, the institutional accumulation of bitcoin has been on the rise, too. The analytics company further outlined that investment firms, hedge funds, private funds, and others seek to join the ecosystem for the long run:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Analyzing the holdings of these funds provides valuable insights into the market dynamics and investor sentiment…Monitoring fund holdings not only provides an understanding of the market sentiment but also highlights the confidence institutional investors have in bitcoin as a long-term asset.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One reason behind that enthusiasm could be the long list of financial giants which recently filed to launch a spot BTC ETF in the States. The spree was started by the world&#8217;s largest asset manager &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">BlackRock</a>. Fidelity Digital Assets, Invesco, WisdomTree, Valkyrie, and more followed suit a few days later, infusing optimism and hope in the entire crypto sector.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-of-btcs-circulating-supply-is-owned-by-long-term-holders-data/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s How Much of BTC&#8217;s Circulating Supply Is Owned by Long-Term Holders: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Crypto Shiba Memu Plans To Be an Unstoppable Marketing Powerhouse</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-crypto-shiba-memu-plans-to-be-an-unstoppable-marketing-powerhouse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258622</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Memu’s machine-learning marketing capabilities make it stand out from the pack of other meme coins in the crypto market. Early whispers suggest that it could become one of the most exciting meme coin in Web3, thanks to its doggone impressive in-built ability to promote itself, learn from its successes, and improve its AI marketing [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Memu’s machine-learning marketing capabilities make it stand out from the pack of other meme coins in the crypto market.</p>
<p>Early whispers suggest that it could become one of the most exciting meme coin in Web3, thanks to its doggone impressive in-built ability to promote itself, learn from its successes, and improve its AI marketing protocol over time.</p>
<p>Meme coins always rely on their marketing campaigns to attract investors, so SHMU’s impressive self-promoting functionality could be the reason it rises to the top of the dogpile. For now, the native token will be released for $0.011125 on the first day of the SHMU token presale. It represents an exciting opportunity for all fans of AI and blockchain.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258623" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="301" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-2-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<h2>Taking Meme Coins to New Horizons</h2>
<p>The bull run of 2023 culminated in meme coin mania during the opening weeks of May, as brand new meme coins such as Pepe (PEPE) were skyrocketing. Demand for meme coins seems strong nowadays as speculators are looking for coins with short-term profits to capitalize on a long-term upward move in the crypto market.</p>
<p>This rapid rise has become common with meme coins. The last instance of a meme coin skyrocketing towards the end of a bull run was in 2021 when Shiba Inu (SHIB) went from a $0 market cap to over $40 billion so rapidly that it surprised everybody.</p>
<p>The crypto seems to be hungry as a stray dog for high potential memes, and the latest meme coin on the blockchain could take top dog rank away from earlier, less advanced tokens in the crypto market. Shiba Memu is an artificial intelligence meme coin that could take center stage over the coming years, as its automatic marketing protocol gives it a real edge over its competitors.</p>
<h2>What is Shiba Memu?</h2>
<p><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=cryptopotato" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shiba Memu</a>, the new dog on the block, combines cutting-edge technologies, <a href="https://www.bbvaopenmind.com/en/technology/artificial-intelligence/blockchain-and-ai-a-perfect-match/" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blockchain and AI</a>, to deliver automated marketing efforts. The protocol can continually promote itself across leading social media networks and interacts with investors directly. Since Shiba Memu uses machine learning algorithms, this dog will become increasingly intelligent.</p>
<p>The developers are coding the new robo-dog meme coin to seamlessly integrate with artificial intelligence enabling it to learn from successful marketing strategies. It will optimize its performance faster than any human organization, with reduced latency and increased accuracy, as it removes subjectivity from the equation.</p>
<p>As a high-spec AI-based marketing protocol, Shiba Memu scans the crypto market for mentions of the brand, allowing it to track and optimize its marketing efforts directly in response to investor sentiment. It is programmed to become exponentially more powerful over time, which could lead to impressive price action for the new meme coin.</p>
<h2>How does Shiba Memu work?</h2>
<p>Shiba Memu lets users track marketing efforts in real-time via its interactive AI dashboard. The dashboard will display all interactions between Shiba Memu and the blockchain community as it automatically generates press releases, social media content, and other marketing materials.</p>
<p>Shiba Memu uses an advanced <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-02-01/traders-see-ai-technology-shaping-their-future-jpmorgan-finds?leadSource=uverify%20wall" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">natural language processing (NLP) technology</a> that allows it to analyze piles of crypto market data from the internet. As people post updates about their views, Shiba Memu will respond like a good dog with tailored marketing efforts to help influence investor sentiment most effectively.</p>
<p>Users have the convenience of directly interacting with the Shiba Memu AI through the dashboard. Additionally, investors can provide feedback by posing specific questions and receive intelligent answers, all thanks to the integrated machine learning capabilities. All things considered, Shiba Memu is a cutting-edge AI protocol designed especially to drive awareness of itself all over the internet.</p>
<h2>SHMU: A Meme Coin Worth Watching</h2>
<p>With a fascinating use case for the new meme coin and some cutting-edge technologies powering it, Shiba Memu has potential to become a major contender in the meme coin field. The AI protocol could drive price action via automated digital marketing, and its brilliant and responsive design makes it an efficient way to create excitement in the crypto market.</p>
<p><strong>You can visit Shiba Memu and find out more about its presale </strong><a href="https://shibamemu.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=cryptopotato" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-crypto-shiba-memu-plans-to-be-an-unstoppable-marketing-powerhouse/" rel="nofollow">New Crypto Shiba Memu Plans To Be an Unstoppable Marketing Powerhouse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Understanding Crypto Liquidity Crisis Triggered by SEC&#8217;s Enforcement Actions: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/understanding-crypto-liquidity-crisis-triggered-by-secs-enforcement-actions-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258566</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/The_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/The_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kraken has emerged as a resilient market player while its peer exchanges feel brunt of the SEC enforcement from liquidity standpoint.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC&#8217;s subsequent enforcement actions, first against Ripple and XRP, followed by Binance and Coinbase, have contributed to the sufferings of other crypto exchanges from a liquidity standpoint. There has been a major shift in the CEX landscape that has already faced challenges following the FTX implosion.</p>
<p>A new report suggested that a slow recovery in liquidity appears to have haunted the second quarter.</p>
<h2>Kraken: An Outlier</h2>
<p>The blockchain data provider Kaiko&#8217;s second quarterly report <a href="https://marketing.kaiko.com/whats-driving-bitcoins-rally-1?ecid=AOKeC1ZsxplPoISj8-MxfRcQE_Oll4kxJQNtgSOc4UfLGw-sOayRHTHK0ewe4KlZd97Wv-_Vkdtk&amp;utm_campaign=Research%20newsletter&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;_hsmi=73538787&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz--clUrUFJxIVPxodu1nuscIXTUntKydcYxOWaQ_9Yndi4M5iHH8NFvqS2WR95NShuWC2vEJw4FlDz2lHhta_uPd4K_ppg&amp;utm_content=73538787&amp;utm_source=hs_email" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that spot trading volumes fell sharply during Q2 2023, plunging to the lowest level since 2020. Binance plummeted by approximately 70%. Coinbase, Kraken, OKX, and Huobi also witnessed their respective trading volumes slash by 50% during the same period.</p>
<p>However, Kraken&#8217;s liquidity has been &#8220;remarkably resilient&#8221; so far. It emerged as one of the very few exchanges that flipped the narrative by increasing market depth since the beginning of the year. Kaiko said the liquidity crisis in the United States is now a significant trend that has affected prices on both Binance.US and Coinbase.</p>
<p>In the short term, the crypto exchanges in the country could potentially lose market share to their overseas counterpart.</p>
<p>The report suggests that Kraken stands out in this case because it looks &#8220;quite strong,&#8221; taking liquidity into consideration. On the other hand, overseas platforms such as OKX have managed to amplify market share and liquidity at the expense of Binance.</p>
<h2>Renewed Optimism</h2>
<p>A spot Bitcoin ETF has long been viewed as the holy grail for the digital asset industry, as a way to achieve a broader swath of consumers. The SEC, however, has different plans and has so far rejected all prior filings.</p>
<p>Despite the continued turbulence in the market, institutional clients appeared optimistic, according to the latest survey <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-60-of-institutional-investors-bullish-on-crypto-for-next-12-months-survey/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">conducted</a> by Binance Research and Binance VIP &amp; Institutional team.</p>
<p>Over 50% of respondents had a crypto AUM of less than $25 million, and 22.6% had AUM larger than $100 million. 63.5% of respondents expressed confidence in the outlook of crypto for the next year, while 88% said they are positive for the next decade.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/understanding-crypto-liquidity-crisis-triggered-by-secs-enforcement-actions-report/" rel="nofollow">Understanding Crypto Liquidity Crisis Triggered by SEC&#8217;s Enforcement Actions: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals Proposal To Reduce Inscription Costs By 90%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-proposal-to-reduce-inscription-costs-by-90/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258662</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solutions to Bitcoin NFTs’ blockchain bloat are already emerging through a technology called “recursive inscriptions.”]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ordinals developers are pioneering ways to make reduce blockchain bloat caused by Bitcoin NFTs, potentially reducing their creation costs by 90%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The latest among these is BRC69 – a new standard proposed by Ordinals launchpad platform Luminex to “optimize the costs of inscribing on Bitcoin using the Ordinals protocol.”</span></p>
<h2>The BRC69 Standard</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Luminex’s GitHub </span><a href="https://github.com/luminexord/brc69" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">proposal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the new standard can not only reduce inscription costs, but also unlocks new on-chain features, such as “pre-reveal collection launching and on-chain reveals.” </span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">This means that NFT collections can use fully on-chain resources to unveil their NFTs, from the pre-reval process to the final reveal of an image and its relevant traits. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This is accomplished by automatically and seamlessly rendering images on the Ordinals explorer, without the need for additional action,” wrote Luminex. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">BRC69 uses a 4-step process: users inscribe images of their NFT traits on-chain, deploy the collection, compile it, and then mint the assets. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The standard builds upon ‘recursive inscriptions’ – a method introduced by Ordinals developers in June that helps work around Bitcoin’s 4MB block size limit. Instead of individually minting thousands of JPEG files onto the blockchain, users can reference content within existing inscriptions of the same collection, and render it later using small amounts of code. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Luminex, a recursive Ordinals standard will be necessary as Ordinals popularity <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-now-has-over-10-million-ordinals-inscriptions/" data-wpel-link="internal">rises</a>, and Bitcoin block space becomes “increasingly scarce and costly.”  Since popularizing in February, there have been nearly 15 million Ordinals inscriptions on Bitcoin, according to </span><a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Dune Analytics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">4/ The brilliance of BRC69 lies in its simplicity. Minters only need to inscribe a single line of text instead of a full image.This text allows the final image to be automatically rendered on all ordinals-frontends,using solely on-chain resources, thanks to recursive inscriptions</p>
<p>&mdash; Luminex (@luminexio) <a href="https://twitter.com/luminexio/status/1675832806839308288?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Blockchain Bloat</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ordinals have been met with major <a href="https://twitter.com/Pleditor/status/1666621731795083267" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">skepticism</a> from some Bitcoiners, who claim the protocol is effectively a bug enabling “spam” on the blockchain. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Criticism swelled in early May after the BRC-20 standard rose to prominence – an Ordinals-based system for launching fungible tokens on Bitcoin, alongside NFTs. This led to a swell of meme coins that briefly caused the average Bitcoin transaction fee to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">soar</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> over $30, raising concerns about the long-term sustainability of Bitcoin as an affordable payments network. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Solutions like BRC69 help remedy this issue but also mean fewer fees for miners, which are needed to sustain Bitcoin’s long-term security. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Fees have since returned to normal levels but could rise again if another NFT hype wave claims Bitcoin as its host. The network has already become the second most popular blockchain for trading NFTs, according to Crypto Slam </span><a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">data</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-proposal-to-reduce-inscription-costs-by-90/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Ordinals Proposal To Reduce Inscription Costs By 90%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258656</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ALEX_shooting_in_space_3_1688467420KUzLe7is9x.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ALEX_shooting_in_space_3_1688467420KUzLe7is9x.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023] Alex The Doge (ALEX), a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Frankfurt, Germany, July 4th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Alex The Doge (ALEX)</a>, a memecoin designed to transform the GameFi ecosystem, has reported strong demand for its presale. The presale, which is currently ongoing, gives the crypto community their first opportunity to purchase ALEX tokens. Following completion of the token sale, ALEX will launch on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>ALEX aims to combine the fun of memecoins with the utility of decentralized finance (DeFi) and play-to-earn gaming. The project has garnered significant attention from crypto enthusiasts, with more than 13.5 million ALEX tokens sold during the presale so far.</p>
<p>ALEX is built on Polygon, a blockchain network known for its scalability, speed, and security. By leveraging the capabilities of Polygon, ALEX is creating a digital gaming world called the Miracle Verse. This innovative ecosystem will empower users with play-to-earn gaming opportunities, social trading, and DeFi activities. With its gamified approach and extensive suite of products under development, ALEX aims to differentiate itself from other memecoins and gain a foothold in the market.</p>
<p>The project operates at the intersection of GameFi and SocialFi, the latter term describing the creation of strong communities that are united by shared interests and common goals. An extensive roadmap gives interested parties an idea of what to expect from the ALEX ecosystem as it takes shape, with the launch of the Miracle Verse sure to be an eagerly anticipated event.</p>
<p>Through combining the fun factor synonymous with memecoins and the utility built into decentralized finance applications, the team behind Alex The Doge believes it has found a winning formula. The completion of the ALEX presale will set the stage for everything that comes next, starting with the token’s DEX debut as Alex The Doge goes live.</p>
<p><strong>Join the Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale using the links below:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Website: </strong><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>https://alexthedoge.live/</strong></a></li>
<li><strong>Telegram: </strong><a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>https://t.me/alexthedoge</strong></a></li>
<li><strong>Twitter: </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e</strong></a></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-reports-14-million-tokens-sold/" rel="nofollow">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Reports 14 Million Tokens Sold</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justin Bieber&#8217;s BAYC Investment Turns Sour as Paper Losses Mount to $1.24 Million in 18 Months</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/justin-biebers-bayc-investment-turns-sour-as-paper-losses-mount-to-1-24-million-in-18-months/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258621</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/JustinBieber-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/JustinBieber-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club NFTs have tanked significantly in value this month.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Justin Bieber might be iconic on stage, but his investment strategy, at least in terms of NFTs, certainly missed the mark. The famous Canadian pop star paid $1.3 million for a Bored Ape NFT last year, which is now worth only around $59,000.</p>
<p>Foraying the hyped NFT space during the digital asset bull run seemed like a lucrative and exciting addition to many celebrities&#8217; investment portfolios. However, many who sang the praises of these non-fungible tokens have not managed to steer clear of the troubles that followed.</p>
<h2>Justin Bieber&#8217;s NFT Losses</h2>
<p>Bieber&#8217;s tryst with NFTs dates back to January 2022, when the sector was raging with celebrity endorsements. The global pop star invested 500 ETH, which was equivalent to $1.3 million, on BAYC. Eighteen months later, his net paper loss stands at $1.24 million.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Justin Bieber spent over $1.3 million on this NFT last year</p>
<p>It is currently worth $59,000 <a href="https://t.co/LwdNkLyRZU" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/LwdNkLyRZU</a></p>
<p>— Dexerto (@Dexerto) <a href="https://twitter.com/Dexerto/status/1675923552250241029?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>BAYC is a collection of 10,000 Bored Ape NFTs-unique digital collectibles living on the Ethereum blockchain. The once-premier collection saw a massive decline in its floor price that dipped below 30 ETH, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bayc-has-tanked-90-as-nft-collection-floor-prices-plummet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">making</a> a multi-year low not seen since October 2021. BAYC&#8217;s current state mirrors a general cooling down of the NFT market. Other prominent players such as MoonBirds, MAYC, Azuki, and Doodles also witnessed declines in value lately.</p>
<p>Bieber isn&#8217;t the only celeb to have suffered financial damage from his NFT purchases as a result of the turbulent market conditions. Last year, the paper losses of the soccer star Neymar Jr. as well as the renowned rapper Eminem stood at $700,000 and $300,000, respectively.</p>
<p>American singer and &#8220;Queen of Pop,&#8221; Madonna, also sported big paper losses with her NFTs after purchasing an evil eye ape and then subsequently watching the price go down.</p>
<h2>Legal Troubles</h2>
<p>Apart from crashing prices, legal troubles for these celebs caught up. Last December, NFT investors sued the creator of the popular BAYC collection of NFTs and its promoters, including A-listers such as Madonna, Paris Hilton, and Justin Bieber, for allegedly using the celebs who didn&#8217;t disclose they were paid to pump sales to dupe them into buying the collectibles.</p>
<p>The proposed class-action lawsuit, <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/celebrities-who-endorsed-crypto-nfts-land-in-legal-crosshairs-after-investor-losses-11675097150" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filed</a> in Los Angeles federal court, accused Yuga Labs, Hollywood agent Guy Oseary and MoonPay USA of using their network of prominent musicians, athletes, and celebrities to misleadingly promote and sell Yuga financial products.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/justin-biebers-bayc-investment-turns-sour-as-paper-losses-mount-to-1-24-million-in-18-months/" rel="nofollow">Justin Bieber&#8217;s BAYC Investment Turns Sour as Paper Losses Mount to $1.24 Million in 18 Months</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
