<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 02:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BMW Revamps Operations With Blockchain Technology From Coinweb And BNB Chain</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bmw-revamps-operations-with-blockchain-technology-from-coinweb-and-bnb-chain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 01:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Adoption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230911</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/bmw_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/bmw_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BMW is relying on blockchain technology to improve its business model. Now, the company is using technology from Coinweb and Binance.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinweb, a layer-2 cross-chain computation platform, announced on December 29 that it has entered into a partnership with BMW to integrate blockchain technology into the automaker&#8217;s infrastructure in order to improve the efficiency of financial transactions.</p>
<p>Coinweb stated that the primary goal of this partnership is to provide a completely new experience for BMW&#8217;s customers in Thailand. To achieve this, the two companies plan to implement two different roadmaps in 2023.</p>
<h2>The Project Will be Divided Into Two Phases</h2>
<p>The first phase of the <a href="https://www.accesswire.com/733393/Coinweb-to-deliver-cross-chain-smart-contract-architecture-and-blockchain-loyalty-programme-to-BMW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">partnership</a> will involve the creation of a roadmap to assess the use of cross-chain parallel-executing smart contracts to automate manual processes that are time-consuming and resource-intensive for the company.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Coinweb brings blockchain technology to BMW &#8211; Introducing their mass user base in Thailand to the cross-chain infrastructure.<a href="https://t.co/lrKKc9YeaG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/lrKKc9YeaG</a></p>
<p>Ecstatic to be ending 2022 with a<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4a5.png" alt="💥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br />
What will 2023 bring us? <a href="https://t.co/Z666FHlEzS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Z666FHlEzS</a></p>
<p>— Coinweb.io (@CoinwebOfficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinwebOfficial/status/1608385747597524992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 29, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Coinweb plans to implement a fully integrated Anti Money Laundering (AML) and Know Your Customer (KYC) tool based on Thailand&#8217;s NDID system to streamline the process of applying for vehicle financing and reduce the associated pain points.</p>
<p>In the second phase of the partnership, Coinweb will create a Software as a Service (SaaS) Web3 application to develop a blockchain-based <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bmw-korea-goes-blockchain-reward-program-inbound/" data-wpel-link="internal">loyalty program</a> for BMW Group customers in Thailand. Binance&#8217;s BNB Chain will serve as the foundation for the program due to its high performance, low cost, and fast transaction speeds.</p>
<p>Customers will be able to earn rewards through a variety of activities, depending on their level and rank. They can later redeem their rewards for various products and services.</p>
<h2>BMW and Coinweb Partner to Improve BMW Thailand&#8217;s Efficiency</h2>
<p>Bjorn Antonsson, CEO of BMW Thailand, said they were grateful to work with Coinweb to improve the company&#8217;s efficiency and transparency by integrating Distributed Ledger Technology (DLT) into their ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are very excited to be working with such a great team at Coinweb, and anticipate all the positive outcomes of embracing DLT into our ecosystem. We foresee this shift of manual paperwork towards immutable records on the blockchain to immensely contribute to infallible efficiency and transparency,&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Antonsson also added that they expect to attract new customers through the blockchain-based reward program they will launch in 2023.</p>
<p>Toby Gilbert, CEO of Coinweb, said it was an honor to work with a prestigious automotive company like BMW and hopes that the project, once launched, will serve as a reference for other companies looking to leverage the benefits of blockchain technology while staying true to their values and missions.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We hope that once this project is fully launched, it can be used as a benchmark to prove that traditional businesses can fully leverage blockchain technology and benefit hugely from it without deviating from their core values and mission.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This is not the first time BMW has shown an interest in the cryptocurrency ecosystem. In late November, the automotive company <a href="https://twitter.com/KondoudisLaw/status/1597934914581958656" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed a trademark</a> to enter the metaverse with the intention of launching a collection of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) for its customers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bmw-revamps-operations-with-blockchain-technology-from-coinweb-and-bnb-chain/" rel="nofollow">BMW Revamps Operations With Blockchain Technology From Coinweb And BNB Chain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Fiji Legalize BTC Next as its New Pro-Bitcoin PM Steps Into Office?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-fiji-legalize-btc-next-as-its-new-pro-bitcoin-pm-steps-into-office/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230834</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fiji.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Fiji.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The former MP of Tonga - Lord Fusitu'a - thinks Fiji and Tonga should both declare bitcoin legal tender in 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sitiveni Rabuka became Fiji&#8217;s 12th Prime Minister after winning the country&#8217;s elections earlier this month. The 74-year-old, commonly known by his nickname &#8220;Rambo,&#8221; is a proponent of bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Former member of Parliament of Tonga Lord Fusitu&#8217;a applauded the Rabuka for his success, supporting the idea of Fiji and Tonga embracing the primary cryptocurrency as legal tender in 2023.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Let&#8217;s Go 2 for 2&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The People&#8217;s Alliance Party (PAP) became the new ruling political group in the Republic of Fiji, and its leader, Sitiveni Rabuka, recently took office. The politician, who has already been in charge of the island nation, succeed the former PM Frank Bainimarama. Biman Prasad will serve as Deputy Prime Minister.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lord Fusitu&#8217;a &#8211; a Tongan noble &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/LordFusitua/status/1459399761023279105" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year that he and Rabuka had a meeting regarding renewable bitcoin mining and how that could benefit Fiji. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He released another tweet earlier today (December 29), </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/LordFusitua/status/1608249344028999680" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">congratulating</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8220;Rambo&#8221; and Prasad for their roles. Lord Fusitu&#8217;a also urged the new government of Fiji to dive deeper into the world of crypto and embrace bitcoin as an official means of payment together with Tonga next year.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">A new pro-<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> friendly Prime Minister in the South Pacific.<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2600.png" alt="☀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f30a.png" alt="🌊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f3dd.png" alt="🏝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Fiji <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1eb-1f1ef.png" alt="🇫🇯" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />‘s newly elected Prime Minister <a href="https://twitter.com/slrabuka?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@slrabuka</a>.</p>
<p>Let’s go 2 for 2 &#8211; BTC Legal Tender Bills for the Pacific in 2023 <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f44a-1f3fd.png" alt="👊🏽" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4af.png" alt="💯" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1f9-1f1f4.png" alt="🇹🇴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1eb-1f1ef.png" alt="🇫🇯" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— Lord Fusitu&#8217;a (@LordFusitua) <a href="https://twitter.com/LordFusitua/status/1608253674673033216?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 29, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Assuming Fiji and Tonga take such action, they will become the third and fourth countries across the globe where bitcoin is legal tender, with El Salvador and the Central African Republic being the first two. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similar to the Latin American nation, the Pacific islands could employ the energy of its active volcanoes in bitcoin mining. In addition, introducing the primary digital asset to locals could increase financial inclusion in Fiji.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tonga&#8217;s Plans</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Polynesian country displayed its intentions to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tonga-could-adopt-bitcoin-btc-as-legal-tender-by-november-says-former-mp/" data-wpel-link="internal">introduce</a> BTC as legal tender at the beginning of 2022. Lord Fusitu&#8217;a supposedly teamed up with Jack Mallers (the CEO of Strike) to roll out the bitcoin project in Tonga.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former MP claimed that the nation could become more &#8220;competitive and wealthy&#8221; if it embraces the digital asset. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;An economy that uses bitcoin for payment at every stage of the supply chain. From the seed to the table. Pay for cassava roots and cattle in bitcoin from the farming supplier all the way to the waitress serving it to you at Kardo&#8217;s steak bar and every step in between in BTC,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lord Fusitu&#8217;a suggested that the bill declaring bitcoin as legal tender in Tonga should have reached Parliament in September/October. However, the ruling body has not yet greenlighted such legislation.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-fiji-legalize-btc-next-as-its-new-pro-bitcoin-pm-steps-into-office/" rel="nofollow">Will Fiji Legalize BTC Next as its New Pro-Bitcoin PM Steps Into Office?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winklevoss Twins and Gemini Sued for Fraud Over Interest Accounts: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/winklevoss-twins-and-gemini-sued-for-fraud-over-interest-accounts-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 22:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230720</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Gemini_Lawsuit.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Gemini_Lawsuit.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This is yet another blow to the Winklevii-spearheaded crypto exchange.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">A group of investors has filed a class-action complaint against Gemini Trust Co. and its founders, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, alleging that the U.S. cryptocurrency exchange sold unregistered securities in the form of interest-bearing accounts.</p>
<p class="p2">The lawsuit comes about a month after Gemini halted withdrawals due to liquidity issues facing one of its business partners.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Gemini Faces Class Action for Fraud</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The plaintiffs, Brendan Picha and Max J. Hastings, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-28/gemini-winklevoss-twins-sued-for-fraud-over-interest-accounts" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed</a> the action in a Manhattan federal court, accusing the company and its founders of fraud and violations of the Exchange Act.</p>
<p class="p2">According to the investors, the Gemini Trust Earn products promised up to 8% returns on their holdings but were not registered with the necessary regulatory bodies. As a result, the plaintiffs claim they were not provided with the required disclosures to assess the risks involved.</p>
<p class="p2">In mid-November, the Winklevoss twins <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-recovers-from-services-outage-following-genesis-withdrawal-freeze/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted</a> redemptions after Gemini&#8217;s business partner Genesis Global ran into financial issues due to FTX&#8217;s sudden collapse. According to reports, Genesis had $175 million locked in FTX before the exchange filed for bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">Picha and Hastings allege that Gemini then refused to honor any further investor redemptions, leading to the loss of all holdings in the program.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Genesis Owes Gemini About $900 Million </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Shortly after the withdrawal suspension, reports <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that Genesis and its distressed parent company, Digital Currency Group (DCG), owe about $900 million to users of the Gemini Earn program.</p>
<p class="p2">Gemini has been trying to recover the funds to no avail. The crypto exchange even established a creditors&#8217; committee to help with the process.</p>
<p class="p2">Genesis, on the other hand, has been working to avert bankruptcy. Earlier this month, the firm&#8217;s creditors <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-creditors-onboard-restructuring-lawyers-exploring-ways-to-avert-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">hired</a> restructuring lawyers to save the company from sinking like other firms such as FTX and BlockFi.</p>
<p class="p2">Although the crypto broker has no imminent intention of filing for bankruptcy, the firm would be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-will-go-bankrupt-without-fresh-funding-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">forced</a> to do so if it fails to raise new funds to resolve its liquidity issues.</p>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, Gemini has not yet commented on the class action. However, the crypto exchange <a href="https://www.gemini.com/earn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> in an update on its website published on December 23 that it was working with &#8220;utmost urgency&#8221; to resolve liquidity issues at Genesis and would continue to work on behalf of its customers through the holidays.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/winklevoss-twins-and-gemini-sued-for-fraud-over-interest-accounts-report/" rel="nofollow">Winklevoss Twins and Gemini Sued for Fraud Over Interest Accounts: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitmain Founder-Backed Asset Manager to Delist Solana</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitmain-founder-backed-asset-manager-to-delist-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 19:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230816</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/solana_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/solana_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto market may have a small memory, but FTX's doom continues to haunt Solana.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Solana ecosystem that was once heavily tied to Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s FTX has been badly wounded after the collapse. As debates accelerated over the prospects of Solana, its native token &#8211; SOL &#8211; has plummeted 96% from its all-time high of $260 in November last year.</p>
<p>Adding to its woes, crypto asset management company Matrixport is reportedly gearing up to delist Solana and Solana-U dual currency investment products on December 30th.</p>
<ul>
<li>Interestingly, Matrixport is founded by Jihan Hu, who happens to be the co-founder of Bitcoin mining hardware giant, Bitmain.</li>
<li>According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1608309183685840899?t=rH7TLXyMml7jHRwKsD3nJw&amp;s=19" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reports</a>, the company now has intentions to roll out new SOL products in the near future.</li>
<li>Despite facing significant competition from Ethereum Layer 2 solutions, Solana had managed to amass a fair share of activity on its network, basking on the premise of faster and low-cost transactions.</li>
<li>However, the collapse of Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s crypto empire and Solana&#8217;s close ties with it dented market confidence. The consequences of growing skepticism in the community more than a month after the implosion have severely affected the Solana ecosystem.</li>
<li>The development activity on the network also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-suffers-major-setback-as-development-activity-plunges-sol-dumps-hard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">suffered</a> significantly as a result.</li>
<li>A few crypto projects have announced their departures from the Solana network, which also suffered multiple outages in the last year. DeGods and y00ts, two popular NFT projects on Solana, are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-projects-degods-y00ts-to-leave-solana-for-ethereum-and-polygon/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">switching</a> to Ethereum and Polygon, respectively.</li>
<li>According to data from CoinMarketCap, SOL was once a top 10 market cap asset, but it slid to the 17th position due to the excessive bearish sentiment around it and the subsequent FUD.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitmain-founder-backed-asset-manager-to-delist-solana/" rel="nofollow">Bitmain Founder-Backed Asset Manager to Delist Solana</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Helios is a &#8216;Transformative Acquisition&#8217; for Galaxy Digital, Says Novogratz</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/helios-is-a-transformative-acquisition-for-galaxy-digital-says-novogratz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230804</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Novogratz-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Novogratz-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital's boss reiterated his firm's pro-bitcoin stance and praised the recent Helios acquisition.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mike Novogratz &#8211; the CEO of Galaxy Digital &#8211; praised his company&#8217;s decision to purchase the bitcoin mining facility &#8211; Helios.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm recently won the auction to acquire another cryptocurrency entity &#8211; the blockchain cybersecurity platform GK8. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Long-Term Believers in BTC&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent tweet, Novogratz justified the Helios&#8217; acquisition with the fact that Galaxy Digital is a &#8220;long-term&#8221; believer in bitcoin. He also thinks lowest-cost BTC miners will prevail in the future, while the current crypto winter is an ideal time to ink such deals.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Bear markets are for building. We’re long-term believers in BTC and expect the lowest-cost miners to win over time. Helios is a transformative acquisition that will expand our mining capabilities and services as we continue to build for the decentralized future. <a href="https://t.co/8Zwf7Fj33t" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/8Zwf7Fj33t</a></p>
<p>— Mike Novogratz (@novogratz) <a href="https://twitter.com/novogratz/status/1608167650609270785?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 28, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argo Blockchain &#8211; a distressed BTC mining organization &#8211; recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/argo-blockchain-agrees-to-sell-helium-facility-to-galaxy-digital-for-65m/" data-wpel-link="internal">agreed</a> to sell its Helios facility to Galaxy Digital for $65 million and thus avoid filing for bankruptcy protection. Novogratz&#8217;s firm will host the mining fleet of Bitmain S19J Pros, while Argo will remain an owner of the machinery. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The miner also secured a new asset-backed loan worth $35 million from Galaxy Digital that should be repaid in three years. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Galaxy&#8217;s Endeavors in the Previous Months</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Galaxy Digital recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/mike-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-will-acquire-celsius-owned-custody-platform-gk8/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">won</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the bid to buy GK8 &#8211; a crypto custody platform previously owned by the bankrupt Celsius Network. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CEO Lior Lamesh and CTO Shahar Shamai remained part of the firm and will lead Galaxy&#8217;s new custodial operations. The former commented: </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;With the backing of Galaxy, we aim to introduce new and exciting offerings to the industry that showcase a combination of Galaxy&#8217;s best-in-class services and GK8&#8217;s cryptography, security, and unparalleled R&amp;D skills.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the recent acquisitions, Galaxy Digital has had a bumpy ride over the past several months. The firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/galaxy-digital-records-over-100-million-loss-in-q1-due-to-crypto-market-downturn/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">recorded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a net comprehensive loss of over $110 million in Q1, 2022, due to the cryptocurrency market crash.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The financial services company was rumored to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-plans-to-reduce-headcount-by-20-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reduce</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the size of its team by up to 20% in November. Thus, it would have joined the likes of multiple cryptocurrency organizations which dismissed employees this year, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-announces-18-layoff-amid-impending-recession/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>, Gemini, Huobi, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchaincom-announces-25-staff-layoff-following-3ac-fallout/" data-wpel-link="internal">BlockchainCom</a>, BitMEX, Bybit, and more.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FTX fiasco also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/galaxy-digital-held-77-million-in-ftx-exposure-earnings-show/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">caused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> severe financial damage to Galaxy Digital, which held more than $76 million worth of exposure to the bankrupt exchange. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/helios-is-a-transformative-acquisition-for-galaxy-digital-says-novogratz/" rel="nofollow">Helios is a &#8216;Transformative Acquisition&#8217; for Galaxy Digital, Says Novogratz</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>COTI Announces Succesful Hard Fork for Multi-Token Network Expansion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coti-announces-succesful-hard-fork-for-multi-token-network-expansion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[COTI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230832</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/coti_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/coti_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coti's MultiDAG 2.0 public mainnet went live on Thursday.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain protocol Coti announced the successful hard fork event &#8211; MultiDAG 2.0 &#8211; that aims to transition the ecosystem from a single currency infrastructure to a multi-token network.</p>
<p>In a press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Coti also revealed the launch of the Mainnet on December 29th, during which Explorer 2.0 was also deployed alongside the Bridge 2.0 wallet app.</p>
<p>In a statement, the team behind the protocol said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This launch signifies a massive step for the crypto industry, as well as COTI, as the MultiDAG 2.0 will increase the growth of the widespread adoption of crypto payments for enterprises that are yet to adopt crypto payment solutions. The transition from a single currency infrastructure to a multi-token network is an exciting step for us, and we&#8217;re glad to have your support on this important path.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>MultiDAG 2.0 Launch</h2>
<p>The MultiDAG 2.0 protocol leverages the CMD (COTI MultiDAG) standard that facilitates the issuance of tokens on top of the COTI Trustchain, a concept similar to the ERC20 token on Ethereum. However, in the case of this protocol, the issuance takes place on a single DAG.</p>
<p>The release is expected to boost Coti&#8217;s position to help enterprises by allowing them to launch their own Private Payment Network (PPN) which includes the issuance of CMD branded payment tokens, issuance of CMD branded loyalty tokens, and more.</p>
<p>According to Coti, these new tokens will have the same capabilities as that of the Trustchain in terms of high scalability, security, and throughput, managing the critical requirements of enterprises.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the new Bridge 2.0 wallet app, which was released alongside the protocol, includes a new refund feature that will enable users to apply for a refund in the event that the swap fails to execute due to technical difficulties or in case of pending processing.</p>
<h2>Djed Stablecoin</h2>
<p>The Coti ecosystem is also involved with Cardano-based Djed Stablecoin. In fact, the Blockchain protocol is the official issuer of the over-collateralized algorithmic stablecoin that is expected to hit the mainnet in January 2023.</p>
<p>Despite the past failures of algorithmic stablecoins and the most recent blow-up of TerraUSD (UST), Coti&#8217;s co-founder Shahaf Bar-Geffen remained optimistic about the launch.</p>
<p>While <a href="https://medium.com/cotinetwork/update-from-the-cardano-summit-main-stage-we-have-a-date-58024fdb67ac" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">speaking</a> at the Cardano Summit this year, the exec said he expects Djed to serve as this &#8220;safe haven&#8221; in the Cardano network.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coti-announces-succesful-hard-fork-for-multi-token-network-expansion/" rel="nofollow">COTI Announces Succesful Hard Fork for Multi-Token Network Expansion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy to Introduce Bitcoin Lightning Applications Next Year</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-to-introduce-bitcoin-lightning-applications-next-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230775</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Microstrategy_Lightning.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Microstrategy_Lightning.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[MicroStrategy is willing to launch solutions powered by Bitcoin Lightning Network that could reach millions of users.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MicroStrategy&#8217;s Executive Chairman &#8211; Michael Saylor &#8211; said the company intends to roll out Bitcoin Lightning Network-powered solutions and applications next year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The business intelligence firm previously planned to launch an enterprise Lightning Wallet and Lightning servers and was looking to hire a software engineer to be in charge.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Presenting the 2023 Plans</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Saylor </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1608161681619947520" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the firm&#8217;s intentions on Twitter Spaces, saying MicroStrategy is exploring ways to integrate Lightning Network solutions. As such, the company could enable consumers to process faster, cheaper, and more efficient bitcoin transactions.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;What if we actually created an enterprise deployable Lightning wallet on one side, and then on the other side … what if we created an enterprise server that you could use to monetize any website?&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Executive Chairman suggested that businesses could employ the Lightning Network to stimulate clients by giving them small amounts of bitcoin (satoshis) when they apply for certain online services. The reward campaign could reach millions of users, he added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Saylor also claimed that the rollout of a Lightning Network Wallet could take part in Internet security. For example, individuals visiting dubious web pages could deposit &#8220;100,000&#8221; satoshis (around $17 at current prices) to protect themselves from cyber threats. The assets would be restored once users complete their website visit.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American said MicroStrategy aims to spread the Lightning Network applications in the first quarter of 2023, believing it could target millions:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We want to make it possible for any enterprise to spin up a Lighting wallet and a Lightning wallet architecture in the matter of an afternoon and deploy it to [thousands or millions of people].&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-looking-to-hire-bitcoin-lightning-software-engineer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hinted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> about its plans in September, adding a job listing for a Bitcoin Lightning Software Engineer. The main role would be to build a Lightning Network-based SaaS platform and provide enterprises with &#8220;innovative solutions to cyber-security challenges and enabling new eCommerce use-cases.&#8221;</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_185746" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185746" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-185746" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg" alt="Michael_Saylor" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Michael_Saylor-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-185746" class="wp-caption-text">Michael Saylor, Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Adding More BTC</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the prolonged bear market, MicroStrategy recently doubled down on its bitcoin agenda, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-adds-2500-btc-total-stack-now-132251-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">buying</a> additional 2,501 BTC. The company&#8217;s stash increased to 132,251 BTC (nearly $2.2 billion at the moment of writing these lines).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It started accumulating bitcoin in the summer of 2020, spending a little over $4 billion to acquire the total in the following years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Due to bitcoin&#8217;s price crash in 2022, MicroStrategy currently sits on around $1.8 billion of unrealized losses.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-to-introduce-bitcoin-lightning-applications-next-year/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy to Introduce Bitcoin Lightning Applications Next Year</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Seeks Deadline Extension</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-seeks-deadline-extension/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230793</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Loan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Loan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The bar date is currently slated for January 3rd.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network said it is preparing to file a motion requesting a deadline extension for users to submit their claims by another month.</p>
<p>In its latest <a href="https://twitter.com/CelsiusNetwork/status/1608285816933031936" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a>, Celsius stated that the motion is scheduled to be heard by the bankruptcy court on January 10. The deadline will be extended until at least then.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For now, the deadline is extended until the motion is heard by the Court. We will provide further updates on the bar date as they become available.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Celsius had filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the US Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York in July following the unraveling of the Terra ecosystem tokens.</li>
<li>As per the court filing by consulting firm Kirkland &amp; Ellis, the company had $2.8 billion in liabilities on its balance sheet.</li>
<li>Celsius was also granted an extension to submit the Chapter 11 reorganization plan until mid-February.</li>
<li>During the same time, bankruptcy judge Martin Glenn <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-ordered-to-return-44m-of-customers-custodied-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the embattled crypto lender to return funds of around $44 million to customers that were not part of its yield-bearing accounts.</li>
<li>Celsius account holders have taken up social media to <a href="https://twitter.com/TheRyanReserve/status/1608294870858305537" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">voice</a> out their outrage over taking to Twitter to complain about the costs and slow progress.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Lawyers &amp; advisors like to spend client money just as much as <a href="https://twitter.com/Mashinsky?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Mashinsky</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Celsius?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Celsius</a> &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SBF_FTX</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/FTX?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#FTX</a> &#8211; All they need is good old Chapter 11 protection &amp; magically it becomes legal. <a href="https://t.co/G7cFzIb61z" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/G7cFzIb61z</a></p>
<p>— Simon Dixon (@SimonDixonTwitt) <a href="https://twitter.com/SimonDixonTwitt/status/1608076400879083520?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 28, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>Recently, Financial Times <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0c9a1df4-2a3e-4aa8-9733-53dd4507d765" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a> that costs are piling up for law firms associated with a series of crypto companies that have succumbed to the ongoing crypto winter.</li>
<li>In the case of Celsius, the lawyers, bankers, and other advisers released detailed fee requests to the New York federal bankruptcy court totaling $53 million.</li>
<li>To investors&#8217; frustration, Kirkland &amp; Ellis and White &amp; Case are involved in Celsius and have top lawyers billing over $1,800 per hour.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-celsius-seeks-deadline-extension/" rel="nofollow">Bankrupt Crypto Lender Celsius Seeks Deadline Extension</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>EQBR Holdings Unveils EQ Hub &#8211; No-Code Web3 Development Platform &#8211; at CES 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eqbr-holdings-unveils-eq-hub-no-code-web3-development-platform-at-ces-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 11:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230819</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/EQBR.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/EQBR.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore – December 28, 2022] EQBR Holdings (“EQBR”), a Web3 business solution provider, announced that it will unveil EQ Hub, a next generation blockchain development platform at upcoming CES 2023 to be held in Las Vegas between January 5, 2023 and January 8, 2023. EQ Hub is a trailblazing product seeking to [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore – December 28, 2022]</strong></p>
<p>EQBR Holdings (“EQBR”), a Web3 business solution provider, announced that it will unveil EQ Hub, a next generation blockchain development platform at upcoming CES 2023 to be held in Las Vegas between January 5, 2023 and January 8, 2023.</p>
<p>EQ Hub is a trailblazing product seeking to remove any barriers in Web3 technology adoption. EQ Hub provides no code programing environment for business users as well as developers. Business users can choose from pre-built dApps and easily configure and customize for quick deployment. For developers who are not familiar with blockchain programing languages such as Solidity, EQ Hub provides a rich smart contract library that can be used to build a broad range of dApps, including DeFi, games and NFT. EQ Hub’s unique differentiation from other blockchain development platform is that developers can build and operate a brand new L1 blockchain network using a very simple user interface. This interface enables developers to configure and launch a new blockchain network less than an hour.</p>
<p>EQ Hub service will be available on Equilibrium &#8211; a blockchain mainnet developed by EQBR &#8211; and deployed in cloud so that any developer can subscribe to the service. Mr. Hyunki Lee, a Chief Technology Officer of EQBR, explains, “We are very confident that Equilibrium’s performance surpasses other blockchain mainnet in terms of scalability and stability but using EQ Hub does not necessarily mean developers must use the Equilibrium mainnet. Developers may build their own mainnet using EQ Hub and interoperate with other L1 blockchain networks, such as Ethereum or BNB, using our gateway service. We do not force developers to use a specific mainnet or a specific network.”</p>
<blockquote><p>Mr. Jae Kun Jung, head of EQBR&#8217;s business division said “The release of EQ Hub is meaningful because it can expedite migration from Web2 into Web3. Existing online services can be transferred to Web3 environment through EQ Hub at minimum time and costs. Those who want to launch Web3 business will be able to use EQ Hub to build and launch a new project as well as a new dApp. There is no need for upfront investment as our service will be provided on a subscription basis. We want many innovative entrepreneurs to venture into Web 3.0 business without a burden of failure.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Even before the official release of EQ Hub, several closed beta customers have already started to build their commercial services on blockchain networks built by EQ Hub. EQBR’s Singaporean affiliate also completed an ICO and established Volare Network, a blockchain network for gaming and entertainment content. Based on the experiences gained in deploying commercial services, EQBR will provide packaged turnkey applications for specific business purposes such as NFT, STO(Securitized Token Offering), and Payment.</p>
<p>EQ Hub will be launching its open beta program at CEO 2023, and those who want to experience EQ Hub may visit North Hall booth 8874/8875 and Web 3.0 Metaverse Studio in Main Hall at Las Vegas Convention &amp; World Trade Center (LVCC) during CES 2023.</p>
<h2>About EQBR Holdings:</h2>
<p>Founded in 2020, EQBR has engaged with various businesses as an operator, investor and third-party solutions provider. EQBR’s innovative blockchain engine called Equilibrium is the world’s first commercially-viable blockchain.  Since then, EQBR has developed several dApps on top of Equilibrium, including Whisper Messenger (a blockchain-based secure messenger), EQ Hub (a no-code developer tool) and now, My Flex (an NFT minting platform).</p>
<p>Related Links</p>
<p>• EQBR<br />
o   To learn more, visit <a href="https://eqbr.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://eqbr.com</a><br />
o   Follow EQBR on Medium: <a href="https://medium.com/eqbr" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://medium.com/eqbr </a><br />
o   Follow EQBR CES 2023: <a href="https://ces2023.eqbr.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://ces2023.eqbr.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eqbr-holdings-unveils-eq-hub-no-code-web3-development-platform-at-ces-2023/" rel="nofollow">EQBR Holdings Unveils EQ Hub &#8211; No-Code Web3 Development Platform &#8211; at CES 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Classic (LUNC) Drops 8%, Bitcoin Dips to Weekly Lows (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/terra-classic-lunc-drops-8-bitcoin-dips-to-weekly-lows-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 09:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230802</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/bitcoin_red_background_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solana also continues to suffer and currently sits below $10.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin continued with minor price declines in the past 24 hours, resulting in a dip to a weekly low of under $16,500.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also in the red, including substantial losses from Solana and Terra Classic.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Dropped to Weekly Lows</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency had a calm weekend, in which it stood at around $16,800 without any movements in either direction. This resulted in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/market-watch-bitcoin-sees-zero-move-weekly-litecoin-jumps-5/" data-wpel-link="internal">closing</a> the week at precisely the same spot it was seven days ago.</p>
<p>The start of the new week saw a minor leg-up that drove the asset to almost $17,000. Nevertheless, BTC failed ahead of that level, as it has been doing for the past several weeks.</p>
<p>The subsequent rejection pushed bitcoin south, culminating in a price dip below $16,500 for the first time in just over a week. This came even with MicroStrategy&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-adds-2500-btc-total-stack-now-132251-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">latest BTC purchase</a>.</p>
<p>Despite reclaiming around $100 since that intraday low, the cryptocurrency is still slightly in the red on a 24-hour scale.</p>
<p>Although its market cap has slipped to just under $320 billion, its dominance over the altcoins has remained inches above 40% on CoinMarketCap.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230805" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230805" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230805" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-11-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230805" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LUNC and SOL Dump Hard (Again)</h2>
<p>Terra Classic and Solana are among the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/altcoins-bleeding-out-solana-and-lunc-crash-by-double-digits-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">poorest performers</a> in the past few days, which is somewhat surprising for the former. LUNC had several consecutive days of price gains, but the trend changed when Binance <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-updates-lunc-burning-model-following-controversial-community-proposals/" data-wpel-link="internal">updated</a> its burning mechanism.</p>
<p>Terra dumped by double digits yesterday, while another 8% daily decline has pushed it down to $0.00014.</p>
<p>SOL has struggled ever since FTX, Alameda filed for bankruptcy. The past 24 hours were not kind to the asset, as it has dumped below $10 for the first time in a while.</p>
<p>Ripple, Cardano, and Litecoin are also well in the red from the larger-cap alts. In contrast, Ethereum, Binance Coin, OKB, and Tron are with insignificant gains.</p>
<p>As such, it&#8217;s no surprise that the crypto market cap has remained just under $800 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230806" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230806" style="width: 1846px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230806" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9.jpg" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1846" height="736" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9.jpg 1846w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9-1024x408.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9-768x306.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9-1536x612.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-9-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1846px) 100vw, 1846px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230806" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terra-classic-lunc-drops-8-bitcoin-dips-to-weekly-lows-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Terra Classic (LUNC) Drops 8%, Bitcoin Dips to Weekly Lows (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
