<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 May – EGLD, TRX, INJ</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-may-egld-trx-inj.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and Ethereum are currently witnessing a significant uptick, coinciding with a downturn in traditional banking equities, particularly in light of the recent sale of First Republic Bank. &lt;br /&gt;
How might this sudden cryptocurrency market bounce affect the selection of the best crypto to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin exhibited a notable ascent earlier today, setting an intra-day high of $28,916 from its opening price of $28,086....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-may-egld-trx-inj.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 2 May – EGLD, TRX, INJ&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>EGLD</category><category>LPX</category><category>TRX</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>INJ</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>MultiversX</category><category>Launchpad</category><category>Tron</category><category>Injective</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>memes</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-2-may-egld-trx-inj.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112785/273060/best-crypto-2-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="264107"/></item><item><title>Can the Bitcoin (BTC) Price Snap its Recent Run of Ugly May Returns?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-bitcoin-btc-price-snap-its-recent-run-of-ugly-may-returns.htm</link><description>Since 2011, Bitcoin (BTC) has posted an average return of 18.3% in May, according to data presented by bitcoinmonthlyreturn.com. &lt;br /&gt;
However, two of the worst three Mays in Bitcoin’s history have come in the last two years. &lt;br /&gt;
In May 2021, Bitcoin shed a stunning 35.38% of its value. &lt;br /&gt;
In May 2022, Bitcoin dropped a more modest, but still ugly 15.56%. &lt;br /&gt;
And it’s not been the best start to May 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/can-bitcoin-btc-price-snap-its-recent-run-of-ugly-may-returns.htm"&gt;Read More: Can the Bitcoin (BTC) Price Snap its Recent Run of Ugly May Returns?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Bank Crisis</category><category>Fed</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-bitcoin-btc-price-snap-its-recent-run-of-ugly-may-returns.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112781/272952/btc-11.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="164285"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Daily Transactions Surge to Record Highs, But These Alternative Metrics Bode Less Well for BTC Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-daily-transactions-surge-record-highs-but-these-alternative-metrics-bode-less-well-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>The number of transactions taking place on the Bitcoin network hit a record high of 682,099 on Monday, according to data presented by crypto analytics firm Glassnode. &lt;br /&gt;
A surge in the last few days has seen the number of Bitcoin transactions fly past its prior record high of around 425,000 printed back in 2019, back when the Bitcoin price was around $5,500....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-daily-transactions-surge-record-highs-but-these-alternative-metrics-bode-less-well-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Daily Transactions Surge to Record Highs, But These Alternative Metrics Bode Less Well for BTC Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Transactions</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-daily-transactions-surge-record-highs-but-these-alternative-metrics-bode-less-well-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112779/272658/btc-33.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6239347"/></item><item><title>Paradigm and Blur Developers Announce Blend, a P2P NFT Lending Protocol – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-blur-developers-announce-blend-p2p-nft-lending-protocol-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>The NFT marketplace Blur on Monday launched a new NFT-focused lending platform that operates without expirations and with no external price oracles like other lending platforms rely on....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-blur-developers-announce-blend-p2p-nft-lending-protocol-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: Paradigm and Blur Developers Announce Blend, a P2P NFT Lending Protocol – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>NFT</category><category>Blur</category><category>Paradigm</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paradigm-blur-developers-announce-blend-p2p-nft-lending-protocol-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112764/272470/nfts.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="257681"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Rumors Emerge Regarding Secret Meetings Between SEC and Ripple – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-rumors-emerge-regarding-secret-meetings-between-sec-ripple-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The price of XRP, the cryptocurrency that powers the XRP Ledger created by US fintech company Ripple, continues to be lower on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite rumors circulating on social media that Ripple and the SEC are to hold an undisclosed meeting next Monday, XRP has failed to pick up and was last changing hands just under $0.46, down about 1.5% on the day, around 6% versus last week’s highs and close to 15% since the start of April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-rumors-emerge-regarding-secret-meetings-between-sec-ripple-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Rumors Emerge Regarding Secret Meetings Between SEC and Ripple – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-rumors-emerge-regarding-secret-meetings-between-sec-ripple-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112772/272485/xrp-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="635150"/></item><item><title>Binance Faces ChatGPT-Powered Smear Campaign Linking Founder to Chinese Communist Party – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-chatgpt-powered-smear-campaign-linking-founder-to-chinese-communist-party-heres-the-latest.htm</link><description>Binance has become a victim of a smear campaign by an AI-powered chatbot that spreads false information regarding its founder Changpeng Zhao (CZ) and his supposed affiliation with the Chinese Communist Party. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance has reportedly received dozens of inquiries from congressional offices regarding CZ and his connection to the China National Petroleum Corporation (CNPC) over the past couple of days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-chatgpt-powered-smear-campaign-linking-founder-to-chinese-communist-party-heres-the-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Faces ChatGPT-Powered Smear Campaign Linking Founder to Chinese Communist Party – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-faces-chatgpt-powered-smear-campaign-linking-founder-to-chinese-communist-party-heres-the-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112762/272469/binance-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="41969"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Poloniex to Pay $7.6M in Settlement with US Authority, Complaint Alleges Coinbase Violated Illinois' Biometric Information Privacy Act, 3AC-founders’ OPNX Reprimanded by Dubai Regulator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-poloniex-to-pay-76m-in-settlement-with-us-authority-complaint-alleges-coinbase-violated-illinois-biometric-information-privacy-act-3ac-founders-opnx-reprimanded-by-dubai-regulator.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-poloniex-to-pay-76m-in-settlement-with-us-authority-complaint-alleges-coinbase-violated-illinois-biometric-information-privacy-act-3ac-founders-opnx-reprimanded-by-dubai-regulator.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Poloniex to Pay $7.6M in Settlement with US Authority, Complaint Alleges Coinbase Violated Illinois' Biometric Information Privacy Act, 3AC-founders’ OPNX Reprimanded by Dubai Regulator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Poloniex</category><category>USA</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Privacy</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>Dubai</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>UK</category><category>Legal</category><category>Security</category><category>Hack</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>ETF</category><category>Canada</category><category>Mining</category><category>Web3</category><category>Market</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-poloniex-to-pay-76m-in-settlement-with-us-authority-complaint-alleges-coinbase-violated-illinois-biometric-information-privacy-act-3ac-founders-opnx-reprimanded-by-dubai-regulator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112704/272373/adobestock-zimmytws-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="82728"/></item><item><title>FTX Investor Temasek Bets $10 Million On New Scalable Algorithmic Currency – Here’s How It Works</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investor-temasek-bets-10-million-new-scalable-algorithmic-currency-heres-how-it-works.htm</link><description>Temasek, a Singapore government-owned firm, is doubling down on its crypto investment strategy with a $10 million injection into Array, a new scalable algorithmic currency that utilizes artificial intelligence and smart contracts. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite suffering significant losses through its exposure to the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, Temasek remains committed to the crypto space....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investor-temasek-bets-10-million-new-scalable-algorithmic-currency-heres-how-it-works.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Investor Temasek Bets $10 Million On New Scalable Algorithmic Currency – Here’s How It Works&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-investor-temasek-bets-10-million-new-scalable-algorithmic-currency-heres-how-it-works.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112725/272442/blockchain-g9a7fa2640-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="387630"/></item><item><title>“Binance Japan” Set to Launch in June – Which Country Comes Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-japan-set-launch-june-which-country-comes-next.htm</link><description>The crypto exchange giant Binance is set to launch “Binance Japan” next month by rebranding a Japanese exchange it bought late last year. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance snapped up shares in the Sakura Exchange BitCoin (SEBC) trading platform in a deal finalized at the end of November 2022. &lt;br /&gt;
And per an official SEBC notice and the Japanese media outlet CoinPost, Binance will now seek to rebrand SEBC under its own name. &lt;br /&gt;
The deal was completed by the Binance affiliate Binance (AP) Holdings....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-japan-set-launch-june-which-country-comes-next.htm"&gt;Read More: “Binance Japan” Set to Launch in June – Which Country Comes Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Japan</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-japan-set-launch-june-which-country-comes-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112724/272421/adobestock-558087473-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="194061"/></item><item><title>William Wendt, Ecosystem Growth Manager at Oasis, on Web3 Decentralized Infrastructure, Privacy, and Security | Ep. 226</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/william-wendt-ecosystem-growth-manager-at-oasis-web3-decentralized-infrastructure-privacy-security-ep-226.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, William Wendt, Ecosystem Growth Manager at Oasis, talks about how blockchain is open and transparent, the intersection of AI and web3, and user protection in the web3 ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/william-wendt-ecosystem-growth-manager-at-oasis-web3-decentralized-infrastructure-privacy-security-ep-226.htm"&gt;Read More: William Wendt, Ecosystem Growth Manager at Oasis, on Web3 Decentralized Infrastructure, Privacy, and Security | Ep. 226&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/william-wendt-ecosystem-growth-manager-at-oasis-web3-decentralized-infrastructure-privacy-security-ep-226.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112729/272428/will-wendt-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="107481"/></item><item><title>Nigeria's SEC May Permit Asset-Backed Tokens, Crypto Trading Remains Off-Limits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-sec-may-permit-asset-backed-tokens-crypto-trading-remains-off-limits.htm</link><description>Despite banning crypto transactions in February 2021, Nigeria is now considering a new approach to digital asset trading by allowing asset-backed tokens.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a recent report by Bloomberg, the Nigerian SEC has opened up the application process for digital exchanges to test tokenized asset offerings.  &lt;br /&gt;
This move is part of the country's efforts to boost market participation in the digital asset space. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-sec-may-permit-asset-backed-tokens-crypto-trading-remains-off-limits.htm"&gt;Read More: Nigeria's SEC May Permit Asset-Backed Tokens, Crypto Trading Remains Off-Limits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-sec-may-permit-asset-backed-tokens-crypto-trading-remains-off-limits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112722/272434/pexels-rodnae-productions.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="233508"/></item><item><title>A16z Crypto Calls for 'More Nuanced' UK Regulatory Framework for Digital Assets</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/a16z-crypto-calls-for-more-nuanced-uk-regulatory-framework-for-digital-assets.htm</link><description>Venture capital giant Andreessen Horowitz, better known as a16z, has called for a “more nuanced” approach to crypto regulations in the UK, saying the current don’t distinguish between risky centralized crypto systems and less risky decentralized systems....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/a16z-crypto-calls-for-more-nuanced-uk-regulatory-framework-for-digital-assets.htm"&gt;Read More: A16z Crypto Calls for 'More Nuanced' UK Regulatory Framework for Digital Assets&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>a16z</category><category>Andreessen Horowitz</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/a16z-crypto-calls-for-more-nuanced-uk-regulatory-framework-for-digital-assets.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112731/272433/a16z.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="108381"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Justin Sun Apologizes Following Clash with Binance CEO Over Sui LaunchPool</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-apologizes-following-clash-with-binance-ceo-over-sui-launchpool.htm</link><description>The founder of Tron and well-known billionaire, Justin Sun, has issued a public apology to Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, following a recent incident involving a $56.1 million TrueUSD deposit.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Twitter statement, Sun revealed that the funds had been mistakenly used by some members of the Tron team without proper confirmation of their purpose. &lt;br /&gt;
After the deposit, Changpeng Zhao warned Sun against plans to grab the LaunchPool Sui tokens using the deposits. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-apologizes-following-clash-with-binance-ceo-over-sui-launchpool.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Justin Sun Apologizes Following Clash with Binance CEO Over Sui LaunchPool&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-justin-sun-apologizes-following-clash-with-binance-ceo-over-sui-launchpool.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112717/272441/screenshot-2023-05-02-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="569224"/></item><item><title>El Salvador’s Bitcoin City Has Not Been Shelved, Say Bukele-linked Bitcoiners</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-city-has-not-been-shelved-say-bukele-linked-bitcoiners.htm</link><description>An El Salvador government-linked organization has rubbished claims that the nation’s ambitious plans to build a haven for Bitcoiners have been shelved. &lt;br /&gt;
Late last month, a number of Twitter-based individuals claimed that they had come across documentary evidence that the Ministry of Public Works had confirmed that the Bitcoin City project “does not exist.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-city-has-not-been-shelved-say-bukele-linked-bitcoiners.htm"&gt;Read More: El Salvador’s Bitcoin City Has Not Been Shelved, Say Bukele-linked Bitcoiners&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>El Salvador</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-city-has-not-been-shelved-say-bukele-linked-bitcoiners.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112698/272369/adobestock-525250918.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="956186"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Meme Coins See Huge Surge in Volume – New Bull Rally Starting?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-see-huge-surge-volume-new-bull-rally-starting.htm</link><description>The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) has dropped by 1% in the past 24 hours, falling to $0.00000990 as the cryptocurrency market as a whole suffers a similar decline. &lt;br /&gt;
SHIB is also down by 4% in the past week and 11% in the last 30 days, with the meme token up by 22%  since the start of the year. &lt;br /&gt;
And while SHIB may be down at the moment, the rise of Pepe (PEPE) has caused a surge in trading volumes for meme tokens, something which could ultimately drive interest towards Shiba Inu....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-see-huge-surge-volume-new-bull-rally-starting.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Meme Coins See Huge Surge in Volume – New Bull Rally Starting?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-see-huge-surge-volume-new-bull-rally-starting.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112696/272368/shiba-inu-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1428918"/></item><item><title>"Shark Tank" Meets Crypto: CoinMarketCap Launches "Killer Whale" TV Show</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-meets-crypto-coinmarketcap-launches-killer-whale-tv-show.htm</link><description>Major crypto price tracking site CoinMarketCap is venturing into the world of reality TV with the launch of “Killer Whales,” a new contest show focused on Web3.  &lt;br /&gt;
The show, inspired by the popular TV series “Shark Tank,” is being produced in partnership with Web3 entertainment company Hello Labs, CoinMarketCap said in a recent blog post. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-meets-crypto-coinmarketcap-launches-killer-whale-tv-show.htm"&gt;Read More: "Shark Tank" Meets Crypto: CoinMarketCap Launches "Killer Whale" TV Show&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CoinMarketCap</category><category>Shark Tank</category><category>TV set</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shark-tank-meets-crypto-coinmarketcap-launches-killer-whale-tv-show.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112697/272366/shark-g4d57f18a7-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="168728"/></item><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 250% in 7 Days – Can PEPE Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-250-7-days-can-pepe-reach-1.htm</link><description>The Pepe Coin price has dropped by 7% in the past 24 hours, although its level of $0.00000126 also represents a massive 250% gain in the past seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
This surge has enabled PEPE to enter the top 100 cryptocurrencies by market cap, with the new Pepe-themed meme token also rising by 525% in two weeks, having launched on April 16....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-250-7-days-can-pepe-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Prediction as PEPE Blasts Up 250% in 7 Days – Can PEPE Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-pepe-blasts-up-250-7-days-can-pepe-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112691/272365/pepe-coin-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1520215"/></item><item><title>Art Auction Giant Sotheby's Unveils On-Chain NFT Secondary Marketplace</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/art-auction-giant-sothebys-unveils-on-chain-nft-secondary-marketplace.htm</link><description>Major auction house Sotheby’s has launched a non-fungible token (NFT) secondary marketplace that allows users to buy curated NFTs on the Ethereum (ETH) and Polygon (MATIC) networks. &lt;br /&gt;
The sales system will be integrated and fully on-chain, enabling the buyers to pay in ETH or MATIC, the native token of the two blockchains.  &lt;br /&gt;
Furthermore, Sotheby's Metaverse, which is the art auction house's Web3 arm, will allow direct transactions between the platform's users.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/art-auction-giant-sothebys-unveils-on-chain-nft-secondary-marketplace.htm"&gt;Read More: Art Auction Giant Sotheby's Unveils On-Chain NFT Secondary Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Sotheby's</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/art-auction-giant-sothebys-unveils-on-chain-nft-secondary-marketplace.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112688/272361/screenshot-2023-05-02-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="453118"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Finds Support at $27,750 - What Lies Ahead?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-finds-support-at-27750-what-lies-ahead.htm</link><description>In recent trading sessions, Bitcoin has found support at the $27,750 level, sparking curiosity among investors and traders about the cryptocurrency's future trajectory. After experiencing a bearish trend, many are wondering if this support level will hold or if further declines are on the horizon.  &lt;br /&gt;
Market participants should keep a close eye on technical indicators, as well as any potential catalysts or news events that could influence the price of BTC. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-finds-support-at-27750-what-lies-ahead.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Finds Support at $27,750 - What Lies Ahead?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-finds-support-at-27750-what-lies-ahead.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112686/272355/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1075440"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bloomberg Analyst Says BTC Could Hit $100,000 if History is Right – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bloomberg-analyst-says-btc-could-hit-100000-if-history-right-time-buy.htm</link><description>As the crypto market continues to evolve, many are looking for reliable Bitcoin price predictions to help guide their investment decisions. A recent statement by a Bloomberg analyst suggests that BTC could reach $100,000 if historical trends hold true.  &lt;br /&gt;
This raises the question – is now the right time to buy Bitcoin and capitalize on this potential price surge?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bloomberg-analyst-says-btc-could-hit-100000-if-history-right-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bloomberg Analyst Says BTC Could Hit $100,000 if History is Right – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bloomberg-analyst-says-btc-could-hit-100000-if-history-right-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112665/272327/m1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="501011"/></item></channel></rss>
