<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Award-Winning Green Web3 Start-up Ecoterra Raises $3.5 Million as Investors Swoop In Ahead of 10% Price Rise</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-green-web3-start-up-ecoterra-raises-35-million-as-investors-swoop-in-ahead-of-10-price-rise.htm</link><description>Award-winning green web3 start-up ecoterra’s presale continues to fly, with sales of its native $ECOTERRA token having now surpassed $3.5 million as investors swoop in ahead of a 10% token price rise. &lt;br /&gt;
Ecoterra is building an all-in-one $ECOTERRA-powered web3 ecosystem, designed to encourage recycling via its first-of-its-kind Recycle-to-Earn (R2E) system, facilitate trade in recycled materials and encourage individuals and businesses to offset their carbon footprint....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-green-web3-start-up-ecoterra-raises-35-million-as-investors-swoop-in-ahead-of-10-price-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Award-Winning Green Web3 Start-up Ecoterra Raises $3.5 Million as Investors Swoop In Ahead of 10% Price Rise&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Presale</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>R2E</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/award-winning-green-web3-start-up-ecoterra-raises-35-million-as-investors-swoop-in-ahead-of-10-price-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113820/275389/ecoterra-presale.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="58085"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 May – Bitget Token, Stellar, Cosmos</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-may-bitget-token-stellar-cosmos.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) has fallen below the critical support level of $27,000 for the first time in almost two months, raising concerns about the immediate future of the cryptocurrency market. &lt;br /&gt;
With skittish macro conditions and lingering uncertainties surrounding the US debt ceiling and the possibility of a recession, the crypto market is facing a challenging periods, right along with other risk assets. &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst these recent market developments, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-may-bitget-token-stellar-cosmos.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 May – Bitget Token, Stellar, Cosmos&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitget token</category><category>Stellar</category><category>Cosmos</category><category>BGB</category><category>XLM</category><category>ATOM</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Sponge</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AI</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web3</category><category>NFT</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-may-bitget-token-stellar-cosmos.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113819/275387/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>US SEC’s Hester Peirce Says European Regulation MiCA Could Serve as a “Model” for the US</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secs-hester-peirce-says-european-regulation-mica-could-serve-as-model-for-us.htm</link><description>Republican leader at the US Securities and Exchange Commission said Europe’s legislation to regulate cryptocurrency could be a model as the country grapples with how to write rules for the industry. &lt;br /&gt;
SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce, also nicknamed “Crypto Mom,” spoke at a Financial Times live event this week. &lt;br /&gt;
“MiCA can serve as a model for us,” Peirce said. &lt;br /&gt;
European Union lawmakers voted in April to pass the Markets in Crypto Assets law (or MiCA). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secs-hester-peirce-says-european-regulation-mica-could-serve-as-model-for-us.htm"&gt;Read More: US SEC’s Hester Peirce Says European Regulation MiCA Could Serve as a “Model” for the US&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Hester Peirce</category><category>Regulation</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Legislation</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-secs-hester-peirce-says-european-regulation-mica-could-serve-as-model-for-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113818/275384/hpeirce.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="196109"/></item><item><title>Binance Says Farewell to Canada Following New Guidance Implementing Restrictions on Exchanges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-says-farewell-canada-following-new-guidance-implementing-restrictions-exchanges.htm</link><description>Binance is pulling out of Canada. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s largest crypto exchange said on Twitter that it was withdrawing from the country due to new guidance about stablecoins and limits to investors. &lt;br /&gt;
“We put off this decision as long as we could to explore other reasonable avenues to protect our Canadian users, but it has become apparent that there are none,” the company said. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, who is a Canadian citizen, retweeted the news....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-says-farewell-canada-following-new-guidance-implementing-restrictions-exchanges.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Says Farewell to Canada Following New Guidance Implementing Restrictions on Exchanges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Canada</category><category>CZ binance</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-says-farewell-canada-following-new-guidance-implementing-restrictions-exchanges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113813/275383/canadian-flag-g32cf213ef-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="113371"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Approaches Long-Term $25,000 Support Level – Will the Price Hold?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-long-term-25000-support-level-will-the-price-hold.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin approaches the long-term support level of $25,000, there are speculations about whether the price will hold or experience further decline.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors closely monitor the market dynamics to determine the next potential move for the leading cryptocurrency. The price prediction for Bitcoin remains uncertain, as it navigates this critical support level. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-long-term-25000-support-level-will-the-price-hold.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Approaches Long-Term $25,000 Support Level – Will the Price Hold?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-long-term-25000-support-level-will-the-price-hold.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113782/275256/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="991362"/></item><item><title>Former Lawmakers Join Coinbase’s New Global Advisory Council</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-lawmakers-join-coinbases-new-global-advisory-council.htm</link><description>Former US lawmakers Patrick Toomey, R-Pa., Tim Ryan, D-Ohio., and Patrick Maloney, D-N.Y will join Coinbase’s newly launched Global Advisory Council to guide its leadership team. &lt;br /&gt;
“The creation of the Advisory Council is a significant step for Coinbase as we navigate an increasingly complex and evolving landscape in the US and internationally,” the exchange said in a statement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-lawmakers-join-coinbases-new-global-advisory-council.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Lawmakers Join Coinbase’s New Global Advisory Council&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-lawmakers-join-coinbases-new-global-advisory-council.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113811/275382/brian-armstrong-coinbase-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="175702"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Bounces Up 20% From Recent Bottom – Can LTC Reach $100 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-bounces-up-20-from-recent-bottom-can-ltc-reach-1-2023.htm</link><description>As broader cryptocurrency markets come under pressure, Litecoin (LTC) is no exception. &lt;br /&gt;
As a result, near-term price predictions remain somewhat downbeat.   &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency, which powers the payment’s focused Litecoin blockchain that was created back in 2011 out of a tweaked version of the Bitcoin source code, was last changing hands around $79 per token....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-bounces-up-20-from-recent-bottom-can-ltc-reach-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Bounces Up 20% From Recent Bottom – Can LTC Reach $100 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Halving</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-bounces-up-20-from-recent-bottom-can-ltc-reach-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113810/275379/ltc.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="8272057"/></item><item><title>Marathon Digital Served with Additional SEC Subpoena for Alleged Violations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-served-with-additional-sec-subpoena-for-alleged-violations.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) mining firm Marathon Digital has been served with an additional subpoena by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over alleged securities laws violations. &lt;br /&gt;
The violations referred to in the subpoena are related to a mining facility built by Marathon Digital in Hardin, Montana in 2020....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-served-with-additional-sec-subpoena-for-alleged-violations.htm"&gt;Read More: Marathon Digital Served with Additional SEC Subpoena for Alleged Violations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Mining</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/marathon-digital-served-with-additional-sec-subpoena-for-alleged-violations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113775/275242/sec-building.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="128378"/></item><item><title>10T Private Equity Firm Seeks $200 Million for New Crypto Startup Investment Fund</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/10t-private-equity-firm-seeks-200-million-for-new-crypto-startup-investment-fund.htm</link><description>Crypto-focused investment firm 10T Holdings is launching a new digital-asset startup investment fund seeking to raise $200 million from investors. &lt;br /&gt;
The new venture, dubbed TenSquared Capital, or 10SQ, aims to back digital asset startups at various stages of growth, Bloomberg reported, citing people familiar with the matter.  &lt;br /&gt;
The firm already has two investments planned, including one in a crypto wallet infrastructure startup expected to close in the coming months....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/10t-private-equity-firm-seeks-200-million-for-new-crypto-startup-investment-fund.htm"&gt;Read More: 10T Private Equity Firm Seeks $200 Million for New Crypto Startup Investment Fund&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Crypto funds</category><category>Investment</category><category>Digital Asset Fund</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/10t-private-equity-firm-seeks-200-million-for-new-crypto-startup-investment-fund.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113802/275318/man-gabb00c8a2-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260411"/></item><item><title>81% of SHIB Holders are in the Red While New Meme Coin NoMeme Eyes Recovery - Here's How to Buy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/81-of-shib-holders-are-in-the-red-while-new-meme-coin-nomeme-eyes-recovery-heres-how-to-buy.htm</link><description>81% of Shiba Inu (SHIB) investors are now in the red, with the world’s second most popular meme coin having largely failed to emulate the bull market seen in other major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum this year. &lt;br /&gt;
That’s according to data from IntoTheBlock, whose summary of six on-chain and exchange signals is “mostly bearish”, with four bearish, one neutral and only one bullish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/81-of-shib-holders-are-in-the-red-while-new-meme-coin-nomeme-eyes-recovery-heres-how-to-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: 81% of SHIB Holders are in the Red While New Meme Coin NoMeme Eyes Recovery - Here's How to Buy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>No Meme Token</category><category>NOMEME</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/81-of-shib-holders-are-in-the-red-while-new-meme-coin-nomeme-eyes-recovery-heres-how-to-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113806/275378/shib-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="88854"/></item><item><title>Former FTX Executive Is Cooperating in a Lawsuit Against Shaquille O’Neal, Tom Brady and Other Celebrities</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-cooperating-lawsuit-against-shaquille-oneal-tom-brady-other-celebrities.htm</link><description>A class action lawsuit against big-name celebrities who promoted bankrupt FTX including Shaquille O’Neal, Tom Brady and Naomi Osaka has garnered cooperation from a former executive, according to a recent court filing. &lt;br /&gt;
Former FTX Chief Compliance Officer Daniel Friedberg provided evidence tying Florida to the celebrities, according to lawyers representing the plaintiffs. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-cooperating-lawsuit-against-shaquille-oneal-tom-brady-other-celebrities.htm"&gt;Read More: Former FTX Executive Is Cooperating in a Lawsuit Against Shaquille O’Neal, Tom Brady and Other Celebrities&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Shaquille O'Neal</category><category>Tom Brady</category><category>Lawsuit</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-ftx-executive-cooperating-lawsuit-against-shaquille-oneal-tom-brady-other-celebrities.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113805/275374/screen-shot-2023-05-12-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="515770"/></item><item><title>$1.4 Trillion Asset Management Firm Franklin Templeton Announces Blockchain Fund II, Targeting Institutional Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/14-trillion-asset-management-firm-franklin-templeton-announces-blockchain-fund-ii-targeting-institutional-investors.htm</link><description>Asset management giant Franklin Templeton has announced that it is setting up a second blockchain fund, after first entering the crypto market in 2021. &lt;br /&gt;
Franklin Templeton Blockchain Fund II, which is the official name of the new fund, will be a private equity fund with a minimum investment amount of $100,000, according to an SEC filing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/14-trillion-asset-management-firm-franklin-templeton-announces-blockchain-fund-ii-targeting-institutional-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: $1.4 Trillion Asset Management Firm Franklin Templeton Announces Blockchain Fund II, Targeting Institutional Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Investment</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/14-trillion-asset-management-firm-franklin-templeton-announces-blockchain-fund-ii-targeting-institutional-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113804/275354/crypto-market.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="637701"/></item><item><title>yPredict Crypto Startup Enters Stage 5, Nears $1 Million Mark as Investors Scoop Up Tokens Ahead of 28.5% Price Increase</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-enters-stage-5-nears-1-million-mark-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm</link><description>Investors are rushing to secure ground-breaking AI-powered trading and market intelligence platform yPredict’s $YPRED crypto token, which continues to fly off the shelves in one of this year’s hottest crypto start-up fundraising presale rounds. &lt;br /&gt;
yPredict’s viral presale, which has already scooped up a whopping more than $935,000 in early investor funds, just entered its fifth stage....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-enters-stage-5-nears-1-million-mark-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: yPredict Crypto Startup Enters Stage 5, Nears $1 Million Mark as Investors Scoop Up Tokens Ahead of 28.5% Price Increase&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-enters-stage-5-nears-1-million-mark-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113796/275311/new-ai-crypto-coin-ypredi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="109980"/></item><item><title>Crypto Leaders Turn to the UAE As Frustration Grows With US Regulators</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-leaders-turn-uae-as-frustration-grows-with-us-regulators.htm</link><description>Some cryptocurrency leaders are turning to the United Arab Emirates as others are showing irritation with US regulators. &lt;br /&gt;
Saqr Ereiqat, co-founder of venture-building firm Crypto Oasis, told CoinTelegraph that the UAE checks all the boxes in terms of countries’ “regulatory infrastructure, digital infrastructure and its ability to attract a global pool of talent.”  &lt;br /&gt;
The UAE checks all those boxes, Ereiqat said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-leaders-turn-uae-as-frustration-grows-with-us-regulators.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Leaders Turn to the UAE As Frustration Grows With US Regulators&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>UAE</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-leaders-turn-uae-as-frustration-grows-with-us-regulators.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113798/275310/dubai-ga0b87404b-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1432118"/></item><item><title>AI Meme-Generating Platform AiDoge’s Presale Surges to $6.2 Million, The Next Dogecoin But With Utility?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-generating-platform-aidoges-presale-surges-to-57-million-the-next-dogecoin-but-with-utility.htm</link><description>Upstart artificial intelligence meme coin project AiDoge’s viral presale continues to surge. &lt;br /&gt;
AiDoge is building a revolutionary new social platform that allows users to generate memes using AiDoge’s cutting-edge generative artificial intelligence (AI) technology and earn crypto if their memes are popular. &lt;br /&gt;
And the project’s presale of its native $AI token continues to pump, reaching $6.2 million on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-generating-platform-aidoges-presale-surges-to-57-million-the-next-dogecoin-but-with-utility.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Meme-Generating Platform AiDoge’s Presale Surges to $6.2 Million, The Next Dogecoin But With Utility?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-generating-platform-aidoges-presale-surges-to-57-million-the-next-dogecoin-but-with-utility.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113793/275308/unnamed-8.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="92694"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Silvergate to Delist from NYSE &amp; Fire 230 Staff, US Trains Ukraine to Target Russian Oligarchs’ Crypto, LG NFT TV</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-silvergate-to-delist-from-nyse-fire-230-staff-us-trains-ukraine-to-target-russian-oligarchs-crypto-lg-nft-tv.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-silvergate-to-delist-from-nyse-fire-230-staff-us-trains-ukraine-to-target-russian-oligarchs-crypto-lg-nft-tv.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Silvergate to Delist from NYSE &amp; Fire 230 Staff, US Trains Ukraine to Target Russian Oligarchs’ Crypto, LG NFT TV&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Silvergate</category><category>Banking</category><category>Career</category><category>USA</category><category>Ukraine</category><category>Russia</category><category>IRS</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Dapp</category><category>Cardano</category><category>Maker</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Bakkt</category><category>Montenegro</category><category>Terra</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>AI</category><category>Staking</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-silvergate-to-delist-from-nyse-fire-230-staff-us-trains-ukraine-to-target-russian-oligarchs-crypto-lg-nft-tv.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113749/275194/adobestock-iurii-gagarin-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="96952"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Gaming Firm Animoca Brands Holds $194 Million in Cash and Stablecoins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-gaming-firm-animoca-brands-holds-194-million-cash-stablecoins.htm</link><description>Animoca Brands has disclosed that it is “financially strong” to continue operations in a recent blog post. &lt;br /&gt;
The Hong Kong-based firm reported a stablecoin reserve of $194 million as of April 30, 2023.   &lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, Animoca Brands holds $566 million worth of liquid digital assets, which includes the utility token for the "Sandbox NFT metaverse platform," known as SAND....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-gaming-firm-animoca-brands-holds-194-million-cash-stablecoins.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Gaming Firm Animoca Brands Holds $194 Million in Cash and Stablecoins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-gaming-firm-animoca-brands-holds-194-million-cash-stablecoins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113783/275295/screenshot-2023-05-12-191017.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="856423"/></item><item><title>Jacobc.eth, Founder at Hyperplay and Founding Contributor at Mantle, on Decentralised Trust, Modular L2s and Account Abstraction | Ep. 229</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/jacobceth-founder-at-hyperplay-founding-contributor-at-mantle-decentralised-trust-modular-l2s-account-abstraction-ep-229.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Jacobc.eth, Founder of Hyperplay &amp; Founding Contributor at Mantle, talks about creating decentralized trust via cryptoeconomic security, re-staking innovation, and account abstraction....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/jacobceth-founder-at-hyperplay-founding-contributor-at-mantle-decentralised-trust-modular-l2s-account-abstraction-ep-229.htm"&gt;Read More: Jacobc.eth, Founder at Hyperplay and Founding Contributor at Mantle, on Decentralised Trust, Modular L2s and Account Abstraction | Ep. 229&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/jacobceth-founder-at-hyperplay-founding-contributor-at-mantle-decentralised-trust-modular-l2s-account-abstraction-ep-229.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113774/275236/jacobc-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="144626"/></item><item><title>Montenegro Court Agrees To Release Terraform’s Kwon and CFO on Bail</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/montenegro-court-agrees-release-terraforms-kwon-cfo-bail.htm</link><description>A court in Montenegro accepted bail to release Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon and former chief financial officer Han Chang-joon from jail on Friday after allegedly using false documents. &lt;br /&gt;
The Basic Court Podgorica said the two would not be allowed to leave their homes in accepting the 400,000 euros in bail for each of them. &lt;br /&gt;
Kwon had been on the run for months after the demise of Terra, which was behind the algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD that fell into a tailspin last year. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/montenegro-court-agrees-release-terraforms-kwon-cfo-bail.htm"&gt;Read More: Montenegro Court Agrees To Release Terraform’s Kwon and CFO on Bail&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>TerraUSD</category><category>Terra Luna</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>Montenegro</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/montenegro-court-agrees-release-terraforms-kwon-cfo-bail.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113778/275253/screen-shot-2023-05-11-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="637793"/></item><item><title>Ripple Managing Directior: 'Crypto Bros Are a Problem' – Calls for More Diversity in Industry</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-managing-directior-crypto-bros-are-problem-calls-for-more-diversity-industry.htm</link><description>Ripple managing director Sendi Young has called for diversity in the crypto industry, citing the Crypto Bros culture as a roadblock to inclusion. &lt;br /&gt;
Seeing that the Crypto Bros stereotype still exists in the crypto industry shows diversification is far from the space. &lt;br /&gt;
Young said this at the Crypto and Digital Assets Summit hosted by the Financial Times....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-managing-directior-crypto-bros-are-problem-calls-for-more-diversity-industry.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple Managing Directior: 'Crypto Bros Are a Problem' – Calls for More Diversity in Industry&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-managing-directior-crypto-bros-are-problem-calls-for-more-diversity-industry.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113776/275252/ripple.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="377491"/></item></channel></rss>
