<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>North Korean ‘Crypto Hackers Targeted S Korean Ministers’ – What Do We Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hackers-targeted-s-korean-ministers-what-do-we-know.htm</link><description>North Korean crypto hackers “targeted South Korean ministers” in a campaign last year, Seoul-based police officials have claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Dong-a Ilbo, police officials took control of a server they claimed was used during the attempted attacks. &lt;br /&gt;
And officers said they had “found two cryptocurrency wallet addresses” on the server. &lt;br /&gt;
They claimed that transactions worth almost $1,600 had been made using these wallets. &lt;br /&gt;
A police official stated:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hackers-targeted-s-korean-ministers-what-do-we-know.htm"&gt;Read More: North Korean ‘Crypto Hackers Targeted S Korean Ministers’ – What Do We Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-crypto-hackers-targeted-s-korean-ministers-what-do-we-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116225/312035/adobestock-123621867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="681584"/></item><item><title>Former Binance.US CEO Brian Brooks Says CZ Was in Charge of the Exchange, Not Him</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-binance-us-ceo-brian-brooks-says-cz-was-charge-of-exchange-not-him.htm</link><description>Brian Brooks, the former CEO of Binance.US, revealed why he left his post at the exchange, in court documents released this week. &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview transcript from December 2021 with the US Securities and Exchange Commission, Brooks was asked about Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao’s role at the US exchange. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-binance-us-ceo-brian-brooks-says-cz-was-charge-of-exchange-not-him.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Binance.US CEO Brian Brooks Says CZ Was in Charge of the Exchange, Not Him&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Brian Brooks</category><category>CZ binance</category><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-binance-us-ceo-brian-brooks-says-cz-was-charge-of-exchange-not-him.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116240/312052/adobestock-321785532-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="216869"/></item><item><title>S Korean Court Set to Decide If LUNC Is a Security – Trial of Terraform’s Shin to Begin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-court-set-decide-if-lunc-security-trail-of-terraforms-shin-begin.htm</link><description>The trial of the Terraform Labs Co-founder Daniel Shin is set to begin in South Korea – with prosecutors determined to prove that Terra Classic (LUNC) is a security. &lt;br /&gt;
Shin (Korean name Shin Hyun-seong) will face trial on fraud charges on June 10. &lt;br /&gt;
And the media outlets Chosun Ilbo and EToday reported that legal experts are expecting a “fierce” battle in court. &lt;br /&gt;
South Korean law currently does not classify any cryptoasset as a “security.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-court-set-decide-if-lunc-security-trail-of-terraforms-shin-begin.htm"&gt;Read More: S Korean Court Set to Decide If LUNC Is a Security – Trial of Terraform’s Shin to Begin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-court-set-decide-if-lunc-security-trail-of-terraforms-shin-begin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116129/311904/s-korea-0706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="246534"/></item><item><title>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Says He Was Met With an “Icy Reception” When Chatting With SEC’s Gensler</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-says-he-was-met-with-an-icy-reception-when-chatting-with-secs-gensler.htm</link><description>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong said he was met with a “pretty icy reception” when chatting with Securities and Exchange Commission Gary Gensler about registering his exchange. &lt;br /&gt;
Armstrong said the exchange tried to get a meeting, and did meet virtually at some point. &lt;br /&gt;
“But unfortunately, it was frankly like a pretty icy reception, I would say,” Armstrong said on Wednesday at a Bloomberg Invest event.  &lt;br /&gt;
Armstrong then said Gensler directed him to talk to his lawyer....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-says-he-was-met-with-an-icy-reception-when-chatting-with-secs-gensler.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Says He Was Met With an “Icy Reception” When Chatting With SEC’s Gensler&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><category>SEC</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-says-he-was-met-with-an-icy-reception-when-chatting-with-secs-gensler.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116242/312054/brian-armstrong-coinbase-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115644"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rallies Up 7% After SEC Fears Wane – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rallies-up-7-after-sec-fears-wane-time-buy.htm</link><description>Bitcoin experienced a significant price surge, rallying up by 7%, as concerns surrounding the SEC's regulatory actions began to subside.  &lt;br /&gt;
This positive development has left investors wondering whether now is the opportune time to enter the market and invest in Bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
With the recent surge in price and the easing of regulatory concerns, many are contemplating whether this could be a favorable moment to buy into the leading cryptocurrency....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rallies-up-7-after-sec-fears-wane-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rallies Up 7% After SEC Fears Wane – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rallies-up-7-after-sec-fears-wane-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116233/312051/7-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480562"/></item><item><title>Unraveling the Crypto Crisis: Timeline of Major Incidents</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/unraveling-crypto-crisis-timeline-of-major-incidents.htm</link><description>The regulatory crackdown on crypto in the US has certainly intensified with the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase, but our timeline shows that the crisis has already been ongoing for a long time. &lt;br /&gt;
These are the major incidents that shaped crypto in 2022 and so far in 2023:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unraveling-crypto-crisis-timeline-of-major-incidents.htm"&gt;Read More: Unraveling the Crypto Crisis: Timeline of Major Incidents&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SEC</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Binance</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/unraveling-crypto-crisis-timeline-of-major-incidents.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116238/312047/crypto-crisis.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3707962"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 June – Optimism, ApeCoin, Lido DAO</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-june-optimism-apecoin-lido-dao.htm</link><description>The U.S. House Financial Services Committee will hold a hearing on June 13 on the topic of cryptocurrencies, potentially giving more clarity to the markets. &lt;br /&gt;
The committee oversees matters like the Federal Reserve Board, the US Treasury, and currency. &lt;br /&gt;
How might this affect the cryptocurrency market and the selection of the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-june-optimism-apecoin-lido-dao.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 June – Optimism, ApeCoin, Lido DAO&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Optimism</category><category>ApeCoin</category><category>Lido Dao</category><category>OP</category><category>APE</category><category>LDO</category><category>WSM</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Crypto Gaming</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web3</category><category>NFT</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>memes</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Rpg</category><category>Role Playing Games</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-june-optimism-apecoin-lido-dao.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116223/312033/best-crypto-7-june.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="478683"/></item><item><title>Crypto Billionaires Lose Big Amid SEC's 2023 Crackdown on Binance and Coinbase</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaires-lose-big-amid-secs-2023-crackdown-binance-coinbase.htm</link><description>Crypto billionaires have been hit hard by the Securities and Exchange Commission's crackdown on Binance and Coinbase, incurring huge losses so far this week. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, known as CZ, has seen his net worth shrink by $1.4 billion to $26 billion, while Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has seen his net worth drop by $361 million to $2.2 billion, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaires-lose-big-amid-secs-2023-crackdown-binance-coinbase.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Billionaires Lose Big Amid SEC's 2023 Crackdown on Binance and Coinbase&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><category>Brian Armstrong</category><category>billionaires</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaires-lose-big-amid-secs-2023-crackdown-binance-coinbase.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116188/311992/money-g860b04e73-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="390489"/></item><item><title>Binance.US To Remove Over 100 Trading Pairs by Thursday Days After SEC Charges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-remove-over-100-trading-pairs-by-thursday-days-after-sec-charges.htm</link><description>Binance.US has decided to remove over 100 trading pairs by June 8, days after the Securities and Exchange Commission sued Binance and its CEO. &lt;br /&gt;
Those trading pairs, which are assets that can be traded for each other on an exchange, included AAVE/USDT, SUSHI/USDT, POLYX/USDT, FLOW/USDT, ATOM/BTC and HBAR/BUSD among others. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-remove-over-100-trading-pairs-by-thursday-days-after-sec-charges.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance.US To Remove Over 100 Trading Pairs by Thursday Days After SEC Charges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>USDT</category><category>BUSD</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-remove-over-100-trading-pairs-by-thursday-days-after-sec-charges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116216/312031/adobestock-456009336-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125292"/></item><item><title>Luxembourg's Antitrust Authority Initiates Probe into Blockchain and Web3 Competition</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/luxembourgs-antitrust-authority-initiates-probe-into-blockchain-web3-competition.htm</link><description>A country in Western Europe, Luxemburg, is making moves amid actions by individual jurisdictions in the European Union for dedicated crypto regulations.  &lt;br /&gt;
 In the latest development, the country's competition regulator, Autorité de la Concurrence, launched a market study on Web3 and Blockchain-based firms. &lt;br /&gt;
The regulator seeks to understand the relationship between blockchain-based products and services and existing digital companies (Web2 firms). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/luxembourgs-antitrust-authority-initiates-probe-into-blockchain-web3-competition.htm"&gt;Read More: Luxembourg's Antitrust Authority Initiates Probe into Blockchain and Web3 Competition&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/luxembourgs-antitrust-authority-initiates-probe-into-blockchain-web3-competition.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116214/312030/pexels-morthy-jameson-9588209.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="46002"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Receives Cease and Desist Notices from 11 US States</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-receives-cease-desist-notices-from-11-us-states.htm</link><description>Following the Securities and Exchanges Commission (SEC) lawsuit, US-based crypto exchange, Coinbase, has received multiple Show Cause orders from US states.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Alabama Securities and Exchange Commission (ASC), alongside ten other US states, filed charges against Coinbase for violating securities laws. &lt;br /&gt;
States that joined the multi-state task force include Kentucky, Illinois, California, South Carolina, Washington, Vermont, Maryland, Wisconsin, New Jersey, and Alabama....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-receives-cease-desist-notices-from-11-us-states.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Receives Cease and Desist Notices from 11 US States&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-receives-cease-desist-notices-from-11-us-states.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116212/312029/securities-and-exchange-g.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="187992"/></item><item><title>ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood Ups Her Stake in Coinbase Following SEC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-ceo-cathie-wood-ups-her-stake-coinbase-following-sec-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Ark Invest CEO Cathie Wood upped her stake in Coinbase after a US regulator accused the exchange of operating unlawfully.  &lt;br /&gt;
Three Ark Investment Management LLC funds, including Wood’s Ark Innovation ETF, bought 419,324 shares of Coinbase on Tuesday, according to Bloomberg News, citing its data.  &lt;br /&gt;
The price of Coinbase shares slumped to as low as $51.61, according to Nasdaq, but has since risen to just over $53 on Wednesday afternoon. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-ceo-cathie-wood-ups-her-stake-coinbase-following-sec-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood Ups Her Stake in Coinbase Following SEC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Cathie Wood</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-ceo-cathie-wood-ups-her-stake-coinbase-following-sec-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116206/312026/adobestock-432529092-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131662"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Pumps Up 12% – Can LUNC Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-pumps-up-12-can-lunc-reach-1.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC), the cryptocurrency which powers the original Terra blockchain that experienced catastrophe after its associated algorithmic “stablecoin” UST lost its 1:1 per to the US dollar last May, is close to 12% higher versus its Tuesday lows in the $0.000085 area. &lt;br /&gt;
LUNC/USD was last changing hands around $0.000094, with the cryptocurrency having experienced extreme volatility in recent days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-pumps-up-12-can-lunc-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Pumps Up 12% – Can LUNC Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-pumps-up-12-can-lunc-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116207/312025/lunc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="680727"/></item><item><title>SEC Chair Gensler Likens Binance to FTX, Expresses Concern Over Crypto Industry</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-likens-binance-ftx-expresses-concern-over-crypto-industry.htm</link><description>Gary Gensler – chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) – sees “parallels” between Binance and its failed competitor FTX’s handling of customer assets.  &lt;br /&gt;
During an interview with Bloomberg on Tuesday, the chairman said financial advisors should not look to Binance as a trustworthy custodian for their crypto assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-likens-binance-ftx-expresses-concern-over-crypto-industry.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Chair Gensler Likens Binance to FTX, Expresses Concern Over Crypto Industry&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-likens-binance-ftx-expresses-concern-over-crypto-industry.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116202/312020/pexels-karolina-grabowska.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="123491"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Bybit Announces AED 1 Million Scholarship Fund at UAE University</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bybit-announces-aed-1-million-scholarship-fund-at-uae-university.htm</link><description>As the regulatory environment in the United States become too hot to handle, cryptocurrency exchanges continue expanding their reach for better business environments. The United Arab Emirates (UAE) presents as one of these greener pastures. One of the most popular exchanges in the world, Bybit, has spotted the region’s potential and is already reaching out for competitive leverage....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bybit-announces-aed-1-million-scholarship-fund-at-uae-university.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Bybit Announces AED 1 Million Scholarship Fund at UAE University&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Adoption</category><category>ByBit</category><category>Bybit. Exchanges</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><category>CZ binance</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bybit-announces-aed-1-million-scholarship-fund-at-uae-university.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116153/311923/sharjah.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="836987"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Pepe Coin? PEPE Price Blasts Up 13% from Recent Bottom and This New AI Crypto Signals Platform Can Help Find the Next Coin to Pump – Here's How it Works</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-blasts-up-13-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-help-find-next-coin-pump-heres-how-it-works.htm</link><description>Amid a turbulent week for major cryptocurrencies following the wide-reaching lawsuit by the SEC against Binance, memecoin markets are enjoying a healthy week - with key memecoins being invigorated by new influx of capital. &lt;br /&gt;
As prudent investor wise to exchange their BNB, SOL, ADA, and MATIC for coins facing less legal headwinds, the enforcement move by Gary Gensler appears to be rebooting a meme season many thought had faded....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-blasts-up-13-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-help-find-next-coin-pump-heres-how-it-works.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Pepe Coin? PEPE Price Blasts Up 13% from Recent Bottom and This New AI Crypto Signals Platform Can Help Find the Next Coin to Pump – Here's How it Works&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-blasts-up-13-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-help-find-next-coin-pump-heres-how-it-works.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116193/312017/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="897917"/></item><item><title>Crypto Whales are Accumulating LPX Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – Best Penny Crypto?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-lpx-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-best-penny-crypto.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market is teeming with opportunities for investors seeking promising projects to put their money in. Penny cryptos, in particular, have piqued the interest of many due to their potential for significant returns on investment.  &lt;br /&gt;
One new project in particular, Launchpad XYZ ($LPX), is capturing the attention of crypto whales and could be the next best penny crypto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-lpx-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-best-penny-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Whales are Accumulating LPX Token Before it Lists on Exchanges – Best Penny Crypto?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Crypto Whales</category><category>Penny Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Launchpad Xyz Presale</category><category>Launchpad Presale</category><category>All In One Crypto</category><category>Crypto Startup</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-lpx-token-before-it-lists-exchanges-best-penny-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116192/312004/adobestock-421631999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="748576"/></item><item><title>Binance Coin is Going to Zero as the SEC Clamps Down on Crypto Exchanges but Eco Friendly Project Ecoterra Just Hit $4.8 Million – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-going-zero-as-sec-clamps-down-crypto-exchanges-but-eco-friendly-project-ecoterra-just-hit-48-million-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>As the aftermath of the seismic SEC v. Binance lawsuit sinks in, crypto markets are reeling at the mass enforcement move by the SEC which has raised major red flags around big projects such as BNB, SOL, MATIC, and ADA. &lt;br /&gt;
Among the worst hit, BNB suffered a sudden -17% cascade as traders took stock of the rocky road ahead for CZ's Binance Coin. &lt;br /&gt;
Binance coin holders are now reeling, in a desperate attempt at consolidation around the $225 support level....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-going-zero-as-sec-clamps-down-crypto-exchanges-but-eco-friendly-project-ecoterra-just-hit-48-million-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Coin is Going to Zero as the SEC Clamps Down on Crypto Exchanges but Eco Friendly Project Ecoterra Just Hit $4.8 Million – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-coin-going-zero-as-sec-clamps-down-crypto-exchanges-but-eco-friendly-project-ecoterra-just-hit-48-million-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116189/312002/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1182796"/></item><item><title>US SEC Files an Emergency Motion in DC Court To Freeze Binance.US Assets — What’s in It?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-files-an-emergency-motion-dc-court-freeze-binanceus-assets-whats-it.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission filed an emergency motion on Tuesday evening seeking a temporary restraining order freezing assets of Binance’s US platform. &lt;br /&gt;
The regulator filed an emergency motion for a temporary restraining order in the US District Court for the District Court of Columbia, asking a judge to freeze assets of BAM Trading and BAM Management, which are doing business as Binance.US.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-files-an-emergency-motion-dc-court-freeze-binanceus-assets-whats-it.htm"&gt;Read More: US SEC Files an Emergency Motion in DC Court To Freeze Binance.US Assets — What’s in It?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sec-files-an-emergency-motion-dc-court-freeze-binanceus-assets-whats-it.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116191/311993/adobestock-521876474-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="389077"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: US Court Orders SEC to Respond to Coinbase's Rulemaking Petition Within 7 Days, Circle Gets Its Singapore MPI Licence, Cathie Woods Uses Drop in Coinbase Stock Price to Stock Up</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-court-orders-sec-to-respond-to-coinbases-rulemaking-petition-within-7-days-circle-gets-its-singapore-mpi-licence-cathie-woods-uses-drop-in-coinbase-stock-price-to-stock-up.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-court-orders-sec-to-respond-to-coinbases-rulemaking-petition-within-7-days-circle-gets-its-singapore-mpi-licence-cathie-woods-uses-drop-in-coinbase-stock-price-to-stock-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: US Court Orders SEC to Respond to Coinbase's Rulemaking Petition Within 7 Days, Circle Gets Its Singapore MPI Licence, Cathie Woods Uses Drop in Coinbase Stock Price to Stock Up&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Legal</category><category>USA</category><category>SEC</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Circle</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Philippines</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>INX</category><category>Bitget</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Aave</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-us-court-orders-sec-to-respond-to-coinbases-rulemaking-petition-within-7-days-circle-gets-its-singapore-mpi-licence-cathie-woods-uses-drop-in-coinbase-stock-price-to-stock-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116146/311967/coinbase-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="40220"/></item></channel></rss>
