<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:31:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gemini Strengthens its Presence in Asia With a New Office in India</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 23:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247407</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gemini_India.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Gemini_India.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gemini's new office in Gurgaon, India will be its second-largest engineering hub behind the one in the USA.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Gemini &#8211; announced plans to establish a new engineering hub in Gurgaon, India. This will be the company&#8217;s second Asian location, as previously it opened an office in Singapore.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The expansion outside the US coincides with the regulatory uncertainty in the States. The CEO of Coinbase &#8211; Brian Armstrong &#8211; recently opined that many American crypto firms could relocate if the watchdogs continue their scrutiny over the industry.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Setting Eyes on Asia</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pravjit Tiwana &#8211; the newly appointed CEO of Gemini Asia Pacific &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.gemini.com/blog/gemini-to-expand-global-engineering-and-operations-teams-with-new-india-office" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">explained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the company has picked India as its next destination because it has &#8220;deep respect and admiration&#8221; for its &#8220;tradition of engineering excellence.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He said the center in Gurgaon has already started looking for software engineers and technical product managers that could lead Gemini&#8217;s efforts on Asian soil. Tiwana added that the office will be the second-largest company hub behind the one in the United States. The exchange has also set foot in Singapore, the United Kingdom, and Ireland over the past few years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO outlined that the products and features built in the new location could be used by institutional and retail clients in more than 70 nations. The newly-formed team will aim to develop next-generation Web and mobile user experience and introduce feature sets for NFT and crypto marketplaces. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Although past experience in Web3 and crypto technologies is not a prerequisite, we are seeking builders who are inspired to learn quickly and work on cutting-edge technologies like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web3,&#8221; Tiwana added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latest foray seems like a breath of fresh air for Gemini, which took a serious beating during the bear market. It laid off a chunk of its employees in the summer of 2022 and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-lays-of-10-of-employees-due-to-crypto-industrys-bad-actors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">continued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the dismissal spree in January this year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also faced issues with the US SEC and the New York Department of Financial Services. The securities regulator </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a complaint against Gemini for allegedly selling securities to retail investors in America. For its part, the NYDFS </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/nydfs-probes-gemini-over-claims-concerning-the-earn-program-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the exchange of misleading Earn customers.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US Crypto Exodus on its Way?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lack of a comprehensive regulatory framework on digital asset operations in the States could be one reason why some American firms have started strengthening their global presence.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase&#8217;s CEO Brian Armstrong recently urged the domestic authorities to apply pertinent rules on the space to prevent the outflow of companies and talent:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This is the reason why we need clarity about legislation and regulation onshore because if the UK doesn&#8217;t have this, if the US doesn&#8217;t have this, these firms are going to be built in offshore havens.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">secured</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a regulatory license in Bermuda earlier this week and revealed plans to establish an offshore derivatives marketplace in the region.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-strengthens-its-presence-in-asia-with-a-new-office-in-india/" rel="nofollow">Gemini Strengthens its Presence in Asia With a New Office in India</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Californian Regulator Takes Action Against AI-Based Alleged Crypto Ponzi Schemes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/californian-regulator-takes-action-against-ai-based-alleged-crypto-ponzi-schemes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247425</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/California.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/California.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the DFPI, one of the companies may even be using an AI-generated CEO.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Californian Department of Financial Protection And Innovation (DFPI) issued cease and desist orders against five companies profiting from the hype around AI to attempt to dupe gullible investors.</p>
<h2>All Hype, Little Info</h2>
<p>According to the regulator, all five companies violate securities law by offering unregistered securities to the public.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Scammers like to deceive investors by using phony CEOs, sham algorithms, &amp; Ponzi schemes. Today, we&#8217;ve issued desist and refrain orders to five entities/individuals who violated CA securities laws. For more information: <a href="https://t.co/gj13z2OE4G" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/gj13z2OE4G</a><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/investing?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#investing</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/hyip?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#hyip</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Cryptonews?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Cryptonews</a> <a href="https://t.co/MXHPYwVIny" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/MXHPYwVIny</a></p>
<p>— CA Department of Financial Protection &amp; Innovation (@CaliforniaDFPI) <a href="https://twitter.com/CaliforniaDFPI/status/1648728681232347137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Furthermore, the firms involved are accused of lying to their customers by omission, misrepresenting, or even allegedly outright falsifying their financial model.</p>
<p>Predictably, all five companies offered high-yield investments, often promising minimum returns every single day. Not only is this a red flag – since guaranteed returns on investments are pretty much impossible to achieve – the promised minimum ROIs were larger than one could reasonably hope to achieve even by betting on blue-chip opportunities.</p>
<p>The twist? According to spokespeople for these companies, the promised results could be achieved with the help of AI.</p>
<h2>Cease and Desist Orders Issued</h2>
<p>According to DFPI Commissioner Clothilde Hewitt, the <a href="https://dfpi.ca.gov/2023/04/19/dfpi-launches-sweep-of-investment-fraud-claiming-ties-to-artificial-intelligence/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">targeted</a> entities are using the recent hype around AI LLMs to entice investors into making potentially grave errors.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today’s enforcement actions continue the DFPI’s crack down on investor fraud. Scammers are taking advantage of the recent buzz around artificial intelligence to entice investors into bogus schemes. We will continue our efforts to protect California consumers and investors by going after these unscrupulous actors.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The most brazen company to be targeted by the DFPI is Maxpread Technologies, which promised a minimum ROI of 0.6% per day. In fact, the firm appears to operate like a regular Ponzi scheme. It is also believed to be using an AI-generated <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bp84WyjxB4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">representation</a> of a fictional CEO, although this has not yet been confirmed.</p>
<p>Up next are Harvest Keeper, Visque Capital, and QuantFund, all offering between 1% and 4.81% guaranteed APRs. The companies in question all named AI as the reason that they could offer this guarantee, as opposed to other firms that promised high-flying possible APRs.</p>
<p>The last of the companies to be targeted by the regulators is Coinbot, which is essentially just another crypto-trading bot – but this time, powered by AI. Coinbot offered investors a minimum 1.5% daily ROI, purportedly earned from trades carried out by the bot. In reality, the company simply paid older investors with funds gathered from newer investors.</p>
<p>The current buzz around AI has gathered much interest from VCs, existing blue-chip corporations, and retail investors alike. Until the hype cools down, we will likely see many more attempts to cash in on the trend, similar to the shitcoin boom of 2017.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/californian-regulator-takes-action-against-ai-based-alleged-crypto-ponzi-schemes/" rel="nofollow">Californian Regulator Takes Action Against AI-Based Alleged Crypto Ponzi Schemes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Slams SEC, Says Gensler-Led Agency Caused Untold Harm to the US</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-slams-sec-says-gensler-led-agency-caused-untold-harm-to-the-us/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247443</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gary Gensler is facing a barrage of criticism over his agency’s crackdown on crypto platforms.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto community has left no stone unturned in lambasting the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and, more importantly, its Chief Gary Gensler. The latter&#8217;s actions were dissented by members of his own agency.</p>
<p>Gensler even received political pushback for his actions. But the SEC boss continued to defend the crackdown on digital assets markets, saying he had never seen an industry so routinely break securities laws.</p>
<h2>SEC Approach of Regulation by Enforcement</h2>
<p>As Coinbase prepares for a court battle with the SEC, its CEO Brian Armstrong had some strong words for the regulatory agency. The executive believes the SEC has caused &#8220;untold harm&#8221; to the country by opting to regulate the digital asset space by way of enforcement rather than through proactive collaboration between regulators and industry leaders.</p>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1649185136833904642" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweet,</a> Armstrong said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Spent the day in DC meeting with members of Congress. We need regulatory clarity in the U.S. for the centralized players in crypto for many reasons &#8211; consumer protection, national security, economic growth, etc. The SEC has caused untold harm to America with its policy of regulation by enforcement. We will fight to fix that.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The top executive at the biggest US crypto exchange also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raised</a> the prospect of relocating outside the country unless the regulatory climate changes after the SEC warned it of potential securities law violations.</p>
<p>Coinbase is not the only industry representative that has been critical of the financial regulator and its policies.</p>
<p>Web3 venture capital firm Paradigm recently <a href="https://policy.paradigm.xyz/writing/secs-path-to-registration-part-iii" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> that SEC&#8217;s attempt to &#8220;brute force crypto assets that may not even constitute ‘securities’ into an ill-fitting disclosure framework is bad policy.&#8221; It also claimed that the agency failed to provide crypto entrepreneurs with a viable path to compliance.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, United States Representative Warren Davidson also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rep-davidson-declares-war-on-sec-boss-gary-gensler-over-long-series-of-abuses/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> his intention to introduce legislation to oust Gensler from his position in a bid to &#8220;correct a long series of abuses.&#8221;</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Crypto War</h2>
<p>The SEC and Chairman Gensler&#8217;s crypto stance was heavily condemned by Republican members of Congress during Tuesday&#8217;s Congressional hearing. In the opening remark, the House Committee on Financial Services Chairman Patrick McHenry (R-NC) called the SEC&#8217;s approach to crypto exchanges &#8220;nonsensical&#8221; and lashed out at the lack of clarity.</p>
<p>Despite mounting criticisms, the agency remains unrelenting in its war on crypto. SEC Chair Gary Gensler <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">defended</a> the crackdown on cryptocurrency markets while reiterating his belief that the agency has sufficient authority to deal with the industry. He also maintained that regulatory clarity exists while adding that he had never seen an industry so routinely break securities laws.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-slams-sec-says-gensler-led-agency-caused-untold-harm-to-the-us/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO Slams SEC, Says Gensler-Led Agency Caused Untold Harm to the US</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global De-Dollarization and the Role of Bitcoin: Arthur Hayes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/global-de-dollarization-and-the-role-of-bitcoin-arthur-hayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247496</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/arthur_hayes.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/arthur_hayes.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BitMEX’s co-founder believes that as the dollar declines, more countries will consider using Bitcoin as a savings vehicle.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Could the US dollar lose its status as the global reserve currency? BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes doesn’t rule out the possibility and believes it’s a question worth considering for those looking to preserve their wealth. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The former exchange CEO published an essay on Thursday exploring the economics and role of the dollar worldwide, and how its shrinking role could affect global crypto adoption. </span></p>
<h2>US Dollar Dominance and Decline</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the essay titled “<a href="https://cryptohayes.medium.com/exit-liquidity-3052309e6bfa" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Exit Liquidity</a>,” Hayes explained that the dollar’s dominance worldwide is propped up by the United States’ open capital account and devotion to free trade. Each creates additional demand for the dollar, as the former allows Asian countries to purchase American assets with USD, and the latter lets Americans purchase cheap Asian products. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, being the issuer of the global reserve currency also means that the US Federal Reserve and US Treasury are responsible for keeping the global economy intact. In other words, when the global economy demands more USD, the US must provide it – even if it stokes inflationary pressure on the domestic economy. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Trillions of dollars of Asia’s wealth also depend on the good graces of American politicians,” wrote Hayes. “As Russia recently found out, rule of law and property rights are not ironclad.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the past few months, several global corridors of trade have signaled interest in moving away from settling trade in dollars. For example, Chinese and French energy companies </span><a href="https://www.rfi.fr/en/business/20230331-petrodollar-under-threat-as-france-s-totalenergies-sells-lng-to-china-in-yuan" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">agreed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> last month to settle a liquified natural gas deal in CNY rather than USD. Brazil and China have also </span><a href="https://en.mercopress.com/2023/04/03/china-and-brazil-reach-accord-to-trade-with-their-own-currencies-avoiding-the-us-dollar" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">struck a deal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to trade using their national currencies, rather than the dollar. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As Hayes explained, being so heavily dependent on the dollar means countries like China must import the United States’ monetary policy, and also be subject to its political risk. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While the United States has long been viewed as a reliable and politically stable nation, the co-founder claims this has changed in light of former President Donald Trump’s arrest earlier this month. As it happens, Trump </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-bail-release-trump-predicts-the-us-dollar-will-lose-global-dominance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">predicted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the US dollar would lose its global dominance shortly after his bail release. </span></p>
<h2>The Future of Global Currency</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hayes predicted that the future will feature multiple currency blocs, but no currency “hegemon” like the US dollar today. Imbalances between the blocs will be settled in a “neutral reserve currency” like gold and crypto, which are “not tied to any particular country”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“As Bitcoin continues to prove it is the hardest money ever created, I expect that more and more countries will at least start to consider whether it is a suitable savings vehicle alongside gold,” he continued.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hayes also connected the threat of the dollar’s weakening role on the global stage to the Biden Administration’s crackdown against crypto companies. “The West is making it harder to buy crypto and store it in a private wallet,” he added. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Since the collapse of FTX, many politicians from America’s political left have become extra-skeptical of crypto, with some </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/democrats-are-not-happy-with-house-committees-draft-stablecoin-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">questioning</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> whether the asset class even belongs in the country. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-de-dollarization-and-the-role-of-bitcoin-arthur-hayes/" rel="nofollow">Global De-Dollarization and the Role of Bitcoin: Arthur Hayes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX-Linked Project Serum Shilling Shitcoins on Twitter: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-linked-project-serum-shilling-shitcoins-on-twitter-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247468</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/serum_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/serum_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In a bizarre development, the Twitter account of an FTX-linked project  - which was once a prominent DeFi player on Solana - is now shilling shitcoins. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to on-chain sleuth Zachxbt, the official Twitter account of the Solana-based decentralized finance project Serum, which had over 200,000 followers, has been renamed &#8216;Luka.&#8217;</p>
<p>The original Serum account is speculated to have been sold to a different user since all the previous tweets have been deleted.</p>
<ul>
<li>Sharing a screenshot of the account, ZachXBT <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1649116171726393344?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that its PFP avatar was replaced with Milady NFT and was used for promoting &#8220;shitcoins.&#8221;</li>
<li>For the uninitiated, Serum was founded in August 2020 by a consortium that included the Solana Foundation as well as the now-collapsed Sam Bankman-Fried’s FTX and trading desk Alameda Research.</li>
<li>Serum received funding from Multicoin Capital alongside FTX.com and FTX US.</li>
<li>It was once heralded as a core decentralized exchange platform and liquidity provider for Solana&#8217;s DeFi ecosystem.</li>
<li>The events leading up to FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy filing forced Solana DeFi projects like Raydium and Jupiter to cut off ties with Serum.</li>
<li>Several exchanges, such as Upbit and Binance, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-removes-trading-pairs-for-ftx-linked-serum-token/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">delisted</a> Serum from their platforms. Soon after, the project&#8217;s native token &#8211; SRM &#8211; also lost over 98% of its value since its all-time high in September last year. It was assumed that the project ended.</li>
<li>Subsequently, a community-driven fork of Serum&#8217;s V3 program was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/serum-srm-backs-community-hard-fork-plans-after-ftx-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> and rebranded as &#8216;OpenBook,&#8217; which has over 5k followers on its Twitter account.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-linked-project-serum-shilling-shitcoins-on-twitter-report/" rel="nofollow">FTX-Linked Project Serum Shilling Shitcoins on Twitter: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC, ETH Retrace, Tesla Sold No Bitcoin in Q1, New Memecoin (PEPE) Hype Soars: This Week&#8217;s Market Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-retrace-tesla-sold-no-bitcoin-in-q1-new-memecoin-pepe-hype-soars-this-weeks-market-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247467</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_eth_bear_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_eth_bear_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After a few weeks of consecutive gains, the crypto market finally began to cool off, with BTC and ETH sliding hard.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last week was significantly more eventful within and outside the cryptocurrency industry, with the CPI numbers showing declining inflation rates in the States, while Ethereum underwent its most notable upgrade since the Merge.</p>
<p>Consequently, the entire market reacted positively, with BTC spiking to $31,000 to chart a 10-month peak, while ETH skyrocketed to above $2,100 and painted its highest price point in 11 months. This week began with less volatility, but the landscape changed for the worse a few days ago.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s peak came exactly a week ago. The following few days were silent before the cryptocurrency headed south on Monday morning. Despite recovering the losses almost immediately, the asset began dropping hard once again mid-week. This time, the bears took it from over $30,000 to under $29,000. The past 24 hours were not kind either, and BTC slumped to under $28,000 for the first time in 12 days.</p>
<p>ETH was among the top performers after the Shapella upgrade, but it quickly lost momentum amid <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-price-retreats-as-nearly-1b-in-kraken-staked-ethereum-is-withdrawn/" data-wpel-link="internal">large-scale withdrawals and deposits. </a>The asset lost over $200 in the past several days, dropping to and below $1,900.</p>
<p>Most of the alternative coins are in similar, if not worse, shape on a weekly scale. The most substantial losses from the top 100 alts come from Stacks (-20%), Immutable (-17.5%), Lido DAO (-17%), Algorand (-16%), Conflux (-15%), Kava (-15%), and many others.</p>
<p>OKB is among the few altcoins that have managed to defy the overall market sentiment by gaining over 13% in the same timeframe. As a result, the asset trades well above $50. Overall, though, the total crypto market cap has declined by roughly $100 billion on CoinGecko.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,238B | 24H Vol: $59B | BTC Dominance: 44.1%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $28,215 (-7.2%) | ETH: $1,916 (-5%) | BNB: $327 (+0.9%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-162363" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1.jpg" alt="" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Better Not Miss</h2>
<p><strong>How Someone Turned $27 into $1 Million in Days With PEPE, But There’s a Catch</strong>. Cryptocurrency hype manias are a relatively frequent development amid bull markets, but this one, involving a new memecoin called PEPE, came out of nowhere for most. However, one investor was savvy enough to make a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-someone-turned-27-into-1-million-in-days-with-pepe-but-theres-a-catch/" data-wpel-link="internal">mind-blowing profit</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Tesla Didn’t Sell BTC During Q1 of 2023</strong>. The most well-known EV maker made the news in 2021 when it purchased over $1 billion worth of bitcoin. Since then, however, the Elon Musk-spearheaded company has disposed of certain portions of its BTC holdings. Yet, Tesla <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tesla-didnt-sell-btc-during-q1-of-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">refrained</a> from selling any more during Q1 of 2023.</p>
<p><strong>Gary Gensler: The SEC Will Not Change its Attitude Toward Crypto Exchanges</strong>. The SEC Chair has become among the most hated people from the crypto community due to his policies on regulating the industry. Despite the massive backlash, some of it coming from SEC personnel and US politicians, Gensler <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gary-gensler-the-sec-will-not-change-its-attitude-toward-crypto-exchanges/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> his agency has no plans to change its behavior.</p>
<p><strong>Coinbase is About to Go to Court With the SEC: Brian Armstrong</strong>. Some of the aforementioned backlash came from the largest US-based crypto exchange &#8211; Coinbase &#8211; and its CEO, in particular. Brian Armstrong <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-about-to-go-to-court-with-the-sec-brian-armstrong/" data-wpel-link="internal">warned</a> the SEC that both parties could go to court if the latter fails to reach clarity on its regulatory stance.</p>
<p><strong>NBA Legend Shaquille O’Neal Served in FTX Class Action</strong>. The FTX drama doesn&#8217;t seem to stop, and it keeps involving more and more celebrities. The latest to be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-legend-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-class-action/" data-wpel-link="internal">served</a> in a class action lawsuit was the NBA legend &#8211; Shaquille O&#8217;Neal &#8211; who did manage to avoid the authorities on numerous occasions before that.</p>
<p><strong>Do Kwon Transferred $7 Million to a Law Firm Shortly Before the Terra Crash (Report)</strong>. The OG drama in 2022 started with the Terra collapse, and there&#8217;s more development on that front as well. One of the latest <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-transferred-7-million-to-a-law-firm-shortly-before-the-terra-crash-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reports</a> on the matter claimed that Do Kwon had transferred $7 million to a law firm shortly ahead of the crash</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-retrace-tesla-sold-no-bitcoin-in-q1-new-memecoin-pepe-hype-soars-this-weeks-market-recap/" rel="nofollow">BTC, ETH Retrace, Tesla Sold No Bitcoin in Q1, New Memecoin (PEPE) Hype Soars: This Week&#8217;s Market Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich Dad, Poor Dad Author Explains Why He Loves Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-he-loves-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 12:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247445</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kiyosaki disclosed that he loves Bitcoin because it is the people’s money and is neither controlled by the Fed nor the government.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">Robert Kiyosaki, an accomplished American investor, businessman, motivational speaker, and author of the bestselling book “Rich Dad, Poor Dad,” recently expressed his admiration for Bitcoin (BTC) and lauded its ability to withstand the test of time.</p>
<p class="p1">According to Kiyosaki, the success of Bitcoin can be attributed to its decentralized nature, as it is driven by the people rather than the Federal Reserve Board or the US government for support.</p>
<h2 class="p1">Here’s Why Kiyosaki Loves Bitcoin</h2>
<p class="p1">In a Friday <span class="s1">tweet</span>, Kiyosaki said he watched BTC climb to $20,000 and then lost almost all of its value when it dropped below $4,000 several years ago. The author noted that he purchased more of the asset when it climbed to $6,000.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">WHY I <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2764.png" alt="❤" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />BITCOIN: Years ago I watched BC climb to $20k then drop to 0. I thought BC finished. Slowly watched BC climb to $6 k &amp; I bought lots. WHY? Because people support BC not FED or Gov. BC did not need FED or Gov bailout because BC people’s money. BC to $100k. Long live BC.</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1649233828517650432?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="p1">As a strong advocate for financial education, Kiyosaki emphasized the importance of understanding the potential of Bitcoin and its role in the future of finance.</p>
<p class="p1">The investor sees BTC, gold, and silver through the same lens and keeps encouraging people to acquire more in preparation for an impending market crash on the US dollar. As <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-kiyosaki-wants-to-buy-more-bitcoin-gold-and-silver/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">reported</span></a>, Kiyosaki intends to increase his exposure to the digital asset and precious metals because the Fed, US Treasury, and President Joe Bideon are “liars.”</p>
<h2 class="p1">Kiyosaki Believes BTC Will Get to $100K</h2>
<p class="p1">It is noteworthy that Kiyosaki believes Bitcoin is the only worthwhile investment within the cryptocurrency space, as it is acknowledged as a commodity, unlike most alternative coins (altcoins) considered as securities. He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-kiyosaki-wants-to-buy-more-bitcoin-gold-and-silver/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">insists</span></a> that once United States regulators such as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) classify them as securities, the watchdogs will go hard on them.</p>
<p class="p1">Meanwhile, the author sees BTC trading at $100,000 soon. He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-rich-dad-poor-dad-author-believes-btc-will-reach-500k-in-3-years/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">predicted</span></a> in February that by 2025, the leading cryptocurrency would be worth $500,000 while gold and silver would trade at $5,000 and $500, respectively.</p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of Kitco</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-he-loves-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Rich Dad, Poor Dad Author Explains Why He Loves Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Post-Merge: Over 100K Coins Eliminated From ETH&#8217;s Supply</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-post-merge-over-100k-coins-eliminated-from-eths-supply/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247408</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Ethereum_Burn.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Ethereum_Burn.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The supply of ETH would have surged by 3.53% each year if the Merge never happened. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Merge represented the Ethereum network&#8217;s transition from proof-of-work to proof-of-stake. 218 days later, more than 103,092 ETH has been eliminated from the supply of the world&#8217;s largest altcoin.</p>
<p>At current prices, this amounts to a little over $197 million. Deflation on the network is on the rise as the supply declined by 0.146% per year.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the latest <a href="https://ultrasound.money/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from the Ethereum monitoring site &#8216;ultrasound.money,&#8217; the current supply of ether stands at nearly 120,416,113 million coins.</li>
<li>The currency burn rate over the last 30 days was found to be at 1,125k ETH and a supply growth of -0.37%.</li>
<li>At this pace, the Ethereum supply is expected to reach 118.1 million by the year 2025.</li>
<li>Issuance rewards for stakers, on the other hand, will be at 3.9% per year, while the burn rate for the non-stakers will stand at 1.8% per year.</li>
<li>Contrastingly, if Ethereum had not undergone the Merge and instead continued to rely on miners to secure the network, the supply of the token would have increased by more than 2.5 million ETH, which translates to an astonishing $4.9 billion in the current market value.</li>
<li>ETH&#8217;s supply, for one, would have increased by 3.53% every year.</li>
<li>While the Merge was indeed responsible for the reduction in ETH supply by a considerable amount, the aspect of burning ether can be attributed to the Ethereum Improvement Proposal 1559, which was implemented via the London upgrade in August 2021. Its main purpose is to slash inflation on the Ethereum network and exert deflationary pressure on the token&#8217;s supply.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, the Shapella upgrade on April 12 enabled stakers to unlock their staked Ether. The exodus of tokens following the event <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-staking-withdrawals-slow-following-initial-1m-eth-exodus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">slowed</a> down.</li>
<li>Within a week, the amount of staked ether <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thats-a-first-after-shanghai-ether-staked-volume-exceeds-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">trumped</a> the number of ETH being withdrawn for the very first time.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-post-merge-over-100k-coins-eliminated-from-eths-supply/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Post-Merge: Over 100K Coins Eliminated From ETH&#8217;s Supply</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pink Moon Studios Launches its Free-to-Play Mode for KMON Genesis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pink-moon-studios-launches-its-free-to-play-mode-for-kmon-genesis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247434</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/KMON.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/KMON.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, April 20th, 2023] Rebranding from Kryptomon to KMON Genesis, the move will significantly lower the barriers of entry to one of the world&#8217;s most popular web3 games. Today, Pink Moon Studios, a leading web3 gaming company, announced the launch of a free-to-play mode for its renowned strategy game, KMON Genesis [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, April 20th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Rebranding from Kryptomon to KMON Genesis, the move will significantly lower the barriers of entry to one of the world&#8217;s most popular web3 games.</p>
<p>Today, Pink Moon Studios, a leading web3 gaming company, announced the launch of a free-to-play mode for its renowned strategy game, KMON Genesis (formerly Kryptomon). KMON Genesis allows players to breed, collect, and trade unique creatures as they traverse the enthralling KMON universe. As one of the first web3 games in the world, KMON Genesis gives players a seamless gaming experience without the need to purchase NFTs in advance, further lowering barriers to entry to a broader range of players.</p>
<p>Set in the Kryptomon universe, community members play as “Trainers,” taking care of their own NFT pets, which have a unique and mutable genetic code made up of 38 randomized parameters that determine their physical and behavioral characteristics. Kryptomons can learn, fall sick, get hungry, and protect their trainers when out on an adventure in the physical world. In turn, trainers will have to care for, feed, and train their Kryptomon partners in order to grow and prepare for the battles ahead. To incentivize gameplay, Pink Moon Studios shares revenue from KMON Genesis with its players by distributing weekly monetary rewards when they complete in-game challenges, which average $50 in tokens.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our core mission has always been to make the enthralling KMON Genesis universe accessible to everyone.” stated Umberto Canessa Cerchi, Founder &amp; CEO of Pink Moon Studios, “The introduction of the free-to-play mode is a game-changer, inviting players from all backgrounds to experience the innovative and exciting world we&#8217;ve developed, without any financial barriers or web3-related technological hurdles.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In a recent partnership with Playdex, Pink Moon Studios also introduced exclusive rental features for KMON on-chain assets, further enhancing the gaming experience and offering players even more flexibility and opportunities for growth within the game. To commemorate the launch of the free-to-play mode, Pink Moon Studios will host a community event showcasing its upcoming mobile MMORPG, World of Kogaea, which is currently under development. Players can obtain a unique digital collectible throughout the event by completing specified quests. Space for the special event is limited, and interested players are encouraged to register early to secure their spots. Further information about the event will be available on the Pink Moon Studios&#8217; official website in the near future.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="KMON - World of Kogaea Preview" width="500" height="281" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QJyI9XpJXmQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div></p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are eager to offer players a sneak peek into the mesmerizing digital realm of World of Kogaea,” said Brian Bento, Chief Product Officer and SVP of Game Development at Pink Moon Studios, shared his enthusiasm, stating, “Our dedicated team has poured countless hours into crafting a visually spectacular and engaging experience that players will find truly captivating.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>About Pink Moon Studios</h2>
<p>Founded in 2021, Pink Moon Studios is revolutionizing web3 gaming by delivering immersive, captivating, and groundbreaking gaming experiences that defy traditional norms. With extensive expertise in web3, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and augmented reality (AR) technology, Pink Moon Studios is uniquely positioned to create gaming solutions that bridge the gap between the digital and physical worlds.</p>
<p>For additional details about KMON Genesis, the revolutionary free-to-play mode, and the latest developments from Pink Moon Studios, please visit <a href="https://pink-moon.studio/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://pink-moon.studio/</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pink-moon-studios-launches-its-free-to-play-mode-for-kmon-genesis/" rel="nofollow">Pink Moon Studios Launches its Free-to-Play Mode for KMON Genesis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Markets Lost $90B in 2 Days as BTC Slips Below $28K: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-90b-in-2-days-as-btc-slips-below-28k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 08:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247415</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dogecoin and ICP are among the poorest performers on a daily scale, with losses exceeding 8%.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price drops continued in the past 24 hours, with the asset falling below $28,000 for the first time since April 9.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also deep in the red. The total market cap has lost almost $90 billion in the past two days.</p>
<h2>BTC Slides Under $28K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin was trading <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/radix-xrd-explodes-30-daily-as-bitcoin-fights-for-30k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">sideways</a> during the weekend, and it wasn&#8217;t until Tuesday that it finally made a move, dropping by a grand to $29,100. However, the bulls quickly intercepted the move and pushed the asset north, which helped it reclaim the coveted $30,000 line.</p>
<p>The landscape started to change shortly after, though, as BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-struggles-at-29k-but-pepe-hype-carries-on-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">slumped</a> by a grand in minutes. That was just the start, though, as the bears pushed it further south in the past 24 hours. This resulted in breaking below $28,000 for the first time in almost two weeks.</p>
<p>Despite recovering a few hundred dollars since then, BTC still struggles to maintain $28,000. It&#8217;s roughly 3% down on the day and over 8% on a weekly scale.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization, which tapped $600 billion just days ago, now struggles at way beneath $550 billion. Its dominance over the altcoins, though, has recovered some ground, but it&#8217;s still under 46%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247418" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247418" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247418" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSD-18-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247418" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Alts Turn Red</h2>
<p>Similar to bitcoin, most alternative coins have not enjoyed the past few days. Ethereum went on to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-tap-near-yearly-highs-as-market-cap-eyes-1-3t-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">chart</a> an 11-month high after the Shapella update last week but has since lost over $200. As a result, the second-largest cryptocurrency currently struggles to remain above $1,900.</p>
<p>Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, Solana, Polkadot, Litecoin, Shiba Inu, and Avalanche are also deep in the red, with losses of up to 5% in a day. Dogecoin has dumped the most (-8.5%), perhaps due to the asset&#8217;s relationship with Elon Musk. As it became known yesterday, Starship&#8217;s latest rocket exploded shortly after its launch.</p>
<p>With ICP, NEAR, GRT, and many other mid- and lower-cap alts charting substantial losses, the total crypto market cap has dumped beneath $1.2 trillion. This means that the metric has lost roughly $90 billion in the past two days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247420" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247420" style="width: 1860px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247420" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1860" height="735" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14.jpg 1860w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14-300x119.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14-1024x405.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14-768x303.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14-1536x607.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-14-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1860px) 100vw, 1860px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247420" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-90b-in-2-days-as-btc-slips-below-28k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Markets Lost $90B in 2 Days as BTC Slips Below $28K: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
