<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>US Consumer Protection Agency Issues Warning on Payment Apps Following Collapses of Crypto Firms, Banks</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-consumer-protection-agency-issues-warning-payment-apps-following-collapses-of-crypto-firms-banks.htm</link><description>The US Consumer Financial Protection Bureau issued a warning on Thursday for people using person-to-person services to store funds, reminding them that they are not federally insured, in the wake of FTX and multiple bank collapses.  &lt;br /&gt;
Transaction volumes on payment apps have “substantially increased,” the CFPB said in the report.  &lt;br /&gt;
The collapse of crypto exchange FTX and crypto lender Voyager Digital led to consumers losing hundreds of millions of dollars, the CFPB said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-consumer-protection-agency-issues-warning-payment-apps-following-collapses-of-crypto-firms-banks.htm"&gt;Read More: US Consumer Protection Agency Issues Warning on Payment Apps Following Collapses of Crypto Firms, Banks&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Consumer</category><category>Consumer rights</category><category>Payment Apps</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-consumer-protection-agency-issues-warning-payment-apps-following-collapses-of-crypto-firms-banks.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115672/278845/adobestock-333531053-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="572533"/></item><item><title>More Colombians Taking to Crypto, Claims Exchange – Next LATAM Nation to Adopt?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-colombians-taking-crypto-claims-exchange-next-latam-nation-adopt.htm</link><description>Colombians are increasingly taking crypto, one of Latin America’s biggest crypto exchanges has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Criptonoticias, the Bitso trading platform says it has increased the number of its individual retail clients “by 10 times” since this time last year. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitso opened its offices in Colombia in the first half of 2022. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm was founded in Mexico in 2014, but has since expanded to a number of Latin American states....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/more-colombians-taking-crypto-claims-exchange-next-latam-nation-adopt.htm"&gt;Read More: More Colombians Taking to Crypto, Claims Exchange – Next LATAM Nation to Adopt?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Colombia</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-colombians-taking-crypto-claims-exchange-next-latam-nation-adopt.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115571/278601/adobestock-460500382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="342551"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 1 June – IOTA, Litecoin, Stellar</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-1-june-iota-litecoin-stellar.htm</link><description>Despite recent legislative action in the United States to avert a government debt default, Bitcoin and other leading cryptocurrencies are experiencing price declines. This drop coincides with the U.S. House of Representatives voting to suspend the national debt ceiling. The bill passed 314 to 117, garnering bipartisan support. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-1-june-iota-litecoin-stellar.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 1 June – IOTA, Litecoin, Stellar&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Best Cryptocurrency To Buy</category><category>Ltc Price</category><category>Ecoterra Presale</category><category>Deelance Presale</category><category>Wall Street Memes Presale</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-1-june-iota-litecoin-stellar.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115673/278850/best-crypto-1-june.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336529"/></item><item><title>How the Upcoming US Jobs Report Might Impact the Bitcoin (BTC) Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-upcoming-us-jobs-report-might-impact-bitcoin-btc-price.htm</link><description>US labor market data for May is due on Friday the 2nd of June. &lt;br /&gt;
The data, which is closely scrutinized by policymakers at the US Federal Reserve, could trigger volatility in the Bitcoin market, depending on how and if it impacts expectations for further interest rate hikes from the US central bank. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the media of a series of polls of economists, the labor market is seen adding 193,000 jobs in May, slightly slower than the 253,000 pace at which jobs were added in April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/how-upcoming-us-jobs-report-might-impact-bitcoin-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: How the Upcoming US Jobs Report Might Impact the Bitcoin (BTC) Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Fed</category><category>US jobs report</category><category>NFP</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-upcoming-us-jobs-report-might-impact-bitcoin-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115674/278849/btc-3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="153373"/></item><item><title>Qatar Needs To Make Some ‘Major Improvements’: Money Laundering Watchdog Says</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/qatar-needs-make-some-major-improvements-money-laundering-watchdog-says.htm</link><description>Qatar needs to make some “major improvements,” on how it responds to terrorist financing, according to a global money laundering and terrorist financing watchdog. &lt;br /&gt;
The Financial Action Task Force accused Qatar of not having enough controls and needs to better understand “more complex forms of money laundering and terrorist financing,” according to a report released by the watchdog on Wednesday.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/qatar-needs-make-some-major-improvements-money-laundering-watchdog-says.htm"&gt;Read More: Qatar Needs To Make Some ‘Major Improvements’: Money Laundering Watchdog Says&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Qatar</category><category>FATF</category><category>Money Laundering</category><category>Terrorist Financing</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/qatar-needs-make-some-major-improvements-money-laundering-watchdog-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115670/278844/adobestock-228133717.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="637933"/></item><item><title>Binance Targets Privacy Coins for Delisting in Four European Countries – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-targets-privacy-coins-for-delisting-four-european-countries-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, is planning to delist a number of privacy coins for users in Spain, France, Italy and Poland. &lt;br /&gt;
The coins that will be delisted are all privacy-focused coins that are designed to make it difficult for third-parties to trace transactions and get information about wallet balances....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-targets-privacy-coins-for-delisting-four-european-countries-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Targets Privacy Coins for Delisting in Four European Countries – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-targets-privacy-coins-for-delisting-four-european-countries-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115621/278707/binance.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="80553"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as $15 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-15-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>In the dynamic world of cryptocurrency, the recent surge in Bitcoin's trading volume, which reached a staggering $15 billion, has captured the attention of market observers.  &lt;br /&gt;
This substantial increase in trading activity raises questions about the involvement of whales, the influential players with significant holdings of Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-15-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as $15 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-15-billion-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115623/278732/1-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480115"/></item><item><title>UAE's Central Bank Introduces New Anti-Money Laundering Guidance for Crypto Businesses – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uaes-central-bank-introduces-new-anti-money-laundering-guidance-for-crypto-businesses-heres-the-latest.htm</link><description>The UAE’s Central Bank just introduced new anti-money laundering (AML) and counter-terrorism financing guidelines for crypto businesses and financial institutions handling digital assets, according to an announcement on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
The new guidance applies to all licensed financial institutions (LFIs), which include banks, exchange houses, finance companies, payment service providers, brokers and insurance companies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uaes-central-bank-introduces-new-anti-money-laundering-guidance-for-crypto-businesses-heres-the-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: UAE's Central Bank Introduces New Anti-Money Laundering Guidance for Crypto Businesses – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>UAE</category><category>Crypto Hub</category><category>New Guidelines</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uaes-central-bank-introduces-new-anti-money-laundering-guidance-for-crypto-businesses-heres-the-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115662/278837/uae-crypto.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3339474"/></item><item><title>T-Mobile Owner Turns to Blockchain, Becomes Polygon Validator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/t-mobile-owner-turns-to-blockchain-becomes-polygon-validator.htm</link><description>Deutsche Telekom, a leading global integrated telecommunications firm, has announced support for Polygon blockchain infrastructure. &lt;br /&gt;
As per a media release, Deutsche Telekom has become a Polygon validator, extending its services to the blockchain sector.  &lt;br /&gt;
Also, the announcement revealed the firm's subsidiary Deutsche Telekom MMS would provide staking and validation services on Polygon's proof-of-stake network and Supernets solutions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/t-mobile-owner-turns-to-blockchain-becomes-polygon-validator.htm"&gt;Read More: T-Mobile Owner Turns to Blockchain, Becomes Polygon Validator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/t-mobile-owner-turns-to-blockchain-becomes-polygon-validator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115660/278836/blockchain-ga25d66a71-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="446337"/></item><item><title>Tribe Capital Launches $100 Million Crypto Fund Targeting Layer 1, 2, and DeFi Projects – Bull Market Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tribe-capital-launches-100-million-crypto-fund-targeting-layer-1-2-defi-projects-bull-market-back.htm</link><description>Venture capital firm, Tribe Capital, has launched a new crypto fund to raise $100 million. &lt;br /&gt;
The tribe plans to channel the funds into early-stage layer 1 and 2 ecosystems and DeFi projects. &lt;br /&gt;
The San Francisco-based company with $1.6 billion in assets under management will invest $500,000-$3 million in these projects to bring real-world assets on-chain.  &lt;br /&gt;
This development comes amid a drastic plunge in venture capital investment value in the crypto and blockchain ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tribe-capital-launches-100-million-crypto-fund-targeting-layer-1-2-defi-projects-bull-market-back.htm"&gt;Read More: Tribe Capital Launches $100 Million Crypto Fund Targeting Layer 1, 2, and DeFi Projects – Bull Market Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tribe-capital-launches-100-million-crypto-fund-targeting-layer-1-2-defi-projects-bull-market-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115658/278829/pexels-burst-545064.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="283121"/></item><item><title>Winklevoss-Owned Gemini Makes a Move in the UAE for Crypto License</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-owned-gemini-makes-a-move-in-the-uae-for-crypto-license.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Gemini, owned by the Winklevoss twins, is headed to the United Arab Emirates. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm announced on Wednesday that it would begin acquiring a crypto license to serve customers in the UAE. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-owned-gemini-makes-a-move-in-the-uae-for-crypto-license.htm"&gt;Read More: Winklevoss-Owned Gemini Makes a Move in the UAE for Crypto License&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/winklevoss-owned-gemini-makes-a-move-in-the-uae-for-crypto-license.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115659/278828/adobestock-592584245-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="108548"/></item><item><title>Cybersecurity Firm dWallet Labs Discovers and Fixes $500 Million Vulnerability in Tron Network</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cybersecurity-firm-dwallet-labs-discovers-fixes-500-million-vulnerability-tron-network.htm</link><description>dWallet Labs, a prominent cybersecurity research team, has uncovered a critical zero-day vulnerability within the multisignature (multisig) mechanism of the Tron (TRX) network, the firm revealed in a blog post this week. &lt;br /&gt;
This vulnerability discovered allows any signer, regardless of their weight, to bypass the multisig security of TRON, impacting over $500 million worth of digital assets held in TRON multisig accounts, dWallet Labs claimed in the post which was also shared via Twitter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cybersecurity-firm-dwallet-labs-discovers-fixes-500-million-vulnerability-tron-network.htm"&gt;Read More: Cybersecurity Firm dWallet Labs Discovers and Fixes $500 Million Vulnerability in Tron Network&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Tron</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cybersecurity-firm-dwallet-labs-discovers-fixes-500-million-vulnerability-tron-network.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115616/278700/tron-coin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="119500"/></item><item><title>Iconic H.R. Giger 'Alien' Sculpture to be Fractionalized as NFTs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/iconic-hr-giger-alien-sculpture-fractionalized-as-nfts.htm</link><description>Art collectors and fans of the cult science fiction film Alien will have a chance to purchase a fractionalized digital artwork of a rare sculpture by the late Swiss artist H.R. Giger.  &lt;br /&gt;
Digital art platform Particle, which uses blockchain technology to offer fractionalized ownership of culturally significant artworks, will conduct the sale, according to the company's website.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/iconic-hr-giger-alien-sculpture-fractionalized-as-nfts.htm"&gt;Read More: Iconic H.R. Giger 'Alien' Sculpture to be Fractionalized as NFTs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Tokenization</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/iconic-hr-giger-alien-sculpture-fractionalized-as-nfts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115654/278781/1993b8c786938c46099b25601.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="389597"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Starts Forming Bullish Chart Pattern – Here's the Next LUNC Target</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-heres-next-lunc-target.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC), the cryptocurrency which powers the original Terra blockchain that experienced catastrophe after its associated algorithmic “stablecoin” UST lost its 1:1 per to the US dollar last May, was last trading roughly flat on Thursday in the $0.000085 area. &lt;br /&gt;
But LUNC has formed a potentially bullish chart pattern that LUNC holders are praying could trigger a much-needed recovery for the cryptocurrency’s price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-heres-next-lunc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Starts Forming Bullish Chart Pattern – Here's the Next LUNC Target&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-starts-forming-bullish-chart-pattern-heres-next-lunc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115656/278800/lunc-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="577342"/></item><item><title>Gate.io Clamps Down on Rumors Following Twitter Upheaval Over Multichain</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-clamps-down-rumors-following-twitter-upheaval-over-multichain.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Gate.io disputed rumors of insolvency after tweets were sent alleging a connection between it and Multichain. &lt;br /&gt;
“We would like to clarify that our operations are running healthily, withdrawals are functioning properly, and there are no issues with our operations or withdrawals as rumored,” Gateo.io said in a statement on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-clamps-down-rumors-following-twitter-upheaval-over-multichain.htm"&gt;Read More: Gate.io Clamps Down on Rumors Following Twitter Upheaval Over Multichain&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gate.io</category><category>Multi-Chain</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/gateio-clamps-down-rumors-following-twitter-upheaval-over-multichain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115650/278768/adobestock-195865436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="313172"/></item><item><title>Mooky (MOOK) is a New Community-Driven Charity &amp; Governance Token Available to Buy on Presale Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mooky-mook-a-community-driven-charity-governance-token-to-buy-on-presale-now.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights from crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com. &lt;br /&gt;
Mooky ($MOOK) is a new cryptocurrency project that aims to leverage blockchain technology for the benefit of the environment. Along with offering utility through the $MOOK token, Mooky’s main goal is to contribute to green charities worldwide. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mooky-mook-a-community-driven-charity-governance-token-to-buy-on-presale-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Mooky (MOOK) is a New Community-Driven Charity &amp; Governance Token Available to Buy on Presale Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mooky-mook-a-community-driven-charity-governance-token-to-buy-on-presale-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115596/278648/mooky-img.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="693768"/></item><item><title>Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Platform DeeLance Could Be the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-deelance-could-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</link><description>Groundbreaking web3 freelancing and remote work metaverse platform DeeLance, which is essentially a decentralized version of Fiverr and Upwork, could be the next cryptocurrency to explode. &lt;br /&gt;
That’s because DeeLance is building an innovative, crypto and NFT-powered metaverse that unites freelancers and employers and promises to transform remote working forever, as well as the $761 billion-dollar recruitment sector....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-deelance-could-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Decentralized Fiverr and Upwork Platform DeeLance Could Be the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Web3</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/decentralized-fiverr-upwork-platform-deelance-could-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115639/278756/dlance-web.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="469857"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: EU Has Option to Deem All Crypto as Securities by Default, Georgia to Launch Mandatory Supervision of VASPs, Bitget is the 'First Exchange' to Support an EVM-Compatible Address</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-eu-has-option-to-deem-all-crypto-as-securities-by-default-georgia-to-launch-mandatory-supervision-of-vasps-bitget-is-the-first-exchange-to-support-an-evm-compatible-address.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-eu-has-option-to-deem-all-crypto-as-securities-by-default-georgia-to-launch-mandatory-supervision-of-vasps-bitget-is-the-first-exchange-to-support-an-evm-compatible-address.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: EU Has Option to Deem All Crypto as Securities by Default, Georgia to Launch Mandatory Supervision of VASPs, Bitget is the 'First Exchange' to Support an EVM-Compatible Address&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Eu. European Union</category><category>European Parliament</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Securities</category><category>Georgia</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Investment</category><category>Bitget</category><category>EVM</category><category>Gemini</category><category>UAE</category><category>Crypto.com</category><category>Singapore</category><category>CleanSpark</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-eu-has-option-to-deem-all-crypto-as-securities-by-default-georgia-to-launch-mandatory-supervision-of-vasps-bitget-is-the-first-exchange-to-support-an-evm-compatible-address.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115599/278733/adobestock-artjazz-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="156699"/></item><item><title>Leading Play-to-Earn Gaming Ecosystem Tamadoge Submits App to iOS and Android Stores, Leading the Charge to Onboard Next Wave of Web3 Users</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-play-earn-gaming-ecosystem-tamadoge-submits-app-to-ios-and-android-stores-leading-the-charge-to-onboard-next-wave-of-web3-users.htm</link><description>Wednesday, Wednesday 31st May - Tamadoge, one of the web3 industry’s leading and most innovative play-to-earn (P2E) gaming ecosystems, just submitted their Tama Arcade app to the iOS and Android stores for approval. &lt;br /&gt;
This is huge news for Tamadoge, as a mobile application will bring a wave of new users to the up-and-coming ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-play-earn-gaming-ecosystem-tamadoge-submits-app-to-ios-and-android-stores-leading-the-charge-to-onboard-next-wave-of-web3-users.htm"&gt;Read More: Leading Play-to-Earn Gaming Ecosystem Tamadoge Submits App to iOS and Android Stores, Leading the Charge to Onboard Next Wave of Web3 Users&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-play-earn-gaming-ecosystem-tamadoge-submits-app-to-ios-and-android-stores-leading-the-charge-to-onboard-next-wave-of-web3-users.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115635/278742/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="263280"/></item><item><title>Reddit Co-Founder Alexis Ohanian Firmly Stands by Play-to-Earn Gaming Model</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/reddit-co-founder-alexis-ohanian-firmly-stands-by-play-earn-gaming-model.htm</link><description>Reddit co-founder Alexis Ohanian firmly believes that play-to-earn is the future of gaming despite the decline in popularity of some major P2E games. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent Twitter thread, Ohanian, who is the founder and current General Partner of Web3-focused venture capital firm Seven Seven Six, said play-to-earn "will become standard for video games in the future." &lt;br /&gt;
“Within the next five years, the majority of gamers won't play games unless they are being properly valued for that time."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/reddit-co-founder-alexis-ohanian-firmly-stands-by-play-earn-gaming-model.htm"&gt;Read More: Reddit Co-Founder Alexis Ohanian Firmly Stands by Play-to-Earn Gaming Model&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>reddit</category><category>Alexis Ohanian</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/reddit-co-founder-alexis-ohanian-firmly-stands-by-play-earn-gaming-model.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115610/278676/forbes-media-library-orig.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="95508"/></item></channel></rss>
