<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Binance Abruptly Terminates Argentine Soccer Association Partnership Citing Contract Breach</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-abruptly-terminates-argentine-soccer-association-partnership-citing-contract-breach.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Binance’s Argentina arm has decided to abruptly call-off its partnership with the Argentine Football Association (AFA), accusing the latter over lack of compliance. &lt;br /&gt;
In January 2022, Binance entered into a five-year contract with AFA, the governing body of football in Argentina, becoming the main sponsor for Argentina's powerhouse national soccer team and naming sponsor of its national soccer league....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-abruptly-terminates-argentine-soccer-association-partnership-citing-contract-breach.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Abruptly Terminates Argentine Soccer Association Partnership Citing Contract Breach&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-abruptly-terminates-argentine-soccer-association-partnership-citing-contract-breach.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119920/318470/soccer-488700-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="345303"/></item><item><title>Shenzhen, China: 36m Digital Yuan Wallets Opened So Far – CBDC Pilot Gathers Pace</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shenzhen-china-36m-digital-yuan-wallets-opened-so-far-cbdc-pilot-gathers-pace.htm</link><description>The Chinese city of Shenzhen says its residents have opened almost 36 million digital yuan wallets, as the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) pilot breaks new ground. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Shanghai Securities News and the China Securities Network News, the claims were made by the Shenzhen branch of the central People’s Bank of China (PBoC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shenzhen-china-36m-digital-yuan-wallets-opened-so-far-cbdc-pilot-gathers-pace.htm"&gt;Read More: Shenzhen, China: 36m Digital Yuan Wallets Opened So Far – CBDC Pilot Gathers Pace&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shenzhen-china-36m-digital-yuan-wallets-opened-so-far-cbdc-pilot-gathers-pace.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119858/318327/adobestock-306852722.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="770165"/></item><item><title>Argentina’s Crypto ‘Awareness’ Hits 75%, Study Finds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinas-crypto-awareness-hits-75-study-finds.htm</link><description>Argentina’s crypto “awareness” levels have risen to 75%, a new study has found, although many citizens say they are still wary of token “volatility.” &lt;br /&gt;
Per Criptonoticias, the study was carried out by Bitso, one of the largest and busiest crypto trading platforms in the LATAM region. &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange surveyed 1,243 people throughout the capital Buenos Aires and all 23 provinces of the country in mid-June this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinas-crypto-awareness-hits-75-study-finds.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina’s Crypto ‘Awareness’ Hits 75%, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinas-crypto-awareness-hits-75-study-finds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119797/318216/arg1707.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="979685"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 17, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-17-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
BinanceAdded Trading Pairs:ARB/ETHBCH/TRYXVG/TRYXVG/TUSDRemoved Trading Pairs:API3/BUSDBLZ/BUSDGHST/BUSDNEXO/BUSDSTPT/BUSDWIN/BUSD &lt;br /&gt;
BitfinexListings: Kava (KAVA)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-17-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: July 17, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-july-17-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119857/318326/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Attorney Deaton Predicts Judge Torres' Rejection of SEC Appeal Request</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/attorney-deaton-predicts-judge-torres-rejection-of-sec-appeal-request.htm</link><description>Speculations and discussions around the Ripple versus SEC lawsuit continue even after the fintech company secured a victory in recently-released summary judgment.  &lt;br /&gt;
Recent tweets capture a correspondence between CryptoLaw founder John Deaton, Attorney Bill Morgan, and former SEC regional director Marc Fagel concerning the possibility of an appeal on the case. &lt;br /&gt;
In a July 16 tweet, Deaton speculated that US District Judge Torres would not approve an appeal request from the SEC. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/attorney-deaton-predicts-judge-torres-rejection-of-sec-appeal-request.htm"&gt;Read More: Attorney Deaton Predicts Judge Torres' Rejection of SEC Appeal Request&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/attorney-deaton-predicts-judge-torres-rejection-of-sec-appeal-request.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119899/318387/maxresdefault.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="40400"/></item><item><title>G20 Watchdog Report Highlights Crypto Firms' Nowhere-to-Hide Situation Under Global Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/g20-watchdog-report-highlights-crypto-firms-nowhere-hide-situation-under-global-rules.htm</link><description>Amid a heightened call for comprehensive digital assets legislation, the G20's Financial Stability Board (FSB), on July 17, published its final recommendations for regulating crypto trading firms. It focuses on issues relating to regulatory supervisory and oversight of crypto assets to help foster innovation. &lt;br /&gt;
The regulator also revised its existing recommendations for stablecoins in light of the catastrophic collapse of TerraUSD/Luna stablecoins. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/g20-watchdog-report-highlights-crypto-firms-nowhere-hide-situation-under-global-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: G20 Watchdog Report Highlights Crypto Firms' Nowhere-to-Hide Situation Under Global Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/g20-watchdog-report-highlights-crypto-firms-nowhere-hide-situation-under-global-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119896/318386/flags.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="48013"/></item><item><title>Report: BlockFi's Risky Investment in FTX and Alameda Despite Knowledge of Infamous Balance Sheet</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-blockfis-risky-investment-ftx-alameda-despite-knowledge-of-infamous-balance-sheet.htm</link><description>According to a recently unsealed report made in Friday's court filing, BlockFi Inc. executives ignored repeated warnings from their risk management team regarding significant loans to Sam Bankman-Fried's Alameda Research, collateralized with digital tokens from FTX....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/report-blockfis-risky-investment-ftx-alameda-despite-knowledge-of-infamous-balance-sheet.htm"&gt;Read More: Report: BlockFi's Risky Investment in FTX and Alameda Despite Knowledge of Infamous Balance Sheet&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>BlockFi</category><category>FTX</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-blockfis-risky-investment-ftx-alameda-despite-knowledge-of-infamous-balance-sheet.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119894/318385/a-68-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="575721"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 17 July – 1NCH, Algorand, Uniswap</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-july-1nch-algorand-uniswap.htm</link><description>As crypto markets hold relatively steady today after recent gains the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has commenced a process inviting the public to share their perspectives on Bitcoin Exchange Traded Funds (ETFs). &lt;br /&gt;
This development surfaces just ahead of the July 2023 assembly of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) set on July 25 to 26, which will give more information to market participants about possible future market sentiment....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-july-1nch-algorand-uniswap.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 17 July – 1NCH, Algorand, Uniswap&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>1NCH</category><category>Algorand</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>THUG LIFE</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Best Meme Coin To Buy Now</category><category>Best Meme Coin</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Project 2023</category><category>ALGO PRICE</category><category>UNI PRICE</category><category>1INCH PRICE</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>WSM</category><category>WSM price</category><category>THUG</category><category>THUG PRICE</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-17-july-1nch-algorand-uniswap.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119890/318369/bc17j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="344017"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Slides Back Below $30,000, But These Metrics Show BTC Bulls Still Anticipating Further Upside</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-slides-back-below-30000-but-these-metrics-show-btc-bulls-still-anticipating-further-upside.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) fell back to the south of the $30,000 level on Monday to hit its lowest point since late June in the $29,600s. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s most valuable cryptocurrency network by market capitalization has now pulled back around 6% from the more than one-year highs it hit last Thursday around $31,800....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-slides-back-below-30000-but-these-metrics-show-btc-bulls-still-anticipating-further-upside.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Slides Back Below $30,000, But These Metrics Show BTC Bulls Still Anticipating Further Upside&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>btc</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Options</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-slides-back-below-30000-but-these-metrics-show-btc-bulls-still-anticipating-further-upside.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119886/318356/btc-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="160058"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Dominates as Crypto Products Record Largest Consecutive Inflows Since 2021</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominates-as-crypto-products-record-largest-consecutive-inflows-since-2021.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) once again stood out as the top target for investments from traditional fund investors last week, the latest report from crypto research and investment firm CoinShares has revealed. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the report, crypto-backed investment funds overall saw $137 million of inflows for the week, with 99% going into funds backed by Bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
The week marked the fourth consecutive week of inflows into crypto funds, CoinShares said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominates-as-crypto-products-record-largest-consecutive-inflows-since-2021.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Dominates as Crypto Products Record Largest Consecutive Inflows Since 2021&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominates-as-crypto-products-record-largest-consecutive-inflows-since-2021.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119871/318338/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="285142"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rests on $30,000 Support – Where is BTC Heading Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rests-30000-support-where-btc-heading-now.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is currently trading at $30,283.26, showing a minor increase of 0.05% over the past 24 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency has found support around the crucial $30,000 level, leading traders and investors to ponder its next direction.  &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst ongoing market volatility, the stability of Bitcoin at this support level raises questions about its potential upward or downward movement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rests-30000-support-where-btc-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rests on $30,000 Support – Where is BTC Heading Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rests-30000-support-where-btc-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119888/318375/17.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481894"/></item><item><title>Binance CEO Confirms Layoffs, Refutes Exaggerated Figures</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-confirms-layoffs-refutes-exaggerated-figures.htm</link><description>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) has confirmed that his exchange is laying off people, but said numbers reported in the media are “way off.” &lt;br /&gt;
“As we continuously strive to increase talent density, there are involuntary terminations,” CZ wrote in a tweet this weekend, while adding “This happens in every company.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-confirms-layoffs-refutes-exaggerated-figures.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO Confirms Layoffs, Refutes Exaggerated Figures&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-confirms-layoffs-refutes-exaggerated-figures.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119855/318321/binance.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="22886"/></item><item><title>Aave's Dollar-Pegged GHO Stablecoin Achieves $2.5M Market Cap within 48 Hours</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/aaves-dollar-pegged-gho-stablecoin-achieves-25m-market-cap-within-48-hours.htm</link><description>In just 48 hours of being launched, Aave's GHO, an algorithmic stablecoin pegged to the United States dollar on the Ethereum network, has already achieved a total minting value of $2.5 million. &lt;br /&gt;
On July 15, Aave launched GHO, a decentralized and over-collateralized stablecoin backed by a variety of digital assets, including Ethereum's Ether (ETH) and Aave's token (AAVE). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/aaves-dollar-pegged-gho-stablecoin-achieves-25m-market-cap-within-48-hours.htm"&gt;Read More: Aave's Dollar-Pegged GHO Stablecoin Achieves $2.5M Market Cap within 48 Hours&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Aave</category><category>Aave GHO</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/aaves-dollar-pegged-gho-stablecoin-achieves-25m-market-cap-within-48-hours.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119869/318341/getpaidstock-com-64b57ed5.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="81033"/></item><item><title>Crypto Industry Turns to Customers Bank as Preferred Partner Amidst Collapse of Silvergate, Signature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-industry-turns-customers-bank-as-preferred-partner-amidst-collapse-of-silvergate-signature.htm</link><description>The US crypto industry has a new favorite banking partner, a small Pennsylvania-based called Customers Bank. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Bloomberg article citing sources familiar with the matter, the bank is partnered with hundreds of crypto companies, with a wave of new clients coming in after the collapse of crypto-friendly banks Silvergate Capital and Signature Bank earlier in the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-industry-turns-customers-bank-as-preferred-partner-amidst-collapse-of-silvergate-signature.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Industry Turns to Customers Bank as Preferred Partner Amidst Collapse of Silvergate, Signature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>Customers Bank</category><category>Silvergate Capital</category><category>Signature Bank</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-industry-turns-customers-bank-as-preferred-partner-amidst-collapse-of-silvergate-signature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119866/318333/customers-bank.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4749524"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Sidechain Gnosis Launches Visa-Backed Debit Card Directly Connected to Crypto Wallet</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-sidechain-gnosis-launches-visa-backed-debit-card-directly-connected-to-crypto-wallet.htm</link><description>Blockchain network Gnosis has unveiled two products that allow users to spend their digital assets directly from wallets using Visa's payment system. &lt;br /&gt;
Gnosis launched Gnosis Pay, pioneering the integration of decentralized payment networks with traditional processors, and Gnosis Card, a self-custodial Visa debit card directly linked to an on-chain wallet....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-sidechain-gnosis-launches-visa-backed-debit-card-directly-connected-to-crypto-wallet.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Sidechain Gnosis Launches Visa-Backed Debit Card Directly Connected to Crypto Wallet&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-sidechain-gnosis-launches-visa-backed-debit-card-directly-connected-to-crypto-wallet.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119864/318330/pexels-energepiccom-2988232.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1298375"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin SV is Going to Zero and yPredict AI Crypto Signals Platform Can Predict the Next Crypto to Explode – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-going-zero-ypredict-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-predict-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm</link><description>Bitcoin Satoshi Vision (Bitcoin SV) has enjoyed a short-lived rally over the past month, after almost two years of downside slide, but will the recovery flop-or-fail? &lt;br /&gt;
Launched in 2018 as a hard fork of Bitcoin Cash, Bitcoin SV, was originally launched on the promise of bringing Bitcoin technology back closer in-line with the original ideas of pseudonymous founder Satoshi Nakamoto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-going-zero-ypredict-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-predict-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin SV is Going to Zero and yPredict AI Crypto Signals Platform Can Predict the Next Crypto to Explode – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-going-zero-ypredict-ai-crypto-signals-platform-can-predict-next-crypto-explode-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119847/318322/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="583996"/></item><item><title>Cathie Wood's ARK Invest Sells Another $50.5 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-sells-another-505-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares.htm</link><description>The tech-oriented investment manager, ARK Invest, is considered to be one of the largest holders of Coinbase (COIN) shares.  &lt;br /&gt;
The company owns over 10.5 million shares, and for a long time, the firm was happy to keep piling up shares and continue purchasing more.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, as of last week, the firm started selling Coinbase shares, so far dumping them on two occasions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-sells-another-505-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares.htm"&gt;Read More: Cathie Wood's ARK Invest Sells Another $50.5 Million Worth of Coinbase Shares&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-sells-another-505-million-worth-of-coinbase-shares.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119850/318316/cathie-woods-ark-invest-s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="100539"/></item><item><title>New Meme Coin Thug Life is Listing Today - Can This Crypto 100x Like $SPONGE?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-coin-thug-life-is-listing-today-can-this-crypto-100x-like-sponge-1.htm</link><description>Monday, 17th July - Meme coin degens are strapping on their seat belts ahead of what is expected to be an explosive launch for Thug Life Token later on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;
$THUG, which analysts are hailing as one of 2023’s top shitcoin investment opportunities, launches at 18:00 CET....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-coin-thug-life-is-listing-today-can-this-crypto-100x-like-sponge-1.htm"&gt;Read More: New Meme Coin Thug Life is Listing Today - Can This Crypto 100x Like $SPONGE?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-coin-thug-life-is-listing-today-can-this-crypto-100x-like-sponge-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119853/318313/thug-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="524592"/></item><item><title>Major Setback: Smart Contract Exploit Results in Over 200 Ethscriptions Being Nabbed</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-setback-smart-contract-exploit-results-over-200-ethscriptions-being-nabbed.htm</link><description>According to its creator, a new protocol allowing the creation and sharing of digital objects on Ethereum has experienced a significant setback due to a major hack in its main marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;
Ethscriptions, a novel method to create Ethereum assets launched last month by Tom Lehman, co-founder and former CEO of Genius.com, utilizes transaction "calldata" to write non-financial data to the blockchain network. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-setback-smart-contract-exploit-results-over-200-ethscriptions-being-nabbed.htm"&gt;Read More: Major Setback: Smart Contract Exploit Results in Over 200 Ethscriptions Being Nabbed&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Ethscriptions</category><category>Ethereum blockchain</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-setback-smart-contract-exploit-results-over-200-ethscriptions-being-nabbed.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119845/318342/getpaidstock-com-64b556eec1ce2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="60651"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Gnosis Released Pay and Card Products, cLabs Proposes Migrating Celo to Layer 2 Built on Ethereum, Unstoppable Domains Adds ENS-based .eth Domains</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gnosis-released-pay-and-card-products-clabs-proposes-migrating-celo-to-layer-2-built-on-ethereum-unstoppable-domains-adds-ens-based-eth-domains.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gnosis-released-pay-and-card-products-clabs-proposes-migrating-celo-to-layer-2-built-on-ethereum-unstoppable-domains-adds-ens-based-eth-domains.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Gnosis Released Pay and Card Products, cLabs Proposes Migrating Celo to Layer 2 Built on Ethereum, Unstoppable Domains Adds ENS-based .eth Domains&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Payments</category><category>Gnosis</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Visa</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Celo</category><category>Layer-2</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Staking</category><category>Web3</category><category>Unstoppable Domains</category><category>ENS</category><category>ConsenSys</category><category>Investment</category><category>Security</category><category>Crime</category><category>Scam</category><category>Chainalysis</category><category>Dfinity</category><category>Internet Computer</category><category>ICP</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gnosis-released-pay-and-card-products-clabs-proposes-migrating-celo-to-layer-2-built-on-ethereum-unstoppable-domains-adds-ens-based-eth-domains.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119820/318296/screenshot-2023-07-17-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="165825"/></item></channel></rss>
