<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 17:28:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Russian Man Charged for $200 Million in Ransomware Crimes Involving Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/russian-man-charged-for-200-million-in-ransomware-crimes-involving-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 22:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251129</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ransomware-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ransomware-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The hacker was allegedly involved with multiple ransomware strains that attacked police departments, hospitals, and the Colonial Pipeline. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Russian man has been charged by US authorities for his alleged connection to multiple ransomware schemes that netted him and other attackers nearly $200 million – much of which came through crypto. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some of the victims of those ransomware attacks included hospitals, schools, and police departments. </span></p>
<h2>$200 Million in Ransomware Payments</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The culprit – Mikhail Pavlovich Matveev – was part of three ransomware gangs: Lockbit, Babuk and Hive. Collectively, they have obtained almost $200 million from victims after demanding funds in excess of $400 million, per figures from the </span><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/alleged-russian-hacker-charged-in-200-million-ransomware-spree-1.1920988" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Department of Justice</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Department noted that Mateev was known online by multiple aliases, including “Wazawaka”, “m1x”, “Boriselcin”, and “Uhodiransomwa.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“These international crimes demand a coordinated response,” said Assistant Attorney General Kenneth A. Polite, Jr. of the Justice Department’s Criminal Division in the DOJ’s statement. “We will not relent in imposing consequences on the most egregious actors in the cybercrime ecosystem.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Some of Mateev’s alleged crimes included helping deploy Babuk ransomware against the Metropolitan Police Department in Washington, D.C. in April 2021, as well as a New Jersey nonprofit behavioral healthcare organization in May 2022. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In the former case, the criminal and his co-conspirators threatened to disclose sensitive materials to the public unless payments were made. Babuk ransomware actors have executed at least 65 attacks around the world since December 2020, demanding $49 million in payments, and receiving at least $13 million. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In January 2022, cybersecurity journalist Brian Krebs reported that Mateev had claimed affiliation with the Darkside ransomware groups, according to </span><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/alleged-russian-hacker-charged-in-200-million-ransomware-spree-1.1920988" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bloomberg</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.  Darkside was responsible for a ransomware attack against the Colonial Pipeline in 2021, which netted the attackers 63.7 BTC in forced payments. </span></p>
<h2>Crypto’s Role in Ransomware</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin have become popular tools for conducting ransomware attacks since 2021. Unlike traditional bank transfers, hackers can easily remain anonymous when requesting payments in Bitcoin, and such payments cannot be reversed or reclaimed by a bank or government. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to Chainalysis, ransomware revenue </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ransomware-revenue-drops-amidst-less-successful-extortion-attempts-chainalysis/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">fell</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> substantially in 2022 to $456.8 million, compared to $765.6 million in 2021. Experts attributed the drop to a decrease in victims’ willingness to pay a ransom – especially as sanctions rules against such payments by the US Treasury Department have made them riskier to conduct.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> In January, the FBI </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fbi-announces-takedown-of-hive-ransomware-network/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that it had taken down the HIVE ransomware network, which had members across North America and Europe. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/russian-man-charged-for-200-million-in-ransomware-crimes-involving-crypto/" rel="nofollow">Russian Man Charged for $200 Million in Ransomware Crimes Involving Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyzing MiCA&#8217;s Role in Shaping Global Crypto Regulation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/analyzing-micas-role-in-shaping-global-crypto-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Union]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251636</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/European_Union.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/European_Union.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Will MiCA's introduction unlock many opportunities within the European market?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) is being hailed as the world&#8217;s first comprehensive set of rules that aims to bring the largely unregulated cryptocurrency markets under government regulation.</p>
<p>It is part of a broader digital finance package, aka ‘Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA),’ which aims at protecting the financial services sector from fraudulent activities and is likely to become law in July 2023, setting the wheels in motion for the rules to take effect by January 2025 in stages.</p>
<p>While the United States is bogged down in the struggle of clarifying what the digital assets are, the European Union, with MiCA in the picture, has doubled down on how to regulate, instead of who is going to regulate the space &#8211; an approach that could prove to be a game-changer.</p>
<p>But the big question is how will MiCA impact the European crypto market.</p>
<h2>Quashing Europe Exit Concerns</h2>
<p>The EU Council &#8211; representing 27 member states, unanimously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eu-council-unanimously-votes-in-favor-of-mica-legislation/" data-wpel-link="internal">approved</a> MiCA, becoming the first major jurisdiction in the world with a crypto licensing regime.</p>
<p>The positive reception received by the EU’s robust regulatory framework can be attributed to the fact that lawmakers have mostly refrained from adopting the “regulation-by-enforcement” approach. Therefore, several other markets and jurisdictions have begun looking to MiCA as a precedent in order to stay competitive in the global market. Following its footsteps are countries like the UK, Australia, and Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Several experts have weighed on how MiCA could shape the regulatory landscape in the broader crypto industry.</p>
<p>Banxa’s Director of Compliance, Brinda Paul, for one, believes MiCA sets a high standard for consumer protection, which will benefit customers immensely from a more reliable and trustworthy crypto market. In a conversation with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the exec further added that “heightened customer confidence has the potential of increasing participation in the crypto economy.”</p>
<p>Its introduction is mostly expected to serve as a catalyst by attracting both startups and prominent businesses, setting the stage for more healthy competition.</p>
<p>As for end-users, Laura Chaput, head of regulatory compliance at Brussels-based market-maker Keyrock, said that rules on governance will increase transparency, rules on stablecoins issuers will offer more “confidence that their tokens are properly reserved and redeemable, and safeguards against market manipulation will increase market integrity.”</p>
<p>But changes won’t be very significant or noticeable for regulated entities that have already enacted strict KYC and AML procedures. But users of unregulated or non-compliant exchanges may encounter withdrawal issues and will likely be asked to provide additional information regarding their identity and source of funds, according to Zonda’s Przemyslaw Kral.</p>
<h2>Addressing Market Manipulations and Abuse</h2>
<p>There are legitimate speculations about how the alleged malpractices at FTX could have been prevented had MiCA been implemented earlier. In fact, European Parliament economics committee member Stefan Berger previously stated that the adoption of MiCA as a global set of regulatory standards would have prevented such a disaster from happening.</p>
<p>On the aspect, Banxa’s Paul noted that MiCA introduces stringent measures to promote a secure, transparent, and fair crypto market, including disclosures of inside information, strict prohibitions of insider dealing, unlawful disclosure of inside information, and market manipulation.</p>
<p>Hence, it is safe to say that obtaining authorization under the regulatory regime will not be an easy task, and ongoing controls exercised by competent authorities will generate substantial and recurring compliance activity by the crypto service providers.</p>
<p>Tiana Whitehouse, Chief Compliance Officer at CLC &amp; Partners, further explained,</p>
<blockquote><p>“MiCA is broadly aligned with the EU’s existing Market Abuse Regulation (MAR), which applies to securities and derivatives. Under the new legislation, CASPs and other participants facilitating trades in crypto-assets in the EU must have adequate controls to prevent and detect market abuse and manipulation.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Bone of Contention</h2>
<p>MiCA is set to be implemented in two stages. The first 12-month phase-in period deals with stablecoins and the next 18-month period for the remainder of the industry. For now, the focus will be on its implementation, which entails offering a wide-encompassing set of rules for the crypto market.</p>
<p>Overall, the regulation seeks to govern the issuance and provision of services related to crypto-assets and stablecoins. But it has left several components of the digital asset industry outside its scope. One such is the non-fungible tokens.</p>
<p>Despite being excluded from MiCA&#8217;s explicit white paper requirements, the NFT sector will still likely feel the regulation&#8217;s influence, as per Yuriy Brisov, Co-Founder and Chief Legal Officer at IOGINALITY NFT Marketplace. He further added,</p>
<blockquote><p>“Indirectly affecting NFT marketplaces by imposing AML/CTF rules, MiCA could contribute to increased transparency and trust in the booming world of digital art, collectibles, and more, ultimately elevating the NFT space.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/analyzing-micas-role-in-shaping-global-crypto-regulation/" rel="nofollow">Analyzing MiCA&#8217;s Role in Shaping Global Crypto Regulation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anthony Scaramucci Explains Why He Is Sticking With Bitcoin and What Is Its Intrinsic Value</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/anthony-scaramucci-explains-why-he-is-sticking-with-bitcoin-and-what-is-its-intrinsic-value/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 17:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251603</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Scaramucci-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Scaramucci-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SkyBridge Capital's founder's experience with the crypto industry has not always been positive.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a recent interview, the former partner of Sam Bankman-Fried doubled down on his belief that the FTX founder is the crypto spin-off of Bernie Madoff.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Scaramucci added that he is sticking with crypto and bitcoin and provided his company&#8217;s intrinsic BTC value at the moment.</p>
<ul>
<li>The former White House Director of Communications for the Trump administration entered the cryptocurrency space shortly after the COVID-19 pandemic broke out and has become a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-the-bitcoin-bear-market-really-over-anthony-scaramucci-thinks-so/" data-wpel-link="internal">permanent member</a> since then, taking every opportunity to praise and invest in bitcoin.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0JupQPbidf8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Speaking</a> to Bloomberg earlier this week, Scaramucci doubled down on his support for the asset despite the recent calamity in the sector and his personal experience.</li>
<li>He said BTC&#8217;s current USD value of around $27,000 is actually an understatement as his company believes &#8220;intrinsically bitcoin is worth about $40,000.&#8221;</li>
<li>Scaramucci justified the higher price with the increasing adoption of the cryptocurrency, including the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wholecoiner-addresses-with-more-than-1-bitcoin-doubled-since-2016/" data-wpel-link="internal">growing number</a> of addresses, as well as miners <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/" data-wpel-link="internal">earning</a> more rewards compared to last year.</li>
<li>He also compared BTC&#8217;s adoption, with over 300 million wallets as of now, to the Internet back in 1998, which is around 4% of the global population. As such, once this percentage doubles to 8, investors will see &#8220;explosive returns&#8221; from their bitcoin exposure.</li>
<li>Aside from BTC, Scaramucci was involved with FTX last year as the now-defunct exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-ventures-to-acquire-30-stake-in-anthony-scaramuccis-skybridge-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">acquired</a> a 30% stake in SkyBridge Capital.</li>
<li>Given everything that happened with SBF just a few months after that deal, Scaramucci has turned against his former partner, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/anthony-scaramucci-calls-sam-bankman-fried-the-bernie-madoff-of-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">calling</a> him the Bernie Madoff of crypto in the past. In the most recent interview, he even went a step further:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;You’re mentioning the Sam Bankman-Fried thing. It was almost like if John Meriwether and Bernie Madoff had a baby, it was Sam Bankman-Fried. You got everything in that story. You got fraud, you got over-leverage, you’ve got excess confidence. And it caused a really big depression in the markets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/anthony-scaramucci-explains-why-he-is-sticking-with-bitcoin-and-what-is-its-intrinsic-value/" rel="nofollow">Anthony Scaramucci Explains Why He Is Sticking With Bitcoin and What Is Its Intrinsic Value</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Predicts: After AI, These 4 Emerging Technologies Can Cause Crypto’s Next Big Boom</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-after-ai-these-4-emerging-technologies-can-cause-cryptos-next-big-boom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 15:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251688</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[AI caused a big boom in the crypto industry in 2023, but which emerging tech will be ahead of the next big trend? ChatGPT chips in.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Artificial Intelligence has been the biggest thread alongside memecoins in 2023. ChatGPT took the world by storm, and with it, this emerging technology was brought to the forefront of mainstream attention.</p>
<p>Everyone seems to have an opinion on AI, and the cryptocurrency industry is no exception. Many projects that incorporate some form of it in their roadmap have seen explosive growth. And, of course, as it&#8217;s almost always the case with crypto &#8211; even if they don&#8217;t use AI but have it in their name &#8211; growth follows, albeit temporarily.</p>
<p>With this in mind, we decided to dig a bit deeper and see what the next emerging technology that could impact crypto as much as AI did is. More importantly, we decided to talk to ChatGPT about it.</p>
<p>Here are its thoughts on the top 4 emerging technologies (apart from AI) that can impact crypto the most in the next 5 years.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251690" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover.jpg" alt="chatgpt_predicts_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_predicts_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>ChatGPT Sees Quantum Computing as a Threat to Crypto</h2>
<p>First things first, recall that a &#8220;boom&#8221; is literally used as a synonym for an explosion, and outside of the word&#8217;s figurative use, it&#8217;s usually associated with devastation.</p>
<p>That said, ChatGPT&#8217;s first prediction was that quantum computing could be a threat to the security of traditional cryptographic algorithms.</p>
<blockquote><p>As quantum computers become more powerful, they could potentially break the cryptographic mechanisms used in cryptocurrencies, compromising their security. This has led to ongoing research into quantum-resistant cryptohgraphic algorithms and the development of post-quantum cryptography to safeguard cryptocurrencies in the future.</p></blockquote>
<p>It probably goes without saying, but this has been a topic of debate for many years now, and both sides have some sort of valid arguments. The downside for those arguing that a quantum computer could be the end of Bitcoin is that it foregoes many variables, such as the motivation behind an act of the kind, the potential competition between multiple quantum computers that would work against each other to solve the algorithm first, the energy required to do so, and much more.</p>
<p>Of course, theoretically, a supercomputer that works out of the restrains of 1s and 0s can crack Bitcoin, but <a href="https://www.ngrave.io/en/blog/can-a-quantum-computer-hack-bitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">there&#8217;s a lot more to it</a>.</p>
<h2>Back to the Roots with Privacy-Preserving Technologies</h2>
<p>Before all the fame and glory and the multi-billion capitalizations of random frog-based memecoins, this industry was mostly about cryptography and the privacy that comes with it.</p>
<p>ChatGPT thinks we&#8217;re going back to our roots.</p>
<blockquote><p>Privacy is a significant concern in the crypto industry. Technologies like zero-knowledge proofs (ZKPs), secure multiy-party computation (MPC), and homomorphic encryption hold promise for enhancing privacy in blockchain technologies.</p></blockquote>
<p>The chatbot argues that these technologies allow for private and secure computations and enable users to prove knowledge of certain information without having to reveal the information itself. For example, I can show you proof that I have a driver&#8217;s license without having to show you my driving license.</p>
<p>These are solutions that are being actively developed. In fact, we spent quite some time talking with StarkWare&#8217;s PM, Gal Ron, about what zK-Proofs are and if they are the future of scaling.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="Why are zK-Proofs the Future of Ethereum Scaling? StarkWare Employee Explains (Podcast)" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dheev3hhhuY" width="701" height="394" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<h2> Interoperability Protocols Come as Number Three</h2>
<p>Interoperability is not just a buzzword in ChatGPT&#8217;s dictionary but an emerging technology that could cause the industry&#8217;s next big boom.</p>
<blockquote><p>Interoperability protocols aim to facilitate seamless communication and data transfer between different blockchain networks. Currently, most cryptocurrencies and blockchain platforms operate in silos, limiting their interoperability and hindering the flow of value and information across networks.</p></blockquote>
<p>According to the AI language model, solutions in this field, including cross-chain bridges, sidechains, and interoperability-focused networks, have the potential to enable the transfer of data across multiple blockchains and foster greater liquidity.</p>
<h2>Last but NOT Least: Scalability Solutions</h2>
<p>Quite naturally, scalability solutions also made the cut in ChatGPT&#8217;s list, mostly because it sees scalability as one of the greatest challenges for many networks, especially when it comes to handling a large number of transactions cost-effectively and quickly.</p>
<blockquote><p>Emerging scalability solutions, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">layer 2 soultions</a> aim to address these issues by offloading transactions or data to secondary layers of dividing the blockchain into smaller partitions.</p></blockquote>
<p>ChatGPT believes that these solutions have the potential to enhance transaction throughput while also improving performance and reducing fees.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-after-ai-these-4-emerging-technologies-can-cause-cryptos-next-big-boom/" rel="nofollow">ChatGPT Predicts: After AI, These 4 Emerging Technologies Can Cause Crypto’s Next Big Boom</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>After Prolonged Consolidation for ETH, is $2.1K Still Possible? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/after-prolonged-consolidation-for-eth-is-2-1k-still-possible-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 14:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251662</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum has been struggling with the 100-day moving average, which stands at $1772, for an extended period. However, the price action at this crucial level has not yet clearly indicated any upcoming direction. A breakout, on the other hand, has the potential to trigger an immediate cascade. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Following [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum has been struggling with the 100-day moving average, which stands at $1772, for an extended period. However, the price action at this crucial level has not yet clearly indicated any upcoming direction. A breakout, on the other hand, has the potential to trigger an immediate cascade.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h2>The Daily Chart</h2>
<p>Following a short-term consolidation phase, the price experienced a decline toward the 100-day moving average of $1.7K. The recent PA of Ethereum has failed to deliver a definite direction, with the price consolidating and printing very small green and red candles. This has left the market in extreme uncertainty.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the cryptocurrency faces two critical support levels: the 100-day moving average at $1772 and the substantial support region at $1.7K. Therefore, if $1.7K prevents a further decline, there is potential for a rally aiming for the resistance area at $2.1K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251667" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251667" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251667 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2105231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-Daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251667" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>On the 4-hour timeframe, the price has continued its bearish trend towards the support region at $1.7K. However, after reaching this level, it formed a slight bounce and entered a consolidation state characterized by very small candles.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a descending wedge pattern can be observed in the 4-hour timeframe, with the price currently consolidating within the narrow range. The wedge’s lower trendline coincides with the significant support region at $1.7K, making it a powerful level.</p>
<p>Ultimately, a downward break of the support zone at $1.7K and the lower boundary of the descending wedge could trigger a cascade as long positions get liquidated and selling pressure soars. Conversely, if the price finds support, it could potentially aim for the mid-boundary of the channel and even the resistance region at $2.1K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251666" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251666" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251666 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2105232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETH-4H-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251666" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-prolonged-consolidation-for-eth-is-2-1k-still-possible-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">After Prolonged Consolidation for ETH, is $2.1K Still Possible? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Explodes 9% Weekly but Is a Correction Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-explodes-9-weekly-but-is-a-correction-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 14:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251670</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price is finally showing some bullishness following 4 weeks of downward movement. However, there are still some concerning signs on the charts. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart The price has rebounded from the $0.43 support level, with the key 200-day moving average located around the same level. Currently, the 50-day moving average [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price is finally showing some bullishness following 4 weeks of downward movement. However, there are still some concerning signs on the charts.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By:<a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> Edris</a></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price has rebounded from the $0.43 support level, with the key 200-day moving average located around the same level. Currently, the 50-day moving average is being tested around the $0.47 mark, but XRP has yet to break above.</p>
<p>If a bullish breakout were to occur, a rally toward the $0.6 resistance level would be the most probable scenario. On the other hand, a drop below the 200-day moving average would be disastrous, as a decline toward the $0.3 level and even lower would become more likely. This would likely prolong the bear market.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator has also risen above 50%, displaying bullish momentum at the moment.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251672" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251672" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251672 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2105231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-21-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251672" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Against BTC, XRP has finally broken out of the large descending channel after more than 6 months. The price has surged above the 50-day moving average located around the 0.000017 mark and is currently attacking the 0.000018 resistance level.</p>
<p>The 200-day moving average trending around the 0.000019 price point could be the next target in case the price breaks through the 0.000018 level. On the other hand, a drop back inside the channel could lead to a crash toward the 0.000013 level.</p>
<p>Judging by the momentum signal by RSI, the bullish scenario seems more likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251671" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251671" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-251671 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2105232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-21-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251671" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-explodes-9-weekly-but-is-a-correction-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Explodes 9% Weekly but Is a Correction Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Pledges &#8216;Inviolable Right&#8217; to Hold and Use Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-pledges-inviolable-right-to-hold-and-use-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251533</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Pro-crypto Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy made a campaign debut at the Bitcoin 2023 conference in Miami.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Democrat candidate for U.S. President took to the “Nakamoto Stage” at the Bitcoin 2023 conference to make some powerful pledges.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-proponent-robert-f-kennedy-announces-run-for-president-of-the-usa/" data-wpel-link="internal">Robert F. Kennedy</a> shared his own experiences with Bitcoin stating that he would protect the rights of Americans to hold and use the asset if he is elected president.</p>
<blockquote><p>“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use Bitcoin is inviolable,”</p></blockquote>
<p>Kennedy went on to add, “I am an ardent defender and lifelong defender of civil liberties, and Bitcoin is both an exercise and a guarantee of those freedoms.”</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">&#8220;As President I will make sure that your right to hold and use Bitcoin is inviolable.&#8221; &#8211; <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Robert F. Kennedy Jr. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin2023?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin2023</a> <a href="https://t.co/oLtCmhiy3D" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/oLtCmhiy3D</a></p>
<p>— The Bitcoin Conference (@TheBitcoinConf) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheBitcoinConf/status/1659624117786624000?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 19, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Is Freedom</h2>
<p>The presidential candidate told the audience that it was Canada’s clampdown on truck drivers protesting Covid-19 restrictions that spurred his interest and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jfks-nephew-bitcoin-is-an-escape-route-from-the-turmoil-caused-by-the-fed/" data-wpel-link="internal">understanding</a> of Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote><p>“When I witnessed this cataclysm, this devastating use of government repression, I realized for the first time how free money is as important to freedom as free expression,” he said before adding:</p>
<p>“Bitcoin is a bulwark against precisely this kind of government and corporate expansion and intrusion.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In his proposed presidential agenda, he also outlined plans to exempt Bitcoin mining operations from electricity taxes and allow Americans to mine BTC at home to generate wealth.</p>
<p>The move is a stark contrast to President Biden’s proposed 30% tax on Bitcoin miners which is another nail in the coffin of the crypto industry in America.</p>
<p>Kennedy also announced that he will be the first presidential candidate in U.S. history to accept campaign donations in BTC.</p>
<h2>Political Figures Behind Bitcoin</h2>
<p>There were several notable political speakers at the 2023 Bitcoin <a href="https://b.tc/conference" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">conference</a>, including former Congresswoman Tulsi Gabbard, Senator Cynthia Lummis, and presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy. Kennedy Jr. is the nephew of the 35th U.S. President John F. Kennedy.</p>
<p>Senator Cynthia Lummis echoed the sentiments stating, “Bitcoin is something that is just so consistent with American values that we need to make sure it is protected, nurtured, and allowed to innovate here in the United States.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-pledges-inviolable-right-to-hold-and-use-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Pledges &#8216;Inviolable Right&#8217; to Hold and Use Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin, Gold Still The Best Insurance Against Corruption and Incompetence, Says Kiyosaki</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-gold-still-the-best-insurance-against-corruption-and-incompetence-says-kiyosaki/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251613</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/RK_190723-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/RK_190723-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The author of Rich Dad, Poor Dad had some harsh words against US President Joe Biden.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the US debt ceiling talks leading to no results, economists are wondering whether this situation could turn out to be a massive global financial crash, despite politicians still claiming that there will be a soft landing.</p>
<p>Robert Kiyosaki, however, doesn&#8217;t believe this assertion and urged investors to turn to gold, silver, and bitcoin to protect themselves.</p>
<ul>
<li>Republicans and Democrats are still <a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/05/19/politics/debt-limit-talks-snag/index.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">unable to decide</a> whether the US should raise the debt ceiling, and questions continue to arise if the country will <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/05/20/business/economy/debt-limit-default-economy.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">default</a> on its debt for the first time. But even if both parties strike a deal, the damage to the world&#8217;s largest economy could have been done already.</li>
<li>As such, the author of Rich Dad, Poor Dad, known for his pessimistic views on the current global economy and its prospects, asserted that there will be no &#8220;soft landing&#8221; despite the lack of concern from President Biden.</li>
<li>Kiyosaki also brought corruption in the country, which he believes is high due to the current leaders. He believes there are three assets that investors can buy to protect themselves, and one of it is the largest cryptocurrency by market cap.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">SOFT LANDiNG? HARD LANDING? Or CRASH LANDING? I say crash landing. I hope I am wrong yet that is what I believe. Corruption is high &amp; leaders corrupt. Buy gokd, silver, Bitcoin. Still best insurance against corruption &amp; incompetence,</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1659309445766324224?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 18, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>In a separate tweet, Kiyosaki went against Biden, saying the current US president is the most &#8220;senile, corrupt, and incompetent&#8221; one in the country&#8217;s history.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Finally a Republican with balls and she is a woman. Marjorie Taylor Green files for Joe Biden’s impeachment. Biden is the most senile, corrupt &amp; incompetent President in history. Please Republican men. Use your balls. Back MTG up and push<br />
Biden out of office.</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1659809236820566017?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-gold-still-the-best-insurance-against-corruption-and-incompetence-says-kiyosaki/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin, Gold Still The Best Insurance Against Corruption and Incompetence, Says Kiyosaki</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Shoots Up 12% Daily, Bitcoin Shaky at $27K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-shoots-up-12-daily-bitcoin-shaky-at-27k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 07:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251619</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE has resumed its bull run with a notable double-digit price pump.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After sitting below $27,000 for a few days, bitcoin finally jumped above that level in the past 24 hours but is yet to decisively reclaim it.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are with insignificant gains on a daily scale, aside from the trending memecoin &#8211; PEPE.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Uncertain at $27K</h2>
<p>Last week started on a positive note for bitcoin, which jumped to over $27,600 after the stagnant weekend. However, that was short-lived, and the asset retraced to below $27,000 in a matter of days. Another price pump followed that drove it back up to $27,500, which, yet again, was stopped in its tracks.</p>
<p>This time, the rejection was even more vigorous and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-defies-market-sentiment-with-3-increase-btc-drops-below-27k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">pushed</a> the cryptocurrency south to a weekly low of $26,400 (on Bitstamp). The bulls tried to intercept the move and helped BTC recover some ground.</p>
<p>As such, bitcoin returned to familiar ground of around $27,000 and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/injective-jumps-20-weekly-bitcoin-stalls-below-27k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">stood</a> there for a few days. It finally jumped above it hours ago but was stopped once more at $27,300. Despite losing some value since then, BTC still stands inches above $27,000 as of now.</p>
<p>Its market cap has risen slightly to $525 billion, while its dominance over the altcoins sits close to 46.5%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251622" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251622" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251622" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-20-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251622" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>PEPE on the Rise Again</h2>
<p>All eyes in the crypto community have been focused on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a> for the past month or so, as the memecoin went from an unknown coin launched in mid-April to a massive trend with a market cap of almost $2 billion a few weeks later.</p>
<p>After making several savvy investors millionaires overnight, it was listed on multiple prominent exchanges, including Binance, which turned out to be a sell-the-news moment. PEPE lost some of its momentum, and its market cap dumped by over a billion in days.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours were a lot more positive for the memecoin, as it has added over 12% of value and is back within the top 70 largest cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The larger-cap alts are also in the green on a daily scale, albeit in a more modest fashion. ETH, BNB, XRP, ADA, MATIC, SOL, LTC, DOT, and TRX have all jumped by up to 2% in a day.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has added around $10 billion daily and sits at $1.130 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_251620" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-251620" style="width: 1882px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-251620" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1882" height="851" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14.jpg 1882w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14-1024x463.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14-768x347.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14-1536x695.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-14-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1882px) 100vw, 1882px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-251620" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-shoots-up-12-daily-bitcoin-shaky-at-27k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Shoots Up 12% Daily, Bitcoin Shaky at $27K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>EDCON 2023 Unveils Open Loyalty Solution from Smart Token Labs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/edcon-2023-unveils-open-loyalty-solution-from-smart-token-labs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 06:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251598</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STL_1684616987lyw2yBLuMc.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/STL_1684616987lyw2yBLuMc.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Sydney, Australia, May 20th, 2023] The EDCON 2023 organizing team has partnered with Smart Token Labs to deliver Permissionless Perks, an Open Loyalty solution that enables event attendees to independently verify ticket ownership to 3rd party perk providers. Attendees at EDCON 2023 in Montenegro from May 19th &#8211; 23rd can claim over [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Sydney, Australia, May 20th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>The <a href="http://www.Edcon.io/perks" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">EDCON</a> 2023 organizing team has partnered with <a href="https://www.smarttokenlabs.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Smart Token Labs</a> to deliver Permissionless Perks, an Open Loyalty solution that enables event attendees to independently verify ticket ownership to 3rd party perk providers.</p>
<p>Attendees at EDCON 2023 in Montenegro from May 19th &#8211; 23rd can claim over 30 exclusive perks available only to them.</p>
<blockquote><p>CEO of Smart Token Labs, Victor Zhang, said Permissionless Perks is one of the few commercial examples of Open Loyalty: “ It’s a permissionless Open Loyalty solution where the verification occurs between the ticket holder and the perk provider without involving the event organizer. A URL delivered to attendees is an attestation that attests ticket ownership and is then stored in the browser’s local storage to enable the seamless claim of perks on the providers’ websites.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Sky Harris, Marketing Lead of De University of Ethereum, co-organizer of EDCON, praised Permissionless Perks as a great way to create additional value for attendees: “What we love about this solution is it enables any 3rd party to add value to the attendee experience by providing perks for our ticket holders. It&#8217;s a truly permissionless and decentralized solution, and attestations unlock unique value.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>“There are over 30 perks for attendees, ranging from the ability to free mint a derivative Cool Cat in EDCON swag to the chance to claim one of 50 serves of ‘Njegusi Prosciutto’ from a famed local Montenegrin restaurant.</p></blockquote>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/IMG_1788_1684616904jA8I5S4j0n-1024x1024.jpg" /></p>
<blockquote><p>“We thank our friends at Smart Token Labs for supporting EDCON by enabling ticket attestations and Permissionless Perks via their fully open source TokenScript technology.”</p></blockquote>
<p>STL has now delivered the Permissionless Perks as a public goods supporter to the three largest ethereum developer events of 2022 and 2023, including EDCON 2023 in Montenegro, Devcon VI in Bogota, and DevConnect in Amsterdam.</p>
<h2>About Permissionless Perks</h2>
<p>Permissionless Perks is an open loyalty platform enabling any brand to offer a perk to event ticket holders through an open marketplace. Because it is open, any brand can create value for verified event attendees, removing the burden of value creation from the event organizer. At Devcon VI in Bogota, Permissionless Perks had a 58% engagement rate, and a 20% claim rate on rewards which is 2X the industry average.</p>
<h2>About Smart Token Labs</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.smarttokenlabs.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Smart Token Labs</a> is the creator of SmartLayer, a chain-agnostic Token Utility Protocol that enables mainstream use cases between web2 and web3. SmartLayer consists of Smart Tokens that let businesses convert user data into smart tokens owned by those users. Token utility is enabled by SmartLayer, seamlessly integrating token utility and logic into products and services across both web2 and web3.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/edcon-2023-unveils-open-loyalty-solution-from-smart-token-labs/" rel="nofollow">EDCON 2023 Unveils Open Loyalty Solution from Smart Token Labs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
