<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 21:09:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dogecoin Foundation Introduces a New Core Devlopment Fund</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-foundation-introduces-a-new-core-devlopment-fund/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231260</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Dogecoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Dogecoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The fund has five custodians, with Marshall Hayner (the newest member of the DF Board of Directors) being one of them.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Dogecoin Foundation &#8211; a nonprofit organization that supports the development of the first-ever memecoin &#8211; announced a new 5,000,000 DOGE development fund. The capital will be distributed to developers who contribute to the advancement of the token&#8217;s ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity also revealed that Marshall Hayner (one of the fund&#8217;s custodians) joined the Dogecoin Foundation Board of Directors. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stimulus for Developers</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://foundation.dogecoin.com/announcements/2022-12-31-corefund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to move five million DOGE (worth around $360,000 at the moment) to a &#8220;segregated multi-signature wallet&#8221; and use the sum to reward core developers for promoting and growing the Dogecoin ecosystem:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The DOGE held in this wallet will disburse rewards to developers of Dogecoin Core for work on all contributions, no matter how big or small.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Members of the Dogecoin Foundation will run the wallet, while the following five custodians will ensure its security: chromatic (Dogecoin Core developer), Marshall Hayner, Patrick Lodder, Michi Lumin, and Ross Nicoll. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The fund will distribute 500,000 DOGE to developers after each minor or major advancement of Dogecoin Core, but the reward&#8217;s size will depend on each contributor&#8217;s actions. It will be entirely transparent, announcing every distribution across social media platforms. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition to his role as a custodian, the Dogecoin Foundation added Marshal Hayner to its Board of Directors. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Marshall brings executive and technical leadership experience to the Dogecoin Foundation and has been instrumental in creating this Core development fund,&#8221; the entity added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Relaunch of the Dogecoin Foundation</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization, established in 2014, stayed inactive for years before its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-foundation-rebooted-elon-musks-associate-and-vitalik-buterin-among-board-advisors/" data-wpel-link="internal">rebirth</a></span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-foundation-rebooted-elon-musks-associate-and-vitalik-buterin-among-board-advisors/" data-wpel-link="internal"> </a>in 2021 with a new Advisory Board. Prominent figures part of that unit include Ethereum&#8217;s Vitalik Buterin, Dogecoin&#8217;s Founder Billy Markus (Shibetoshi Nakamoto), and Jared Birchall (a key person in Elon Musk&#8217;s inner cycle).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Dogecoin Foundation collaborated with Buterin at the end of 2021 to create a &#8220;community staking&#8221; system based on Proof-of-Stake (PoS), hinting that the memecoin might shift from the Proof-of-Work (PoW) consensus mechanism. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The Foundation is also working with Vitalik (Founder of the Ethereum blockchain) on crafting a uniquely DOGE proposal for a &#8216;Community Staking&#8217; version of PoS that will allow everyone, not just the big players, to participate in a way that rewards them for their contribution to running the network, and at the same time gives back to the whole community through charitable causes,&#8221; the team announced at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, Michi Lumin recently denied those rumors, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/michilumin/status/1608317788426489856" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">saying</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> DOGE has no plans to imitate Ethereum&#8217;s move. Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s brainchild remains the only crypto protocol to switch from PoW to PoS. The upgrade, more popular as </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-merge-is-official-ethereums-transition-to-proof-of-stake-now-complete/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The Merge,&#8221;</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> was finally completed in September last year.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-foundation-introduces-a-new-core-devlopment-fund/" rel="nofollow">Dogecoin Foundation Introduces a New Core Devlopment Fund</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Alameda-FTX Crisis Started Years Before Bankruptcy: WSJ Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-alameda-ftx-crisis-started-years-before-bankruptcy-wsj-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231345</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alameda_SBF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alameda_SBF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The report claims Alameda Research was already a sinking ship long before Bankman-Fried launched FTX.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The 2022 crypto winter got colder and darker in November when one of the biggest and most prominent crypto exchanges, FTX, imploded. The company, which had bailed out several crypto firms during the Terra-induced crash in May 2022, ended up filing for bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">While FTX&#8217;s founder, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), and other executives are currently facing multiple <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-alameda-crisis-caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">lawsuits</span></a> for fraud, fresh reports have surfaced alleging that the FTX-linked crypto trading firm, Alameda Research, was a walking red flag from its early days.</p>
<h2>A Sinking Ship From the Beginning</h2>
<p class="p1">According to a recent Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/alameda-sam-bankman-fried-ftx-crypto-crash-11672434101?mod=business_lead_pos2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">report</span></a>, which cited multiple sources familiar with the matter, including former employees, Alameda&#8217;s collapse had been long coming, even before FTX came into the picture.</p>
<p class="p2">The report noted that Alameda&#8217;s first big trade was an arbitrage play in Japan, where Bitcoin was sold at higher prices than in other regions. Alameda leveraged that opportunity to make profits of between $10 million and $30 million shortly before the price gap closed in early 2018.</p>
<h2 class="p1"><b>From Arbitrage to Bankruptcy</b></h2>
<p class="p2">As per the WSJ, despite claiming to have made massive profits from its trading activities, Alameda was incurring heavy losses from its crypto trading algorithm due to guessing the wrong way on price movements. By mid-2018, the company had lost over two-thirds of its assets, partly due to a major drop in XRP prices.</p>
<p class="p2">However, SBF raised funds from several lenders and investors to rescue the failing firm, promising annual returns of up to 20%. In April 2019, the former exec launched the crypto exchange FTX, which was marketed as a safe haven for institutional investors seeking exposure to cryptocurrencies. Bankman-Fried then used Alameda to fuel the exchange&#8217;s growth as the trading firm became FTX&#8217;s primary market maker.</p>
<p class="p2">Despite claiming that FTX and Alameda operated independently, recent lawsuits revealed that both firms worked together from the beginning.</p>
<h2>FTX Used Alameda to Lure Customers</h2>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">Speaking on this, Jeff Dorman, chief investment officer at Arca, said: &#8220;The potential conflicts of interest and embedded risks are large when a digital asset exchange also acts as the largest market maker.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">According to people familiar with the firm&#8217;s strategy, Alameda occasionally took the losing side of a trade to lure customers to FTX. Recent lawsuits revealed that Bankman-Fried further told his co-founder to create a piece of code that would allow Alameda to maintain a negative balance on FTX regardless of how much collateral it posted with the exchange.</p>
<p class="p2">SBF also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alameda-secretly-exempted-from-ftxs-auto-liquidation-engine-court-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal">ensured</a> that Alameda&#8217;s collateral on FTX would not automatically be sold if its value fell below a certain level. This arrangement, thus, gave Alameda a line of credit from FTX, allowing the trading firm to borrow tens of billions of customers&#8217; funds to pursue its bad gambles.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-alameda-ftx-crisis-started-years-before-bankruptcy-wsj-report/" rel="nofollow">The Alameda-FTX Crisis Started Years Before Bankruptcy: WSJ Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Bulls Attempting to Get Back in Town, is $0.40 in Sight? (XRP Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-bulls-attempting-to-get-back-in-town-is-0-40-in-sight-xrp-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 21:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231329</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price has gone through increased volatility over the last 24 hours, experiencing fluctuations of around 15% in a matter of hours. Yet, there might be more of it en route. Technical Analysis  By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart On the daily timeframe, it is evident that the price has dropped towards and rebounded from $0.3 [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price has gone through increased volatility over the last 24 hours, experiencing fluctuations of around 15% in a matter of hours. Yet, there might be more of it en route.</p>
<h2><strong>Technical Analysis</strong><strong> </strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: </strong><a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><strong>Edris</strong></a></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, it is evident that the price has dropped towards and rebounded from $0.3 rapidly, as demonstrated by the considerable wick to the downside. The initial decline has been in play since the price was rejected from the 200-day and 50-day moving averages on multiple occasions.</p>
<p>However, the $0.3 support level that previously held the price from crashing further has done so successfully again, pushing the cryptocurrency to the upside.</p>
<p>Currently, the 50-day and 200-day moving averages remain significant dynamic resistance levels around the $0.37 and $0.39 marks, respectively, with the $0.42 area being the critical resistance zone for the price to break for a rally in the short term. On the other hand, a breakdown of the $0.3 level would be catastrophic, as no recent support is available beyond it to turn things around.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231332" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231332" style="width: 1638px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231332 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_020123" width="1638" height="955" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg 1638w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022-300x175.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022-768x448.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022-1536x896.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jan-2-2022-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1638px) 100vw, 1638px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231332" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</strong></h3>
<p>Against Bitcoin, XRP&#8217;s price has gone through similar volatility today, testing the 0.000018 SAT support level and instantly exploding back up. Still, the price remains trapped between the 50-day and 200-day moving averages, trending around the 0.000022 SAT and 0.000022 SAT levels, respectively.</p>
<p>While the price has seemingly climbed back above the 200-day moving average earlier today, it could be targeting the 50-day one located near the significant 0.000022 SAT static resistance level.</p>
<p>In case of a breakout above this area, a rally and breakout above the higher boundary of the large bearish flag could be expected, leading to a potential bullish trend in the near future. Conversely, a drop below the 200-day moving average would make a decline toward the 0.000018 SAT, and even the 0.000015 SAT support levels probable. However, considering the current market structure, the bullish scenario seems more reliable.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231331" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231331" style="width: 1587px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231331 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_020123" width="1587" height="851" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022.jpg 1587w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022-300x161.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022-1024x549.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022-768x412.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022-1536x824.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-2-2022-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1587px) 100vw, 1587px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231331" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-bulls-attempting-to-get-back-in-town-is-0-40-in-sight-xrp-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Ripple Bulls Attempting to Get Back in Town, is $0.40 in Sight? (XRP Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here Are the Dates for the 2023 CPI Releases and FOMC Meetings</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-are-the-dates-for-the-2023-cpi-releases-and-fomc-meetings/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231221</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/USAmerica.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/USAmerica.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The next CPI release is on January 12, while the following FOMC meeting is on February 1.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Consumer Price Index (CPI) releases showing the current inflation rate in the USA and the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meetings which determine the rate hikes in the country, have resulted in significant price swings in the cryptocurrency market over the past several months.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the following, we take a look at the events&#8217; dates in 2023.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CPI Calendar</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Year-over-Year inflation numbers are quite staggering in certain countries, such as Lebanon (162%), Venezuela (over 150%), Turkey (nearly 90%), and Argentina (88%). The situation in well-developed and leading countries like the US might sound less harmful at first, but the world&#8217;s most powerful economy<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-inflation-clocks-in-at-9-1-for-june/" data-wpel-link="internal"> saw a 40-year high</a> in June with inflation of over 9%. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Although the latest data revealed the figures for November have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-inflation-cpi-clocks-in-at-7-1-for-november/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">decreased</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to 7.1%, the numbers are still multiple times higher than what economists believe it&#8217;s healthy &#8211; around 2% YoY increases.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CPI releases typically affect the prices of most cryptocurrencies, including bitcoin. Almost every announcement from 2022 brought <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/major-bitcoin-and-ethereum-volatility-as-us-inflation-cpi-clocks-in-at-8-3/" data-wpel-link="internal">enhanced volatility</a> for the market, which is why it is important to see when the 2023 numbers will be made public.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Bureau of Labor Statistics will <a href="https://www.bls.gov/schedule/news_release/cpi.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">provide</a> </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the December inflation figures on January 12. The January numbers will go live on February 14, while the following dates are: March 14, April 12, May 10, June 13, July 12, August 10, September 13, October 12, November 14, and December 12 (respectively showing the inflation rate for the previous month).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FOMC Meetings</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Federal Reserve has applied multiple procedures to combat the economic crisis and galloping inflation, with the most notable perhaps being controlling the interest rates. Thus, the cost of borrowing money becomes more expensive, which is supposed to limit the purchase of certain goods and services.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Fed announced seven interest rate hikes in 2022, lifting the benchmark to 4.5% (the highest level in 15 years). Some estimate this percentage could go higher in 2023, and here are <a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/calendar.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">the next FOMC meetings</a> that will take place throughout the year: February 1, March 22, May 3, June 14, July 26, September 20, November 1, and December 13.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin&#8217;s price swings were evident each time the central bank of the USA adjusted the interest rates. When the institution raised the benchmark by 0.5% in December, the primary cryptocurrency <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-falls-below-18k-after-federal-reserves-announces-50bps-rate-hike/" data-wpel-link="internal">tumbled</a> from $18,300 to $17,850 in a matter of minutes.</span></p>
<p>On the contrary, BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-announces-75-bps-rate-hike-bitcoin-rockets-to-20600/" data-wpel-link="internal">spiked</a> above $20,500 when the Fed increased the interest rates by 75 basis points in November.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-are-the-dates-for-the-2023-cpi-releases-and-fomc-meetings/" rel="nofollow">Here Are the Dates for the 2023 CPI Releases and FOMC Meetings</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zero USDT, USDC, BUSD, and TUSD Printed in December 2022: Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/zero-usdt-usdc-busd-and-tusd-printed-in-december-2022-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 19:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231247</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Stablecoins.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Stablecoins.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether's USDT and Circle's USDC were last printed in May and June respectively.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoins have continued to play a very critical role in the crypto economy. The ongoing bear market also demonstrated that dollar-pegged coins like USDT and USDC witnessed a parabolic growth in market cap this year.</p>
<p>However, top stablecoin issuers seemingly took a break from printing in December amidst a great deal of market turmoil and increased scrutiny. According to <a href="https://twitter.com/usdcoinprinter/status/1609459560716111872" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from the &#8216;Stablecoin Printer,&#8217; USDT, USDC, BUSD, and TUSD, have not been printed during the last month of 2022.</p>
<ul>
<li>In fact, the two-largest stablecoins by market cap have not been printed for the past several months.</li>
<li>USDT was last printed by its issuer, Tether, in May 2022, while USDC&#8217;s printing continued till June of the same year.</li>
<li>The two tokens have been in a constant battle for dominance, and the de-pegging and the subsequent collapse of Terra ecosystem&#8217;s now-defunct algorithmic stablecoin &#8211; UST &#8211; did help in closing the gap between them.</li>
<li>USDT laid low amidst concerns of Terra-induced contagion spread. USDC, on the other hand, saw an increase in consumer confidence. This resulted in 4% growth YTD from $42.9 billion to $44.6 billion.</li>
<li>Market participants <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-stablecoin-records-second-highest-trading-volume-ever-amid-massive-volatility/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ditched</a> USDT for USDC. The latter went on to become the stablecoin of choice on the Ethereum blockchain.</li>
<li>The collapse of Terra left a vacuum in the Cosmos ecosystem, where the algorithmically pegged to the US dollar was used heavily across its interconnected family of blockchains. Stablecoin issuer Circle grabbed the chance to natively launch USDC on Cosmos in early 2022.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, Binance’s branded stablecoin &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-usd-busd-fully-backed-and-regulated-stablecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">BUSD</a> &#8211; happens to be another prominent contender in the stablecoin space that has seen an upward growth trajectory.</li>
<li>BUSD more than doubled its market cap from the beginning of 2022 to November. Despite its decline in the weeks that followed, the stablecoin has managed to add added an overall 12% to its market cap YTD.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zero-usdt-usdc-busd-and-tusd-printed-in-december-2022-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Zero USDT, USDC, BUSD, and TUSD Printed in December 2022: Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>13 Biggest Crypto Scandals and Controversial Stories of 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/13-biggest-crypto-scandals-and-controversial-stories-of-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Axie Infinity (AXS)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230921</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/scandals_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/scandals_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Several icons of the crypto world turned out to be rotten eggs in 2022. But there's more.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market behaving erratically is nothing new, but absolutely no one saw such epic levels of fund mismanagement coming from established giants. The young industry&#8217;s turn to a more sordid state of affairs hit everyone by surprise, especially after the heady rush of the bull run last year.</p>
<p>2022 was marred by corruption and fraudulent activity. An industry that claims to have traceable and public transactions saw big bucks being funneled maliciously with much audacity and uniqueness. NFTs were being stolen, but no one knew what to do. Rug pulls wreaked havoc in DeFi space. Trillions have been wiped from the markets so far.</p>
<p>All that remains now are the tales of incompetence and arrogance of some of the fallen bigwigs that serve important lessons for those watching closely. Let&#8217;s look at the year that was.</p>
<h2>The True Face of Sam Bankman-Fried</h2>
<p>FTX&#8217;s collapse weighs heaviest on the market marking the fall of the golden boy of the industry. Sam Bankman-Fried resigned as CEO of FTX as the company filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in November. He is now being touted as the new Bernie Madoff.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231275" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231275" style="width: 2000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231275 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737.jpeg" alt="sbf_image" width="2000" height="1333" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737.jpeg 2000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737-300x200.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737-1024x682.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737-1536x1024.jpeg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/np_file_194737-50x33.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2000px) 100vw, 2000px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231275" class="wp-caption-text">Source: The Japan Times</figcaption></figure>
<p>His media tour comments that chimed something along the lines of &#8211; &#8220;I&#8217;m an idiot, not a crook&#8221; &#8211; did not sit well with the community. The former FTX exec was slapped with a litany of charges and accused of ripping off nearly one million people.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried and his once closely-knit circle of friends/colleagues were accused of committing international fraud in billions of dollars and sinking millions into political candidates in just three years. From the wild DM exchange between him and a reporter to post-scandal interviews, it has been a train wreck for the 30-year-old dethroned billionaire.</p>
<p>It all came crashing down for SBF as his exchange faced a massive liquidity crunch in a storm of withdrawals and a complete failure to honor the redemption requests. A quick thread on some of the most shocking findings that liquidators brought to light can be found here:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">While the collapse of <a href="https://twitter.com/FTX_Official?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@FTX_Official</a> is now common knowledge, did you know that the root user to access private keys and critically sensitive data was accessed through an unsecured group email?</p>
<p>The bankruptcy filing made several shocking claims, here are some of them. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/mOcxCGPTpQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/mOcxCGPTpQ</a></p>
<p>— CryptoPotato Official (@Crypto_Potato) <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Potato/status/1594668603625840643?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">November 21, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Terra&#8217;s Downfall</h2>
<p>What exactly happened with Terra ecosystem&#8217;s algorithmic stablecoin, UST, is still a mystery. But regulators and Do Kwon critics have been quick to dismiss it as a case of market manipulation.</p>
<p>Its once arrogant CEO humbling came only after the ecosystem descended to a disastrous fall from grace. The subsequent crypto crash wiped out an estimated $60 billion, shaking the entire global digital currency market.</p>
<p>In any case, the collapse of the entire ecosystem led to increased scrutiny of stablecoins, in general. Following the meltdown, global regulators started proposing various ways to regular stablecoins better in an attempt to prevent similar incidents from occurring in the future.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the contagion spread throughout the market like wildfire, which leads us to the next point.</p>
<h2>Three Arrows Capital Goes Bye</h2>
<p>What was one of the industry&#8217;s largest hedge funds turned out to be a firm operating with particularly lenient risk management, having been overexposed on multiple fronts.</p>
<p>The trading firm, spearheaded by community powerhouses Kyle Davis and Zhu Su, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-arrows-capital-ordered-into-liquidation-by-a-birtish-virgin-islands-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> into liquidation by a British Virgin Islands court in June. Citing sources familiar with the matter, Sky News reported that the &#8220;liquidation would be a significant moment in the current unraveling of the cryptocurrency sector, which has grown at breakneck speed in recent years.&#8221;</p>
<p>This, in itself, had an impact on the industry as a lot of cryptocurrency businesses had funds managed by 3AC. But it didn&#8217;t stop there.</p>
<h2>Shady Mashinsky</h2>
<p>Several CEOs exited this year as the bear market took hold. Alex Mashinsky too, resigned as the head of the bankrupt crypto lender Celsius in September.</p>
<figure id="attachment_216779" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-216779" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-216779 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" alt="Alex_Mashinsky" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-216779" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoPotato Archives</figcaption></figure>
<p>But his shady moves continued to make noise. A report of Mashinsky and top company executives cashing out just before the platform halted user withdrawals emerged.</p>
<p>It turned out that someone like Mashinsky, who simply parrots simpleminded slogans such as &#8220;banks are not your friends,&#8221; ended up building a conventional bank, hoping to churn in gains from crypto trading and speculation.</p>
<p>His hubris showed no end, yet as the saying goes, if it sounds too good to be true, it probably is. Celsius, as reported, filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection after acknowledging a $1.2 billion hole in its balance sheet. A separate lawsuit now accuses Celsius of &#8220;operating a &#8220;Ponzi scheme.&#8221;</p>
<h2>The Undoing of Axie Infinity</h2>
<p>Several different forms of crypto scams proliferated this year. But crypto game <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-biggest-ever-crypto-hack-what-happened-in-the-ronin-bridge-attack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Axie Infinity&#8217;s Ronin bridge</a> bore the maximum manage in a high-profile hack carried out in an elaborate phishing scheme involving fake LinkedIn job ads.</p>
<p>The notorious North Korean group &#8211; Lazarus &#8211; was responsible for Axie&#8217;s undoing.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/7/6/23196713/axie-infinity-ronin-blockchain-hack-phishing-linkedin-job-offer" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reports</a>, the scammers targeted employees of Sky Mavis and reached out over LinkedIn on behalf of a fictitious company. One senior engineer took the bait and proceeded with multiple rounds of the interview that had an &#8220;extremely generous&#8221; fake compensation package. Upon clicking a PDF supposedly containing the official offer, the hackers were able to compromise the engineer&#8217;s computer.</p>
<p>At its peak, Axie Infinity was huge, boasting 2.7 million daily active users and over 200 million in weekly trading volume for its in-game NFTs in November last year.</p>
<h2>A Highly Profitable Trading Strategy&#8230; or Not?</h2>
<p>Mango Markets attacker Avraham &#8220;Avi&#8221; Eisenberg drained the Solana-based trading and lending market&#8217;s liquidity pools.</p>
<p>While maintaining that his actions were legal, Eisenberg <a href="https://twitter.com/avi_eisen/status/1581326197241180160?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> that the trading strategy he applied was a &#8220;highly profitable&#8221; one which was made possible because the developers of the DeFi trading platform &#8220;did not fully anticipate all the consequences of setting parameters the way they are.&#8221;</p>
<p>The regulators feel differently. The self-described game theorist was charged with commodities fraud and market manipulation by US prosecutors and was arrested in Puerto Rico on December 26th.</p>
<h2>Shaking the Belief System</h2>
<p>NFT marketplace Superrare&#8217;s senior community manager Ashni Christensen and Ethereum Name Service (ENS) director of operations Brantly Millegan came under sharp scrutiny in February over past tweets. The usage of racist language and tweets about transphobic abuse caused a stir in the community, with a wide majority calling for the execs&#8217; removal.</p>
<p>This was the time when &#8220;woke&#8221; culture clashed head-on with certain beliefs in the crypto industry that vouches for inclusivity.</p>
<h2>American Actor Seth Green Got Phished</h2>
<p>Actor Seth Green&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bored-ape-yacht-club-bayc-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFTs</a> were stolen. The Robot Chicken creator had his entire NFT collection swiped from him after succumbing to a phishing scam in May. His NFT losses included Bored Ape Yacht Club #8398, two Mutant Apes, which is another NFT project by Bored Ape Yacht Club creators Yuga Labs, and a Doodle NFT.</p>
<p>Blockchain sleuth, ZachXBT later <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1546534852769505284" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">uncovered</a> that the theft of the actor&#8217;s NFTs was part of a sophisticated multimillion-dollar scam operation that has roped in numerous victims.</p>
<h2>Outrage Over Tornado Cash Sanctions</h2>
<p>OFAC sanctioning controversial crypto mixer, Tornado Cash, hit crypto&#8217;s libertarian roots.</p>
<p>Always seen as an enemy by law enforcement agencies, Tornado Cash was believed to be heavily relied on by North Korean state hackers who were behind the $625 million heist from the Ronin Bridge as well as $100 million from the Horizon Bridge. Shortly thereafter, a 29-year-old developer of Tornado Cash was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tornado-cash-developer-is-arrested-in-amsterdam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested</a> by Dutch Crime Agency (FIOD).</p>
<p>The crypto industry responded with outrage and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coin-centre-may-bring-legal-action-against-ofac-for-tornado-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuits</a>.</p>
<h2>Kyle Roche Recordings</h2>
<p>Law firm Roche Freedman is notorious for bringing class action suits against some of the most popular crypto firms. Stablecoin issuer Tether and sister exchange Bitfinex, the Tron Foundation, and BitMEX are a few of them.</p>
<p>However, things turned embarrassing for partner Kyle Roche in August when he was caught on video calling jurors &#8220;10 idiots&#8221; and boasting that he &#8220;sues half the companies in the industry.&#8221;</p>
<p>What followed was a complete mockery of himself and some astonishing claims about industry insiders. Roche claimed that his law firm had a &#8220;secret pact&#8221; with Avalanche blockchain developer Ava Labs to go after its rivals in exchange for &#8220;a massive quantity&#8221; of stock and millions of dollars worth of AVAX tokens.</p>
<p>The judge called him &#8220;uniquely stupid.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Endorsing Securities Became a Costly Affair for This Kardashian</h2>
<p>Celebrity influencer Kim Kardashian was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kim-kardashian-settles-with-sec-pays-1-26m-for-unlawfully-promoting-ethereummax/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">fined</a> with $1.26 million settlement with the SEC over her endorsement of EthereumMax (EMAX).</p>
<figure id="attachment_163213" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-163213" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-163213 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian.jpg" alt="Kim_kardashian" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Kim_kardashian-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-163213" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoPotato Archives</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kardashian had promoted the obscure token to her 225 million followers on Instagram without disclosing that the post was an ad. She was paid $250,000 for the same.</p>
<h2>Elon Musk&#8217;s Chaotic Twitter takeover</h2>
<p>The Tesla chief has only been in charge of Twitter since late October, but a lot of things have changed in the social media platform.</p>
<p>From booting top execs, slashing rank-and-file headcount by 50%, to bombarding its remaining employees with an ultimatum with regards to their work ethic and instating a number of new features such as including charging users to get or keep a verification check mark, the Blue Bird has been turned upside down.</p>
<p>You can check the full series of events that led to the acquisition in our thread here:</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">This is <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@elonmusk</a> walking in Twitter’s HQ carrying a literal sink. Whimsically capturing the video “entering Twitter HQ &#8211; let that sink in!” Tesla’s boss also revealed his reasoning for acquiring Twitter.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Here’s the complete breakdown of how the entire deal went down: <a href="https://t.co/ZcZdplcleL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/ZcZdplcleL</a></p>
<p>— CryptoPotato Official (@Crypto_Potato) <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Potato/status/1585625790066331649?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">October 27, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>BBC&#8217;s Puff Piece</h2>
<p>No one loves a rags-to-riches story more than BBC and almost ran a &#8220;puff piece&#8221; on a crypto scammer. Hanad Hassan is a 20-year-old refugee who said that he &#8220;wants to use his wealth to help people&#8221; and claimed that the crypto project he founded deployed $270,000 on good causes. He was reportedly the founder of Orfano X in 2021.</p>
<p>But it wasn&#8217;t until this year that BBC took note of him. The broadcaster prepared an almost 30-minute documentary on a crypto scammer titled &#8220;We Are England: Birmingham&#8217;s Self-Made Crypto-Millionaire.&#8221; Social media did what it does best. Users across Twitter accused the founder of stealing users&#8217; funds after creating a scam project.</p>
<p>BBC then launched an internal investigation after quietly taking down the <a href="https://archive.is/6taZ8" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">article</a>. The scheduled airing was also pulled hours before it was supposed to go live in February. BBC is now facing questions over how much due diligence it actually conducted on the project and into the scammer&#8217;s work.</p>
<h2>That&#8217;s a Wrap</h2>
<p>There&#8217;re surely more stories that fit the criteria of a scandal, and we might have forgotten some in what seemed an endless list.</p>
<p>For what is worth, let&#8217;s at least hope that 2023 will provide more tales of pride than of sordid.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/13-biggest-crypto-scandals-and-controversial-stories-of-2022/" rel="nofollow">13 Biggest Crypto Scandals and Controversial Stories of 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Proprietary Metaverse Casino Cloverland to Be Showcased at CES 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/first-proprietary-metaverse-casino-cloverland-to-be-showcased-at-ces-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231372</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] The Authentic Casino Experience Uses Advanced XR and Blockchain Technologies for Immersive, Secure, Interactive Gaming in the Metaverse Santo Domingo, DR (December 28, 2022) JM2 Clover Gaming will officially launch its Metaverse Cloverland which is an interactive, immersive environment with a full interoperable technology that utilizes advanced XR (extended [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p><em>The Authentic Casino Experience Uses Advanced XR and Blockchain Technologies for Immersive, Secure, Interactive Gaming in the Metaverse</em></p>
<p>Santo Domingo, DR (December 28, 2022) JM2 Clover Gaming will officially launch its Metaverse Cloverland which is an interactive, immersive environment with a full interoperable technology that utilizes advanced XR (extended reality) technology to virtually deliver the IRL (In Real Life) sensation of a real casino.</p>
<p>The Clover Casino, the first building on Cloverland, is going to be showcased at the Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in Las Vegas in early January 2023.</p>
<p>Cloverland is compatible with any devices, so players can interact with one another regardless of their equipment, and integrates the most advanced real-time 3D creation tool, Unreal Engine, to provide an unparalleled experience in the growing online gambling marketplace by proposing our first building Clover Casino.</p>
<p>According to Jean-Mathieu Marinetti, JM2 Clover Gaming CEO: “Cloverland will bring together all the advantages of the two worlds, physical and online casinos, to offer the most immersive and interactive experience for players and others who love the atmosphere of casinos,”</p>
<p>Cloverland allows for an immersive experience in a 3D virtual environment where players can socialize with each other as if they are in a physical casino.</p>
<p>The platform’s high-quality graphics are made possible by state-of-the-art XR technologies. The world’s most advanced real-time 3D creation tool, Unreal Engine, supports the development of an immersive VR and XR environment, including the creation of a dedicated metaverse. Furthermore, players could create a full-body 3D avatar with a selfie and use it in the metaverse.</p>
<p>However, the platform proposes a cross-chain framework to be supported by different devices even if they don’t have access to a XR/VR Headset.</p>
<p>The use of Blockchain as a Trustworthy network is important for multiples reasons like security, immutability &amp; decentralization, but the most important one for a player is to be able to audit our Metaverse available Gaming liquidity.</p>
<p>Indeed, the current gaming online industry is powered by centralize organisations or companies who propose the gaming services. However, on the Gambling industry there is no possibility to audit how much the company running it has on his treasury to be certain to be paid when an significant prize is won. Our gaming architecture approach is allowing any users to check the liquidity balance of each table games (poker, blackjack …) or electronic casino machines proposed on our Clover Casino.</p>
<p>The creators of Cloverland noticed that the gaming industry suffers from a stunning interoperability between the use of blockchain technology through smart contracts and XR/VR, which leaves users with limited immersive experiences. They solved this challenge with Cloverland, a platform that sets a new standard for online casino gaming. These new technologies give players the ability to gamble cryptocurrency, level up gains with NFTs, attend top-of-the-class events, and socialize with other users.</p>
<p>Coverland will be exhibiting from booth #61233 in the Eureka Park Marketplace at the Venetian Expo Center at CES 2023. The virtual gambling industry projections is growing fast since the pandemic.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-231374" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2.jpg" alt="Cloverland2" width="925" height="463" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2.jpg 925w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2-768x384.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cloverland2-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 925px) 100vw, 925px" /></a></p>
<h2>About Cloverland</h2>
<p>Cloverland is an interactive, immersive proprietary Metaverse gaming platform with a full interoperable technology that utilizes advanced XR (extended reality) technology to virtually deliver the IRL (In Real Life) sensation of a real casino based in Santo Domingo.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-proprietary-metaverse-casino-cloverland-to-be-showcased-at-ces-2023/" rel="nofollow">First Proprietary Metaverse Casino Cloverland to Be Showcased at CES 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cardano Spikes 4% in a Day, but Is The Worst Over? (ADA Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-spikes-4-in-a-day-but-is-the-worst-over-ada-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231238</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After making a lower low in December, Cardano surprised the market in the new year by opening in green. Key Support levels: $0.24, $0.20 Key Resistance levels: $0.30, $0.34 Optimism is building up as Cardano seems to have found good support at $0.24. Since the start of 2023, ADA is in green and does not [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">After making a lower low in December, Cardano surprised the market in the new year by opening in green.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.24, $0.20</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.30, $0.34</strong></p>
<p>Optimism is building up as Cardano seems to have found good support at $0.24. Since the start of 2023, ADA is in green and does not appear to be looking back. If this momentum continues then, this cryptocurrency could even target $0.30, which is the next key resistance.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231241" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231241" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231241" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19" width="1791" height="822" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19-300x138.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19-1024x470.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19-768x352.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19-1536x705.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-27-19-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231241" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume:</strong> The volume is rather flat, but despite this, ADA closed in the green for the past three days. Buyers may be returning.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI made a bullish divergence as the price fell to a yearly low in December 2022. This is promising, particularly in light of the current price action.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD charted a bullish cross on New Year&#8217;s Eve. Perhaps this was the signal buyers waited for.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231240" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231240" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231240" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11" width="1791" height="820" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11-300x137.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11-1024x469.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11-768x352.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11-1536x703.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ADAUSDT_2023-01-02_11-28-11-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231240" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for ADA is leaning bullish, but a clear break of the key resistance at $0.30 is needed to confirm it.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for ADA Price</h2>
<p>With a good start in 2023, ADA could attempt a recovery. The indicators seem to support such a reversal in the price action, but market participants need to be careful in case this is just a bull trap. It&#8217;s important to keep a close eye on the $0.30 resistance, as that will be decisive on where Cardano moves next.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-spikes-4-in-a-day-but-is-the-worst-over-ada-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Cardano Spikes 4% in a Day, but Is The Worst Over? (ADA Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cameron Winklevoss Calls Out Barry Silbert on $1.675B Debt, Latter Fires Back</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231341</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/104943886-GettyImages-531109726-min-e1609407819640.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/104943886-GettyImages-531109726-min-e1609407819640.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cameron Winklevoss and Barry Silbert are starting the new year with a bang.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an open letter to Barry Silbert, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss said that Digital Currency Group owes Genesis approximately $1.675 billion.</p>
<ul>
<li>Cameron Winklevoss <a href="https://twitter.com/cameron/status/1609913051427524608/photo/1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shared</a> an open letter to Barry Silbert &#8211; the founder of Digital Currency Group &#8211; on Twitter.</li>
<li>On behalf of many people, he argued that Genesis &#8211; a subsidiary of DCG &#8211; owes $900 million to them.</li>
<li>Winklevoss argued that the two companies are &#8220;beyond commingled.&#8221;</li>
<li>Furthermore, he alleged that:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>To be clear, this mess is entirely your own making. Digital Currency Group (DCG) &#8211; of which you are the founder and CEO &#8211; owes Genesis (its wholly owned subsidiary) approx. $1.675 billion. This is money that Genesis owes to Earn users and other Creditors. You took this money &#8211; the money of schoolteachers &#8211; to fuel greedy share buybacks, illiquid venture investments, and kamikaze Grayscale NAV trades that balooned the fee-generating AUM of your Trust&#8230;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Silbert was quick to respond, saying:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>DCG did not borrow $1.675 billion from Genesis.</p>
<p>DCG has never missed an interest payment to Geneiss and is current on all loans outstanding; next loan maturity is May 2023.</p>
<p>DCG delivered to Genesis and your advisors a proposal on December 29th and has not received any response.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/" rel="nofollow">Cameron Winklevoss Calls Out Barry Silbert on $1.675B Debt, Latter Fires Back</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Great and One Terrible Bitcoin Price Predictions for 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/four-great-and-one-terrible-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231312</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_price_prediction_2023.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_price_prediction_2023.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are four optimistic and one doom-and-gloom predictions for Bitcoin's price in 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>2023 is here, and with that comes an influx of predictions regarding the price of Bitcoin during the year. The past 12 months have been particularly devastating for the cryptocurrency, which lost upwards of 70% of its dollar value.</p>
<p>That said, many seem to be quite optimistic about the short-term future of BTC. Here are four great and one not-so-much predictions for 2023.</p>
<h2>Tim Draper Says BTC to $250K</h2>
<p>Tim Draper is perhaps one of the most outspoken and prominent Bitcoin permabulls. As such, it comes to no surprise that he maintains his optimistic stance and considers that it&#8217;s possible for the price to reach $250 by the end of the year.</p>
<p>This would require a rally of around 1400%.</p>
<p>Draper is also quite positive about the 2024 halving, thinking that it will have a great impact on the prices.</p>
<figure id="attachment_124139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-124139" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-124139" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper.jpg" alt="Tim Draper. Source: TechCrunch" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/TimDraper-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-124139" class="wp-caption-text">Tim Draper. Source: TechCrunch</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Carol Alexander: $50K in 2023</h2>
<p>Another one with a positive prediction is the professor of finance at Sussex University &#8211; Carol Alexander. She was getting somewhat close in his previous call that the price of BTC would slip to $10K in 2022, even though it didn&#8217;t quite get there.</p>
<p>Now, though, she believes that the cryptocurrency is primed for gains, albeit for slightly different reasons than one might expect.</p>
<p>The professor believes that the catalyst would be the influx of more dominos from the FTX fallout rolling over that would catalyze what she refers to as a &#8220;managed bull market.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>There will be a managed bull market in 2023, not a bubble &#8211; so we won&#8217;t see the price overshooting as before. [&#8230;] We&#8217;ll see a month or two of stable trending prices interspersed with range-bound periods and probably a couple of short-lived crashes.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Alistair Milne Sees BTC at Approx. $45K</h2>
<p>Another one that gave multiple predictions, including for the price of Bitcoin, is the CIO of Altana Digital Currency Fund &#8211; Alistair Milne.</p>
<blockquote><p>We should see at least ~$45k by end of 2023 (which you might discount due to the damage done). Alternatively if central banks decide to tollerate a higher inflation target (e.g. cut earlier to avoid recession despite 3-4% inflation), hard assets may become en vogue again. &#8211; He said.</p></blockquote>
<p>In a Twitter thread, he also said that the price should reach $150-300K by the end of 2024, arguing that &#8220;this is no time to be bearish and is likely peak opportunity for the bulls.&#8221;</p>
<p>He said that he is all in once again (excluding capital he expects to use for other things during the next two or three years.)</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I had a decent track record for predictions until 2022. A combination of macro influence and full-retard actions has forced <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> to break most models and completely detatch from fundamentals</p>
<p>So let&#8217;s try again&#8230;</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9f5.png" alt="🧵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— Alistair Milne (@alistairmilne) <a href="https://twitter.com/alistairmilne/status/1608803149690843137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 30, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2> Eric Wall Thinks BTC Will Pump Above $30K</h2>
<p>Another one to join the bullish train is Eric Wall, who believes that the cryptocurrency will pump above $30K at some point during 2023 without giving an exact timeline.</p>
<p>He also said that $15.4k was the bottom for BTC.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Wall also laid down a string of other predictions. He believes that Sam Bankman-Fried will go to prison for more than 10 years, which implies that the lawsuits against him and his companies will be over by then. SBF was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> on a $250M bail in December.</p>
<p>In addition, he believes that Ethereum will enable withdrawals for the staked ETH &#8211; something that <em>CryptoPotato </em>discussed in a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/talking-ethereum-2-0-with-consensys-pm-matt-nelson-when-can-eth-validators-unstake/" data-wpel-link="internal">recent podcast</a> with ConsenSys PM Matt Nelson.</p>
<h2>Standard Chartered: Bitcoin at $5K</h2>
<p>All of the above were the better predictions, as promised in the title. Here comes the terrible one.</p>
<p>According to Standard Chartered, BTC may sink as low as $5K. The financial institution put forth its thoughts back in December, saying:</p>
<blockquote><p>More and more crypto firms and exchanges find themselves with insufficient liquidity, leading to further bankruptcies and a collapse in investor confidence in digital assets.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/four-great-and-one-terrible-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023/" rel="nofollow">Four Great and One Terrible Bitcoin Price Predictions for 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
