<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Two Thirds of World’s Largest Banks Are Crypto-Friendly: Research</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/two-thirds-of-worlds-largest-banks-are-crypto-friendly-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:10:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263024</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/USBanks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/USBanks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Recent research has revealed that there are more crypto-friendly banks across the globe than previously thought.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to recent research by CoinGecko, two-thirds of the 30 biggest global banks by assets under management (AUM) support crypto trading through regulated exchanges.</p>
<p>Furthermore, around 74% of the top 50 banks worldwide support crypto trading by connecting to regulated exchanges, the report added.</p>
<blockquote><p>“However, none support retail crypto trading or on-ramping from respective native platforms.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ How many of the top 30 banks in the world support crypto trading?</p>
<p>66% or 20 out of the 30 biggest global banks by assets under management support crypto trading through regulated exchanges like <a href="https://twitter.com/binance?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Binance</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Coinbase</a>. <a href="https://t.co/aI3mC6Rbxx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/aI3mC6Rbxx</a></p>
<p>— CoinGecko (@coingecko) <a href="https://twitter.com/coingecko/status/1684599986288545792?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Crypto-Friendly Banks</h2>
<p>It comes as no surprise whatsoever that the top four non-crypto-friendly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-banks-are-venturing-into-crypto-despite-ongoing-bear-market/" data-wpel-link="internal">banks</a> are Chinese. They manage $19.87 trillion worth of assets which is over 20% of the total.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency trading and investing are still outlawed on the mainland, with Beijing pushing its own programmable CBDC (central bank digital currency).</p>
<p>However, China could be warming to crypto with Hong Kong opening up and inviting large exchanges such as Coinbase to set up in the city.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the subsidiaries of some of the largest Chinese banking institutions have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/leading-chinese-banks-support-hong-kong-based-crypto-firms-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reportedly</a> either started offering their services to crypto businesses based in Hong Kong or reached out to them.</p>
<p>The report noted that the top 50 biggest banks in the world managed a combined $89.37 trillion worth of assets in 2023. The United States and China dominate this list, with 19 banks in the top 50 by AUM.</p>
<p>The report blamed the slow adoption of blockchain and crypto by big banks on regulations, volatility, and last year’s meltdown.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Strict regulations, market volatility, and recent high-profile exchange failures like FTX have hindered the integration of crypto trading into these large banks.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>UK Banks and Crypto</h2>
<p>The research also lists several U.K. banks as being “crypto-friendly.” However, several British banks, including two in that list, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-02/sunak-s-crypto-hub-plan-in-jeopardy-as-hsbc-natwest-restrict-transfers" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">restricted</a> customer transactions to crypto companies earlier this year, so the report may not be that accurate.</p>
<p>The research defined if a bank was crypto-friendly or not based on whether it “offered crypto trading or on-ramping services within the bank’s native platforms” or “the ability to connect a bank’s current account to a regulated crypto exchange.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/two-thirds-of-worlds-largest-banks-are-crypto-friendly-research/" rel="nofollow">Two Thirds of World’s Largest Banks Are Crypto-Friendly: Research</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BNB Chain Average Daily Active Addresses Spiked 25% to 1.4M in Q2 2023: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bnb-chain-average-daily-active-addresses-spiked-25-to-1-4m-in-q2-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Chain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263167</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/BNB_Chain.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/BNB_Chain.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The growth in daily addresses and transactions on BNB Chain was majorly driven by increased activity from LayerZero.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The number of average daily active addresses on the BNB Chain spiked to 1.4 million in the second quarter of 2023, signaling a 25.6% increase from the figure recorded in Q1.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-bnb-chain-q2-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> by crypto intelligence firm Messari, the number of daily active addresses almost reached an all-time average of approximately 1.5 million recorded in Q4 2021, during the end of the last bull season.</p>
<h2>BNB Chain Sees Increase in Daily Active Addresses</h2>
<p>Messari’s researchers found that BNB Chain’s average new unique addresses increased by 91.1% in Q2, hitting all-time highs, and at the same time, daily transactions soared by 24%. The firm revealed that the growth in daily addresses and transactions was majorly driven by a rise in activity from omnichain interoperability and cross-chain messaging protocol LayerZero.</p>
<p>Besides LayerZero, notable transaction activity was recorded on PancakeSwap, Hooked Protocol, and CyberConnect.</p>
<p>While<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-the-binance-bnb-chain-will-hard-fork-and-why/" data-wpel-link="internal"> BNB Chain’s</a> daily transactions increased, the average daily transaction fee plunged by 25.5%. This resulted from BSC validators voting to slash gas fees by 40% from 5 to 3 gwei to remain competitive with other low-cost protocols. The gas fee cut also affected BNB Chain’s revenue, which decreased by 6.1%.</p>
<h2>BNB Chain’s Market Cap Plummeted</h2>
<p>Messari further reported that the market capitalization of the BNB Chain <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-coin-price-analysis-bnb-crashes-10-on-sec-lawsuit-is-250-in-sight/" data-wpel-link="internal">plunged</a> by 25.2% after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">tagged</a> Binance Coin (BNB) as a security in its lawsuits against crypto exchanges Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>In addition, BNB’s circulating supply decreased in Q2 due to the asset’s token-burn mechanism. By the end of the quarter, roughly 23% – 46 million BNB – of BNB’s 200 million circulating supply had been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-completes-23rd-quarterly-burn-heres-how-much-bnb-was-destroyed/" data-wpel-link="internal">burned</a> in the program, which began in 2017, strengthening the asset’s deflationary rate of 1.1% attained in the past year.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, staking and decentralization on the BNB Chain remained stable in Q2. The total stake, average engaged stake, and the number of validators that validated a block were relatively unchanged, according to Messari.</p>
<p>The network also recorded two consecutive quarters of expansion after implementing the BEP-131, BEP-153, and BEP-159 standards for increased staking participation and decentralization.</p>
<p>BNB Chain intends to further decentralize by implementing a validator reward model and reputation system that would increase the number of validators from 29 to 100.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bnb-chain-average-daily-active-addresses-spiked-25-to-1-4m-in-q2-2023-report/" rel="nofollow">BNB Chain Average Daily Active Addresses Spiked 25% to 1.4M in Q2 2023: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX and Genesis Finally Reach in Principle Agreement: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-genesis-finally-reach-in-principle-agreement-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263106</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Court.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Court.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The settlement would address and resolve the claims made by the two bankrupt firms against each other while being under court supervision]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX and Genesis have come to an agreement in principle to settle claims made by both parties in their ongoing legal brawl. Both bankrupt firms had previously claimed that the other party owed money. However, the legal counsel representing both wrote to bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane stating that they had agreed to a settlement.</p>
<p>The exact settlement details remain undisclosed.</p>
<ul>
<li>The letter filed by their representatives at the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-28/bankrupt-crypto-platforms-ftx-genesis-set-to-resolve-dispute" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a>,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Parties have reached an agreement in principle, subject to documentation, regarding a settlement that would resolve, among other things, the claims asserted by the FTX Debtors against the Debtors in these Chapter 11 Cases and the claims asserted by the Genesis Debtors against the FTX Debtors in the FTX Chapter 11 Cases.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>While FTX filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy last November, Genesis followed suit three months later after being battered by the fall of Three Arrows Capital in addition to the SBF-led crypto exchange.</li>
<li>In a bid to help recoup its extensive list of creditors, FTX tried to claw back funds received by the lending firm and non-debtor affiliates.</li>
<li>A previous filing showed that Genesis was the largest unsecured creditor of FTX and its affiliated companies, owing more than $226 million.</li>
<li>On the other hand, FTX claimed that DCG&#8217;s lending arm owed approximately $4 billion. The figure was later altered to $2 billion.</li>
<li>Genesis rebuffed the claim and even <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-judge-denies-ftxs-bid-to-participate-in-confidential-mediation-sessions-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> its own motion estimating that FTX is entitled to nothing.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-genesis-finally-reach-in-principle-agreement-report/" rel="nofollow">FTX and Genesis Finally Reach in Principle Agreement: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wall Street Bank Endorses Elizabeth Warren&#8217;s Strict Crypto Bill</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-bank-endorses-elizabeth-warrens-strict-crypto-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263224</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/ElizabethWarren-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/ElizabethWarren-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The bill seeks to strengthen enforcement of BSA compliance.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well-known crypto critic, Senator Elizabeth Warren, won support from Washington-based banking advocacy group, the Bank Policy Institute (BPI), for newly introduced bipartisan legislation that seeks to regulate the crypto industry and eliminate loopholes for illicit activity.</p>
<p>Its support has been viewed as a peculiar move because both Warren and the Wall Street banks have hardly agreed on the same things before. In fact, the Senator has been known to blast at the trade group every now and then.</p>
<h2>Counting on BPI&#8217;s Support</h2>
<p>In an unexpected turn of events, the Bank Policy Institute (BPI) threw its weight behind the bill, which calls for more stringent anti-money laundering rules and counter-terrorism financing measures specifically for the crypto sector.</p>
<p>The whole premise of BPI&#8217;s decision is that the existing AML structure in the US does not cover digital assets.</p>
<p>Explaining its decision to back the legislation, the banking lobbyists <a href="https://www.warren.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/warren-marshall-manchin-graham-renew-push-for-bipartisan-legislation-to-crack-down-on-cryptos-use-in-money-laundering-drug-trafficking-and-financing-of-terrorism-and-rogue-nations" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;BPI supports bipartisan efforts to help crack down on money laundering and believes this measure is an important step in that direction. The existing anti-money laundering and Bank Secrecy Act framework must accounts for digital assets, and we look forward to engaging in this process to defend our nation&#8217;s financial system and illicit finance in all its forms.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The bill was initially introduced by the Massachusetts Senator back in December 2022, a month after the dramatic collapse of FTX. It was re-introduced by Warren and three other Senators, West Virginia Democratic Senator Joe Manchin and Republican Senators Roger Mashall of Kansas and Lindsey Graham of South Carolina, on Friday.</p>
<p>Apart from BPI, the bill has also been endorsed by the Massachusetts Bankers Association, Transparency International US, Global Financial Integrity, National District Attorneys Association, Major County Sheriffs of America, Massachusetts Sheriff&#8217;s Association, AARP, National Consumer Law Center (on behalf of low-income clients), National Consumers League.</p>
<h2>The Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act</h2>
<p>The bill seeks to extend Bank Secrecy Act (BSA) responsibilities, including KYC requirements, to crypto wallet providers, miners, validators, and other network participants.</p>
<p>It also seems to address what it describes as a &#8220;major gap&#8221; in terms of &#8220;unhosted&#8221; digital wallets, which enable users to bypass AML and sanction checks. The legislation also includes measures to direct FinCEN to roll out guidance to financial institutions in mitigating the risks of dealing with digital assets that have been shuffled with coin mixers such as Tornado Cash and other privacy technologies.</p>
<p>Strengthening enforcement of BSA compliance, extending BSA rules regarding reporting of foreign bank accounts to include digital assets, and granting FinCEN to have oversight on illicit financial risks of digital assets ATMs are some of the other aspects of the seven-page legislation.</p>
<p>The latest development comes in the wake of another important crypto bill, FIT21, that seeks to end the turf war between the SEC and the CFTC over regulatory oversight of the space and bring much-needed clarity to the industry. The bill has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-calls-for-voting-in-favor-of-fit21/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">garnered</a> support from several crypto players, including Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-bank-endorses-elizabeth-warrens-strict-crypto-bill/" rel="nofollow">Wall Street Bank Endorses Elizabeth Warren&#8217;s Strict Crypto Bill</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism (OP) Soars 6% Daily, Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Declines as Price Stagnates (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/optimism-op-soars-6-daily-bitcoin-btc-dominance-declines-as-price-stagnates-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 08:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263272</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_MW_Cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Uniswap has added the most value from the top 20 alts, followed by Shiba Inu, Litecoin, and Dogecoin.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price movements continue to be highly uneventful as the asset continues to remain just inches above $29,000.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have mimicked BTC&#8217;s performance, aside from DOGE, SHIB, UNI, and OP, all of which have jumped by more than 3% daily.</p>
<h2>BTC Boring at $29K</h2>
<p>It was precisely a week ago when the primary cryptocurrency tried its hand at taking down $30,300 but failed in its tracks, and the subsequent rejection pushed it south hard. In about a day, the asset had lost more than a grand and fell to a monthly low of just under $29,000.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, bitcoin managed to bounce off and reclaim that level. What followed was almost a week of sideways price action, which saw BTC standing between $29,000 and $29,700. The latter came a day after the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-loses-30k-as-us-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-another-25bps-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">raised</a> the interest rates by 25bps, something that has led to enhanced volatility in the past, but not this time.</p>
<p>The past 48 hours have been particularly boring as BTC has stalled somewhere between $29,300 and $29,400. This means that its market capitalization has remained inches below $570 billion, but its dominance over the altcoins has suffered in the past week. The metric is down by more than 0.5% within that timeframe to 48.1% now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263273" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263273" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263273" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-26-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263273" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SHIB on a Roll</h2>
<p>Upon news about the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-goes-live-for-public-testing-as-layer-2-launch-inches-closer/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of the beta version of the project&#8217;s Shibarium, the largest native token &#8211; SHIB &#8211; began to rapidly increase in value, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-jumps-5-following-shibarium-beta-launch-btc-stands-still-above-29k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">adding</a> 5% yesterday and another 4.5% today. As such, the second-largest meme coin now stands above $0.0000085.</p>
<p>Speaking of meme coins, the OG is also well in the green today, having surged by more than 3%. DOGE is up by 11% weekly following the recent Elon Musk engagements and trades at $0.08.</p>
<p>Uniswap and Litecoin are the other notable gainers from the larger-cap alts, being up by 5.5% and 4%, respectively.</p>
<p>Optimism has jumped the most from the top 100 alts. OP is up by just over 6% now, which has pushed it to $1.6.</p>
<p>The cumulatively market cap of all crypto assets, though, has remained relatively stagnant as well at just over $1.180 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263274" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263274" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263274 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18-1024x458.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18-768x344.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18-1536x687.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-18-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263274" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/optimism-op-soars-6-daily-bitcoin-btc-dominance-declines-as-price-stagnates-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Optimism (OP) Soars 6% Daily, Bitcoin (BTC) Dominance Declines as Price Stagnates (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ducati Partners With Ripple-Founded XRP Ledger for its First NFT Collection</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ducati-partners-with-ripple-founded-xrp-ledger-for-its-first-nft-collection/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 04:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262494</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ripple_Ducati.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ripple_Ducati.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ducati unveiled its first-ever NFT launch in partnership with XRP Ledger (XRPL).]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Italian motorcycle manufacturer Ducati partnered with XRP Ledger to enter the Web3 space. The main goal is to launch its first-ever digital collectible, which is a video sequence of all the Ducati logos that have appeared on the tanks of motorbikes produced in Borgo Panigale from 1946 to the present day.</p>
<p>The first release is essentially a gift to Ducati fans as it pivots into the Web3 world and is scheduled to be launched on Wednesday, 26 July. Users are required to sign up within seven days of the release date. Following the traditional route of NFT drops, Ducati announced that those who get the first collectible will have access to subsequent projects.</p>
<h2>Ducati&#8217;s Web3 Foray</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.ducati.com/ww/en/news/ducati-announces-its-entry-into-the-world-of-web-3-0-in-partnership-with-nft-pro" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, upcoming projects by the motorcycle manufacturing giant will be deployed using Ripple, which is tasked with providing technical support on the fast, low-cost, and carbon-neutral XRP Ledger (XRPL) blockchain.</p>
<p>Ducati plans to develop a series of Web3 activities over the next few months through the creation of new digital aggregation spaces, NFT collections, and other opportunities. The company said the move represents the &#8220;natural evolution of its digital strategy.&#8221;</p>
<p>For the initiative, Ducati has also teamed up with Web3 Pro, which had previously worked with its parent company, Lamborghini, for brand engagement on an NFT collection called &#8220;The Epic Road Trip.&#8221;</p>
<p>Commenting on the latest development, Ducati CEO Claudio Domenicali said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Entering WEB 3.0 is another way to get closer to the Ducatisti community by further extending the number of services offered to them. It also represents an opportunity to meet and make ourselves known to a new community of NFT enthusiasts, giving them the opportunity to live unique Ducati-style experiences and collect the digital assets that we will develop exclusively for this new dimension of the brand.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>XRPL Growth</h2>
<p>The development comes more than a year since the Bologna-based motorcycle manufacturer announced plans to embrace the sector and, interestingly, on the heels of Ripple&#8217;s partial <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/has-ripple-xrp-won-or-will-the-sec-appeal-what-will-happen-next/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">win</a> against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>In Q1, the San Francisco-based blockchain company <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q1-2023-xrp-markets-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">noted</a> that on-chain activity on XRPL remained strong, with transactions surging by 9% to 116 million, as compared to 106 million from the previous quarter. It further stated that &#8220;NFTs continue to drive activity,&#8221; and more than a  million assets have been minted on the Ledger since XLS-20 went live on the mainnet.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ducati-partners-with-ripple-founded-xrp-ledger-for-its-first-nft-collection/" rel="nofollow">Ducati Partners With Ripple-Founded XRP Ledger for its First NFT Collection</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainalysis and Deloitte Partner to Strengthen Blockchain Tracking, Compliance Capabilities</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chainalysis-and-deloitte-partner-to-strengthen-blockchain-tracking-compliance-capabilities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 22:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263026</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Deloitte-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Deloitte-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The collaboration will leverage Chainalysis' proprietary blockchain dataset and Deloitte's forensic and investigative services.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deloitte, a prominent member of the renowned &#8220;Big Four&#8221; accounting, consulting, and professional service firms, has joined forces with Chainalysis, a blockchain analytics company, this week. The newly formed strategic alliance aims to offer comprehensive solutions and services for digital asset data and analytics.</p>
<p>The collaboration will enable their shared clients to utilize Chainalysis&#8217; exclusive blockchain dataset and analytics software and training program, as well as Deloitte&#8217;s services to help customers manage forensic, investigative, and compliance programs.</p>
<h2>Chainalysis Deloitte Alliance</h2>
<p>The official <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/deloitte-and-chainalysis-alliance/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> stated that Chainalysis is set to collaborate closely with Deloitte&#8217;s blockchain and digital assets practice, encompassing various aspects such as cryptocurrency and digital asset risk management, analytics, investigation, anti-money laundering/know your customer (AML/KYC) processes and regulatory compliance.</p>
<p>Deloitte, on the other hand, will double down on expanding its practitioner pool trained and certified in Chainalysis products designed for blockchain analytics and investigations.</p>
<p>Commenting on the development, Chainalysis&#8217; President and Chief Revenue Officer Thomas Stanley, said</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For law enforcement agencies, regulators, and financial ecosystem players across the nation, the alliance offers new, collaborative solutions that help identify transformation gaps, accelerate mission success at enterprise scale, and mitigate risk while increasing revenue.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Deloitte’s Advisory Blockchain and Digital Asset practice lead and principal, Tim Davis, also weighed in on the collaboration and added that the move demonstrates the company&#8217;s investment in its digital asset innovation ecosystem for the benefit of its clients.</p>
<p>As part of its expansion in the Web3 space, Deloitte recently became one of the major enterprise partners to come to the Polkadot ecosystem after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polkadots-kilt-identity-blockchain-integrates-with-deloitte/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">teaming up</a> with a latter&#8217;s parachain project to improve digital identification protocols.</p>
<h2>Chainalysis&#8217; Range of Clients</h2>
<p>In recent years, Chainalysis has roped in several prominent players, including BNY Mellon and Barclays, payment providers, such as Worldpay and Square, as well as crypto exchanges and firms.</p>
<p>The New York-based company raised over $520 million in funding, with the last announced Series F round of $170 million in May 2022 led by BNY Mellon. The round catapulted Chainalysis&#8217; valuation to $8.6 billion. However, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainalysis-to-dismiss-48-employees-prepares-to-reorganize-structure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> laying off 48 of its 900 employees as part of a reorganization in February.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainalysis-and-deloitte-partner-to-strengthen-blockchain-tracking-compliance-capabilities/" rel="nofollow">Chainalysis and Deloitte Partner to Strengthen Blockchain Tracking, Compliance Capabilities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shibarium Beta Bridge Goes Live for Public Testing as Layer-2 Launch Inches Closer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-goes-live-for-public-testing-as-layer-2-launch-inches-closer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 19:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263132</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/shibainu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/shibainu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The launch of the Shibarium blockchain is slated for August. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst a lack of bullish cues in the market, SHIB rose by almost 6% over the past day, which pushed its monthly gains to nearly 12%.</p>
<p>The meme coin&#8217;s surge can be attributed to the Shibarium Beta Bridge, which went live for public testing this week. The move is part of an ambitious roadmap that seeks to transform the Shiba Inu project into a complete ecosystem.</p>
<ul>
<li>The team behind SHIB <a href="https://twitter.com/LucieSHIB/status/1684252125704880131" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> the release of the Shibarium Bridge beta version for public testing, which would allow users to transfer tokens between the two networks.</li>
<li>Initially, the bridge will enable users to transfer testnet ether tokens to the layer-2 network, with each transfer expected to take a maximum of up to 30 minutes.</li>
<li>The bridge is also compatible with the ERC-20 token standard and focuses on enhancing the scalability factor.</li>
<li>The development comes weeks after developer Shytoshi Kusama <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-pumps-after-lead-developer-shares-shibarium-update-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that Shibarium is slated to go live after a Toronto conference in August this year.</li>
<li>The updates regarding the much-anticipated layer-2 have sparked several minor <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-pumps-after-lead-developer-shares-shibarium-update-details/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">rallies</a>, but Shibarium code concerns <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-shib-tumbles-7-on-concerns-about-shibarium-code/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">dragged</a> SHIB&#8217;s value significantly in March.</li>
<li>Despite this, Shibarium has been touted to be crucial for the meme coin to place it among more serious contenders in the Web3 space. The addition of layer-2 specifically is aimed at increasing throughput, allowing the project to handle significant growth. A considerable boost in transaction speed could attract more users.</li>
<li>Shibarium will leverage four tokens, namely, BONE, TREAT, SHIB, and LEASH, for applications developed on top of the blockchain.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shibarium-beta-bridge-goes-live-for-public-testing-as-layer-2-launch-inches-closer/" rel="nofollow">Shibarium Beta Bridge Goes Live for Public Testing as Layer-2 Launch Inches Closer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tennessee Couple Faces CFTC Charges for &#8216;Blessings of God Thru Crypto&#8217; Scheme</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tennessee-couple-faces-cftc-charges-for-blessings-of-god-thru-crypto-scheme/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 16:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262590</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CFTC-1-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/CFTC-1-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The CFTC alleged that the Tennessee couple managed to persuade 100 individuals to entrust them with their money despite having no trading experience. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Tennessee couple was charged for operating a $6 million digital assets commodity pool scheme by the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) this week.</p>
<p>The United States derivatives market regulator charged the owners of a Clarksville real estate company, Michael and Amanda Griffis, for allegedly defrauding more than 100 people across the country. The couple was also accused of failing to register with the CFTC in connection with a multi-million dollar commodity pool scheme they operated between July 2022 and January 2023.</p>
<h2>&#8216;Blessings of God Thru Crypto&#8217; Fraud</h2>
<p>The CFTC&#8217;s complaint alleged that Michael and Amanda Griffis lured their colleagues and customers of their real estate business by offering them the opportunity to pool funds with others to trade digital asset commodity futures contracts.</p>
<p>The couple did not have any trading or other relevant experience but managed to convince over 100 individuals to send them more than $6 million to participate in a commodity pool called &#8220;Blessings of God Thru Crypto.&#8221;</p>
<p>As part of the scheme, the pool participants sent more than $4 million in funds to the &#8220;Apex Trading Platform.&#8221; However, the funds were instead quickly transferred to several digital wallets &#8220;outside the control&#8221; of the Griffises and are now &#8220;beyond recovery.&#8221; The couple also misappropriated nearly $1 million of pool funds to pay their debts and purchase various items, including expensive jewelry and an all-terrain vehicle.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the remainder of pool funds were misappropriated by the Griffises to issue Ponzi-like payments in an attempt to carry on the scheme for as long as possible.</p>
<h2>CFTC Statement</h2>
<p>In a statement, Director of Enforcement Ian McGinley said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As alleged, the defendants promised pool participants a safe investment in digital asset futures contracts with huge profit potential. The promises were underpinned by the trust the victims placed in the defendants. The defendants betrayed their pool participants, and they profited from that betrayal. Today’s filing reinforces the CFTC’s long-standing commitment to hold accountable those who take advantage of victims.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The CFTC has sought restitution to defrauded pool participants, civil monetary penalties, and permanent trading and registration bans. In its complaint, the agency also requested the imposition of a permanent injunction against further violations of the Commodity Exchange Act (CEA) and CFTC regulations.</p>
<p>The agency, however, warned that the victims may not be able to recover the lost funds because the defendants may not have sufficient assets.</p>
<p>Prior to this case, the CFTC had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-charges-man-for-defrauding-investors-of-21m-in-crypto-ponzi-scheme/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">charged</a> William Koo Ichioka for allegedly defrauding investors of $21 million by claiming to be a digital asset and foreign exchange (forex) trader a month ago.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tennessee-couple-faces-cftc-charges-for-blessings-of-god-thru-crypto-scheme/" rel="nofollow">Tennessee Couple Faces CFTC Charges for &#8216;Blessings of God Thru Crypto&#8217; Scheme</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>These US Politicians Criticized the SEC and Gensler for Their Crypto Approach</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/these-us-politicians-criticized-the-sec-and-gensler-for-their-crypto-approach/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 14:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262654</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/USAmerica.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/USAmerica.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Congressmen Patrick McHenry and Senator Cynthia Lummis are some of the people that scolded the SEC for its actions on the crypto scene. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its Chairman, Gary Gensler, have received a significant wave of criticism from numerous organizations and individuals (including some American politicians) for the way they have treated the cryptocurrency industry over the years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ripple&#8217;s recent court victory against the Commission prompted even more lawmakers to castigate the regulator. In the next lines, we will name some of the most vocal opponents of the SEC and their reasons.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Lengthy List of Politicians</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">United States Representative Warren Davidson was among the first to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rep-davidson-declares-war-on-sec-boss-gary-gensler-over-long-series-of-abuses/" data-wpel-link="internal">display</a> his dissatisfaction with Gary Gensler&#8217;s anti-crypto campaign this year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmaker raised his concerns after the SEC announced new rules that could &#8220;modernize&#8221; the concept of an &#8220;exchange&#8221; so it could be more closely referred to as a system that &#8220;brings together buyers and sellers of securities that offer the use of non-firm trading interest and provide another type of non-discretionary method.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Davidson </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> this proposal is another example of the agency&#8217;s &#8220;long series of abuses&#8221; toward the cryptocurrency sector. He went further, introducing legislation that could remove the current Chair of the SEC from his post.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from applying enhanced supervision on digital asset exchanges, the watchdog </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> lawsuits against two of the behemoths in the industry &#8211; Binance and Coinbase. It insisted they had violated certain rules and offered trading services with alleged unregistered securities, such as BNB, BUSD, ADA, SOL, MATIC, and more.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senator Cynthia Lummis (a keen proponent of bitcoin and even a HODLer) was quick to react to that move. She </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/SenLummis/status/1666181240167317507?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">believes</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the SEC had failed to provide &#8220;a path&#8221; for crypto marketplaces and did not offer &#8220;adequate legal guidance on what differentiates a security from a commodity.&#8221; She also scolded the agency for the lack of comprehensive crypto rules in the USA, which could push the industry offshore or &#8220;into the shadows.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC was involved in the cryptocurrency space again in mid-June when multiple finance giants, including BlackRock, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> with it to release a spot BTC ETF in the States. The Commission was initially unsupportive of the idea of such monetary products, calling the applications &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US Congressman Patrick McHenry </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/PatrickMcHenry/status/1674876179344392195" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">opposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the SEC&#8217;s vision, maintaining that the only reason Gensler would be against spot BTC ETFs is &#8220;if he wants to kill crypto&#8221; in America. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Effect of Ripple&#8217;s Victory</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One groundbreaking event for the entire cryptocurrency field was Ripple&#8217;s recent court win against the SEC. A US judge </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ruled</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in favor of the enterprise blockchain provider in mid-July, stating that most XRP sales do not constitute securities transactions. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulator filed its lawsuit against Ripple more than three years ago, alleging the entity&#8217;s native token should be treated as a security, similar to bonds or stocks, and therefore it should become subject to SEC regulation. Interestingly, Gensler has claimed over the past few years that the only digital currency with the status of a commodity is bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Representative Ritchie Torres wrote a letter a few days after Ripple&#8217;s landmark victory, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/digital-assets/2023/07/18/nys-torres-asks-if-sec-will-ease-up-on-cryptocurrencies/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claiming</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the SEC (under the rule of Chair Gensler) has failed to issue &#8220;a single rule on crypto assets, nor has it given any clear guidance.&#8221; He also asked whether the watchdog will end its war on the industry following its court loss.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senator Lummis was once again vocal on the topic, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/SenLummis/status/1683845466306252801" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">opining</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the outcome of the Ripple vs. SEC legal battle has &#8220;reinforced the need for Congress to create a regulatory structure for crypto assets.&#8221; She pointed out the bill, introduced by her and Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, which aims to categorize most digital currencies as commodities (or in the same bracket as gold, silver, oil, and natural gas).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Last but not least, US Representative Dusty Johnson </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://thehill.com/opinion/congress-blog/4117714-the-ripple-effect-a-new-wave-in-digital-asset-regulation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">argued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in a recent statement that Gensler&#8217;s &#8220;consistent efforts to project an air of certainty&#8221; in the crypto sector and outline that almost every digital asset is a security were put to the test by the result of the case against Ripple. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmaker believes the court ruling was a double-edged sword since it damaged Gensler&#8217;s approach to the industry and created even bigger confusion. He concluded that the only solution to that problem is the implementation of crypto legislation coming from Congress. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-us-politicians-criticized-the-sec-and-gensler-for-their-crypto-approach/" rel="nofollow">These US Politicians Criticized the SEC and Gensler for Their Crypto Approach</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
