<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>New Coin Listing PepeHub Explodes 35,000% on Uniswap - PEHUB Top Crypto Gainer on DEXTools</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-pepehub-explodes-on-uniswap-pehub-top-crypto-gainer-on-dextools.htm</link><description>PepeHub (PEHUB), has exploded onto the top crypto gainers list on DEXTools - is it legit though? &lt;br /&gt;
Within just five hourly candles, $PEHUB pumped over 35,000% and is the top daily gainer, with $CENA and $AK in the #2 and #3 spot. &lt;br /&gt;
Pepe2.0 (PEPE2.0) is also up 70% in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
This new crypto asset is not yet listed on CoinMarketCap, and the only PepeHub social media account is for a separate project on the Binance Smart Chain - @PepehubBSC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-pepehub-explodes-on-uniswap-pehub-top-crypto-gainer-on-dextools.htm"&gt;Read More: New Coin Listing PepeHub Explodes 35,000% on Uniswap - PEHUB Top Crypto Gainer on DEXTools&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-coin-listing-pepehub-explodes-on-uniswap-pehub-top-crypto-gainer-on-dextools.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118503/315855/pepehub-pehub-dextools-to.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="583780"/></item><item><title>Jinan, China: All Our Buses Accept Digital Yuan – And CBDC Customers Get Discounts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jinan-china-all-our-buses-accept-digital-yuan-cbdc-customers-get-discounts.htm</link><description>Jinan, China, says all of its bus routes now accept digital yuan pay, and will incentivize adoption by granting discounts to central bank digital currency (CBDC)-paying passengers. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the news outlet Shunwang-Jinan Daily (via e23), the city said that all of its bus routes’ software and card readers had been updated to allow all buses to accept payments in the Chinese CBDC. &lt;br /&gt;
Jinan is the capital of Shandong, a province in Eastern China, and has a population of over 9.2 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jinan-china-all-our-buses-accept-digital-yuan-cbdc-customers-get-discounts.htm"&gt;Read More: Jinan, China: All Our Buses Accept Digital Yuan – And CBDC Customers Get Discounts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jinan-china-all-our-buses-accept-digital-yuan-cbdc-customers-get-discounts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118490/315812/adobestock-291422836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="795157"/></item><item><title>Hong Kong Government Sets Up Web3 Development Task Force – Next Crypto Hub?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-government-sets-up-web3-development-task-force-next-crypto-hub.htm</link><description>Hong Kong has taken another major step towards becoming a leading hub for cryptocurrency and blockchain technology.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Hong Kong Government has announced the establishment of a task force, known as the Web3 Development Task Force, dedicated to promoting the growth of Web3, with a particular focus on ethical development, according to a recent statement....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-government-sets-up-web3-development-task-force-next-crypto-hub.htm"&gt;Read More: Hong Kong Government Sets Up Web3 Development Task Force – Next Crypto Hub?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Web3</category><category>Web3. Adoption</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-government-sets-up-web3-development-task-force-next-crypto-hub.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118486/315808/flag-gc00cbe5c3-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="298111"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin SV Price Prediction as $400 Million Trading Volume Pushes BSV Up 30% – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-pushes-bsv-up-30-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>Bitcoin SV has experienced a surge in price, with a remarkable 30% increase fueled by a trading volume of $400 million. This significant boost has led to speculation about the involvement of large investors, commonly known as whales, in the market. &lt;br /&gt;
Today's live Bitcoin SV price is $49.39, with a 24-hour trading volume of $2.4 million. Over the past 24 hours, Bitcoin SV has shown a slight gain of less than 0.25%. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-pushes-bsv-up-30-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin SV Price Prediction as $400 Million Trading Volume Pushes BSV Up 30% – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-sv-price-prediction-as-400-million-trading-volume-pushes-bsv-up-30-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118484/315775/bsv.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="266743"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Kraken Ordered to Submit User Transaction Data to IRS – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-kraken-ordered-submit-user-transaction-data-irs-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Kraken has been ordered by a judge to submit a vast amount of user information to the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) for an investigation into potential tax evasion.  &lt;br /&gt;
The United States District Court for the Northern District of California issued the order on Friday, stating that Kraken must provide account and transaction details to the IRS to determine whether any users have underreported their taxes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-kraken-ordered-submit-user-transaction-data-irs-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Kraken Ordered to Submit User Transaction Data to IRS – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Kraken</category><category>IRS</category><category>Tax</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-kraken-ordered-submit-user-transaction-data-irs-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118480/315764/11-media-library-original.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="66218"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Shoots Past $30,000 Resistance Level – How High Can BTC Go This Week?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-shoots-past-30000-resistance-level-how-high-can-btc-go-week.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price currently stands at $30,558, experiencing a slight drop of nearly 0.50% on Sunday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The recent rejection of Bitcoin spot-price ETF applications by the US SEC surprised bullish investors hoping to maintain Bitcoin's price above $31,000. &lt;br /&gt;
In other news, Cboe has resubmitted Spot Bitcoin ETFs in partnership with Coinbase, although the SEC remains cautious.  &lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, FTX's successful recovery of billions in assets has positively impacted Bitcoin prices....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-shoots-past-30000-resistance-level-how-high-can-btc-go-week.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Shoots Past $30,000 Resistance Level – How High Can BTC Go This Week?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-shoots-past-30000-resistance-level-how-high-can-btc-go-week.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118476/315763/2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="523907"/></item><item><title>Bank of America Forecasts Transformative Role of Tokenization in Finance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-forecasts-transformative-role-of-tokenization-finance.htm</link><description>According to a recent research report by Bank of America (BofA), tokenization can revolutionize financial and non-financial infrastructure and financial markets in the next five to 15 years.  &lt;br /&gt;
The report highlights the transformative power of tokenization and its wide-ranging implications for various sectors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-forecasts-transformative-role-of-tokenization-finance.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of America Forecasts Transformative Role of Tokenization in Finance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-forecasts-transformative-role-of-tokenization-finance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118372/315497/pexels-joel-de-la-cruz-53.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="339432"/></item><item><title>Six Clovers Unveils Versal Network for Cross-Border Crypto Payments in Stablecoins and CBDCs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/six-clovers-unveils-versal-network-for-cross-border-crypto-payments-in-stablecoins-and-cbdcs.htm</link><description>On June 29, Six Clovers, a company founded by former PayPal business and technology leaders Jim Nguyen and Nas Kavian, introduced the Versal Network on Sui blockchain.  &lt;br /&gt;
This decentralized global payments network aims to streamline cross-border transactions for businesses worldwide. By utilizing Six Clovers' crypto payment systems, users can now conduct digital currency transactions on a global scale....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/six-clovers-unveils-versal-network-for-cross-border-crypto-payments-in-stablecoins-and-cbdcs.htm"&gt;Read More: Six Clovers Unveils Versal Network for Cross-Border Crypto Payments in Stablecoins and CBDCs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>PayPal</category><category>SUI</category><category>Versal Network</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/six-clovers-unveils-versal-network-for-cross-border-crypto-payments-in-stablecoins-and-cbdcs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118409/315604/pexels-alesia-kozik-6770774-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="265186"/></item><item><title>Logan Paul Under Fire: CryptoZoo NFT Buyers Still Waiting for Refunds Six Months Later</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-under-fire-cryptozoo-nft-buyers-still-waiting-for-refunds-six-months-later.htm</link><description>Popular YouTuber and influencer Logan Paul has come under fire yet again after he failed to refund CryptoZoo NFT buyers six months after promising to do so.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent YouTube video, crypto journalist and online detective Stephen Findeisen, better known as Coffeezilla, said Paul has not paid back the victims of his "scam" project CryptoZoo so far. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-under-fire-cryptozoo-nft-buyers-still-waiting-for-refunds-six-months-later.htm"&gt;Read More: Logan Paul Under Fire: CryptoZoo NFT Buyers Still Waiting for Refunds Six Months Later&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Logan Paul</category><category>CryptoZoo</category><category>Coffeezilla</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/logan-paul-under-fire-cryptozoo-nft-buyers-still-waiting-for-refunds-six-months-later.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118463/315731/logan-paul-documentary.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1999961"/></item><item><title>MEME Token Pumps Up 20,000% on DEXTools But Experts Say It’s a Scam and Prefer These New Coins Instead - Here’s Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-token-pumps-up-20000-on-dextools-but-experts-say-its-a-scam-and-prefer-these-new-coins-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>A newly-listed crypto project, MEME token, took the crypto space by storm after it clocked over 20,000% in 24 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;
While this would seem like a profitable trade to enter, many crypto experts believe it might be a honeypot scam due to its irregular chart pattern.  &lt;br /&gt;
The project also scored poorly in the community votes on DEXTools, which raises doubts about its authenticity. &lt;br /&gt;
Nonetheless, not all nascent crypto projects fall under this ignominious light....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-token-pumps-up-20000-on-dextools-but-experts-say-its-a-scam-and-prefer-these-new-coins-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: MEME Token Pumps Up 20,000% on DEXTools But Experts Say It’s a Scam and Prefer These New Coins Instead - Here’s Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/meme-token-pumps-up-20000-on-dextools-but-experts-say-its-a-scam-and-prefer-these-new-coins-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118462/315732/meme-token.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="815317"/></item><item><title>Celsius Debtors Can Start Converting Altcoins to Bitcoin and Ether Starting Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-debtors-can-start-converting-altcoins-bitcoin-ether-starting-today.htm</link><description>The United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York has allowed Celsius debtors to trade their altcoins for Bitcoin and Ether starting today.  &lt;br /&gt;
The order issued by the bankruptcy judge Martin Glenn on 30th June will also help the distribution of the funds to creditors in the near future. &lt;br /&gt;
The proposal to sell and trade cryptocurrencies was approved after the discussion with Celsius and the US SEC. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-debtors-can-start-converting-altcoins-bitcoin-ether-starting-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Celsius Debtors Can Start Converting Altcoins to Bitcoin and Ether Starting Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-debtors-can-start-converting-altcoins-bitcoin-ether-starting-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118461/315740/celsius-altcoin-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96929"/></item><item><title>FTX (Re)Turns, BTC (Not)Moneyz, ETF (Un)Coming and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/ftx-returns-btc-notmoneyz-etf-uncoming-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/ftx-returns-btc-notmoneyz-etf-uncoming-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX (Re)Turns, BTC (Not)Moneyz, ETF (Un)Coming and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/ftx-returns-btc-notmoneyz-etf-uncoming-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118251/315404/coingape-tv-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="277758"/></item><item><title>Luxury Fashion House Dior Embraces Ethereum for New Line of Men's Sneakers</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/luxury-fashion-house-dior-embraces-ethereum-for-new-line-of-mens-sneakers.htm</link><description>Luxury fashion house Dior has unveiled a new line of men's sneakers that leverages the Ethereum blockchain to offer a matching non-fungible token (NFT). &lt;br /&gt;
The sneakers, called the B33, are part of Dior's Men's Fall 2023 collection and were designed by Dior Menswear artistic director Kim Jones, the company said in a Friday tweet. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/luxury-fashion-house-dior-embraces-ethereum-for-new-line-of-mens-sneakers.htm"&gt;Read More: Luxury Fashion House Dior Embraces Ethereum for New Line of Men's Sneakers&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Luxury</category><category>Dior</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/luxury-fashion-house-dior-embraces-ethereum-for-new-line-of-mens-sneakers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118456/315715/85baed3841d92eb66ce43d6cf.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1978638"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction Turns Bullish as $20 Billion Trading Volume Sends BTC Above $30,000 – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-turns-bullish-as-20-billion-trading-volume-sends-btc-above-30000-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin has experienced a bullish turnaround, propelled by a substantial trading volume of $20 billion, which has pushed BTC above the $30,000 mark.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, amidst the bullish surge in Bitcoin's price, the cryptocurrency faces some pressure following the recent announcement by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) stating that spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) filings are inadequate....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-turns-bullish-as-20-billion-trading-volume-sends-btc-above-30000-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction Turns Bullish as $20 Billion Trading Volume Sends BTC Above $30,000 – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 07:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-turns-bullish-as-20-billion-trading-volume-sends-btc-above-30000-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118451/315722/1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="522507"/></item><item><title>Tether Strikes Partnership Deal with Georgia Government</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-strikes-partnership-deal-with-georgia-government.htm</link><description>Tether, the firm behind the USDT coin, says it has struck a partnership deal with government of Georgia. &lt;br /&gt;
Per an official Tether release and a report from Forklog, the firm has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) deal with the nation’s government. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm will initially create a fund that provides investment and grants to Georgian startups working in the blockchain technology field....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-strikes-partnership-deal-with-georgia-government.htm"&gt;Read More: Tether Strikes Partnership Deal with Georgia Government&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Georgia</category><category>Tether</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 23:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-strikes-partnership-deal-with-georgia-government.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118350/315444/georgia-3006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="890131"/></item><item><title>UK’s New Financial Law to Regulate Crypto, Includes Provisions for 'Crypto Hub'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uks-new-financial-law-regulate-crypto-includes-provisions-for-crypto-hub.htm</link><description>The United Kingdom on Thursday officially passed legislation to regulate cryptocurrencies and stablecoins as part of its broader financial regulatory reforms post-Brexit. &lt;br /&gt;
The new law, dubbed the Financial Services and Markets bill, will grant regulators the authority to establish a tailored framework for the digital asset sector, supporting crypto’s “safe adoption in the UK,” a press release from the UK Treasury said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uks-new-financial-law-regulate-crypto-includes-provisions-for-crypto-hub.htm"&gt;Read More: UK’s New Financial Law to Regulate Crypto, Includes Provisions for 'Crypto Hub'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>UK</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uks-new-financial-law-regulate-crypto-includes-provisions-for-crypto-hub.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118421/315668/uk.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="120175"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 30 June – Bitcoin Cash, Synthetix Network, Pepe</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-june-bitcoin-cash-synthetix-network-pepe.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency markets are mixed on Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether (ETH) is up over 4% and rallying into the mid-$1,900s and bitcoin alternatives like Litecoin, Bitcoin SV, Zcash and eCash have all been pumping. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin, meanwhile, was last trading in the $30,400s, having been knocked off its prior perch above $31,000 on a WSJ report that the SEC has told spot bitcoin ETF applicants that their filings are currently insufficient....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-june-bitcoin-cash-synthetix-network-pepe.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 30 June – Bitcoin Cash, Synthetix Network, Pepe&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ether</category><category>Bitcoin Cash</category><category>BCH</category><category>Pepe</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-30-june-bitcoin-cash-synthetix-network-pepe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118429/315685/bc30.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="323639"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as DOGE Pumps Up 4% – Where Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-pumps-up-4-where-next.htm</link><description>Dogecoin (DOGE) has pumped up a little over 4% on Friday, with the world’s most popular meme coin last trading close to $0.066. &lt;br /&gt;
That means DOGE has managed to recover back above its 21-Day Moving Average at $0.0635. &lt;br /&gt;
The Friday recovery comes as crypto markets shrug off reports that the SEC has told spot bitcoin ETF applicants that their filings are inadequate, with a helping hand from a downside surprise from the latest US PCE inflation report....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-pumps-up-4-where-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as DOGE Pumps Up 4% – Where Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-pumps-up-4-where-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118427/315683/doge1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="693658"/></item><item><title>Americans Want Regulated Spot Bitcoin ETFs, Says Coinbase's Chief Legal Officer</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/americans-want-regulated-spot-bitcoin-etfs-says-coinbases-chief-legal-officer.htm</link><description>The American people want access to more safe and regulated crypto-based investment products, and the market is now responding to this, Coinbase’s chief legal officer Paul Grewal has stated....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/americans-want-regulated-spot-bitcoin-etfs-says-coinbases-chief-legal-officer.htm"&gt;Read More: Americans Want Regulated Spot Bitcoin ETFs, Says Coinbase's Chief Legal Officer&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/americans-want-regulated-spot-bitcoin-etfs-says-coinbases-chief-legal-officer.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118415/315605/etf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="64317"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Where is the Next BTC Target as $25 Billion in Trading Volumes Flood In?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-where-next-btc-target-as-25-billion-trading-volumes-flood-in.htm</link><description>Bitcoin saw a spike in trading volumes on Friday, which have exceeded $25 billion in the past 24 hours as per CoinGecko. &lt;br /&gt;
The spike in trading activity came as Bitcoin dipped back to test the $30,000 level from above $31,000 on a WSJ report that the SEC had informed spot bitcoin ETF applicants that their filings were insufficient....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-where-next-btc-target-as-25-billion-trading-volumes-flood-in.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Where is the Next BTC Target as $25 Billion in Trading Volumes Flood In?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-where-next-btc-target-as-25-billion-trading-volumes-flood-in.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118426/315679/btc-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="671078"/></item></channel></rss>
