<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 23:49:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Metaverse Will Influence Travel Decisions in 2023, BookingCom Predicts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-metaverse-will-influence-travel-decisions-in-2023-bookingcom-predicts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 22:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229242</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/img1_metaverse.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/img1_metaverse.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In the near future, people will travel a lot. But first, they will visit their destinations in the metaverse.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The extended COVID-19 lockdown changed the travel industry —and the lifestyle of millions of people. But now that the pandemic seems to be under control, businesses are looking to rise from the ashes with new ideas to engage customers, and the metaverse seems like an exciting topic to explore.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.booking.com/articles/travelpredictions2023.htmlen-2023-2335269" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">survey</a> conducted by the popular traveling portal Booking.com to more than 24,000 people in 32 countries, a considerable number of users responded that the metaverse could help them define their travel destination.</p>
<h2>Next Vacation Destination: The Metaverse</h2>
<p>The survey shows a significant interest among travelers in virtually experiencing destinations while choosing a place to spend their vacation. Of all of them, the most inclined to experience virtual trips in the metaverse are those from Generation Z (45%) and Millennials (43%). More than half of the respondents claimed that virtual reality is a viable tool when choosing a good travel destination.</p>
<p>Booking.com also says that 4,574 respondents were willing to travel to new places only upon having experienced them in the metaverse. Also, 35% of respondents are willing to spend several days in the metaverse to get a perspective on the environment and places that might catch their attention.</p>
<p>According to Booking.com, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/virtual-reality-experience-in-your-palm-special-interview-with-rapid-growing-sensorium-platform/" data-wpel-link="internal">virtual reality</a> and blockchain technologies will allow users to experience anything from a sunny beach to the desert without being physically on-site. However, 60% of respondents still believe that the experience offered by the metaverse and other virtual technologies does not compare to actually being there in person.</p>
<h2>The Future of the Internet</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-metaverse-is-still-popular-despite-bear-market-dappradar/" data-wpel-link="internal">metaverse</a> is a concept created to describe a persistent online 3D universe that combines multiple virtual spaces. It is like a futuristic vision of the Internet where users work, meet, play, and socialize together in an alternate reality.</p>
<p>Video games offer the closest metaverse experience there is; the developers have pushed the boundaries of what a game is by organizing in-game events and designing virtual economies. With that in mind, the metaverse is a virtual environment that attempts to replicate the real world on a digital foundation.</p>
<p>Some companies, like Microsoft and Meta, are working on their own virtual worlds, or &#8220;metaverses.&#8221; But other projects, like The Sandbox and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/decentraland-guide-and-review/" data-wpel-link="internal">Decentraland</a>, are using the decentralized technology of blockchain to build metaverses that offer more privacy, openness, and depth. These initiatives have the backing of many fans who believe in their values and are willing to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-unveils-2b-metaverse-fund/" data-wpel-link="internal">financially support</a> them.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-metaverse-will-influence-travel-decisions-in-2023-bookingcom-predicts/" rel="nofollow">The Metaverse Will Influence Travel Decisions in 2023, BookingCom Predicts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>a16z Leads $100M Funding Round For Web3 Privacy Layer Aztec Network</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/a16z-leads-100m-funding-round-for-web3-privacy-layer-aztec-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 20:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229072</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aztec_network_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/aztec_network_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The company plans to hire more engineers despite the intense bear market.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The company plans to hire more engineers despite the intense bear market.</p>
<p>Aztec Network &#8211; a privacy layer 2 chain for Web3 &#8211; <a href="https://medium.com/@aztecnetwork/aztec-raises-100-million-to-build-encrypted-ethereum-dd5062ba949c" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> raising $100 million in a Series B financing led by VC giant Andreessen Horowitz (a16z). The funding round also saw participation from A Capital, King River, Variant, SV Angel, Hash Key, Fenbushi, and AVG.5.</p>
<ul>
<li>Its partnership with a16z will fund the development of a &#8220;next-generation encrypted architecture&#8221; that would enable users to verify that blockchain rules were followed correctly without revealing any underlying information.</li>
<li>The main focus of these encrypted blockchains is to allow privacy and anonymity with respect to transaction execution.</li>
<li>Following the development, Aztec CEO Zac Williamson stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;What we’re building is a revolutionary piece of technology that transforms how we interact with each other online, in which the end user is the customer, rather than the product. End-to-end encrypted blockchains protect individuals, obviating the need for centralized financial systems.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Aztec Network rolled out Aztec Connect, which happens to be an ecosystem that integrates with Ethereum decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols such as Aave, Lido, and Element Finance, last summer.</li>
<li>Going forward, the company plans on integrating with Compound and five other DeFi protocols.</li>
<li>Aztec is also planning to deploy a new Ethereum-secured public-private execution layer that will facilitate the seamless interplay of encrypted and unencrypted applications on its blockchain.</li>
<li>The new capital infusion will be used to onboard more engineers across the world to build the network across Noir tooling, SDK development, P2P network construction, data science, crypto, and full-stack engineering.</li>
<li>Over the past year, the Aztec team has expanded to nearly 40 from seven employees, and expects the figure to double in the near term.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a16z-leads-100m-funding-round-for-web3-privacy-layer-aztec-network/" rel="nofollow">a16z Leads $100M Funding Round For Web3 Privacy Layer Aztec Network</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Distressed Crypto Platform Amber Group Secures a $300 Million Fundraiser</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/distressed-crypto-platform-amber-group-secures-a-300-million-fundraiser/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 17:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229045</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/AMBER.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/AMBER.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The funds will reach clients affected by the FTX crash, Amber Group outlined.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group &#8211; a cryptocurrency platform backed by Singapore&#8217;s investment company Temasek &#8211; completed a $300 million funding round. The money will be distributed to clients affected by the FTX collapse. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company, which had to cope with severe issues due to the ongoing bear market, recently acquired the Singaporean exchange &#8211; Sparrow Holdings.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Trying to Reimburse Victims</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/ambergroup_io/status/1603608618216984576?s=20&amp;t=gJrDgoaJyaLP1vekUoEszA" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on Twitter, the Series C fundraiser was led by Fenbushi Capital US. Amber Group said the move shows &#8220;investor confidence&#8221; in the firm&#8217;s operations and commitment to cooperate with the platform despite its recent issues. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;As part of that future, it&#8217;s important for us to adapt and protect our clients in this challenging market environment,&#8221; the platform stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As previously revealed, Amber Group did not have exposure to FTX or Alameda Research. On the other hand, it has been an &#8220;active trading participant&#8221; in the bankrupt trading venue. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The funds from the latest funding round will reach those clients who lost money on the platform&#8217;s products due to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX meltdown</a>.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/amber-group-slows-down-expansion-plans-on-bear-market-worries-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">aimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to secure another $100 million fundraiser earlier this month but completed only half of the planned amount, citing the negative effects of the crypto winter.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the organization had over 1,000 employees a few months ago, it had to trim the size of its team as a cost-cutting measure. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/downturn-effects-amber-groups-workforce-to-see-5-10-reduction-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">laid off</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> around 10% of its headcount in September and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-07/crypto-firm-amber-cuts-staff-pauses-fundraising-in-ftx-fallout?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&amp;utm_content=crypto#xj4y7vzkg&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">continued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the dismissal spree in December. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, Amber Group had to enforce salary reductions and terminated some of its partnerships, such as the one with the popular British soccer team &#8211; Chelsea FC. CEO Michael Wu further hinted that the collaboration with Atletico de Madrid might also cease as the entity is &#8220;reducing all marketing efforts.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The unexpected death of Amber Group&#8217;s Co-Founder &#8211; Tiantian Kullander &#8211; was another shocking event for the organization. The Hong Kong businessman, known as &#8220;TT,&#8221; mysteriously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-recent-wave-of-mysterious-deaths-in-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">passed away</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in his sleep, aged just 30.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Latest Acquisition</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group recently <a href="https://www.finews.asia/finance/38237-amber-group-acquires-singapore-s-crypto-exchange" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">purchased</a> the Singaporean cryptocurrency exchange Sparrow Holdings. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latter obtained a payment institutions license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore in August and offers a variety of digital asset products and solutions to customers. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/distressed-crypto-platform-amber-group-secures-a-300-million-fundraiser/" rel="nofollow">Distressed Crypto Platform Amber Group Secures a $300 Million Fundraiser</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FC Barcelona and Crypto Exchange WhiteBIT Shake Hands on a Global Partnership Deal</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fc-barcelona-and-crypto-exchange-whitebit-shake-hands-on-a-global-partnership-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 14:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228526</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Barcelona.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Barcelona.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[WhiteBIT will serve as FC Barcelona's Official Cryptocurrency Exchange partner until June 30, 2025.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the most successful soccer clubs in Europe &#8211; FC Barcelona &#8211; inked an agreement with the cryptocurrency platform WhiteBIT.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Тhe trading venue will serve as the Official Cryptocurrency Exchange partner of the team until June 2025.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Barca&#8217;s Next Crypto Step</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In an official <a href="https://www.fcbarcelona.com/en/club/news/2982159/fc-barcelona-and-whitebit-sign-a-new-global-partnership-agreement" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement</a> on its website, the soccer giant claimed that the partnership with WhiteBIT will underpin its commercial strategy and consolidate its &#8220;international expansion&#8221; by remaining a &#8220;benchmark both on and off the pitch.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">WhiteBIT and FC Barcelona intend to offer a variety of online and offline activities to bring together crypto participants and soccer fans. The exchange will also collaborate with Barcelona&#8217;s handball, basketball, roller hockey, and futsal teams.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Spanish club revealed that another main target of the initiative is to raise awareness about cryptocurrencies and their merits to the sports community, adding that WhiteBIT&#8217;s logo will be visible on the legendary Camp Nou stadium during match days.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Commenting on the matter was Juli Guiu &#8211; FC Barcelona Vice president of the Marketing area:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are pleased to announce this new partnership, another example of the Club&#8217;s commitment to innovation. Additionally, this is a partnership that will help us to continue growing and developing our global commercial expansion strategy, strengthening the Club further while remaining a benchmark in an increasingly competitive field&#8221;.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Volodymyr Nosov &#8211; CEO of WhiteBIT &#8211; described the collaboration between his entity and FC Barcelona as a &#8220;significant step for the community as a whole.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We dream, and we dream big, hence we&#8217;re sure that our cooperation will bring a new experience of using cryptocurrencies, their accessibility, and comprehensibility for everyone. From the very first days, we have been inspired to bring the future closer and set a new level of integration of crypto solutions into our lives,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Barcelona&#8217;s Previous Crypto Efforts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Catalan soccer club </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/fc-barcelona-partners-with-chilliz-to-launch-a-cryptocurrency-for-their-fans/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">jumped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on the bandwagon in 2020 by joining forces with the crypto project Chilliz. The partnership aimed to introduce a specific token, ticked BAR.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Barca doubled down on its endeavors last November by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/fc-barcelona-to-launch-iconic-historical-moments-as-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">signing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a global partnership with the NFT marketplace Ownix. Both parties vowed to release digital collectibles representing iconic events from the team&#8217;s history, like displaying the record 75 trophies it won in Spain and the 5 UEFA Champions League titles.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A few weeks later, though, Barca </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.timesofisrael.com/fc-barcelona-drops-deal-with-crypto-firm-linked-to-arrested-beitar-owner-hogeg/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">terminated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its agreement with Ownix as one of the latter&#8217;s consultants &#8211; Moshe Hogeg &#8211; was arrested for several offenses, such as fraud and sexual assault.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Surprisingly, the club </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/soccer-giants-barcelona-and-real-madrid-team-up-on-a-metaverse-trademark/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shook hands</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with its biggest rival &#8211; Real Madrid &#8211; earlier this year, filing for a joint Metaverse trademark application. The soccer colossuses sought to offer NFTs, virtual clothing, cryptographic software for managing cryptocurrency transactions, and downloadable software for using as an e-wallet.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fc-barcelona-and-crypto-exchange-whitebit-shake-hands-on-a-global-partnership-deal/" rel="nofollow">FC Barcelona and Crypto Exchange WhiteBIT Shake Hands on a Global Partnership Deal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>60% of Americans Believe Crypto Investing is Highly Risky (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/60-of-americans-believe-crypto-investing-is-highly-risky-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 11:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228550</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/bitcoin_retail_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/bitcoin_retail_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Just 5% of the US respondents think there are no risks when investing in digital currencies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;Your Money Survey&#8221; estimated that 60% of the American participants consider the risk of investing in cryptocurrencies to be high.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Just 5% of the respondents believe it is entirely safe to allocate some wealth to the asset class.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Looks Riskier to Americans</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decline of the cryptocurrency market, as well as the various adverse events in the sector, have had an impact on the sentiment among many Americans. CNBC&#8217;s latest </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.momentive.ai/en/blog/cnbc-your-money-nov-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">research</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> found out that 60% of the US respondents think of crypto investing as highly risky, while this figure was 45% in August 2021.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">26% think delving into bitcoin and alternative coins hides a &#8220;moderate&#8221; risk, while only 5% consider it to be totally safe.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cryptocurrency investors have also lost some of their confidence, with 60% claiming there&#8217;s a real chance of severe losses when dealing with the asset class. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">10% of the research&#8217;s participants revealed they are HODLers. Millennials are the most active demographic group, with 15% of them holding some crypto. Generation Z and Generation X follow closely with 12% each.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Youngsters Diversify With Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bank of America (BoA) also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/75-of-young-us-investors-want-to-diversify-portfolios-with-crypto-boa-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">conducted</a> a survey which showed that 75% of US residents aged between 21 and 42 think it is impossible to achieve above-average returns relying only on traditional finance. In their view, diversifying with alternative assets, such as cryptocurrencies, real estate, private equity, and commodities, could generate better future profits.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another CNBC survey from 2021 disclosed that Millennial millionaires had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-millennials-have-a-large-chunk-of-their-wealth-in-crypto-cnbc-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">invested</a> at least 25% of their funds in digital assets.</span></p>
<p>When bitcoin was charting its all-time high in November 2021, young Americans were even willing to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-millennials-and-generation-z-prefer-to-get-parts-of-their-salaries-in-bitcoin-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">receive</a> some of their salaries in crypto instead of fiat currencies. <span data-preserver-spaces="true">Generation Z (those not older than 23) were most supportive, with 50% wishing for that option.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/60-of-americans-believe-crypto-investing-is-highly-risky-survey/" rel="nofollow">60% of Americans Believe Crypto Investing is Highly Risky (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Bloodbath: Bitcoin Plummets Below $17K, BNB Crashes 7% (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-bloodbath-bitcoin-plummets-below-17k-bnb-crashes-7-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 09:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BNBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229210</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency markets took a beating in the past 24 hours, with BTC losing $17K and BNB crashing by around 10%.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past 24 hours have been tough in the cryptocurrency markets, with the total capitalization dropping by some $40 billion. This comes on the back of major coins charting serious declines and BTC plummeting below $17K.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Goes Below $17K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price took a serious beating over the past couple of days, losing about 9% of its value since hitting $18,300 earlier in the week. For the past 24 hours alone, the cryptocurrency is down by almost 3%, training at around $16,700 at the time of this writing.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229211" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229211" style="width: 1912px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-229211" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_171201" width="1912" height="868" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201.jpg 1912w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201-1024x465.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201-768x349.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201-1536x697.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_171201-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1912px) 100vw, 1912px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229211" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance via TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that Bitcoin dominance &#8211; used as a primary means of gauging its share relative to that of the entire market &#8211; is increasing. This means that altcoins are having it worst than BTC during this period.</p>
<p>In any case, it&#8217;s important to see if BTC will be able to reclaim the coveted $17K level or if there&#8217;s more pain to come in the following days.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Bleeding Hard</h2>
<p>Practically all major altcoins are trading well in the red throughout the past day, with few exceptions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_229212" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-229212" style="width: 1857px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-229212" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201" width="1857" height="792" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201.jpg 1857w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201-300x128.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201-1024x437.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201-768x328.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201-1536x655.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_171201-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1857px) 100vw, 1857px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-229212" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>As seen above, ETH is down almost 3%, but a lot of the other altcoins are down a lot more. For instance, BNB is trading at a 7% decline, having recovered a bit &#8211; its price crashed by more than 10% earlier. DOGE is down over 5%, ADA &#8211; almost 7%, MATIC &#8211; 4.5%, and so forth.</p>
<p>With that said, there are also some exceptions. For example, Toncoin (TON) is up 7.5% in the past day, which contributes to gains of 33.7% in the past week.</p>
<p>On the other end of the spectrum, there&#8217;s Filecoin&#8217;s FIL, which is down a whopping 20%, making it the worst performer in the past 24 hours. It&#8217;s followed closely by Trust Wallet (TWT), which is down by 19%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-bloodbath-bitcoin-plummets-below-17k-bnb-crashes-7-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Bloodbath: Bitcoin Plummets Below $17K, BNB Crashes 7% (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Japan to Enforce Less Stringent Crypto Tax Rules</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/japan-to-enforce-less-stringent-crypto-tax-rules/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 01:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229056</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Japan_Flag.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Japan_Flag.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Japanese crypto issuers might no longer have to pay 30% corporate tax on their holdings as of April 1, 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Japanese government greenlighted a bill to exempt local cryptocurrency issuers from paying corporate tax on their holdings.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The ruling body currently requires such firms to pay 30% on their ownings even if they haven&#8217;t gained profits through a sale.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Japan&#8217;s ruling political party &#8211; The Liberal Democratic Party &#8211; <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/japan-moves-closer-to-easing-tax-on-corporate-crypto-holdings-1.1859699" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">aims</a> to ease corporate tax legislation for domestic crypto issuers and thus stimulate such entities to operate in their homeland.</span></li>
<li>Akihisa Shiozaki &#8211; an LDP lawkamer &#8211; described the move as a &#8220;very big step forward.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It will become easier for various companies to do business that involves issuing tokens,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Prime Minister Fumio Kishida&#8217;s cabinet is expected to complete its annual taxation standards by the end of 2022 based on the Liberal Democratic Party&#8217;s decisions.</li>
<li>The relaxed rules could come into force as of April 1, 2023 (the start of the new fiscal year in Japan).</li>
<li>Local lobbying groups have previously <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/07/27/business/japan-crypto-talent-exodus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">urged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Japanese lawmakers to stop taxing paper gains on crypto holdings and thus cease the talent exodus.</span></li>
<li>High taxes have proved to be burdensome for numerous domestic startups, many of which have relocated to countries with friendlier regulations, such as Singapore.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/japan-to-enforce-less-stringent-crypto-tax-rules/" rel="nofollow">Japan to Enforce Less Stringent Crypto Tax Rules</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warner Music Group Delves Deeper into Metaverse, Invests in DressX</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/warner-music-group-delves-deeper-into-metaverse-invests-in-dressx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229096</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Warner-Music-Group.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Warner-Music-Group.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The extent of digital asset usage in the deal has not been disclosed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American entertainment and record label conglomerate &#8211; Warner Music Group &#8211; is continuing to expand its metaverse strategy, evident in its latest partnership and investment in DressX, a digital fashion retailer.</p>
<p>Under the agreement, Warner Music artists will be able to collaborate directly with DressX to design and launch 3D and AR virtual clothing, which can be collected and accessed by fans across various social media channels such as Instagram, Snapchat, and other platforms partners.</p>
<h2>Warner Music Group Metaverse Push</h2>
<p>According to the official blog <a href="https://www.wmg.com/news/warner-music-group-announces-partnership-with-and-investment-in-leading-digital-fashion-company-dressx" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a>, artists will also be able to leverage additional revenue streams through the partnership while simultaneously creating new outlets for fans to exhibit their fandom across multiple digital worlds.</p>
<p>In a statement, Oana Ruxandra, WMG&#8217;s Chief Digital Officer &amp; EVP of Business Development, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The representation of our future digital selves will be as important and, if you’re measuring by the sheer volume of interactions, maybe more important than how we represent ourselves physically. As our digital identities become exponentially more robust and impactful, we are focused on building partnerships that will enable WMG and our artists.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Warner Music Group has not revealed the amount invested in DressX as a part of the agreement.</p>
<p>Earlier this summer, DressX had partnered with Meta (formerly Facebook) and began selling outfits in the Mark Zuckerbereg-led company&#8217;s Avatar Store. This marked the first time a digital-native fashion company got the opportunity to be invited by the social media giant alongside prominent luxury labels &#8211; Prada, Balenciaga, and Thom Browne.</p>
<h2>Web3 Push</h2>
<p>The music and entertainment conglomerate partnered with Animoca Brands&#8217; The Sandbox to launch a music-themed virtual world in January this year. This was Warner Music Group&#8217;s first venture in the Web3 space, as part of which the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sandbox-partners-with-warner-for-musical-metaverse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">acquired</a> &#8220;ESTATE.&#8221;</p>
<p>For context, the &#8220;ESTATE&#8221; was described as a hybrid of a musical theme park and concert venue that will act as a portal for Warner&#8217;s artists to make an appearance in the metaverse.</p>
<p>A month later, Warner dived into record label company dived into blockchain gaming by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-music-mogul-warner-music-group-partners-with-splinterlands/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnering</a> with a developer, Splinterlands. The deal was to develop mobile-friendly, accessible games by moving towards arcade-style gaming in a bid to further advance the adoption and bolster community building more seamlessly than the conventional play-to-earn (P2E) games.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/warner-music-group-delves-deeper-into-metaverse-invests-in-dressx/" rel="nofollow">Warner Music Group Delves Deeper into Metaverse, Invests in DressX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Donald Trump&#8217;s NFT Collection Sold Out in One Day</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trumps-nft-collection-sold-out-in-one-day/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Donald Trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229197</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/DonaldJTrump-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/DonaldJTrump-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Trump’s “major announcement” appears to have attracted an audience of hungry buyers.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite his seemingly poor market timing, former U.S. President Donald Trump’s recently launched collection of digital “baseball cards” sold out within 24 hours of their release. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The crypto community has reacted with amusement – especially given Trump’s prior statements berating crypto as a “scam.”</span></p>
<h2>Trump Has an NFT Collection?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As CryptoPotato </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trump-announces-personal-nft-collection/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Thursday, Trump’s NFTs – or “cards” – portray art representing parts of his life and career. The collectibles featured him in various outfits and places, ranging from cowboy getup, to an astronaut suit, to a racecar driver. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Trump Digital Trading Cards (NFTs) are intended as collectible items for individual enjoyment only, not for investment vehicles,” clarified the investment page.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The collection featured 2,533 NFTs in total sold for $99 each – meaning the sale raised over $250,000. Each NFT purchased entered buyers into sweepstakes with a chance to win various prizes, including a 20-minute meeting with Trump, a zoom call, a golf game, or an autograph signed by the celebrity. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, buyers of 45 separate NFTs earned a guaranteed ticket to a 2000-person Gala dinner with the former president. Each NFT could beat bought with cash, ETH, or WETH. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Melania Trump </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/melania-trump-launches-an-nft-and-blockchain-venture-based-on-solana/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> her own Solana-based NFT collection exactly one year ago today. Proceeds were used to raise money for foster children’s education.</span></p>
<h2>Trump’s Crypto Flip Flop?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Trump has repeatedly bashed Bitcoin and cryptocurrency in the past as a “scam” backed by nothing, which threatens the dominance of the U.S. dollar. Nevertheless, he was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-potus-donald-trump-says-crypto-is-dangerous-but-praises-melanias-nft-project/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">supportive</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> of his wife’s NFT foray last year. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I don’t want to have all these other (cryptocurrencies),” he said in an interview with FOX business at the time. “There could be an explosion someday, the likes of which we’ve never seen. It will make the big tech explosion look like baby stuff. I think it’s a very dangerous thing.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto Twitter couldn’t help but appreciate the contradiction since Trump unveiled his NFTs on Thursday. In total disbelief, crypto podcast host Scott Melker </span><a href="https://twitter.com/scottmelker/status/1603435725990551554?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1603435725990551554%7Ctwgr%5Ee24b092aa362577b925bc136ca813ea049535c41%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fdecrypt.co%2F117317%2Fdonald-trump-nft-collection-crypto-cant-even" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> he hoped the collection would ultimately go to zero so the industry could “start again.”</span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/PeterMcCormack/status/1603438364841197570</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">So far, that hasn’t happened. In fact, Trump’s NFTs are </span><a href="https://opensea.io/collection/trump-digital-trading-cards?search[sortAscending]=true&amp;search[sortBy]=UNIT_PRICE" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">trading</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> above their original sale price on OpenSea, with a current floor price of 0.17 ETH – worth $205 at writing time. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/donald-trumps-nft-collection-sold-out-in-one-day/" rel="nofollow">Donald Trump&#8217;s NFT Collection Sold Out in One Day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Price Winter Continue in 2023? 8 Key Considerations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-price-winter-continue-in-2023-8-key-considerations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 18:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227948</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/2022_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Which way bitcoin’s price will go next is a question with many zeroes on it for many crypto investors as we finish 2022. Who knows? Here are 8 key factors to consider.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2022 Bitcoin, Ethereum, and the bevy of altcoins riding on the original gangster cryptocurrency&#8217;s very long coattails weathered their most brutal crypto winter to date. Of course, the cryptocurrency industry is eager for an end to the long, drawn-out Bitcoin price winter.</p>
<p>From Bitcoin miners and mining pools to Layer-2 chain developers like the Lightning Network to crypto day traders and crypto investors &#8211; confidence is shaken, fear and greed are high, and the metaphorical blood just keeps pouring out into the streets. When will it end?</p>
<h2>2023 Bitcoin Price History Was a Doozy and a Half</h2>
<p>The sharp market correction after the $69K ATH in November 2021 was reasonable, understandable, and even expected by many. When the price fell to the $30,000 handle in May, it was nerve-wracking. But the Bitcoin price still looked pretty good to anyone hodling bitcoin from Jan 1, 2018, through Jan 1, 2021. During that three-year period, BTC traded at an average of around $10,000.</p>
<p>Then, the fear really started to set in when Bitcoin&#8217;s price fell into an unequivocal crypto winter pattern as the Northern Hemisphere approached summer. The sudden slide during one week in June from the $30K handle to the $20K level was a major shock to the heart of crypto traders.</p>
<p>As we round out Q4 toward 2023, the situation with Bitcoin&#8217;s price is especially dire. While there was no doubt at all that we were in winter all year, at least Bitcoin held at the key support level of $20K from June until the beginning of November.</p>
<h2>FUD Sets In, Then Goes From Bad to Worse</h2>
<p>That $20,000 price per coin was an important psychological support level. Four-and-a-half months of price action firmly in the vicinity of that number seemed, after the dramatic price collapses in H1, like the good promise of a drawn-out bottom before the next trend rally.</p>
<p>The question now is how will Bitcoin perform in Q1 2023 and beyond.</p>
<p>There are several proverbial 8,000-pound gorillas in the room:</p>
<p>Among others &#8211; rampant losses to financially and legally insane crypto ventures, fierce competition from smart contract chains, the question of BTC&#8217;s correlation to U.S. tech stocks, intense regulatory ambiguity, and a pause from wary but very interested institutional investors.</p>
<p>The following is a brief summary review of 8 key long-range factors and their confluences on the Bitcoin price heading into 2023. (You can read a similar analysis and commentary published by the same author on CryptoPotato for the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-price-rally-continue-in-2021-8-key-considerations/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin price at the beginning of 2021 here</a>.)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-119996" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover.jpg" alt="bearbitcoin_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/bearbitcoin_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Bearish Indicators: Four Bitcoin Headwinds in 2023</h2>
<h3>1. Collapses of LUNA, FTX, and Others in 2022 Are Weighing on The Spot Price of Bitcoin</h3>
<p>&#8220;You don&#8217;t find out who&#8217;s been swimming naked until the tide goes out&#8221; is an oft-used aphorism of Warren Buffett, the old &#8216;Oracle of Omaha,&#8217; to describe the effect of broad market corrections on the weakest participants in the game. They shake out of the game altogether as the downturn becomes a cash squeeze for the underlying businesses evaluated by the market.</p>
<p>The first phase of 2022&#8217;s Bitcoin winter appeared to market watchers as a clear-cut case of a necessary and inevitable price correction to a deeply overheated price level after the Nov 2021 peak. But the secondary effect of the price correction was to see who was just boasting to investors and who really had cash reserves to weather the Bitcoin crash. When the bear market revealed several crypto enterprises were insolvent, it sent the prices of BTC, along with other coins cratering over the rest of the year. Investors are now understandably wary to divine the industry and exchange markets to pick out winners.</p>
<p>This year&#8217;s bear market revelations of insolvency and zero confidence in billion-dollar crypto startups like LUNA, FTX, and several crypto hedge funds even hit high-profile crypto investors <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/winklevoss-crypto-firm-employees-saw-020240051.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">like the Winklevoss Twins</a> and <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/08/ftx-spokesman-kevin-oleary-says-he-lost-15-million-crypto-payday.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Kevin O&#8217;Leary</a>, costing them dearly.</p>
<h3>2. U.S. Crypto Regulatory Ambiguity Could Drag Bitcoin Price Down Through 2023</h3>
<p>Regulatory ambiguity toward cryptocurrencies in the United States and across the globe where major crypto players operate is hurting the industry&#8217;s growth prospects by keeping huge investors on pause. They&#8217;re waiting to know what the government is going to do about cryptocurrencies before jumping into these turbulent waters.</p>
<p>Investing in cryptocurrency is fraught enough with dangers and risks, even without a sudden encroachment by government regulators that unexpectedly raises regulatory compliance costs. One of the most critical questions hanging in limbo at the moment is whether the United States will classify cryptocurrencies as commodities, securities, or something else entirely.</p>
<h3>3. Bitcoin Faces More Fierce Competition Than Ever</h3>
<p>While the constant and seemingly never-ending tumble of crypto prices this year has shocked investors, the crypto industry&#8217;s developers have been plugging away through the Bitcoin winter to improve the sectors&#8217; products and get them ready for more adoption and scale. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-schiff-blames-altcoins-for-bitcoins-fall-as-ethereum-merge-nears/" data-wpel-link="internal">Competition from BTC substitutes</a> like Ethereum and other altcoins could keep the original gangster crypto from rallying with the strength it otherwise could.</p>
<p>Vitalik Buterin, in <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1599166783541628928" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">a recent reply</a> to a frustrated crypto investor on Twitter, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I&#8217;d recommend increasing your distance from trading/investing circles, and getting closer to the tech and application ecosystem. Learn about ZK-SNARKs, visit a meetup in Latin America, listen to All Core Devs calls and read the notes until you&#8217;ve memorized all the EIP numbers&#8230;&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That&#8217;s what Buterin and the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-completes-merge-successfully-crypto-markets-take-a-beating-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum team have been doing</a>, not sweating the extended market price downturn and keeping their heads down and their nose to the grindstone. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">The Ethereum merge to upgrade Ethereum Mainnet</a> from a proof-of-work system to a proof-of-stake network is calculated to scale the smart contract blockchain&#8217;s adoption faster when the next bull run occurs. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-merge-is-official-ethereums-transition-to-proof-of-stake-now-complete/" data-wpel-link="internal">It was completed in September</a>.</p>
<h3>4. Bitcoin / Stock Market Correlation Stronger Than Ever</h3>
<p>Macro conditions are difficult for all financial markets heading into 2023. As Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1600945923898556417" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recently summarized</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Macro conditions are difficult: energy in Europe, real estate in China &amp; crazy Fed rates in USA&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, permabear Nouriel Roubini (who attention markets call &#8220;Dr. Doom&#8221; for his inveterate bearishness) <a href="https://fortune.com/2022/12/07/how-bad-recession-economist-dr-doom-nouriel-roubini-stock-market-forecast/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">predicts a</a> looming severe recession will continue to discount U.S. stock prices. Even though the broad S&amp;P 500 benchmark is already down some 15% for the year, Roubini says we can expect another 25% haircut on stock prices from here.</p>
<p>Because the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-high-bitcoin-and-ethereum-correlation-with-wall-street-continues/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin stock market correlation</a> has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-price-has-correlated-with-us-stocks-for-the-last-month/" data-wpel-link="internal">remained tightly coupled</a> for over a year now, if stocks continue to go down, they could easily take bitcoin spot prices down with them. Some more recent bearish stock market data and analyses are <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/08/the-stock-market-is-trapped-in-a-clear-downtrend-and-the-situation-could-get-worse.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">here</a> and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-07/bruising-stock-market-reversal-shows-how-fed-s-pivot-may-come-too-late" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">here.</a></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-169779" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" alt="bitcoinbull_cover (1)" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Bullish Indicators: Four Bitcoin Tailwinds in 2023</h2>
<h3>1. Bitcoin / Stock Market Correlation Stronger Than Ever (Familiar?)</h3>
<p>Now the Bitcoin to stock market correlation could be a bullish indicator for bitcoin, depending on your view of how equities markets will move in 2023. If equities continue their downward trend into Q1 and Q2, supposing the Bitcoin spot price remains coupled to stocks, we will see a bear market extending into 2023.</p>
<p>However, if Bitcoin does not decouple from the stock market and we get a NASDAQ rally in 2023, odds are good that bitcoin spot prices will rally along with the broader tech and overall economy benchmarks.</p>
<p>In the very short term, stocks <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-stock-market-investors-shouldnt-count-on-a-santa-claus-rally-this-year-11670628375" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">are unlikely</a> to get a Santa Claus rally to round out Q4. It could very well be, though, that stocks will rally again in 2023 after posting significant losses for the calendar year of 2022. (On the year-to-date pane, the NASDAQ Composite is down some 30%, while the S&amp;P 500 Index is down 18%.</p>
<p>At least one top Wall Street analyst <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/one-of-the-most-frequently-cited-risks-to-stocks-in-2023-is-overstated-140558319.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">says that</a> one of the biggest headwinds potentially facing stocks in 2023&#8211; downward revisions in earnings estimates&#8211; is overstated. That&#8217;s because changes in Year over Year earnings have a statistical correlation to stock price changes of virtually zero.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, a recent report by <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/08/retail-investors-say-stock-market-will-bottom-in-2023-finimize-survey.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">CNBC is optimistic</a> about a stock market rally in 2023, citing retail investors&#8217; sentiment. They seem to think the bottom will be in next year and are going on a buying spree of tech equities especially.</p>
<h3>2. Bitcoin Is Oversold Like Crazy As We Head into 2023</h3>
<p>Perhaps one of the most important bullish leading indicators for the Bitcoin price next year is the absolutely <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-bitcoin-is-oversold-like-crazy-right-now-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">viciously oversold condition</a> of bitcoin trading pairs on liquid crypto exchange markets.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is so oversold at this point that its trendline on the Bitcoin Rainbow Chart <a href="https://www.tradingview.com/chart/BTCUSD/dSTTgyYJ-Bitcoin-Rainbow-chart/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">has screamed straight through</a> the &#8220;BUY!&#8221; zone and settled for months now in the &#8220;Basically A Fire Sale!&#8221; zone of the chart.</p>
<p>The logarithmically graphed Bitcoin Rainbow Chart is a static BTC trading recommendation tool that helps investors and traders to determine the fair value of Bitcoin on the basis of its historical trends.</p>
<h3>3. BTC Fundamentals Are Strong</h3>
<p>While the price of a coin at the exchange has taken one steep fall after another, with each headline-making hit to the industry&#8217;s big players, the fundamentals of the economy and market for Bitcoin remain strong.</p>
<p>While the hash rate <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hash-ribbon-reversal-confirms-bitcoin-miner-capitulation-phase/" data-wpel-link="internal">has dropped some</a> over the last month, the overall view of the Bitcoin economy is one of a very <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hash-rate-marks-new-all-time-high-after-55-increase-in-2-months/" data-wpel-link="internal">solid hash rate</a> to price ratio for the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-bitcoin-is-oversold-like-crazy-right-now-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">Miners have continued to invest</a> heavily in their operations even with the price in steep and entrenched capitulation all year. Throughout the Bitcoin winter, a solid half to near-half of the coins held have actually been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-bitcoin-is-held-at-a-net-unrealized-profit/" data-wpel-link="internal">held at an unrealized profit</a>.</p>
<h3>4. It&#8217;s About to Rain Institutional Investors and Hedge Funds</h3>
<p>Most of the institutional investment in cryptocurrencies is yet to come as we finish 2022. Big hedge funds that invest for retirees&#8217; pensions and venture capitalists are still waiting with dry powder to get in on the opportunities that Bitcoin&#8217;s price growth and volatility represent for them.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/most-institutional-investment-in-crypto-is-still-late-in-2022-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">They&#8217;re waiting</a> to get the regulatory green light from authorities to advance, and as they&#8217;re waiting, they continue to learn and hire blockchain experts and engineers to make preparations for when that day finally comes &#8211; maybe in 2023.</p>
<p>When they finally enter, allocating a half percent or one percent of their books to crypto like Bitcoin or Ethereum, the market will undoubtedly find a new center of gravity, with resilient key support at a much higher level than the market has so far seen with retail investors.</p>
<p>Also: Don&#8217;t forget the Millennials! <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/social-security-gets-8-boost-why-millennials-are-turning-to-crypto-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">They like crypto better than stocks</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-price-winter-continue-in-2023-8-key-considerations/" rel="nofollow">Will Bitcoin Price Winter Continue in 2023? 8 Key Considerations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
