<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 15:11:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>dApp Industry Thrives Despite Crypto Winter: DappRadar</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dapp-industry-thrives-despite-crypto-winter-dappradar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230024</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/blockchain_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/blockchain_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto winter has not harmed at least one industry niche. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The cryptocurrency market is facing one of its most brutal crypto winters, marked by a sustained drop in digital asset prices and the failure of major crypto companies, as well as high-profile cases of hacks and heists.</p>
<p class="p2">Nonetheless, a recent report from blockchain data and analytics firm DappRadar suggests that the industry may not be in such a gloomy state, as it has shown remarkable resilience and maturity amid the crypto winter.</p>
<p class="p2">According to DappRadar&#8217;s <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/dapp-industry-report-2022-dapp-industry-proves-resilient-in-crypto-winter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">2022 Industry Report</a>, decentralized applications (dApps) usage has skyrocketed despite the bearish market conditions.</p>
<p class="p2">The dApp industry saw a 50% year-on-year increase in its daily unique active wallets (dUAW), rising from 1.58 million in 2021 to 2.37 million in 2022. This growth can be attributed to increased acceptance among consumers and businesses, as well as increased investor interest.</p>
<h2 class="p3">Blockchain Gaming and NFTs Lead Dapp Market Growth</h2>
<p class="p2">Blockchain gaming projects, specifically the GameFi sector, played a significant role in the dApp industry this year. GameFi accounted for 49% of all dApp activity, with an average of 1.15 million daily dUAW and 7.4 billion transactions.</p>
<p class="p2">The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible token</a> (NFT) market also contributed to the dApp industry&#8217;s growth, with a 33% increase in daily dUAW and an 876% jump in unique NFT traders.</p>
<p class="p2">However, while the number of unique NFT traders rose significantly, the trading volume only increased by 0.41% compared to the previous year. NFT sales also boomed, rising 10.6% to $68.35 million, although another report <strong>suggested</strong> that nearly 60% of NFT trading volume this year was fake.</p>
<h2 class="p3">DeFi Shows Resilience Despite 73% Drop in TVL</h2>
<p class="p2">The decentralized finance (DeFi) sector faced challenges in 2022, losing more than 73% of its total value locked. Despite this, the market saw a 2% increase in daily dUAW, reaching 652,970.</p>
<p class="p2">This may not seem significant, but DappRadar notes that it is an impressive achievement for the DeFi sector after the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-sorry-for-cocky-tweets-takes-full-responsibility-for-terras-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of Terra Luna</a>, which was the second-largest DeFi ecosystem at the time.</p>
<p class="p2">The report concludes by acknowledging that the bear market has created an opportunity for the industry to learn from mistakes and focus on building sustainable projects while preparing for the next bull season. It also highlights the industry&#8217;s resilience and maturity as it continues to grow despite challenging market conditions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dapp-industry-thrives-despite-crypto-winter-dappradar/" rel="nofollow">dApp Industry Thrives Despite Crypto Winter: DappRadar</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Impact of FTX&#8217;s Contagion to Continue into 2023: CryptoCompare</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/impact-of-ftxs-contagion-to-continue-into-2023-cryptocompare/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 21:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229792</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Frozen.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Frozen.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CryptoCompare predicts that the impact of FTX's crash will continue into 2023, providing an opportunity for reflection ahead of the next bull run.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">This year has been tumultuous for the cryptocurrency industry, with major players like Terra, Three Arrows Capital (3AC), and FTX going underwater.</p>
<p class="p2">As the crypto space struggles to find footing amid the second wave of the crypto winter exacerbated by the latest FTX debacle, digital asset data provider CryptoCompare believes it will take a while for the industry to recover from the impact of the collapse.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Crypto Projects to Focus on Survival</b></h2>
<p class="p2">In its 2022 Year in Review <a href="https://blog.cryptocompare.com/cryptocompare-year-in-review-2022-df6e3bb2cb5f" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, CryptoCompare noted that it would take some time for the market to fully recover from the impact of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX&#8217;s collapse</a>, as the exchange&#8217;s ties to numerous crypto firms will continue to influence the industry&#8217;s recovery into the new year.</p>
<p class="p2">Nonetheless, the FTX debacle has also highlighted the need for developers to create sustainable projects.</p>
<p class="p2">As such, CryptoCompare predicts that in 2023, there will be a greater focus on &#8220;protocols and projects focusing on survival through cash preservation and on building applications with a market-product fit, rather than on marketing and copy-cat initiatives.&#8221;</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Increased Regulatory Clarity Expected in 2023</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The crypto data provider also suggested that the FTX bankruptcy may encourage more global financial regulators to establish frameworks for regulating the crypto market.</p>
<p class="p2">Some regulators are already implementing stringent measures to protect investors. For instance, the Thai Securities and Exchange Commission recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stringent-crypto-regulation-incoming-after-ftx-collapse-warns-thai-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to incorporate stricter regulations on crypto assets.</p>
<p class="p2">CryptoCompare believes these regulations will be more effective if they distinguish between centralized and decentralized entities within the crypto space, as many failed companies were centralized. This distinction would also foster continued innovation in the decentralized finance sector.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>A Time for Reflection</b></h2>
<p class="p2">In conclusion, CryptoCompare believes the crypto winter offers a chance for market participants to reflect and focus on developing the industry while preparing for the next bull run.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;In 2022, we saw the end of the bull market and the start of a bear cycle, which provides market participants with an opportunity to take a step back, reflect on the developments of the industry, and plan for the future,&#8221; the report said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">While disheartening, bear markets are one of the proven ways to filter the broader market as they show that investors are in the market for the long term, not for speculation and short-term gain.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/impact-of-ftxs-contagion-to-continue-into-2023-cryptocompare/" rel="nofollow">Impact of FTX&#8217;s Contagion to Continue into 2023: CryptoCompare</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>1inch Network Introduces Fusion Update for DeFi Swaps</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/1inch-network-introduces-fusion-update-for-defi-swaps/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 18:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[1inch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230193</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1inch_Fusion.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/1inch_Fusion.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Users will be able to choose between three options with the Fusion mode. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The popular DEX aggregator announced the launch of Fusion, which focuses on the 1inch Swap Engine and aims to enhance user experience with DeFi swaps.</p>
<p>The team behind the project promised to deliver &#8220;almost limitless&#8221; liquidity and maximum user protection.</p>
<ul>
<li>The press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em> informed that 1inch Swap Engine &#8220;facilitates Fusion, which empowers DeFi users to place orders with a specified price and time range, paying no network fees.&#8221;</li>
<li>1inch Swap Engine is a decentralized trading and matching protocol, partially based on the 1inch Limit Order Protocol and the 1inch Aggregation Protocol. According to the team, this allows customers to access &#8220;almost all available liquidity in the crypto market.&#8221;</li>
<li>The orders are completed by professional market makers paying applicable gas fees called resolvers. Users have to stake 1INCH tokens to become resolvers, and the top five stakers will have priority executing orders.</li>
<li>The team said Fusion mode allows users to swap tokens on various decentralized exchanges without paying any network fees, &#8220;at the most favorable rates.&#8221; They can choose from three options:</li>
<li>Fast &#8211; in which the user accepts a less desirable rate to have the swap executed within a few blocks. Fair &#8211; the user can wait a bit longer for a better rate. And Auction &#8211; the user waits up to 10 minutes to receive the most favorable rate.</li>
<li>The Fusion update will initially work on BNB Chain, Ethereum, and Polygon, with more networks to be added in the future.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“Fusion makes swaps on 1inch dramatically more cost efficient, as users won’t have to pay network fees, plus, an extra layer of security is added, protecting users from sandwich attacks. Our aim is to make users’ DeFi experience as smooth as never before. Thanks to the 1inch Swap Engine and Fusion mode, now, everyone gets incredible UX with a high degree of security.” &#8211; commented 1inch Network co-founder Sergej Kunz.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/1inch-network-introduces-fusion-update-for-defi-swaps/" rel="nofollow">1inch Network Introduces Fusion Update for DeFi Swaps</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Judge in SBF Case Recuses Herself Citing Possible Conflict of Interset</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/judge-in-sbf-case-recuses-herself-citing-possible-conflict-of-interset/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 16:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230215</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_legal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_legal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A US Federal judge Ronnie Abrams recused herself from the case, citing a possible conflict of interest.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Federal judge Ronnie Abrams, who used to oversee the case against Sam Bankman-Fried, Caroline Ellison, and Gary Wang, has formally recused herself.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to an <a href="https://s3.documentcloud.org/documents/23531804/order-in-ftx-case-judge-abrams-recuses-herself-after-delayed-transcripts-unsealed-recusal-order-here-whos-next-innercitypresscom-is-on-it.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">order</a> from December 23rd, Federal judge at the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York has recused herself from the action.</li>
<li>The order states:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>It has come to the Court&#8217;s attention that the law firm of Davis Polk &amp; Wardwell LLP, at which my husband is a partner, advised FTX in 2021, as well as represented parties that may be adverse to FTX and Defendant Bankman-Fried in other proceedigs (or potential proceedings). My husband has no involvement in any of these representations. [&#8230;] Nonetheless, to avoid any possible conflict, or the appearance of one, the Court hereby recuses itself from this action.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Meanwhile, Sam Bankman-Fried was previously allowed to stay in his parents&#8217; home and released on a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">$250 million bail</a>.</li>
<li>It&#8217;s important to note that he didn&#8217;t have to pay the full amount, which is used as a deterrent in case he fails to honor the conditions of his bail agreement.</li>
<li>The judge who allowed the bail was Gabriel Gorenstein.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-in-sbf-case-recuses-herself-citing-possible-conflict-of-interset/" rel="nofollow">Judge in SBF Case Recuses Herself Citing Possible Conflict of Interset</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Using LastPass to Store Passwords? You Must Act Quickly</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/using-lastpass-to-store-passwords-you-must-act-quickly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230196</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/security_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/security_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LastPass users are likely at risk, and it's important to take the necessary precautions to safeguard your crypto. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the most popular password management tools &#8211; LastPass &#8211; has recently been compromised, and cryptocurrency users may have been affected.</p>
<p>With that in mind, it&#8217;s important to take reasonable action.</p>
<ul>
<li>First off, <a href="https://www.cshub.com/attacks/news/customer-details-compromised-in-lastpass-data-breaches" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a> of LastPass being compromised started appearing yesterday. Some claim that customer details were leaked in data breaches, and these include contact details, company and customer names, as well as IP addresses.</li>
<li>The breaches themselves took place back in August and November and were acknowledged by the company, which said that a malicious actor was able to steal the source code and technical information from their development environment.</li>
<li>With that in mind, Udi Wertheimer took it to Twitter to suggest a few steps users can take to prevent their crypto from being stolen, assuming someone used LastPass to secure crypto-related apps and wallets.</li>
<li>He argued that changing the master password now won&#8217;t help because &#8220;they already have a copy that is unlockable&#8221; with the old password.</li>
<li>Therefore, Wertheimer suggested that users stop using the app altogether and immediately move their assets to new wallets.</li>
<li>In addition, he also advised changing passwords to email accounts, crypto exchanges, and virtually all applications, including account passwords for Google or iCloud.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ LASTPASS USERS READ THIS <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/203c.png" alt="‼" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Twitter is full of misinformation and bad advice.</p>
<p>If you use LastPass, attackers probably have a copy of your vault.</p>
<p>CHANGING YOUR MASTER PASSWORD NOW WON’T HELP, they already have a copy that is unlockable with your old password.</p>
<p>What to do? <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— Udi Wertheimer (@udiWertheimer) <a href="https://twitter.com/udiWertheimer/status/1606501962526097408?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 24, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/using-lastpass-to-store-passwords-you-must-act-quickly/" rel="nofollow">Using LastPass to Store Passwords? You Must Act Quickly</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The State of Bitcoin Development in 2022: NYDIG</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-state-of-bitcoin-development-in-2022-nydig/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 12:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230157</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinNYDIG.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/BitcoinNYDIG.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin development is growing more decentralized with time – especially within its broader ecosystem. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Bitcoin-focused investment group, New York Digital Investment Group (NYDIG), released a report in September examining how Bitcoin’s protocol has managed to attract such wide adoption despite its tiny developer ecosystem. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Here are the highlights:</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The network, which launched in early January 2009, has only 40-60 monthly active developers, according to the </span><a href="https://nydig.com/research/developers-of-bitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">This is not a static bunch. 1,140 developers have contributed to Bitcoin over its lifetime, with 5 to 10 new monthly active developers arriving each month, while others cycle out or scale back activity. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Roughly 84% of Bitcoin Core’s suggested software changes on GitHub come from devs in 20 different countries. However, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weeks-before-replacing-its-top-executives-nydig-dismissed-30-of-its-workforce-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">NYDIG</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> noted that most development appears to occur in the United States and Europe.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Over half of Bitcoin Core code commits in 2021 came from developers that joined the ecosystem after the 2017 bull market cycle.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bitcoin Core has historically had someone serve as a lead maintainer to cryptographically sign off on new protocol changes. This way, users downloading the software could verify that they weren’t installing malicious code.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, as of September 2021, the lead maintainer role was abolished in favor of a more egalitarian model whereby a group of maintainers (12 at present) signs off on new changes. “This group will likely vary going forward,” said NYDIG.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Earlier this year, Gloria Zhao became the first known female maintainer of Bitcoin. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Beyond Bitcoin’s core protocol, its “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-aims-to-bitcoinize-the-dollar-with-taros-alpha-release/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">broader ecosystem</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">” has attracted 600-1000 monthly active developers, with over 13,000 in total. This number is generally increasing over time, although it appears to have some correlation with Bitcoin’s halving cycles. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">“The ecosystem of applications and developers continues to grow, with contributions coming from around the world, expanding Bitcoin’s reach as a global monetary system,” concluded NYDIG.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-state-of-bitcoin-development-in-2022-nydig/" rel="nofollow">The State of Bitcoin Development in 2022: NYDIG</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekend Watch: Terra Classic (LUNC) Jumps 6%, Bitcoin Flat Amid $17K</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-terra-classic-lunc-jumps-6-bitcoin-flat-amid-17k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 09:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230176</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra_Green.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra_Green.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Terra Classic has jumped the most ahead of Christmas, with a 6% daily increase. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest PCE data announced by the US yesterday brought little volatility to the crypto market, in which BTC dropped by a few hundred dollars but recovered almost immediately.</p>
<p>The altcoins are still on a daily scale, with a few exceptions in the likes of Terra Classic, Decentraland, and Lido.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Remains Chill at $17K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin dropped to a 3-week low on December 20 at $16,300 but reclaimed almost all lost value in less than a day. Another price decline two days later saw the asset slipping to $16,500, but it bounced back off to $16,800 hours later.</p>
<p>The end of the working week saw two major announcements from the US &#8211; about the GDP (an increase of 3.2% in Q3) and the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-inflation-gauge-pce-clocks-in-at-4-7-yoy/" data-wpel-link="internal">PCE numbers</a>, which is an inflation gauge that covers consumer costs. Both had little impact on BTC, while the largest US stock market indexes <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-stocks-fall-on-gdp-data-bitcoin-ethereum-hold-on-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">experienced more volatility</a>, closing the trading days in the red.</p>
<p>Yesterday, bitcoin fell by $100 from its familiar spot of $16,800 before it shot up by $200 to an intraday low of just shy of $17,000. However, the asset has returned to $16,800 once again ahead of Christmas Eve.</p>
<p>This means that there are no real movements in its market cap (calm at $325 billion), and its dominance over the alts is still at 40%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230178" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230178" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230178" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-7-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230178" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LUNC Marks 6% Increase</h2>
<p>Most of the altcoins have mimicked BTC&#8217;s performance in the past 24 hours, meaning they are quite stagnant. Ethereum has sustained above $1,200 as it sits flat on a daily scale.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, Dogecoin, Cardano, Polygon, OKB, Tron, Shiba Inu, Litecoin, and Polkadot are all with insignificant losses.</p>
<p>Solana has dropped the most from the larger-cap alts. A 5.3% decline on a 24-hour scale has pushed SOL down to just over $11.</p>
<p>LUNC has popped as today&#8217;s top performer, with a 6% increase, followed by Decentraland (5%) and Lido (4.5%).</p>
<p>Overall, though, the crypto market cap has remained still at just over $810 billion on CoinMarketCap.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230179" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230179" style="width: 1849px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230179" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1849" height="739" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5.jpg 1849w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5-1024x409.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5-768x307.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5-1536x614.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-5-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1849px) 100vw, 1849px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230179" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-terra-classic-lunc-jumps-6-bitcoin-flat-amid-17k/" rel="nofollow">Weekend Watch: Terra Classic (LUNC) Jumps 6%, Bitcoin Flat Amid $17K</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nearly 60% of NFT Trading Volumes in 2022 Was Wash Trading: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nearly-60-of-nft-trading-volumes-in-2022-was-wash-trading-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 05:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229944</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/NFT_Wash.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/NFT_Wash.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[NFT marketplaces use token reward trading strategies to entice traders, boost volume, and appear to be the most successful platforms.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">A recent report published by blockchain analytics firm Dune revealed that nearly 60% of non-fungible token (NFT) trading volumes this year were wash trades.</p>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wash-trading-in-the-nft-space-the-problem-and-possible-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wash trading</a> is a form of market manipulation in which a trader buys and sells a security to create the appearance of increased trading volume and activity in the market. In crypto, these activities involve buying and selling digital assets &#8211; fungible or non-fungible tokens &#8211; on trading platforms, intending to inflate transaction volumes. The end goal is to mislead other traders about the demand level for the asset.</p>
<p class="p2">One example of wash trading in the context of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) might involve a trader who owns a particular NFT and wants to create the impression that it is in high demand. The trader could set up multiple accounts on an NFT marketplace and use them to buy and sell the NFT back and forth, creating the appearance of high trading volume and driving up the price of that asset.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Most NFT Platforms Engage in Wash Trading</b></h2>
<p class="p2">According to Dune, wash trades <a href="https://community.dune.com/blog/nft-wash-trading-on-ethereum" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">started</span></a> gaining traction in the crypto industry in 2019 but became pertinent to the NFT space in 2022.</p>
<p class="p2">The analytics firm noted that NFT wash trading is boosted by enticing traders with token rewards due to the high competitiveness of the space and the frequent launch of new platforms.</p>
<p class="p2">The most common wash trading methods involve investors trading their NFTs between two or more wallets, which they control, for the highest amount of Ether (ETH) possible. They aim to accumulate token rewards more valuable than the gas fees spent.</p>
<p class="p2">In February, blockchain analytics firm Chainalysis <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-crypto-crime-report-preview-nft-wash-trading-money-laundering/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">reported</span></a> that about 110 wash trading addresses had generated $8.9 million in profit. Notably, a significant number of such wallets lost money to transaction fees. However, the profitable addresses exceeded the losses of the unprofitable ones.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>$30B of NFT Trading Volume on Ethereum is Wash Trades</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Notably, the wash trade ratio varies among NFT marketplaces, but some platforms depend more on the activity. According to the report, platforms such as LooksRare and X2Y2 depend on wash trading with 98% and 87% of their respective volumes, depending on the activity. However, only 25% and 22% of their total trades are washes.</p>
<p class="p2">Furthermore, Element and Sudoswap are major wash trading platforms, with their respective volumes accounting for 66% and 11% of the activity. On the other hand, only 18.5% and 14.5% of their total trades are washes.</p>
<p class="p2">Dune also revealed that approximately 45% of all NFT trading volume on <span class="s1">Ethereum</span> are wash trades, accounting for $30 billion of the volume. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/transition-in-nft-markets-as-openseas-monopoly-diminishes-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">OpenSea</span></a> has just 2.4% of wash trading volume and less than 1% of trades.</p>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, in June, <span class="s1">Vijay Pravin</span>, CEO and founder of NFT analytics provider bitsCrunch, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-33-of-nft-volume-is-wash-trading-bitscrunch-ceo-interview/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that over 33% of NFT trading volume was fake.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nearly-60-of-nft-trading-volumes-in-2022-was-wash-trading-report/" rel="nofollow">Nearly 60% of NFT Trading Volumes in 2022 Was Wash Trading: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Freedom? OpenSea Blocks Cuban Artists due to US Sanctions</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/web3-freedom-opensea-blocks-cuban-artists-due-to-us-sanctions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 23:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenSea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230151</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/OpenSea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/OpenSea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[OpenSea is blocking Cuban artists from using its platform, arguably working against Web3’s promise of economic freedom.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In compliance with U.S. sanctions law, OpenSea – the world’s largest NFT marketplace – is delisting Cuban artist and collector accounts from its platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A recent statement from the company confirms previously held suspicions that its platform discriminates against Cuban users. </span></p>
<h2>Compliance With Sanctions</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an email received by </span><a href="https://news.artnet.com/market/nft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Artnet News</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, an OpenSea spokesperson clarified that the company bars “sanctioned individuals, individuals in sanctioned jurisdictions, or services,” from using its platform. That extends to the likes of Cuba, as well as Venezuela, Iran, and Syria. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The confirmation is a blow to Cuban artists who leveraged NFTs to make a profit when the asset class boomed in 2021 – especially after tourist money in the region dried up due to pandemic travel restrictions. Earlier this year, NBC News </span><a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/now/video/cubans-turn-to-cryptocurrency-amid-heavy-u-s-sanctions-139124805728" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interviewed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Ernesto Cisneros – a Cuban musician who revived his music business by tokenizing his music and videos and selling them for money over the internet. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Another artist to benefit was photographer Gabriel Bianchini, whose work has been featured at the Havana Biennial and Milan’s MIA Photo Fair. His NFT Hotel Havana, which contrasts the Cuban capital’s colorful and decaying buildings, sold out within days of listing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Speaking with Artnet News, Bianchini explained that the technology helped people like him navigate the tough economic and political climate of the past two years. “This technology was a liberation, not only economically but creatively, a bridge that allowed us Cuban artists to connect with the world,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The restrictions appear to even expand to the Cuban diaspora. NFTCuba.ART, a </span><a href="https://nftcuba.art/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> promoting Cuban artists’ NFT drops, claims to have had its OpenSea profile </span><a href="https://twitter.com/nftcubaart/status/1602301816749842433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1602301816749842433%7Ctwgr%5E8bb3dc1dd1d475714f9dd4e9f149fb4c2d4dec97%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.artnet.com%2Fmarket%2Fnft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">disabled.</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span></a></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/nftcubaart/status/1602301816749842433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1602301816749842433%7Ctwgr%5E8bb3dc1dd1d475714f9dd4e9f149fb4c2d4dec97%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&#038;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.artnet.com%2Fmarket%2Fnft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Your account has been disabled due to activity that goes against our Terms of Service,” read a notice from OpenSea received by the group. “This means you can no longer access OpenSea with your account.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A notice on the group’s website notes that OpenSea’s ban of its account is “sad and unfortunate” and that it was likely only enacted “because it has the name Cuba in it and or they are fearful of sanctions.”</span></p>
<h2>Against Web3 Principles?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One of the core principles of Web3 is the extension of financial services to all, irrespective of nationality or geographic borders. As such, some users interpreted OpenSea’s ban as going against those principles – and surprising given that it was encouraging of Cuban artists not long ago. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/threadoor/status/1606367793724768256</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others expected this outcome, however. Cuban NFT artist Yordanis García Delgado told Artnet News that he “saw it coming,” adding that “It is very difficult to be decentralized and not be accountable” to US sanctions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">NFTs are difficult to directly monetize without some sort of centralized exchange or marketplace to facilitate trades. On the other hand, fungible and divisible cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ether are easier to directly transact with for goods and services – making sanctions enforcement on such transactions more difficult. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-100000-cubans-are-now-using-cryptocurrency-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in May that over 100,000 Cubans have turned to crypto to bypass centralized payment service providers that must comply with sanctions law. Nevertheless, Chainalysis </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-warrens-bill-will-hurt-crypto-not-russia-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">maintains</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that it is too difficult for large-scale parties, like national governments, to work around such restrictions using crypto. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/web3-freedom-opensea-blocks-cuban-artists-due-to-us-sanctions/" rel="nofollow">Web3 Freedom? OpenSea Blocks Cuban Artists due to US Sanctions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Thiel-Backed Bullish Pulls the Plug on $9B SPAC Deal</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiel-backed-bullish-pulls-the-plug-on-9b-spac-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229978</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Stop.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Stop.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The decision to end the drawn-out deal was amicable.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bullish has called off the planned merger worth $9 billion with Far Peak Acquisition Corp.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://bullish.com/news/press-releases/far-peak-acquisition-corporation-and-bullish-announce-the-termination-of-proposed-business-combination/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, the two entities have mutually agreed to terminate their proposed business combination.</p>
<p>Far Peak is led by Thomas Farley, a former president of the New York Stock Exchange.</p>
<h2>Terminated Merger</h2>
<p>Bullish is audited by Deloitte and recently assured that it has no exposure to FTX or related entities. The Gibraltar-based exchange, which is backed by tech investor Peter Thiel, had planned to go public via a merger with a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC), Far Peak Acquisition (FPAC), in July 2021</p>
<p>Since then, its merger prospectus has undergone several amendments, but the SEC remains unsatisfied. The latest allowed the two companies to terminate the merger agreement on December 31 if not completed before then. But that deadline now appears moot, given Friday&#8217;s announcement.</p>
<p>Commenting on the terminated SPAC merger, Brendan Blumer, Chairman and CEO of Bullish, said that the &#8220;quest to become a public company&#8221; is taking longer than previously anticipated. He added that he &#8220;respects&#8221; the ongoing work by the securities watchdogs in bringing out a relevant framework on digital asset space. The exec also noted,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I’m proud of the dedicated team of Bullish employees and advisors who have devoted countless hours to ensure Bullish operates with the highest standards of transparency and responsibility. This work has formed the operating foundation required to service our customers in the best and safest possible way.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto-SPAC Deals</h2>
<p>As a result of the ongoing market rout, several planned mergers between Web 3 companies and SPACs have been either delayed or canceled. SPACs, also known as blank-check firms, are essentially publicly traded shell companies that are created to take private firms public.</p>
<p>These entities have a reputation for being a backdoor way of going public and gained traction during the pandemic-driven market boom. In fact, SPAC deals skyrocketed at 81, climbing over $155 billion last year.</p>
<p>Over the last two years, SPACs have become a preferred route for crypto companies looking to sidestep a traditional initial public offering. Several prominent players, including Cipher Mining, Bakkt, and Core Scientific entering merger agreements with SPACs but only five out of 14 deals have actually been successful since 2019.</p>
<p>A crypto mining and infrastructure company Prime Blockchain mutually ended its $1.25 billion merger deal Blank-check vehicle 10X Capital Venture Acquisition Corp II in August this year.</p>
<p>More recently, USDC stablecoin issuer Circle mutually <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-nixes-spac-deal-with-concord-still-nurses-public-listing-ambition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">terminated</a> its merger agreement with SPAC partner Concord Acquisition.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiel-backed-bullish-pulls-the-plug-on-9b-spac-deal/" rel="nofollow">Peter Thiel-Backed Bullish Pulls the Plug on $9B SPAC Deal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
