<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:31:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Biden Administration Publishes Roadmap to Combat Crypto Fraud and Protect Investors</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-publishes-roadmap-to-combat-crypto-fraud-and-protect-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235264</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Joe_Biden.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Joe_Biden.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Biden Administration announced a new roadmap to regulate cryptocurrencies and provide clarity to the industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Biden Administration announced on January 27th that it will launch a new legal framework for cryptocurrencies in the coming months to combat the multiple cryptocurrency scams that impacted the crypto market last year, causing multi-million dollar losses.</p>
<p>According to a statement <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/nec/briefing-room/2023/01/27/the-administrations-roadmap-to-mitigate-cryptocurrencies-risks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> by the White House, &#8220;2022 was a tough year for cryptocurrencies.&#8221; Hence, this new regulatory framework aims to ensure that cryptocurrencies cannot undermine the financial stability of the United States.</p>
<h2>The Government Wants to Prevent Crypto-related Risks</h2>
<p>Among the measures that the U.S. Congress may take to &#8220;redouble its security efforts&#8221; through the new cryptocurrency regulatory framework are: expanding the powers of regulators to prevent the misuse of assets; strengthening transparency and disclosure requirements for crypto companies; and toughening penalties for violating rules on illicit financing, among others.</p>
<p>Additionally, it seeks to protect investors through new &#8220;liability requirements&#8221; for those who commit criminal acts. Although these measures are not currently 100% contemplated in the new regulatory framework, they demonstrate that regulators will not tolerate malicious actors going unpunished.</p>
<p>The release has a pretty strong tone against crypto, but among the measures that could be approved, the financing of additional training for law enforcement —including international partnerships— stands out.</p>
<h2>Biden Wants to Eliminate The Possibility of a New FTX</h2>
<p>The White House emphasized that President Biden is working to avoid new scams similar to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX scandal</a>, perpetrated by the former CEO of the company, Sam Bankman-Fried, through which thousands of Americans <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-owes-over-3-billion-to-50-largest-creditors-court-filing/" data-wpel-link="internal">lost billions of dollars</a>, according to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/maxine-waters-is-not-playing-with-sbf-says-it-is-imperative-that-he-attends-their-hearing/" data-wpel-link="internal">court filings</a>.</p>
<p>The Administration is committed to protecting American investors and consumers from fraud and financial crime. It is also actively working with international partners to combat the illicit use of cryptocurrency. Shortly after the White House&#8217;s announcement, the FED published a press release with new rules regarding cryptocurrencies for banks (with or without FDIC protection).</p>
<p>In order to achieve this goal, the Administration will also be taking steps to strengthen the regulatory structure around digital assets and cryptocurrencies, including strengthening the Anti-Money Laundering (AML) and Know Your Customer (KYC) requirements, as well as the implementation of other measures to protect consumers and investors. The White House also highlighted that it will work with Congress to provide additional regulatory oversight and enforcement tools to better protect American consumers and investors.</p>
<p>The goal is to create a safe and transparent environment for the growth and development of the digital asset and cryptocurrency industry. The Biden Administration&#8217;s announcement is a clear sign that the U.S. government is committed to protecting American investors and consumers from fraud and financial crime and is also actively working with international partners to combat the illicit use of cryptocurrency. But it is doing it his way, even though <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pro-crypto-us-senator-introduces-stablecoin-trust-act-ahead-of-retirement/" data-wpel-link="internal">republicans think very differently</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-publishes-roadmap-to-combat-crypto-fraud-and-protect-investors/" rel="nofollow">Biden Administration Publishes Roadmap to Combat Crypto Fraud and Protect Investors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US SEC Inquires Investment Advisers Over Crypto Custody: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-inquires-investment-advisers-over-crypto-custody-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235109</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/TheSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/TheSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The intersection of crypto and traditional finance is now under the watchful eye of the top US regulator. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is targeting investment advisors for potentially offering digital asset custody to its clients without meeting proper criteria.</p>
<p>Citing three unnamed sources, Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-securities-regulator-probes-investment-advisers-over-crypto-custody-sources-2023-01-27/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reported</a> that the Commission is probing advisers&#8217; efforts to follow the rules around custody of clients&#8217; digital assets after the implosion of FTX.</p>
<ul>
<li>The investigation has not been made public yet, but the enforcement staff of the SEC has sought details from the investment advisers for details with regard to the steps followed by them to assess custody for platforms, including the now-bankrupt crypto exchange, according to one of the sources.</li>
<li>Typically, clients&#8217; digital assets are stored with a third party.</li>
<li>Investment advisers cannot hold custody of client funds or securities if they do not meet certain requirements that are meant to protect the assets.</li>
<li>The SEC does not have any licenses, but the advisers that custody such assets with a firm should be classified to be &#8220;qualified custodians.&#8221; The investment advisers also <a href="https://www.sec.gov/investor/alerts/bulletincustody" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">need</a> to reveal to the clients detailing how their assets are being held.</li>
<li>The Commission has already doubled down and dedicated more resources to its crypto team &#8211; Crypto Assets and Cyber Unit &#8211; which was formerly known as the Cyber Unit.</li>
<li>The latest move could indicate the regulator&#8217;s increasing scrutiny amidst the expansion of traditional Wall Street firms in crypto.</li>
<li class="text__text__1FZLe text__dark-grey__3Ml43 text__regular__2N1Xr text__large__nEccO body__full_width__ekUdw body__large_body__FV5_X article-body__element__2p5pI" data-testid="paragraph-7">Anthony Tu-Sekine, head of Seward and Kissel&#8217;s Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Group, was quoted saying,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p data-testid="paragraph-7">&#8220;This is an obvious compliance issue for investment advisers. If you have custody of client assets that are securities, then you need to custody those with one of these qualified custodians.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-inquires-investment-advisers-over-crypto-custody-report/" rel="nofollow">US SEC Inquires Investment Advisers Over Crypto Custody: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York Senate Bill Proposes Legalizing Crypto for Payment in State Agencies</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-senate-bill-proposes-legalizing-crypto-for-payment-in-state-agencies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 23:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235253</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/new_york-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/new_york-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A recently proposed bill would give state agencies the option to accept Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, or Bitcoin Cash as payment for various fees. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A new bill introduced to the New York Senate seeks to make certain cryptocurrencies a legal form of payment for state agencies.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This would include accepting crypto as payment for civil penalties, fines, taxes, and other fees charged by the state. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As detailed in the </span><a href="https://www.nysenate.gov/legislation/bills/2023/a2532" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">legislation</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> set forth on Thursday, accepted cryptocurrencies would include Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Bitcoin Cash, though it could include more. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Specifically, the legislation describes cryptocurrency as “any form of digital currency in which encryption techniques are used to regulate the generation of units of currency and verify the transfer of funds, operating independently of a central bank.” </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The bill would allow the state to voluntarily enter into agreements “with persons to provide the acceptance, by offices of the state, of cryptocurrency as a means of payment,” though they would not be legally bound to accept such transactions. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The proposal was introduced by Democratic Assembly Member Clyde Vanel. He is often regarded as a crypto-friendly politician, though many members of his party oppose crypto for fears of its </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/23-congressional-democrats-call-for-investigating-proof-of-work-facilities/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">environmental impact</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and use for </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-warrens-bill-will-hurt-crypto-not-russia-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">sanctions evasion</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Last week, a bill was introduced in Arizona by senator Wendy Rogers to make Bitcoin and other cryptos legal tender across the state. Like Vanel’s bill, it would allow state agencies to enter agreements with cryptocurrency issuers to provide a pathway to citizens for paying taxes rent, and fines in crypto. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Rogers proposed a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arizona-state-senator-proposes-a-bill-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">similar bill</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in January 2022, but it didn’t appear to gain traction. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-senate-bill-proposes-legalizing-crypto-for-payment-in-state-agencies/" rel="nofollow">New York Senate Bill Proposes Legalizing Crypto for Payment in State Agencies</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beware These NFT Scammers on Twitter, On-Chain Sleuth Warns</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/beware-these-nft-scammers-on-twitter-on-chain-sleuth-warns/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235247</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ZachXBT warns that Twitter users @radako and @Fitz_lol are stealing from their followers using NFT scams. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The popular on-chain sleuth ZachXBT recently called out two growing Twitter accounts for perpetrating multiple NFT-related scams over the past month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The analyst explained the timeline of events on Friday, including their sudden rise to prominence and the rug pulls they’ve managed to pull off. </span></p>
<h2>Calling Out the Scammers</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As outlined in the analyst’s </span><a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1618959294053097472" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Twitter thread</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Friday, Twitter handles <a href="https://twitter.com/radoko" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@radako</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/Fitz_lol" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@Fitz_lol</a> suddenly began using NFT profile pictures and tweeting about NFTs at the end of last month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though both accounts appear to have joined Twitter years ago, their follower accounts skyrocketed by tens of thousands within the following weeks. Radako, for example, grew his follower count from 2,806 to 47,021 between December 18 and December 26, while Mr. Fit’s followers grew from 6,496 to 32,793 between January 3 and January 11. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">ZachXBT believes these accounts were either sold or stolen, explaining the sudden turn of events. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Shortly after they began making cringe Tweets botting the engagement and promoting 6+ rug projects they create,” he said. For example, the accounts would make tweets provoking people to follow or reply while replying to the other account’s tweets encourages users to follow @FatNutzETH for a “free mint.”</p>
<p></span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The analyst said that we can verify these two accounts as having created the projects using on-chain data. The Ethereum address associated with Radako’s profile picture is only “one hop away” from the deployer Ethereum contract address connected to Fitz’s NFT rug. The latter is also closely connected to public wallets used by <a href="https://twitter.com/TrippyFrogsNFT" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@TrippyFrogsNFT</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/FatNutzETH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@FatNutzETH</a>. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“In total these projects the scammer created netted them ~40 ETH in the span of a few weeks,” he continued. That’s worth roughly $64,000 at writing time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Numerous Twitter users have </span><a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1618959339808784384/photo/2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">called attention</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to projects promoted by Radako and Fitz as being scams, after being rug-pulled themselves. ZachXBT warned followers not to follow, tweet, or reply to “random NFT accounts” simply because they have a high follower count. </span></p>
<h2>The Most Common Scams</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In July 2022, Chainalysis researcher Kim Grauer </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/silver-linings-crypto-scams-have-receded-alongside-bitcoins-price/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">warned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that classic investment scams promising unrealistic returns are still the most common and profitable in the industry. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, more sophisticated scams – including romance and business/ government imposter scams – netted thieves over $300 million between January 2021 and March 2022. Thankfully, crypto scams appeared to have quieted down as the bear market set into place. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">NFT scams often take place after an influential and trusted social media page is compromised. For example, several Bored Ape Yacht Club NFTs have been stolen following a hack of the group’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/beware-bayc-instagram-hacked-several-bored-ape-nfts-already-lost/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Instagram</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in April, and another of its </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/32-nfts-stolen-as-bayc-and-otherside-discord-servers-compromised/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Discord</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in June. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/beware-these-nft-scammers-on-twitter-on-chain-sleuth-warns/" rel="nofollow">Beware These NFT Scammers on Twitter, On-Chain Sleuth Warns</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF Rejected by the SEC Once Again</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-the-sec-once-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235112</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The regulator rejected the joint application for the second time.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) rejected the joint effort of Ark Investment Management and 21Shares to list a spot Bitcoin ETF on the Cboe BZX Exchange.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency dismissed another application filed by the partners in the spring of 2022. </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As indicated in a recent <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-96751.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a>, the American financial regulator did not allow Ark 21Shares&#8217; BTC Spot ETF to launch on the US market.</span></li>
<li>The product was supposed to be listed on the CBOE BZH Exchange. However, the SEC claimed the venue did not &#8220;demonstrate that its proposal is consistent with the requirements&#8221; to prevent manipulation of prices and fraud.</li>
<li>Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Management and the Swiss fintech company &#8211; 21Shares &#8211; displayed intentions to introduce a BTC Spot ETF in the states in 2021, but the watchdog <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/cboebzx/2022/34-94571.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">rejected</a> their application in Q2 last year, citing a lack of investor protection.</li>
<li>The SEC has dismissed many other similar efforts in the recent past, with Grayscale, VanEck, and NYDIG being some examples.</li>
<li>Discouraged by the constant rejections, Grayscale vowed to engage in a legal battle with the regulator. Both sides will <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-and-grayscale-to-debate-on-a-bitcoin-etf-in-court-in-march/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">present</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> their arguments in court at the beginning of March.</span></li>
<li>Despite its unfriendly stance towards such products, the SEC <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-futures-etf-is-live-generates-around-500m-volume-in-its-first-hour-of-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">approved</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the ProShares&#8217; Bitcoin Futures-backed ETF (dubbed BITO) in October 2021. </span></li>
<li>It later <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-approves-valkyries-bitcoin-futures-etf/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> &#8220;yes&#8221; to Valkyrie&#8217;s proposal to list a BTC Futures Fund. The VBTC is available to accredited investors and provides exposure to the primary cryptocurrency.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-the-sec-once-again/" rel="nofollow">Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF Rejected by the SEC Once Again</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strike Integrates Lightning With Point of Sale Giant Clover</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/strike-integrates-lightning-with-point-of-sale-giant-clover/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235232</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264660884_s-2019-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264660884_s-2019-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Strike’s plans to integrate Bitcoin’s lightning network with American POS providers are beginning to take effect. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin payment and wallet company Strike has partnered with fintech giant Fiserv to integrate Bitcoin’s lightning network with the point-of-sale terminal provider, Clover. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This will allow certain Clover merchants to accept lightning payments, expanding Bitcoin’s use case as a medium of exchange. </span></p>
<h2>Dollars Over Lightning</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://twitter.com/jackmallers/status/1618731420998049798" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">explained</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Strike CEO Jack Mallers over Twitter on Thursday, the integration effectively allows Clover to accept “cash-final” USD over lightning. Strike’s service converts Bitcoin payments into a merchant’s currency of choice on the back end, letting merchants accept alternative forms of payment – like Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This doesn&#8217;t integrate Strike. This integrates Lightning,” clarified Mallers in his tweet. “Anyone can use any service to checkout at any enabled merchant. If it can make a Lightning payment, you can use it.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Strike is a custodial platform offering various features to Bitcoin users, including the ability to receive one’s salary in Bitcoin, or interact with the lightning network. However, Strike’s efforts allow alternative lightning wallets, including </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-network-transfers-are-now-fully-available-on-cashapp/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">CashApp</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Muun wallet, to operate with Clover. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">That said, not all Clover merchants have been enabled yet. Thursday marked the beginning of a 90-day pilot period, during which Strike will measure the new lightning-based system’s cost and settlement speeds compared to other networks, alongside any new business that lightning attracts. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After the pilot, Strike will look to integrate with Clover directly through its App Store.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This would enable Lightning as an accepted payment network for all Clover merchants by default, sitting next to card networks like Visa and MasterCard,” he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Mallers is a loud proponent of Bitcoin’s lightning network as a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-is-superior-to-all-other-payment-networks-strike-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">superior payment network</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> compared to legacy alternatives. In an interview with Yahoo Finance last year, he called it cheaper, faster, global, more inclusive, and more innovative than its competitors, arguing that it can interface with dollars just as well as BTC. </span></p>
<h2>Strike’s Grand Mission</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At Bitcoin 2022 last year in Miami, Mallers </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-announces-integration-with-shopify-to-facilitate-bitcoin-payments-via-lightning-network/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">revealed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Strike had partnered with Shopify, Blackhawk, and NCR, to integrate lightning for merchants across the United States, much like its doing with Clover. This would enable lightning payments at multiple leading American retailers, including McDonald’s, Walmart, and Macy’s. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While originally promised to be fully implemented within 2022, Mallers published a blog post at the end of December admitting that his timelines for the integrations were off. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“These partnerships and developments are huge and they’re simply going to take a bit longer than I initially thought,” he wrote. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-integrates-lightning-with-point-of-sale-giant-clover/" rel="nofollow">Strike Integrates Lightning With Point of Sale Giant Clover</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bithumb Offices Raided as Legal Woes Pile up (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-offices-raided-as-legal-woes-pile-up-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235156</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The raid centers around suspected price manipulation of an unidentified coin.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More troubles for South Korean crypto exchange Bithumb brews as its offices were reportedly raided on Thursday.</p>
<p>Authorities launched an investigation into potential price manipulation of a coin listed on the platform, according to a <a href="https://www.yna.co.kr/view/AKR20230126165500004?input=1195m" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by Yonhap. The token in question has not been revealed.</p>
<p>Prosecutors said they are probing transactions linked to a specific person or entity allegedly manipulating the coin&#8217;s price to make a profit. In a statement, the Seoul District Prosecutor&#8217;s Office said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is a search and seizure to secure the transaction details of a specific coin, and it has nothing to do with Bithumb.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to Bithumb, the prosecutors are planning to look into the transaction details at other crypto exchanges where the token is listed.</p>
<h2>Founder&#8217;s Arrest</h2>
<p>The latest development comes just days after South Korean authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-real-owner-faces-arrest-warrant-on-embezzlement-charges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">requested</a> an arrest warrant for Kang Jong-Hyun, Bithumb&#8217;s chairman and owner, over embezzlement allegations. Two other executives, including his younger sister, Kang Ji-Yeon, the CEO of two publicly traded Bithumb affiliates &#8211; Inbiogen and Bucket Studio -were also accused of embezzlement, breach of trust, and illegal transactions.</p>
<p>The Seoul Southern District Prosecutor’s Office alleged that the executives had swindled company funds and conspired to manipulate stock prices.</p>
<p>Bithumb is one of five remaining crypto exchanges in the country following an industry-wide crackdown in 2021 which led to the shutdown of nearly 70 local trading venues that failed to meet regulatory requirements. Several of its executives have faced serious charges in recent years.</p>
<p>In December, the crypto exchange&#8217;s largest shareholder, Park Mo, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vp-of-bithumb-linked-company-found-dead-in-seoul-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">found</a> dead outside his home after being framed by the Kang siblings as a suspect in prosecutors’ investigation into the alleged embezzlement and stock manipulation. Mo was arrested for allegedly destroying evidence prior to a prosecution search. Several local media reports suggest that the exec took his own life.</p>
<h2>Tax Fraud Charges</h2>
<p>In yet another separate probe, the South Korean National Tax Service (NTS) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korea-starts-investigating-crypto-exchange-bithumb-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a &#8220;special tax investigation&#8221; against Bithumb Korea and Bithumb Holdings and its affiliates for potential tax evasion via domestic and international transactions.</p>
<p>Bithumb was subjected to tax investigation for the second time after 2018 when it was slapped with a multi-million-dollar bill for back taxes, even as the investigation found the company not guilty of tax evasion.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-offices-raided-as-legal-woes-pile-up-report/" rel="nofollow">Bithumb Offices Raided as Legal Woes Pile up (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bearish Signs for Ripple Appear, Will $0.40 Hold? (XRP Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bearish-signs-for-ripple-appear-will-0-40-hold-xrp-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 16:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235192</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Presently, XRP&#8217;s price action is not looking overly promising against either USDT or BTC. Things could worsen in the coming days if all remains as it is right now. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart On the daily chart, the price continues its struggle to break above the $0.43 resistance level, following a push [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Presently, XRP&#8217;s price action is not looking overly promising against either USDT or BTC. Things could worsen in the coming days if all remains as it is right now.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price continues its struggle to break above the $0.43 resistance level, following a push above both the 50-day and 200-day moving average lines.</p>
<p>In case the cryptocurrency finally moves beyond the aforementioned level, a rally toward the $0.55 resistance area could be expected. This scenario would likely lead to a new bullish phase in the short term.</p>
<p>On the contrary, a rejection from the $0.43 level would likely initiate a decline toward the 50-day moving average located around the $0.35 mark, and the $0.3 support level would even be highly probable.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235193" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235193" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-235193 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2701231" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-Daily-Jan-27-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235193" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Against Bitcoin, the price is seemingly on the verge of breaking the 0.000018 level to the downside after days of consolidation above it. This would lead to a drop towards the lower boundary of the descending channel and the 0.000015 area.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the 50-day MA is also crossing the 200-day MA to the downside, around the 0.00002 mark. This is considered a bearish signal and would further increase the probability of a drop toward the 0.000015 level in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235194" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235194" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-235194 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2701232" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/XRPBTC-4H-Jan-27-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235194" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bearish-signs-for-ripple-appear-will-0-40-hold-xrp-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bearish Signs for Ripple Appear, Will $0.40 Hold? (XRP Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos Leads L1 Trade With 130% Gains, Bitcoin Bulls Fight For $23K, Sentiment Improves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-leads-l1-trade-with-130-gains-bitcoin-bulls-fight-for-23k-sentiment-improves-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235201</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aptos is this week's hottest story, gaining over 130% in seven days. Bitcoin's dominance, however, continues increasing as BTC outperforms the altcoin market.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The market sentiment continues to improve as cryptocurrencies see another week of trading in the green. The market added around $70 billion to its total capitalization, while the overall sentiment is at a 10-month high.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance continues to increase. This means it fared better than altcoins in terms of price performance. The leading cryptocurrency managed to add around 9% and is now battling for the important level at $23,000. A couple of days ago, the price pushed toward $24K aggressively but was immediately rejected in what were a few hours of massive volatility.</p>
<p>Macroeconomic data, according to many, favors risk-on assets as inflation is slowing down, the US GDP numbers were better than expected, and today&#8217;s PCE was in line with expectations. This has, perhaps, prevented any considerable corrections in January, as the price is moving almost entirely up only.</p>
<p>This hasn&#8217;t been the case for many altcoins.</p>
<p>For example, ETH is up around 2%, heavily underperforming Bitcoin. BNB is about 3.4%, XRP &#8211; 3.5%, and so forth. However, others, such as ADA, MATIC, Solana, and DOT, charted increases above 10%.</p>
<p>This brings us to this week&#8217;s hottest story &#8211; Aptos. In fact, APT has been dominating throughout the entire month, charting a massive increase of 400% in the past 30 days. Over the last week alone, it gained about 130%. Here are a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-why-aptos-exploded-by-400-in-30-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">few reasons</a> why this might be.</p>
<p>All in all, the market continues to trend upward. It remains very interesting to see if this will continue or if the broader concerns of a macroeconomic downturn will drag it down in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1085B | 24H Vol: 69B | BTC Dominance: 41%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BTC:</strong> $23,091 (+9.5%) | <strong>ETH:</strong> $1,584 (+2.4%) | <strong>BNB</strong>: $305 (3.4%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-235205" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover.jpg" alt="golden_bull_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/golden_bull_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>3 Reasons Why Aptos Exploded by 400% in 30 Days. </strong>Aptos is this week&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency in terms of overall price performance, at least amongst the larger caps. Here are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-reasons-why-aptos-exploded-by-400-in-30-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">three possible reasons</a> why it&#8217;s up 400% in the past 30 days.</p>
<p><strong>Today in 2014: Ethereum Was Announced by Vitalik Buterin on Bitcointalk. </strong>Nine years ago, Vitalik Buterin first <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/today-in-2014-ethereum-was-announced-by-vitalik-buterin-on-bitcointalk/" data-wpel-link="internal">introduced</a> Ethereum on the Bitcointalk forum. It&#8217;s safe to say that almost a decade later, the project has become among the most important ones in the industry.</p>
<p><strong>BTC Fear and Greed Index Flashes &#8220;Greed&#8221; for the First Time in 10 Months. </strong>For the first time in 10 months, the Bitcoin fear and greed index <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-fear-and-greed-index-flashes-greed-for-the-first-time-in-10-months/" data-wpel-link="internal">flashed</a> &#8220;greed.&#8221; This is an indication of the improving market sentiment following the most recent rally in BTC&#8217;s price.</p>
<p><strong>FTX Creditors List Includes Apple, Google, Amazon, WSJ, and Even Australia&#8217;s Govt. </strong>A recent court filing <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-creditors-list-include-apple-google-amazon-wsj-and-even-australias-govt/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the list of entities that FTX owes money to includes, but is not limited to, Apple, Google, Amazon, the Wall Street Journal, and even Australia&#8217;s government.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood&#8217;s Twitter Hacked, Used to Promote Scam Token. </strong>The Twitter account of the popular retail-oriented trading platform, Robinhood, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhoods-twitter-hacked-used-to-promote-scam-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">hacked</a> earlier this week. It was used to promote a scam token.</p>
<p><strong>dYdX Extends 156 Million Token Lock-up Period by 10 Months. </strong>The decentralized cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; dYdX &#8211; has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-extends-156-million-token-lock-up-period-by-10-months/" data-wpel-link="internal">postponed</a> its plans to unlock around 156 million tokens for another 10 months. This propelled the price of its native cryptocurrency by a whopping 24% in a day.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Aptos, and Binance Coin – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-jan-27-eth-xrp-ada-apt-and-bnb/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-leads-l1-trade-with-130-gains-bitcoin-bulls-fight-for-23k-sentiment-improves-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">Aptos Leads L1 Trade With 130% Gains, Bitcoin Bulls Fight For $23K, Sentiment Improves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flare Partners With Blockchain Security Specialist FYEO For Ongoing Audits</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/flare-partners-with-blockchain-security-specialist-fyeo-for-ongoing-audits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235179</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Fyeo_flare.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Fyeo_flare.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, 26th January 2023] Flare is pleased to announce an official partnership with blockchain security specialist FYEO. The firm will perform ongoing security audits of Flare’s codebases, providing actionable feedback to support safer smart contract development and help to minimize risk for all users of the network. Rigorous professional auditing and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, 26th January 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Flare is pleased to announce an official partnership with blockchain security specialist FYEO. The firm will perform ongoing security audits of Flare’s codebases, providing actionable feedback to support safer smart contract development and help to minimize risk for all users of the network.</p>
<p>Rigorous professional auditing and testing are an important part of Flare’s blockchain security strategy. Alongside stringent internal testing measures, ongoing code audits help to establish a level of security assurance to application developers and users on the network.</p>
<blockquote><p>Flare Co-Founder &amp; CEO Hugo Philion said, “We are building our protocols with auditor reviews initiated from close to day one. We believe this guarantees a safer outcome than an auditor reviewing an entire code base at the end of development.”</p></blockquote>
<p>In addition to continuous auditing from partners including FYEO, Flare also employs rigorous testing with testnets and a Canary network called Songbird. The Canary network is a live but more experimental version of Flare (similar to Kusama’s relationship to Polkadot) where Flare can test their protocols. The network advises application developers and builders to do the same. Flare recognizes that risk minimization from both an auditing and testnet perspective is crucial to building reputational trust amongst users.</p>
<blockquote><p>In the words of Flare Co-Founder, Hugo Philion, &#8220;Our game as an organization within the industry is to mitigate the risk in blockchain such that people feel comfortable to use it. As a result of that, the usage can increase substantially.”</p>
<p>Tammy Kahn, Co-CEO of FYEO, said, “FYEO could not be more aligned with this vision for supporting adoption through user risk minimization, and look forward to our continuous work with Flare as it expands its presence as a leader of decentralized innovation.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>About Flare</h2>
<p><a href="https://flare.network/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Flare</a> is an EVM-based Layer 1 blockchain designed to allow developers to build applications that can use data from other chains and the internet. By providing decentralized access to high-integrity data, Flare enables new use cases and monetisation models.</p>
<p>Flare’s <a href="https://flare.network/stateconnector/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">State Connector</a> protocols enable information, both from other blockchains and the internet to be used securely, scalably and trustlessly with smart contracts on Flare.</p>
<p>The Flare Time Series Oracle delivers highly-decentralized price and data feeds to dapps on Flare, without relying on centralized providers.</p>
<p>Build on Flare with more data than ever before or build with Flare to serve multiple ecosystems.</p>
<h2>About FYEO</h2>
<p>FYEO is focused on solving the growing problem of cyber crime in Web3. FYEO’s code audit team is composed of some of the best DeFi logic experts in the world having worked on 100s of projects and protocols such as Solana, Ethereum, Cardano, ICON, Hyperlane, Sommelier Finance, and more. Its flagship product, FYEO Domain Intelligence, which provides real-time threat monitoring and intelligence for organizations, was developed to provide unparalleled security and address present-day security issues impacting both organizations and individuals. Today, the FYEO team continues its work to identify and evolve its products to solve the biggest security problems facing Web3 ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/flare-partners-with-blockchain-security-specialist-fyeo-for-ongoing-audits/" rel="nofollow">Flare Partners With Blockchain Security Specialist FYEO For Ongoing Audits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
