<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:49:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>I Will Always Stick With Bitcoin: American Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones III</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/i-will-always-stick-with-bitcoin-american-billionaire-paul-tudor-jones-iii/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250847</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PaulTudorJones.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PaulTudorJones.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Paul Tudor Jones likes bitcoin because of its fixed maximum supply. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legendary hedge fund manager &#8211; Paul Tudor Jones III &#8211; said he will always keep a &#8220;small&#8221; exposure to bitcoin since it is &#8220;the only thing that humans can&#8217;t adjust the supply in.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American billionaire also suggested that the US Federal Reserve will cease its aggressive interest rate hike policy. Many experts previously opined that such a move could benefit the entire cryptocurrency industry and positively affect BTC&#8217;s price. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTC Investor for Life </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prominent legacy investor Paul Tudor Jones, who entered bitcoin&#8217;s ecosystem in 2017, seems to remain tied to the primary cryptocurrency for the rest of his life. In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/15/paul-tudor-jones-says-hes-going-to-keep-bitcoin-in-his-portfolio.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for CNBC, he vowed to always have exposure, praising its fixed supply of 21 million coins ever to exist:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;From the beginning, I&#8217;ve always said I want to have a small allocation to it because it&#8217;s a great tail event. It&#8217;s the only thing that humans can&#8217;t adjust the supply in. So I&#8217;m sticking with it; I&#8217;m going to always stick with it. It&#8217;s just a small diversification in my portfolio.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_250873" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250873" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250873" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor.webp" alt="Paul Tudor Jones" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor.webp 960w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor-300x200.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor-768x512.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Paul-Tudor-50x33.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250873" class="wp-caption-text">Paul Tudor Jones, Source: Forbes</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For some HODLers who have been present long enough in the space to witness BTC trading at nearly $70,000, the current valuation could seem like a good buying opportunity. Such is the case with Jones, who said he &#8220;would probably&#8221; purchase more of it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, the billionaire touched upon the inflationary environment in the USA and the Fed&#8217;s efforts to solve the issue. According to him, the central bank&#8217;s interest rate hikes at the beginning of May (bringing the benchmark to 5%-5.25%) were the last one. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Higher rates result in higher borrowing costs which logically lowers consumer spending and makes risky investments (such as dealing with crypto) less appealing. Numerous experts have argued that the opposite scenario could trigger a bull run for digital assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One example is Anthony Scaramucci &#8211; the Founder of SkyBridge Capital and former White House official &#8211; who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bull-market-to-start-once-us-inflation-drops-to-4-5-scaramucci/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I do believe that the Fed declares victory at 4% to 5% inflation. If I&#8217;m right, there will be a resurgence in the market. There&#8217;ll be a lot of short covering in crypto, and there&#8217;ll be a rebirth of risk assets.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paul Tudor Jones&#8217; Crypto Journey</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 68-year-old billionaire initially bought Bitcoin in 2017 at around $10,000 and later doubled his money by selling at $20K. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His more notable interaction with the asset began in the spring of 2020 (shortly after the COVID-19 pandemic hit the financial world) when he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/adoption-the-reason-why-hedge-fund-manager-paul-tudor-jones-has-started-buying-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">purchased</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> BTC as a hedge against inflation. Back then, the American forecasted that inflation would surge in a short period of time, prompted by the mass printing of fiat currency by central banks. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The best profit-maximizing strategy is to own the faster horse. If I am forced to forecast, my bet is it will be Bitcoin,&#8221; he stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His prediction came true, with inflation hitting record levels in many parts of the globe. On the other hand, BTC skyrocketed to almost $70K at the end of 2021 before diving in 2022. Still, the asset started the ongoing year on the right foot, reclaiming some of its lost ground. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paul Tudor Jones&#8217; support towards BTC has risen so much in the following years that at one point, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-is-winning-the-race-against-gold-paul-tudor-jones/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">deemed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it superior to gold as a hedge against inflation:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I do think we&#8217;re moving into an increasingly digitized world. Clearly, there&#8217;s a place for crypto, and clearly, it&#8217;s winning the race against gold at the moment, right?&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/i-will-always-stick-with-bitcoin-american-billionaire-paul-tudor-jones-iii/" rel="nofollow">I Will Always Stick With Bitcoin: American Billionaire Paul Tudor Jones III</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Moves to Block Coinbase’s Request for Clarification in Court (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-moves-to-block-coinbases-request-for-clarification-in-court-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 23:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250819</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[If the judge were to grant the SEC’s request, Coinbase would be left trying to figure out the SEC's intent on its own.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Late last month, Coinbase – who had previously been hit with a Wells notice, an informal warning from the SEC usually followed by a lawsuit – asked the courts to force the agency to clearly explain what actions they should take in order to remain compliant.</p>
<p>The SEC, on the other hand, remains tight-lipped.</p>
<h2>Amicable Discussion Preferred</h2>
<p>According to Brian Armstrong – the CEO of Coinbase – his firm <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-slams-sec-says-gensler-led-agency-caused-untold-harm-to-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">intends</a> to fight the current trend of regulation by enforcement and seeks to promote cooperation and amicable discussion regarding regulation.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Spent the day in DC meeting with members of Congress. We need regulatory clarity in the U.S. for the centralized players in crypto for many reasons – consumer protection, national security, economic growth, etc. The SEC has caused untold harm to America with its policy of regulation by enforcement. We will fight to fix that.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The exec further said the company is ready to defend itself in court but would prefer not to and reiterated that he and his exchange are open to good faith talks with regulators.</p>
<h2>Framework Already Established, Says Gensler</h2>
<p>In spite of Coinbase’s willingness to negotiate, Gary Gensler, the head of the SEC, stated in court that existing regulation is already clear and that crypto exchanges simply refuse to take it into account, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-16/sec-urges-judge-to-reject-coinbase-demand-for-rules-explanation" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Bloomberg.</p>
<p>In return, Coinbase requested a clear rule-making guideline to abide by, submitted via a notice-and-comment process that would allow the newly clarified rules to be examined in public.</p>
<p>Unfortunately for the exchange, the SEC moved to block the request in court, <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.ca3.119939/gov.uscourts.ca3.119939.26.0_1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stating</a> that regulation may take years to set in stone.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Coinbase’s preference for faster or different regulatory action by the commission does not entitle it to extraordinary relief from this court. The petition should be denied.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Paul Grewal, Coinbase’s chief legal officer, took to Twitter to reiterate his firm’s stance that the SEC does not provide clarity to the companies it regulates.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today the SEC responded to Coinbase’s petition for a writ of mandamus — asking the court to require the SEC to respond just yes or no to whether it will undertake rulemaking for our industry. The SEC’s answer? A resounding maybe. 1/7</p>
<p>— paulgrewal.eth (@iampaulgrewal) <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1658271335066505217?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The securities regulator has stated that Gensler’s public comments are not to be taken as policy statements – despite acknowledging that they may continue to use enforcement actions in lieu of a regulatory framework until they’ve smoothed out the edges.</p>
<p>In the meantime, Coinbase has remained firm in its position, stating that they do not list securities. According to a spokesperson for the company, the exchange already takes SEC guidelines regarding securities into account when deciding which tokens to list, leading them to reject about 90% of applications.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-moves-to-block-coinbases-request-for-clarification-in-court-report/" rel="nofollow">SEC Moves to Block Coinbase’s Request for Clarification in Court (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Worldcoin Project Closing $100M: Is It About Freedom or Surveillance? (Op-Ed)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/worldcoin-project-closing-100m-is-it-about-freedom-or-surveillance-op-ed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 21:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250747</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/digital_world_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/digital_world_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Sam Altman's Worldcoin cryptocurrency aims to use blockchain for retina scans and universal basic income (UBI). But wil it lead to more freedom or surveillance?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been a big week for Worldcoin, the blockchain brainchild of OpenAI CEO Sam Altman. The blockchain biometrics project is closing a $100 million funding deal. The investors in this round include new backers in addition to previous ones.</p>
<h2>Worldcoin&#8217;s $100 Million Seed Round</h2>
<p>Past seed round investors in Worldcoin include a16z (Andreessen Horowitz), Coinbase&#8217;s venture capital division, Khosla Ventures, and even Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>(The disgraced FTX founder is currently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-files-to-dismiss-almost-all-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal">defending</a> against multiple U.S. criminal charges and enforcement actions.)</p>
<p>Fortune <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/05/15/openai-sam-altman-100-million-worldcoin-funding-iris-human-artificial-intelligence/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The funding news is a bright spot in a bleak year for crypto investments. Venture funding for Web3 startups plummeted from $9.1 billion in the first quarter of 2022 to $1.7 billion in 2023, an 82% year-over-year decrease, according to Crunchbase.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The ChatGPT founder&#8217;s big fundraiser shows there&#8217;s still enormous VC demand for investments in the crypto space. That&#8217;s despite the year-long crypto winter that just may have ended in January, a string of failed crypto companies in recent months, and an epic regulatory battle with U.S. regulators.</p>
<h2>Biometric Keys: Freedom or Surveillance?</h2>
<p>Worldcoin has bold ambitions to bring biometric identification to Web 3.0.</p>
<p>The OpenAI founder&#8217;s cryptocurrency project seeks to collect and develop ID authentication support for retina scans. VCs enthusiastic backing of the project means they might just be able to deliver on such a bold plan.</p>
<p>But is Worldcoin more apt to unleash the benefits of blockchain freedom or high-tech, Orwellian surveillance capitalism? For decades now, civil libertarians have considered the digitalization of medical records fraught with legal and humanitarian dangers.</p>
<p>Using biometric data as a security and authentication standard may violate people&#8217;s privacy. Worldcoin&#8217;s aim would be to create a world that eventually demands folks give up their biomarkers to use apps and do business.</p>
<p>Although, this is not the inevitable outcome of Worldcoin. Moving biometric data to the blockchain and using Web 3 techniques to manage private, personally identifying info for Internet users might be the safest, fairest, freest way to do it. Web 3 can use <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zero-knowledge-proofs-a-trend-towards-blockchain-privacy/" data-wpel-link="internal">zk-proofs</a> and multi-party computation to keep that data private while proving to servers that request it that the user is who they say they are.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/worldcoin-project-closing-100m-is-it-about-freedom-or-surveillance-op-ed/" rel="nofollow">Worldcoin Project Closing $100M: Is It About Freedom or Surveillance? (Op-Ed)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin&#8217;s Long-Term Metrics Resemble Early Stages From Previous Bull Markets: Bitfinex</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-long-term-metrics-resemble-early-stages-from-previous-bull-markets-bitfinex/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250799</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-7.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-7.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Short-term metrics have a different story to tell. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As speculators flocked to mint BRC-20 tokens via text inscriptions, Bitcoin blockspace saw an explosion in demand in recent weeks.</p>
<p>This dramatic shift in network activity triggered a surge in transaction fees to levels not seen in the last two years.</p>
<h2>Signs of Strain</h2>
<p>A new <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitfinex-Alpha-54.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> published by Bitfinex observed that the inception of BRC-20 and Bitcoin-based smart contracts is transforming the blockchain into a more &#8220;dynamic, smart-contract-enabled chain&#8221; from its traditional repute of a &#8220;straightforward digital currency ledger.&#8221;</p>
<p>Data suggested that BRC-20 tokens accounted for more than 60% of all transaction activity on the Bitcoin blockchain last week, contributing nearly 43% of all fees.</p>
<p>However, the rapid popularity of BRC-20 and subsequent fee surge have strained other metrics. Active and new addresses interacting with the network are nearing two-year and annual lows, respectively. Such a trend could potentially indicate that higher transaction fees are likely deterring new and existing Bitcoin network users.</p>
<p>The report added that while higher transaction fees have likely deterred new Bitcoin addresses from increasing, it has boosted network health. The brief bump in mining revenue was certainly a welcome reprieve for network miners after the savage bear market of 2022. So much so that Bitcoin miners <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">earned</a> a total of $17.75 million in revenues on May 8th.</p>
<h2>Long-Term Bitcoin Metrics</h2>
<p>In the short term, the events of last week, including Binance&#8217;s recent double halt of Bitcoin withdrawals, appear to be impacting the flagship crypto-asset sentiment negatively. Hence, the short-term metrics still indicate a possible pullback in Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>On zooming out, the long-term on-chain indicators, on the other hand, appeared more favorable and resemble the early stages of the previous bull markets. It was observed that a potent bullish sign for the market came in the form of Bitcoin trading comfortably above its 200 Day Moving Average as well as its Realised Price.</p>
<p>Another positive sign was the Bitcoin Realised HODL Multiple which was on an upward trajectory over the last 90 days. This essentially indicated that the USD-denominated wealth is moving back towards new demand inflows. In such a case, &#8220;even when profits are being realized, the market is capable of absorbing them.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-long-term-metrics-resemble-early-stages-from-previous-bull-markets-bitfinex/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin&#8217;s Long-Term Metrics Resemble Early Stages From Previous Bull Markets: Bitfinex</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Under Fire for Allegedly Exposing User Seed Phrases</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-under-fire-for-allegedly-exposing-user-seed-phrases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 18:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250920</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/LedgerSecurity-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/LedgerSecurity-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ledger's new wallet firmware update has many concerned that the company has had access to its users’ private keys all along. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto hardware wallet provider Ledger is receiving major backlash from its online user base after releasing a controversial update that many fear exposes major security flaws with the manufacturer. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger has claimed that the new functionality is both safe and entirely optional, but security experts and crypto holders are already distancing themselves from the company. </span></p>
<h2>Ledger’s Controversial Recovery Service</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Concerns began to swell late on Monday after Reddit user Joe_Smith _Reddit published a </span><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ledgerwallet/comments/13itm7u/comment/jkbyyfp/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> asking for an official “yes or no” on whether Ledger has a built-in backdoor for accessing users’ private keys. A private key is the secret alphanumeric string that lets users access their crypto on the blockchain. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Smith’s question specifically pertained to Ledger’s new “Ledger Recover” service – a </span><a href="https://www.ledger.com/recover" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">subscription service</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for Nano X device holders that lets them recover their crypto even if they’ve lost both their wallet device and recovery phrase. A recovery phrase is a user’s private key expressed in mnemonic form.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Ledger, the service – enabled in firmware update 2.2.1 – works by duplicating the device’s recovery phrase on the device, encrypting the copy, fragmenting it into three parts, and securing it with Ledger, Coincover, and a third unnamed provider. To access the service, users must verify their identity using an ID document and a selfie recording. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a follow-up </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Ledger/status/1658458714771169282" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Twitter thread</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Ledger clarified that the service is entirely “optional” and is not automatically enabled by any firmware update. “Your Secret Recovery Phrase is securely generated on your device. We have no access to it,” the company added. </span></p>
<h2>Can Ledger “Rug” Users’ Private Keys?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite Ledgers’ assurances, community concerns continued to swell around one key idea: the update proved that Ledger devices do not, despite the manufacturer’s claims, protect its users’ private keys from all external access. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Trusting the proprietary secure element to do its part was the single thread that held this company together and now, that&#8217;s been severed,” wrote Reddit user StPinkie in response to Ledger on Tuesday. “I can no longer recommend Ledger to anyone who gives a damn about their digital sovereignty.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Popular crypto developer, writer, and auditor “foobar” on Twitter echoed this response, urging followers to migrate away from Ledger wallets immediately.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Stop using Ledger hardware wallets. Migrate away from them immediately. They’ve shown nothing but gross incompetence and wild misunderstanding of their own purpose. And now they’ve publicly  admitted to intentionally backdooring their own proprietary hardware. Stop using Ledger <a href="https://t.co/LLFFUsOW4y" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/LLFFUsOW4y</a></p>
<p>&mdash; foobar (@0xfoobar) <a href="https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1658460603831263232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The glaring issue with this update is that this exposes your private key can be rugged at any time with a malicious or mistaken firmware update,” he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1658478186408337408" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">added</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other users </span><a href="https://twitter.com/wholisticguy/status/1658480962483929089" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">noted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the contradiction between Ledger’s assertions on its website that users’ keys “never leave the device,” versus its Ledger Recover service, which “distributes” users&#8217; private keys to three different providers in shards, according to CEO Pascal Gauthier. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This is a masterclass in how to kill your core business trying to “innovate”. </p>
<p>I kept recommending you guys even after doxxing your customers, but this is the final straw. </p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/270c.png" alt="✌" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Chris Dunn (@ChrisDunnTV) <a href="https://twitter.com/ChrisDunnTV/status/1658482003694751744?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many in the community recommended that Ledger launch a separate wallet that offers a seed-recovery service, rather than rolling it out as a firmware update to existing customers who expected maximum security from their devices. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger has </span><a href="https://www.ledger.com/message-ledgers-ceo-data-leak" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">compromised</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> user security in the past by accidentally leaking personal information about over 270,000 customers in July 2020, who were later victims to email and SMS phishing campaigns. This leak did not impact the security of users’ private keys. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ledger sales </span><a href="https://twitter.com/jacqmelinek/status/1592213991090229248?s=20&amp;t=ufH0fSaCx0x2ituAtNfzkQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">spiked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in the aftermath of FTX’s collapse in November, precisely as investors sought to secure their own crypto safely without trusting centralized intermediaries. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-under-fire-for-allegedly-exposing-user-seed-phrases/" rel="nofollow">Ledger Under Fire for Allegedly Exposing User Seed Phrases</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Optimism Bedrock Upgrade Release Date Revealed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/optimism-bedrock-upgrade-release-date-revealed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism (OP)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250834</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Optimism_Bedrock.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Optimism_Bedrock.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Bedrock upgrade will bring a 47% reduction in protocol costs and security fees to Optimism Mainnet.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Optimism, a popular layer-2 blockchain, is set to release its long-awaited Bedrock upgrade on June 6th at 16:00 UTC.</p>
<p>The Bedrock release &#8211; which is a complete rewrite of an entire rollup stack &#8211; is expected to be the largest upgrade ever released on OP Mainnet with a focus on reducing fees and improving Ethereum compatibility.</p>
<h2>Bedrock Upgrade</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://twitter.com/optimismFND/status/1658202279147601921" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announcement</a>, the upgrade will require 2-4 hours of downtime for OP Mainnet, during which there will be downtime at the chain and infrastructure level while the old sequencer is spun down and the Bedrock sequencer starts up.</p>
<p>Transactions, deposits, and withdrawals will also remain unavailable for the duration, and the chain will not be progressing. While the read access across most OP Mainnet nodes will stay online, users may encounter a slight decrease in performance during the migration process.</p>
<p>Bedrock seeks to improve on its predecessor by reducing transaction fees with the help of optimized batch compression and Ethereum as a data availability layer. It also focuses on shortening delays of including layer-1 transactions in rollups by handling their re-orgs more &#8220;gracefully.&#8221; In addition to improving node performance by removing technical debt, it will also enable modular proof systems via code reuse.</p>
<p>The team behind the project stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We couldn’t be more thrilled to bring Bedrock to OP Mainnet. The protocol team at OP Labs has been working very hard for over a year to bring this complete re-architecture of the OP Stack to production.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The development has had no impact on the price of its native OP token, which was down by nearly 4% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<h2>Optimism&#8217;s Waning Market Share</h2>
<p>The move comes as competition within Ethereum&#8217;s layer-2 ecosystem heats up. Optimism has enjoyed its fair share of success, taking on an early lead over the space with its optimistic rollup solutions that offer high compatibility with the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). However, its market dominance has been threatened by EVM-compatible zero-knowledge rollups (ZkEVMs), which have gained significant prominence lately.</p>
<p>Optimism <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/projects/optimism" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">witnessed</a> no notable growth in its TVL throughout this year and was currently hovering around $1.71 billion. Besides the emerging competition from zkEVMs, the buzz surrounding Arbitrum&#8217;s recent airdrop could be another factor for Optimism&#8217;s receding share.</p>
<p>At over $252 million in TVL, ZKSync Era has been rapidly increasing its presence across the layer-2 spectrum. In fact, the general-purpose zk-roll-up platform created by Matter Labs <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/projects/zksync-era#chart" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">surpassed</a> Optimism in terms of transactions in May.</p>
<p>Moreover, Polygon zkEVM has also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-announces-polygon-bridge-for-its-zero-knowledge-rollup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">witnessed</a> an impressive growth to $9.15 billion in TVL since its beta mainnet launch in March this year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/optimism-bedrock-upgrade-release-date-revealed/" rel="nofollow">Optimism Bedrock Upgrade Release Date Revealed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Asked ChatGPT Which 5 Cryptos Will Survive in 10 Years: The Answer Might Surprise You</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-which-5-cryptos-will-survive-in-10-years-the-answer-might-surprise-you/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250879</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_crystalball_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/chatgpt_crystalball_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[We asked ChatGPT one of the more pressing questions that many are wondering about. The answer might indeed surprise you.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many crypto naysayers are heard arguing that most of the existing projects won&#8217;t stand the test of time. And it&#8217;s true that a lot of them haven&#8217;t been existing for a long period. In the grand scheme of things, even Bitcoin is a baby.</p>
<p>With that said, we took the opportunity to talk to no other but ChatGPT itself &#8211; the AI language model that took the world by storm in the past few months.</p>
<p>We decided to ask which five cryptocurrencies will survive in the coming decade. The answer is somewhat interesting.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin is no Surprise</h2>
<p>To anyone following the cryptocurrency industry, it shouldn&#8217;t come much as a surprise that Bitcoin took the first spot. ChatGPT argued that it&#8217;s the first and most well-known cryptocurrency.</p>
<blockquote><p>Bitcoin has established itself as a store of value and a medium of exchange. It has a significant network effect, widespread adoption, and strong brand recognition.</p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that there&#8217;s a massive debate within the community about whether BTC serves as a good medium of exchange or an even better store of value. Both sides of it seem to be rather polarized, and it&#8217;s a topic debated for a long while. ChatGPT seems to consider it to be both. That&#8217;s cool.</p>
<p>At this point, it&#8217;s worth noting that the response also included a disclaimer:</p>
<blockquote><p>I can&#8217;t predict the future with certainty, especially when it comes to the volatile cryptocurrency market.</p></blockquote>
<p>It also clarified that its knowledge cutoff was in September 2021. This is what the top 10 (by market cap) looked like back then:</p>
<figure id="attachment_250884" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250884" style="width: 1383px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250884" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic.jpg" alt="img1_crypto_historic" width="1383" height="502" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic.jpg 1383w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic-300x109.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic-1024x372.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic-768x279.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/img1_crypto_historic-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1383px) 100vw, 1383px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250884" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinMarketCap</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Number Two and Three Also Expected</h2>
<p>ChatGPT argued that ETH and BNB will also stand the test of time. Commenting on Ethereum, it explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Ethereum&#8217;s robust ecosystem and ongoing development make it a prominent player in the cryptocurrency space.</p></blockquote>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum&#8217;s merge</a> had not taken place at the time of ChatGPT&#8217;s knowledge cutoff on this topic.</p>
<p>At number three came BNB &#8211; the native cryptocurrency of the Binance exchange. The AI explained:</p>
<blockquote><p>Binance&#8217;s strong market position and innovative offerings contribute to BNB&#8217;s potential longevity.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Cardano Also Made the Cut</h2>
<p>According to ChatGPT, ADA has a unique approach and a growing community, and this makes it a cryptocurrency to watch.</p>
<p>Now, to those of you who have been following the industry for a while, this probably doesn&#8217;t come much as a surprise since Cardano has been amongst the frontrunners for quite some time.</p>
<p>Charles Hoskinson, Cardano&#8217;s founder, is also one of the founding members of Ethereum.</p>
<p>But this is where things get a bit interesting and, quite frankly, surprising.</p>
<h2>Tether or Ripple? ChatGPT Thinks Neither</h2>
<p>Tether&#8217;s USDT and Ripple&#8217;s XRP have been some of the veteran cryptocurrencies that almost always made their cut in the top 10. Both of them are backed by major companies with considerable funding and a ton of talent.</p>
<p>However, ChatGPT thinks that Polkadot (DOT) is the fifth cryptocurrency from our question that will make the cut and survive in the next decade.</p>
<p>It argued that:</p>
<blockquote><p>Polakdot&#8217;s interoperability features and growing ecosystem position it as a potential long-term player in the cryptocurrency industry.</p></blockquote>
<p>Now, does the above mean other cryptocurrencies will collapse? Probably not. Of course, none of this should be construed as financial advice. The content is for educational and entertainment purposes only, and you should always make your own research and consult a professional on the matter. However, it is quite interesting to poke the digital brains of an AI language model that seems to have an answer different than what many would think.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-which-5-cryptos-will-survive-in-10-years-the-answer-might-surprise-you/" rel="nofollow">We Asked ChatGPT Which 5 Cryptos Will Survive in 10 Years: The Answer Might Surprise You</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Bounced 40% Off the Weekend Lows, But Is Another Crash Incoiming? (PEPE Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-bounced-40-off-the-weekend-lows-but-is-another-crash-incoiming-pepe-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 13:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250855</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE managed to find support and buyers were quick to jump in over the weekend. Key Support levels: $0.0000011 Key Resistance levels: $0.0000020 This meme coin managed to rally and double in price between Friday and Saturday, but it was not enough to break the key resistance at $0.0000020. Sellers came in strong and stopped [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">PEPE managed to find support and buyers were quick to jump in over the weekend.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.0000011</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.0000020</strong></p>
<p>This meme coin managed to rally and double in price between Friday and Saturday, but it was not enough to break the key resistance at $0.0000020. Sellers came in strong and stopped the rally. In the process, the price made a lower high which is a bearish signal. The current support is at $0.0000011.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250857" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250857" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250857" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-14-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250857" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume: </strong>The volume increased over the weekend, but this quickly faded as of Tuesday. Buyers could not sustain the rally.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The 12h RSI made a lower high and is again under 50 points. This is bearish.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The 12h MACD is bearish, but the histogram is making higher lows. This shows that sellers have lost some momentum.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250858" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250858" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250858" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48" width="1813" height="802" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48-1024x453.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48-1536x679.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-16_18-39-48-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250858" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for PEPE is bearish so long it cannot break the key resistance.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for PEPE Price</h2>
<p>With buyers absent, it appears PEPE is unable to break higher at this time and has been ranging under the key resistance at $0.0000020. This can continue for the remainder of the week.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-bounced-40-off-the-weekend-lows-but-is-another-crash-incoiming-pepe-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Bounced 40% Off the Weekend Lows, But Is Another Crash Incoiming? (PEPE Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE but on Solana and Other Web 3.0 Frogs Got A Bump on Pepe Coin Mania</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-but-on-solana-and-other-web-3-0-frogs-got-a-bump-on-pepe-coin-mania/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 12:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250612</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pepe_Rocket.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pepe_Rocket.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Pepe coin rocked the Web 3.0 space in May with a 1,800% price rally. But crypto investors are also looking at a host of other frog coins like Pepe (S0L) for their next prince charming.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The dramatically popular debut of Pepe coin this year has put frog meme cryptos in the spotlight. While the new Ethereum ERC-20 token launched on April 15th, Pepe coin went parabolic starting May 1st, and that would soon blow out sales of Pepe (SOL) as well.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-price-madness-how-to-find-the-next-meme-surprise/" data-wpel-link="internal">price madness</a> was a bullish portent for Ethereum and DeFi crypto blockchains.</p>
<p>Moreover, it was so popular on crypto exchanges that supporters compared it to DOGE and SHIB. That was during the beginning of May amidst the flash rally.</p>
<h2>Pepe Coin Surge Shifts Attention Elsewhere</h2>
<p>After the Pepe coin price settled from its all-time high, it got legs and rallied again Friday, May 12th. As a result, markets have more evidence that PEPE is a project with long-term horizons, not a rug pull. That might be giving confidence crypto investors taking another look at Pepe (SOL).</p>
<p>But Pepe Coin isn&#8217;t the only one out there. Before it, there was PepeSol. Additionally, it&#8217;s not the only frog meme coin, either.</p>
<p>Just as a group of geese is a flock and a group of bees is a swarm, a group of frogs is called an army. Well, there&#8217;s a small army of frog meme coins out there on the blockchains.</p>
<p>Here are just a couple examples of frog cryptos that are getting a bump out of Pepe coin&#8217;s rise:</p>
<h3>Pepe (SOL) Blew up on Pepe Coin (ERC-20)&#8217;s Coattails.</h3>
<p>PepeSol (also listed as PEPE token) is a meme coin on Solana. The fast and low-fee smart contract blockchain <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-sees-significant-growth-across-defi-nfts-messari/" data-wpel-link="internal">has seen</a> significant growth recently.</p>
<p>While it was launched earlier this year in February, Pepe SOL didn&#8217;t get to hopping the way Pepe Coin did a couple of months later.</p>
<p>When Pepe Coin went viral in crypto markets, however, Pepe (SOL) <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepesol/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">jumped from</a> $0.000078 on Apr 29th to $0.00153 on May 2nd. That was a 1,860% increase in its price in three days.</p>
<p>Crypto investors holding Pepe Sol only had until May 3 to sell at that massive ROI for the flash rally. It crashed to around $0.00023 by May 7th.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s also a Pepe coin on Arbitrum, a layer-2 scaling solution for Ethereum.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-but-on-solana-and-other-web-3-0-frogs-got-a-bump-on-pepe-coin-mania/" rel="nofollow">PEPE but on Solana and Other Web 3.0 Frogs Got A Bump on Pepe Coin Mania</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kush Kriminals Unveils Crypto-Cannabis Collaboration for Web3</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kush-kriminals-unveils-crypto-cannabis-collaboration-for-web3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 11:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250861</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kush_Kriminals.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kush_Kriminals.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] In the ever-evolving world of Web3 and digital collectibles, the role of trust and transparency is paramount in ensuring a brand&#8217;s success and endurance. Enter Kush Kriminals, an ingenious union of the burgeoning cannabis industry and the digital collectibles domain, garnering the attention of the crypto community. Spearheaded by [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>In the ever-evolving world of Web3 and digital collectibles, the role of trust and transparency is paramount in ensuring a brand&#8217;s success and endurance. Enter <a href="https://www.kushkriminals.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Kush Kriminals</a>, an ingenious union of the burgeoning cannabis industry and the digital collectibles domain, garnering the attention of the crypto community.</p>
<p>Spearheaded by Tyler and Jason, this innovative venture is redefining traditional Web3/NFT approaches and charting new territory.</p>
<p>Kush Kriminals forged an exceptional alliance with Cookies, a reputable cannabis dispensary chain. The partnership boasts an extensive array of exclusive cannabis products, including three unique strains, flowers, prerolls, edibles, and concentrates. By becoming part of the Kush Kriminals community, members enjoy access to Cookies merchandise, lifetime discounts, and a variety of future additions, such as CBD products and beverages.</p>
<p>The imaginative dimension of Kush Kriminals is realized through the expertise of Sam Humphries, a seasoned comic book writer whose portfolio features collaborations with DC, Marvel, and popular franchises like The Avengers, Guardians of the Galaxy, and Harley Quinn. Humphries has created distinctive &#8220;Legendaries&#8221; characters for Kush Kriminals, set to appear in marketing campaigns, comics, e-books, shows, video games, podcasts, and beyond.</p>
<p>In a recent milestone, Kush Kriminals announced a collaboration with Magic Eden, a notable NFT marketplace. By minting on Magic Eden&#8217;s platform, the project will reach a larger audience, strengthening its foothold in the digital collectibles ecosystem.</p>
<p>The driving forces behind Kush Kriminals are well-versed in the uncertainties and challenges of the crypto market. To navigate these obstacles, they crafted a long-term strategy that accounts for market variations and employs risk management methods. Additionally, they assembled a reliable and proficient team through comprehensive screening processes, ensuring an ideal blend of skills, experience, and cultural cohesion.</p>
<p>Fostering trust within the Web3 community is a crucial aspect of Kush Kriminals&#8217; success. The team actively engaged with partners and the Kriminals community by attending industry events, contributing to online discussions, and maintaining transparency about the project&#8217;s goals and advancements.</p>
<p>Kush Kriminals&#8217; journey underscores the significance of honesty, integrity, and expertise, as well as the merits of commitment, perseverance, and adaptability. The brand&#8217;s bold vision for the future includes expanding to every Cookies location across the United States and introducing CBD products for holders in non-legal states.</p>
<p>Kush Kriminals exemplifies how trust and transparency can drive a project to thrive in the Web3 arena. By cultivating robust relationships with their community and partners, the team established a solid foundation for their ambitious aspirations. With Kush Kriminals continuously pushing the limits of the digital collectibles and cannabis industries, the future appears exceptionally promising.</p>
<p>Keep abreast of Kush Kriminals&#8217; exhilarating journey as they revolutionize the digital collectibles and cannabis sectors. Immerse yourself in this vibrant community and stay up-to-date on the latest developments, exclusive promotions, and engaging content. Interact with Kush Kriminals on Instagram and Twitter, and join the conversation with fellow Kriminals on Discord. To learn more about the project and explore its unique offerings, visit the official website. Follow the Kush Kriminals movement today, and witness the future of cannabis and digital collectibles.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kush-kriminals-unveils-crypto-cannabis-collaboration-for-web3/" rel="nofollow">Kush Kriminals Unveils Crypto-Cannabis Collaboration for Web3</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
