<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Blockchain Game Pikamoon Raises $3.6M, Final ICO Phase Selling Out Fast</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259833</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Fire_biome_render_16890623225I2PXb63xs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Fire_biome_render_16890623225I2PXb63xs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 11th, 2023] Pikamoon, an emerging Ethereum blockchain game, has raised $3.6 million in its ongoing ICO to bring more value to the Ethereum ecosystem and revolutionize the blockchain gaming space. Pikamoon would launch the world’s most immersive metaverse game and a first-of-its-kind earning model that allows players [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 11th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Pikamoon,</a> an emerging Ethereum blockchain game, has raised $3.6 million in its ongoing ICO to bring more value to the Ethereum ecosystem and revolutionize the blockchain gaming space. Pikamoon would launch the world’s most immersive metaverse game and a first-of-its-kind earning model that allows players to withdraw their in-game rewards directly to their wallet or bank account without the need for a third party.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Pikamoon focuses on becoming the most realistic metaverse game where players can get a 360-degree experience of the growing virtual space through unparalleled gameplay, stunning visuals, and innovative DeFi features. Drawing inspiration from legendary games like Fortnite, Pokemon, and FIFA, the Ethereum game has leaped forward and is prepared to blend NFTs, video gaming, and metaverse entertainment perfectly.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The Pikamoon game is built on Unity, the world’s most advanced game development technology, to create the stunning visuals and architecture needed to give players a truly immersive experience.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Additionally, Pikamoon is built across two blockchains: Ethereum and MultiversX (formerly Elrond). While Ethereum provides scalability, MultiversX complements it by providing efficiency and ensuring the game is environmentally friendly by reducing carbon emissions generated by transactions. This dual blockchain feature ensures that the Pikamoon ecosystem can cater to legions of gamers without any lag.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot_2023-07-11_at_113639_1689064806IU4w0Bn5ye-744x1024.jpg" /></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Gaming enthusiasts and smart investors are convinced Pikamoon is the future of gaming, and this is evident in how fast phase one and phase two of the ICO sold out. In the first phase, one PIKA sold for $0.0002, which increased to $0.0004 in the second phase, and now in the third and last phase, one PIKA is selling for $0.0006 and selling out faster.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Notable partners of this Ethereum-based game include future-thinking Web3 brands such as Ethereum, Transak, Cryptonews.com, Kevuru Games, and MultiversX. This line-up of industry leaders further reinforces the credibility of the project, reaffirming the fact that the team is committed to building the best of the best gaming projects.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Pikamoon offers investors the opportunity to enter what is strategically seen as a huge market of the Metaverse and gaming on the Ethereum blockchain. A core feature of the PIKA token is its deflationary nature. Whenever a sell or transfer transaction occurs in the Pikamoon ecosystem, 0.5% of the tokens involved in the transaction are burned forever, translating into more profits for long-term investors.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">The much-talked-about presale, which is still on, uses Ethereum as its base currency, becoming the new favorite of the Ethereum community. This seamless integration with Ethereum not only simplifies the investment process for eager investors but also strengthens the overall Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/CqoH9AZiZVA?showinfo=0"></iframe></div></p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Pikamoon</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Pikamoon</a> makes metaverse gameplay exciting and rewarding for players of all age groups. The Pikamoon’s metaverse, the Pikaverse, offers players endless opportunities to explore, battle, trade, and earn a living within the game. It operates on two blockchains, Ethereum and MultiversX, ensuring smooth and glitch-free gameplay for every player. Similarly, Pikamoon’s unique earning model allows players to easily monetize gameplay, solidifying its place as one of the best metaverse games on the market.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><strong>Find out more about Pikamoon (PIKA)</strong></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://pikamoon.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://pikamoon.io/buy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Where to purchase PIKA</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/Pikamooncoin" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/pikamoonofficial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-blockchain-game-pikamoon-raises-3-6m-final-ico-phase-selling-out-fast/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Blockchain Game Pikamoon Raises $3.6M, Final ICO Phase Selling Out Fast</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Trader Became a Millionaire by Investing $1,000 in Pepe: Can Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-trader-became-a-millionaire-by-investing-1000-in-pepe-can-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259830</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pepe_wsm_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/pepe_wsm_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Stories of remarkable gains and life-changing investments are not uncommon in the world of cryptocurrency. Many of these tales revolve around crypto traders turning modest amounts into millions by investing in Pepe ($PEPE) – this year’s breakout meme coin star. Moreover, these inspiring stories ultimately beg the question: What could be the next cryptocurrency to [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stories of remarkable gains and life-changing investments are not uncommon in the world of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Many of these tales revolve around crypto traders turning modest amounts into millions by investing in Pepe ($PEPE) – this year’s breakout meme coin star.</p>
<p>Moreover, these inspiring stories ultimately beg the question: What could be the next cryptocurrency to produce 1,000x returns?</p>
<h2>Czech Trader’s $PEPE Investment Makes Them a Crypto Millionaire</h2>
<p>One of the most prominent examples of $PEPE turning someone into a millionaire is from a Czechoslovakian trader who recently <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/feed/post/720801" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">posted</a> on the Binance Feed.</p>
<p>This trader, who goes by the name IB_JUNIOR, states that he discovered $PEPE on April 17 – immediately before the coin&#8217;s bull run.</p>
<p>After reviewing the token, the trader opted to invest &#8220;a small sum&#8221; – and within 24 hours, their investment had multiplied by over 1,000x.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-10.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259840" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-10.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="484" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-10.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-10-300x241.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-10-50x40.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Interestingly, the trader opted to hold out rather than immediately cash in.</p>
<p>This decision proved beneficial, as when the trader eventually sold their $PEPE tokens in early May, they made a whopping 4,000% return.</p>
<p>As IB_JUNIOR notes, he &#8220;turned his initial investment into millions of dollars.&#8221;</p>
<p>This incredible story is a shining example of the transformative power of cryptocurrency investments – especially in the ever-evolving meme coin niche.</p>
<h2>Pepe’s Market Impact Creates Extraordinary Gains &amp; Anonymous Fortunes</h2>
<p>However, IB_JUNIOR&#8217;s success story is one of many that&#8217;s made headlines.</p>
<p>In mid-April, crypto journalist Constantine Crypto <a href="https://twitter.com/Keldamaa88/status/1649000971446435842" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">tweeted</a> about an anonymous trader who invested $250 in $PEPE – and saw it turn into $1.02 million.</p>
<p>At the time, the trader owned 5.9 trillion $PEPE tokens, although whether they were able to cash out their profits remains unclear.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-10.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259839" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-10.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="668" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-10.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-10-270x300.jpg 270w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-10-45x50.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Crypto YouTuber ClayBro also released a video on $PEPE’s “millionaire maker” status, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o6Z5h2hxk0U&amp;ab_channel=ClayBro" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">highlighting</a> several crypto wallets that became multi-millionaires during the token’s three-week bull run.</p>
<p>Much like the trader referenced by Constantine Crypto, the owners of these wallets remain anonymous – but their remarkable gains demonstrate the immense wealth-building potential of low-cap coins.</p>
<p>All in all, these stories underscore the allure and excitement surrounding the meme coin niche, which has captured the attention of both newbies and market veterans worldwide.</p>
<h2>What Could Be the Next Crypto to Explode?</h2>
<p>However, with many believing that Pepe’s heyday may be behind it, attention is now being paid to which meme coins could be the next to explode in value.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes has emerged as an interesting contender in this regard, having already raised $13.2 million in its recently-launched presale phase.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Looks Ready for Price Pump After $13.2m Presale Raise</h2>
<p>As its name implies, <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-trader-became-a-millionaire-by-investing-1000-in-pepe-can-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is a brand-new meme coin project that draws inspiration from the subculture formed around the r/WallStreetBets subreddit.</p>
<p>Although not directly connected to this subreddit, Wall Street Memes holds many of the same values – and uses a similar branding style to appeal to retail investors.</p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes team has already experienced success in the realm of digital assets. This is evidenced by the remarkable response to the <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT</a> collection, which completely sold out within a mere 32 minutes back in 2021.</p>
<p>Now the team hopes to replicate that success with $WSM, which has made an incredible impact on the retail trading community.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259836" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-8.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="301" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-8.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-8-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-8-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Although the token isn’t yet available on the open market, this hasn’t stopped meme coin enthusiasts from clamoring to acquire $WSM through the ongoing presale.</p>
<p>This is because presale investors can purchase $WSM tokens for just $0.031 – which is expected to be a discount on the eventual CEX listing price.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not just retail investors getting involved, with crypto influencer <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aHGxKJjOzIU&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">My Financial Friend</a> stating that $WSM could be &#8220;the biggest new crypto coming to the market.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ultimately, the optimism around Wall Street Memes shows no signs of slowing – hinting that it could be the next big crypto to hit the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=this-trader-became-a-millionaire-by-investing-1000-in-pepe-can-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-trader-became-a-millionaire-by-investing-1000-in-pepe-can-wall-street-memes-be-the-next-big-meme-coin/" rel="nofollow">This Trader Became a Millionaire by Investing $1,000 in Pepe: Can Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Meme Coin?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos Teams Gather in Paris as Interchain Ecosystem Faces Pivotal Year</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cosmos-teams-gather-in-paris-as-interchain-ecosystem-faces-pivotal-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259828</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Youtube_1_1689007330bIdFFy43Q2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Youtube_1_1689007330bIdFFy43Q2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, July 11th, 2023] Nebular Summit, Europe’s premiere Interchain builders conference, returns to Paris, France, July 24th and 25th, 2023. Key thought leaders, founders, engineers, and investors will unveil the latest innovations within the Interchain developer community and discuss divisive issues crucial to the ecosystem’s long-term success. “Teams have fortified the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, July 11th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://nebular.builders" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Nebular Summit</a>, Europe’s premiere Interchain builders conference, returns to Paris, France, July 24th and 25th, 2023. Key thought leaders, founders, engineers, and investors will unveil the latest innovations within the Interchain developer community and discuss divisive issues crucial to the ecosystem’s long-term success.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Teams have fortified the Cosmos stack for dApp scalability and cross-chain compatibility for years. As it matures, developers recognize its stability for building Web3 apps. However, Interchain grapples with the inherent challenges of decentralized leadership, market liquidity challenges, and direct competition with Ethereum L2s. The upcoming year will be vital in shaping this space’s future.” says <a href="https://twitter.com/seb3point0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Sebastien Couture</a>, Founder of <a href="https://interop.ventures/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Interop Ventures</a> and Organizer of Nebular Summit.</p></blockquote>
<p>Thought leaders of Cosmos are vocal about critical issues jeopardizing the network’s long-term success, such as the lack of coordination mechanisms for infrastructure development (e.g., MetaMask sign-in), lack of usable native stablecoins, and liquidity challenges impacting Cosmos DeFi protocols.</p>
<p>Despite these threats, unlike Ethereum Layer 2 (L2) solutions adapting to interoperability, Cosmos was designed to embrace modular and interoperable dApps from the start, learning from past cycles, which infrastructure is crucial for long-term success.</p>
<p>Last year, <a href="https://thedefiant.io/dydx-chain-cosmos/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">dYdX’s</a> announced migration from an Ethereum L2 dApp to its own Cosmos-based blockchain bolstered the ecosystem, and the <a href="https://www.cointrust.com/market-news/dydx-to-unveil-public-testnet-of-its-cosmos-powered-blockchain-next-week" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">testnet launched</a> on July 5th.</p>
<p>Alongside the momentum spurred by dYdX’s adoption of Cosmos, the wider ecosystem is experiencing significant financial and infrastructure growth, evident from recent metrics.</p>
<p>This year Neutron raised $10M to develop smart contracts on Cosmos, Polymer Labs raised $3.6M to expand the use of the Inter-Blockchain Communication (IBC) protocol standard to other ecosystems, Circle plans to launch USDC on Cosmos via Noble, the Interchain Foundation allocated $40M for ecosystem development in 2023, and Injective Labs launched a $150M ecosystem fund to support interoperable infrastructure and DeFi.</p>
<p>Cosmos is redefining how interconnected chains that leverage a common technology stack can benefit builders and projects looking for solutions to interconnectivity issues.</p>
<p>Paris remains a prime location for fostering Web3 innovation, with the influential Ethereum Community Conference (EthCC) gathering thousands of developers each year.</p>
<p>And in April, the European Parliament adopted “Markets in Crypto-Assets” (MICA), meaning they are the first governing body to establish regulations for crypto assets and stablecoins, welcoming crypto projects to the EU, including France.</p>
<p>This year’s Nebular Summit themes will explore the emerging modular blockchain stack, the Cosmos SDK, CosmWasm, IBC, cross-chain MEV, Interchain Security, zero-knowledge, and more through a series of technical talks and intense debates.</p>
<p>Its highlight speakers include Charles d’Haussy, CEO of dYdX Foundation, who enables community-led growth, development, and self-sustainability of the dYdX protocol, Ethan Buchman, Co-Founder of Cosmos itself and of Informal Systems, a Rust and Formal Verification for Cosmos, Sunny Aggarwal, Co-Founder of Osmosis, the largest interchain decentralized exchange in the Cosmos ecosystem and Zaki Manian, Co-Founder of Sommelier Finance, a platform that aims to optimize DeFi with off-chain computation and improved interoperability.</p>
<p>The conference starts with Nebular Hack Day on July 23rd, a free-to-attend event offering technical workshops by dYdX, Neutron, Juno, OKP4, Lava Network, Gno.land, and more.</p>
<p>Nebular Summit is curated by Interop Ventures, a venture fund concentrating on the rapidly evolving Interchain ecosystem.</p>
<h2>About Nebular Summit</h2>
<p>Nebular Summit is a confluence for teams and innovators from every corner of the Interchain universe. Participants share the most recent advancements in the Cosmos technology stack while openly addressing the ecosystem’s challenges. The two-day event happening in Paris from July 24th to 25th will feature technical talks, hands-on developer workshops, and debates on controversial issues. Nebular Summit will explore appchains, modular blockchains, novel smart contract VMs, interoperability, zero-knowledge, and beyond!</p>
<h2>About Interop Ventures</h2>
<p>Interop Ventures is a venture fund concentrating on the rapidly evolving Interchain ecosystem, a network of interconnected decentralized applications built on the Cosmos technology stack. They invest in infrastructure and applications that are scalable, interoperable, and secure, embodying the future direction of Web3 applications.</p>
<p><strong>RVSP: </strong>People who would like to join Nebular Summit and be set up with press access or pursue interview requests can contact mia@nebular.events.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cosmos-teams-gather-in-paris-as-interchain-ecosystem-faces-pivotal-year/" rel="nofollow">Cosmos Teams Gather in Paris as Interchain Ecosystem Faces Pivotal Year</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Challenges $31K Again, MATIC Explodes 10% Daily (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-challenges-31k-again-matic-explodes-10-daily-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259802</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Polygon.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Polygon.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BNB, LTC, and SOL are also well in the green from the top 10 alts.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin tried its hand at taking down $31,000 once more but was stopped in its tracks, at least for now.</p>
<p>The altcoins have turned green today, with ETH nearing $1,900, BNB closing down to $250, and MATIC soaring by double digits.</p>
<h2>BTC&#8217;s $31K Challenge</h2>
<p>Bitcoin soared last Thursday to $31,500 to mark its highest price tag in over a year but failed there and quickly returned to approximately $30,000. Then came the weekend, and the asset <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-defends-30k-after-blackrock-refiled-its-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">calmed</a> in a tight range between $30,000 and $30,500.</p>
<p>Not much happened on Monday, either. BTC was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-shaky-at-30k-pepe-drops-7-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">close to breaking below $30,000</a>, but the bulls managed to defend that level and pushed the asset north.</p>
<p>As such, bitcoin went on the offensive early Tuesday and jumped to just over $31,000 for the third time within the past week or so.</p>
<p>As it happened with its previous attempts, though, this one wasn&#8217;t all that successful, and BTC retraced heavily by around a grand. As of now, the cryptocurrency trades at about $30,500, and its market cap has climbed above $590 billion.</p>
<p>Its dominance over the alts has taken a slight hit since yesterday and is just shy of 50%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259806" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259806" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259806" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-11-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259806" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>MATIC Steals the Show</h2>
<p>The altcoins posted some losses yesterday, but the landscape is entirely different now, with most of them being well in the green. Ethereum is among the most modest performers, having jumped by just over 1% to almost $1,900. XRP, DOGE, TRX, DOT, and AVAX have seen similar gains.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, on the other hand, is up by nearly 7% and sits close to $250. SOL and LTC have increased by over 5% to $22 and $98, respectively.</p>
<p>Polygon is the top performer from the larger-cap alts. MATIC is up by approximately 10% and trades well above $0.7.</p>
<p>With most lower- and mid-cap alts also in the green, the total crypto market cap has added over $20 billion in a day and is now close to $1.2 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259807" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259807" style="width: 1878px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259807" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1878" height="843" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8.jpg 1878w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8-1024x460.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8-768x345.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8-1536x689.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-8-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1878px) 100vw, 1878px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259807" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-challenges-31k-again-matic-explodes-10-daily-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">BTC Challenges $31K Again, MATIC Explodes 10% Daily (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dubai Takes Enforcement Action Against Middle East Crypto Exchange BitOasis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-takes-enforcement-action-against-middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259776</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dubai has been widely considered as a crypto-friendly destination but that hasn’t stopped local regulators from taking action against companies that are not in compliance.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 10, the Emirate’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) issued a market alert stating that it had initiated an enforcement action against the BitOasis crypto exchange.</p>
<p>BitOasis is one of the largest crypto platforms focused on customers in the Middle East.</p>
<h2>Dubai Regulators on Alert</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.vara.ae/en/regulations/regulatory-notices/market-alert-bitoasis-technologies-fze-bitoasis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">alert</a>, BitOasis is under review for “not meeting mandated conditions, required to be satisfied within 30-60 day timeframes prior to being permitted to undertake any VARA regulated market activity.”</p>
<p>BitOasis was awarded the first of Dubai’s “minimum viable product operational licenses,” earlier this year but the regulator may rescind that license.</p>
<p>The Dubai regulator stated that it was “exercising its authority to supervise and monitor compliance,” adding that enforcement actions could include “holding BitOasis’ license status as non-operational.”</p>
<p>The license allows the firm to offer broker-dealer services for crypto assets to qualified retail and institutional investors from its Dubai headquarters.</p>
<p>BitOasis, which operates in 14 countries across MENA (Middle East and North Africa), claims more than $3 billion in trading volume, according to its website.</p>
<p>Last year, the exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis-cuts-staff-citing-recession-and-market-turmoil/" data-wpel-link="internal">axed 5% of its staff</a>, citing recession and market turmoil.</p>
<p>It is not the first time Dubai regulators have issued warnings and reprimands. In April, VARA issued a reprimand to Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, co-founders of the bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>In May, the regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-regulator-reprimands-opnx-founders-for-conducting-unregulated-activity/" data-wpel-link="internal">reprimanded</a> OPNX founders Mark Lamb and Sudhu Arumugam, as well as its Chief Executive Officer Leslie Lamb, for conducting unregulated activities.</p>
<p>In late June, Dubai-based crypto exchange Bybit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-scores-preparatory-license-by-dubais-virtual-assets-regulatory-authority/" data-wpel-link="internal">landed</a> a minimum viable product preparatory license from VARA. Bybit has also slashed staff during the crypto bear market.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Markets are up marginally, but volume remains low, and trading remains sideways. Total capitalization has reached $1.23 trillion at the time of writing, following a 1.6% gain on the day.</p>
<p>Bitcoin spiked to $31,000 briefly during late trading on July 10 but could not hold that level and sharply retreated back to yesterday’s levels around $30,400.</p>
<p>Ethereum was up 1.3% on the day at $1,881 at the time of writing. Binance Coin (BNB) and Polygon (MATIC) were performing well, gaining 5% and 8%, respectively</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-takes-enforcement-action-against-middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis/" rel="nofollow">Dubai Takes Enforcement Action Against Middle East Crypto Exchange BitOasis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter&#8217;s New Rival Threads Hits 100 Million Users in 4 Days </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/twitters-new-rival-threads-hits-100-million-users-in-4-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259729</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Threads_Twitter.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Threads_Twitter.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Zuckerberg's Threads has attracted over 100 million users less than four days after launch. Will it overtake its rival platform, Twitter?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 6, Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO and founder of Facebook&#8217;s parent company Meta Platforms, launched a new platform dubbed Threads in 100 countries across the globe. The social media network is considered a rival to the micro-blogging platform Twitter.</p>
<p>Speaking against the newly launched platform, Twitter owner and former CEO Elon Musk hauled Threads as a copycat project.</p>
<h2>Will Threads Overpower Twitter?</h2>
<p>In a Monday Threads <a href="https://www.threads.net/t/CuhOXGmr74R/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post</a>, Zuckerberg wrote that the new project attained 100 million sign-ups over the weekend, only four days after launch. It took Twitter five years to <a href="https://blog.twitter.com/en_us/a/2011/one-hundred-million-voices" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">achieve</a> this feat.</p>
<p>Threads function as a sister app for Instagram, as users need to own an Instagram account before creating a Threads page. The platform also has features similar to Twitter&#8217;s, such as liking, commenting, reposting, and sharing. It also freely offers some features only available to subscribed Twitter users, like 500 characters per thread, and allows up to five minutes of videos.</p>
<p>However, Threads doesn&#8217;t support direct messaging, hashtags, and trending stories – features existing within the Twitter ecosystem.</p>
<p>Stressing the purpose of the Threads platform, Instagram CEO Adam Mosseri said in an <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/5/23784870/instagram-threads-adam-mosseri-interview-twitter-competitor" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with The Verge:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Obviously, Twitter pioneered the space. And there are a lot of good offerings out there for public conversations. But just given everything that was going on, we thought there was an opportunity to build something that was open and something that was good for the community that was already using Instagram.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Mosseri was likely referring to Musk&#8217;s recent actions to bolster Twitter&#8217;s revenue by encouraging the subscription to its paid verification option. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-chief-elon-musk-to-pass-on-mantle-to-new-ceo-takes-ceo-role/" data-wpel-link="internal">former Twitter CEO</a> also limited the number of tweets viewable by users daily.</p>
<p>Still, Mosseri claimed that Threads was not introduced to replace Twitter.</p>
<h2>A Lawsuit Threat?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the popular micro-blogging platform is taking the offensive as the internet buzzes about the similarities and differences between Threads and Twitter.</p>
<p>In a legal letter <a href="https://cdn.sanity.io/files/ifn0l6bs/production/27109f01431939c8177d408d3c9848c3b46632cd.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> last Thursday, Twitter attorney Alex Spiro alleged that Meta employed former Twitter employees to design Threads using insider information from Twitter. Meta, however, denied these allegations. The issue is yet to exacerbate to constitute a lawsuit case.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitters-new-rival-threads-hits-100-million-users-in-4-days/" rel="nofollow">Twitter&#8217;s New Rival Threads Hits 100 Million Users in 4 Days </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital Shrinks Portfolio by Nearly 40%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-digital-shrinks-portfolio-by-nearly-40/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259643</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Voyager recorded outflows of more than $250 million worth of crypto assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender &#8211; Voyager &#8211; is slowly working towards making customers whole.</p>
<p>Voyager held nearly $413 million in multiple crypto-assets at one point. However, since enabling withdrawals to users on June 23rd, it has recorded a steady stream of outflow totaling $250 million worth of crypto assets. As a result, Voyager&#8217;s crypto portfolio has shrunk by 39.46%.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the <a href="https://dune.com/21co/potential-contagion?Voyager+Interval_ee9bc0=weekly" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> compiled by Dune Analytics, Voyager currently holds $176.38 million worth of crypto. This includes $69,02 million in Bitcoin, $50,99 million in Ether, $18,56 million worth of USDC, $15,70 million worth of SHIB, and $2,46 million MATIC, among others.</li>
<li>The bankrupt firm has a Clean Asset ratio of 96.15% (excluding its native token VGX) and sits at a stablecoin balance of nearly $19 million.</li>
<li>The United States Bankruptcy Judge Michael Wiles <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-approved-to-start-repaying-frozen-customers-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">greenlighted</a> Voyager&#8217;s proposed liquidation plan in May this year.</li>
<li>The move enabled the crypto lender to compensate about $1.33 billion in crypto assets to customers and end its efforts to reorganize under Chapter 11.</li>
<li>Voyager soon announced that customers will be able to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-this-month/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">recover</a> around 36% of their cryptocurrency deposits.</li>
<li>More recently, Gemini <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-allows-voyager-victims-to-claim-funds-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that it would be allowing withdrawals for victims of the Voyager bankruptcy case.</li>
<li>The firm had been crippled by the implosion of Zhu Su-led crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) last year, which had earlier defaulted on a $665 million Voyager loan.</li>
<li>It later suffered two failed recovery deals from FTX and Binance.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-digital-shrinks-portfolio-by-nearly-40/" rel="nofollow">Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital Shrinks Portfolio by Nearly 40%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arcadia Finance Hit by $455K Exploit on Both Ethereum, Optimism Networks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arcadia-finance-hit-by-455k-exploit-on-both-ethereum-optimism-networks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 23:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259680</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Hack.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Hack.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The team behind Arcadia said that it has initiated contact with the attacker.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Non-custodial decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, Arcadia Finance, is the latest victim of a $455,000 exploit that occurred on both the Ethereum and Optimism networks. Confirming the hack, Arcadia revealed that it is working with security partners to minimize the damage after pausing the contracts.</p>
<p>The platform has also roped in law enforcement to deal with the issue.</p>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain security expert PeckShield was first to notify the attack on Arcadia and <a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1678263478774013952" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">claimed</a> that it was caused due to &#8220;the lack of untrusted input validation,&#8221; which is exploited to drain funds from both darcWETH and darcUSDC vaults.</li>
<li>The firm highlighted another vulnerability in the DeFi protocol &#8211; &#8220;lack of reentrancy protection&#8221; &#8211; which enables instant liquidation to bypass the internal vault health check.</li>
<li>The stolen funds from the Optimism network portion were washed on the controversial coin mixer, Tornado Cash. But the Ethereum portion of the stolen funds, worth over $103,000, continued to remain parked in a <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x5c75e94dd0ab9c10bfd1b8073dafef031d3c050d#code" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">flagged</a> wallet address.</li>
<li>Arcadia has not yet confirmed the validity of the root cause identified by PeckShield, but it said that an investigation is being carried out. The protocol&#8217;s latest <a href="https://twitter.com/ArcadiaFi/status/1678310473832312833" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We will continue to work with our security partners, law enforcement, and the broader community to resolve this as best we can. Our number one priority is recovering funds for Arcadia protocol users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Arcadia is a non-custodial, permissionless protocol that was launched on Ethereum and Optimism in March this year. The platform essentially enables users to trade spot with leverage and boost staked ether.</li>
<li>The latest exploit surfaces amid rampant hacks recorded in the digital asset sector.</li>
<li>In the first of 2023 alone, Web3 security firm Beosin <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1674618821766971392" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">identified</a> a loss of $470 million across 108 DeFi protocol attacks.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arcadia-finance-hit-by-455k-exploit-on-both-ethereum-optimism-networks/" rel="nofollow">Arcadia Finance Hit by $455K Exploit on Both Ethereum, Optimism Networks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouTuber Turned NFT Scammer? On-Chain Sleuth Investigates $1.5 Million Crypto Thief</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/youtuber-turned-nft-scammer-on-chain-sleuth-investigates-1-5-million-crypto-thief/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259756</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/hackers_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/hackers_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A 16-year-old NFT scammer appears connected to the infamous Monkey Drainer responsible for stealing $24 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain detective ZachXBT has implicated a YouTuber with over 120,000 subscribers in over $1.5 million worth of crypto scams over the past two years.</p>
<p>Some of those scams are connected to the infamous Monkey Drainer, an anonymous and boastful phishing scammer known for stealing people’s NFTs.</p>
<h2>Linking “Blue” to Monkey Drainer</h2>
<p>Before entering the world of crypto scams in July 2021, the scammer – known as either “BlueXBT” or “JB Adventures” (Jack) – had grown his YouTube following “by uploading gaming and trolling videos,” <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1678384939048263682" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a> ZachXBT on Monday.</p>
<p>The on-chain sleuth connected Jack to the ENS address cool-breeze.eth, which he was shown publicly sharing in a leaked image from his Snapchat account.</p>
<p>That same address <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xc9a4fe3da7fb38e57fa14b273f05f190b535e395" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">purchased</a> BAYC 8668 in October 2022. However, had also received inflows of over 85 ETH from 8 Ethereum addresses connected to Monkey Drainer’s phishing scams.</p>
<p>Monkey Drainer is known for stealing over $24 million worth of NFTs using a technique called “ice phishing.” With this tactic, rather than soliciting a victim’s private keys directly, one baits them into signing a transaction that gives the hacker control of a user’s funds, using fraudulent crypto and NFT websites.</p>
<p>In November, CryptoPotato <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/monkey-drainer-on-hacking-spree-steals-another-520-eth-worth-nfts/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that Monkey Drainer has stolen over 1200 ETH worth of NFTs, including from collections like BAYC, CryptoPunks, and Otherside.</p>
<p>ZachXBT shared screenshots from Discord in which Blue bragged about his BAYC purchase, while also instructing his workers assisting with his scams.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5/ On Discord Blue flexed his BAYC purchase and would share his methods scamming. </p>
<p>The second and third screenshot is from an internal Discord server where Blue would instruct his workers. <a href="https://t.co/l22ZubSCAc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/l22ZubSCAc</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1678384963836604416?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“Unfortunately Blue was robbed of his BAYC in late 2022 after allegedly scamming Monkey out of his cut from a phishing scam,” continued ZachXBT.</p>
<h2>Blue’s Scams</h2>
<p>Blue got back to scamming in short order, however, using new ENS addresses. He spent his stolen funds on luxury items like cars, watches, and shoes, while using others to gamble on Stake.</p>
<p>One of Blue’s more recent scams included 61.5k ETH and 93.3k USDT stolen rom <a href="https://twitter.com/g13m" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">LoveMake.eth</a>. “Blue received 49 ETH and 74K USDT for himself after the drainer fee,” said ZachXBT.</p>
<p>Another included a Milady &amp; Squiggle NFT phished from <a href="https://twitter.com/ystrickler" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">yancey.eth</a> to Blue’s ENS purplelobster.eth. The NFTs were worth roughly 12 ETH, of which Blue kept 10.3 ETH after the drainer fee.</p>
<p>“It’s disgusting to see these phishing scammers show zero remorse and spend the funds on tasteless items,&#8221; concluded ZachXBT. He said that information about Blue (Jack) has been shared with many of his victims to help eventually bring legal action against him.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/youtuber-turned-nft-scammer-on-chain-sleuth-investigates-1-5-million-crypto-thief/" rel="nofollow">YouTuber Turned NFT Scammer? On-Chain Sleuth Investigates $1.5 Million Crypto Thief</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Holds Bitcoin (BTC)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-holds-bitcoin-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259601</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[JFK's nephew previously vowed to apply a pro-crypto regulatory framework should he win the 2024 US Presidential elections. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy &#8211; a US presidential candidate from the Democratic party and an outspoken advocate of the cryptocurrency industry &#8211; revealed owning between $100,001 and $250,000 worth of bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The disclosure comes approximately two months after the Miami BTC conference, where he said he is not a crypto investor.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy Owns Over 3 BTC</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a financial disclosure report seen by CNBC, the Kennedy family <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/07/rfk-jr-bitcoin-investment-raises-ethics-concerns.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">held</a> up to $250K in bitcoin as of June 30. While this could be another example outlining the American&#8217;s pro-crypto stance, some might argue that the situation could cause a conflict of interest. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy attended the Miami Bitcoin conference in May this year and told the crowd that he had not invested in the primary digital asset. On the other hand, he assured that he would accept BTC donations for his political campaign.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I am not an investor, and I am not here to give investment advice,&#8221; he said at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Former Democratic Rep. Dennis Kucinich &#8211; who serves as Kennedy&#8217;s campaign manager &#8211; claimed that the BTC purchase occurred after the speech and prior to the June 30 filing deadline.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The list of American politicians holding the leading digital asset does not end with John F. Kennedy&#8217;s nephew. US Senator Cynthia Lummis </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-cynthia-lummis-bought-up-to-100000-worth-of-btc-in-august/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">bought</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> between $50,001 to $100,000 worth of bitcoin in the summer of 2021. It is worth mentioning that she jumped on the bandwagon in 2013 when BTC was worth a mere $300 apiece. Senators Pat Toomey and Ted Cruz have also joined the ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Presidential candidate and current mayor of Miami &#8211; Francis Suarez &#8211; has gone even further, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-continues-to-receive-his-salary-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">receiving</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his salary in bitcoin instead of fiat currency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy&#8217;s Crypto Vision</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 69-year-old environmental lawyer has expressed some controversial views over the years. For one, he is an opponent of conventional nuclear power and promoted multiple conspiracy theories regarding COVID-19 and the vaccination program.</span></p>
<p>Kennedy is also in favor of the cryptocurrency sector and against the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s actions. He <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-f-kennedy-to-enforce-pro-bitcoin-laws-should-he-become-president/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to impose BTC-friendly laws should he become President:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I will make sure that we have policies that support Bitcoin and the freedom to transact and that allow individuals to manage their own Bitcoin wallets, nodes, and passwords.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, he assured that his cabinet will implement only necessary control to the industry (to prevent money laundering) and not hamper its development. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) will most likely not receive much support should Kennedy win the elections since he described them as financial tools used for &#8220;oppression.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-proponent-robert-f-kennedy-announces-run-for-president-of-the-usa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">criticized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the US Fed, suggesting it had collaborated with some banks to print a considerable amount of money between 2008-2022. According to him, this has negatively impacted the American economy, while BTC could serve as an &#8220;escape route from the splatter zone.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-holds-bitcoin-btc/" rel="nofollow">US Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Holds Bitcoin (BTC)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
