<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:46:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Gemini Lays of 10% of Employees Due to Crypto Industry&#8217;s &#8220;Bad Actors&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-lays-of-10-of-employees-due-to-crypto-industrys-bad-actors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234611</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Gemini.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Gemini.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gemini downsizes again while pointing fingers at “unprecedented fraud” in recent months.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Gemini – the Winklevoss-owned cryptocurrency exchange – has commenced its third round of job cuts in under a year, dismissing another 10% of its workforce. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Cameron Winklevoss claims the layoff was motivated by a combination of macroeconomic pressure and “unprecedented fraud” within the crypto industry.</span></p>
<h2>Gemini’s Shrinking Team</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As reported by </span><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/gemini-is-laying-off-10-of-staff-marking-latest-blow-for-winklevoss-crypto-startup" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">The Information</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Monday, the outlet received an internal message from Winklevoss stating that he’d been left with “no choice” but to reduce headcount.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“It was our hope to avoid further reductions after this summer, however, persistent negative macroeconomic conditions and unprecedented fraud perpetuated by bad actors in our industry have left us with no other choice but to revise our outlook and further reduce headcount,” he said in the letter.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Data from Pitchbook shows that Gemini had 1000 staff as of November 2022, meaning roughly 100 people were likely laid off. The last cut took place in July with 7% of the company losing their jobs, after 10% were dismissed a month earlier.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">They’re not alone in taking such drastic measures: Coinbase </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">laid off</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> another 950 employees earlier this month after shafting 18% of its workforce in June. CryptoCom also </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-respite-from-layoffs-crypto-com-cuts-20-workforce/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">cut</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> another 20% of employees two weeks ago. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Most firms cite macroeconomic factors as their primary pain point. Rising interest rates helped crater crypto asset prices in 2022, hurting exchanges, miners, and trading firms alike. </span></p>
<h2>Gemini’s Legal Battles</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Winklevoss has been particularly aggressive in calling out Barry Silbert – the CEO of DCG whose trading arm, Genesis, went </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">officially bankrupt</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> last week. Winklevoss </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-for-the-removal-of-dcg-ceo-barry-silbert/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claims</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Silbert and the two firms misrepresented the state of their financials to Gemini, whose Earn program has its users&#8217; funds now locked inside Genesis. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In regards to fraud, FTX’s former boss Sam Bankman-Fried has been widely accused and charged of much the same after his exchange collapsed in July. The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has levied charges against him for defrauding his customers by funneling user funds to his trading desk, Alameda Research – to which he has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pleaded</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> not guilty. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yet Gemini and Genesis are now both embroiled in their own trouble with the SEC, which alleges each offered unregistered securities to the retail investing public through Gemini Earn. Nexo, a rival crypto lending platform, has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nexo-agrees-to-pay-45-million-in-fines-to-us-authorities/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">given up</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on servicing U.S. customers after numerous challenges from regulators along these same lines. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-lays-of-10-of-employees-due-to-crypto-industrys-bad-actors/" rel="nofollow">Gemini Lays of 10% of Employees Due to Crypto Industry&#8217;s &#8220;Bad Actors&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Central African Republic Appoints a Committee to Design Crypto Legislation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-central-african-republic-appoints-a-committee-to-design-crypto-legislation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234498</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Central_African_Republic.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Central_African_Republic.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Several departments of the Central African Republic, including some of the Ministries, have to form a cryptocurrency bill.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the poorest countries &#8211; the Central African Republic (CAR) &#8211; formed a team of 15 agencies, whose responsibility will be to draft a &#8220;comprehensive&#8221; cryptocurrency bill.</p>
<p>The nation made the headlines last year, becoming the second after El Salvador to embrace bitcoin as a legal tender.</p>
<h2>Another Crypto Step</h2>
<p>Faustin-Archange Touadéra – President of the Central African Republic (CAR) &#8211; revealed that the government established a committee of 15 experts to design a pertinent cryptocurrency regulatory framework. The bill should encourage the development of the digital asset industry and potentially aid the hindered local economy.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="fr">15 experts <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/centrafricains?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#centrafricains</a> issus de plusieurs ministères de mon gouvernement composent le comité chargé d&#8217;élaborer un nouveau projet de loi plus complet sur l&#8217;utilisation des crypto-monnaies et d&#8217;offrir à la RCA cette opportunité unique de développement économique &amp; technologique <a href="https://t.co/bZTS8HQxH3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/bZTS8HQxH3</a></p>
<p>— Faustin-Archange Touadéra (@FA_Touadera) <a href="https://twitter.com/FA_Touadera/status/1616430057580367875?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 20, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Some departments tasked to form the legislation include the Ministry of Mines and Geology, the Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Development, the Ministry of Water, Forests, Hunting and Fishing, and others.</p>
<p>The CAR is among the poorest countries across the globe, with a GDP of around $2.5 billion and a GNI per capita of $980. President Touadéra raised hopes the upcoming transition to the world of crypto could solve some of the financial issues:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With access to cryptocurrencies, the monetary barriers existing until now will disappear, the main objective of the measures adopted by the government being the development of the national economy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Following El Salvador&#8217;s Example</h2>
<p>The CAR <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/its-official-central-african-republic-makes-bitcoin-legal-tender/" data-wpel-link="internal">became</a> the world&#8217;s second country where bitcoin serves as an official payment method in April last year. El Salvador was the first to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-months-later-bitcoin-now-officially-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">embrace</a> the cryptocurrency as a legal tender in September 2021.</p>
<p>The authorities of the Central African Republic suggested that the adoption could boost the monetary recovery and improve the well-being of the residents.</p>
<p>President Touadéra has displayed himself as a keen supporter of the primary digital asset, describing it as &#8220;universal money.&#8221;</p>
<p>He also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/undestand-bitcoin-now-to-prosper-in-the-future-says-the-cars-president/" data-wpel-link="internal">advised</a> locals to acknowledge BTC&#8217;s merits which could help them generate long-term wealth in times when surging inflation, global military conflicts, and economic crises reign across the globe:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Understanding bitcoin is crucial to acknowledge its disruptive power to bring long-term prosperity. Mathematics doesn&#8217;t account for human emotions. Future generations will look behind at these very moments to our strength and unity in choosing the right path during hard times.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-central-african-republic-appoints-a-committee-to-design-crypto-legislation/" rel="nofollow">The Central African Republic Appoints a Committee to Design Crypto Legislation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Africa Regulator Takes Action Against False Crypto Advertising Claims</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-africa-regulator-takes-action-against-false-crypto-advertising-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Africa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234601</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/regulations_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/regulations_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[South Africa's Advertising Regulatory Board (ARB) has introduced new rules to protect crypto investors from misleading advertising.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On January 23, South Africa&#8217;s Advertising Regulatory Board (ARB) introduced new cryptocurrency-focused rules into the nation&#8217;s advertising code to protect consumers from misleading advertising.</p>
<p>The new guidelines aim to ensure that cryptocurrency advertisements accurately state the risks involved with all cryptocurrency investments, making it clear to consumers that they stand to lose their capital due to market volatility.</p>
<p>&#8220;Advertisements must expressly and clearly state that investing in crypto assets may result in the loss of capital as the value is variable and can go up as well as down,&#8221; the ARB <a href="https://www.arb.org.za/assets/section-iii-specific-categories-of-advertising-v2023.1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stated</a>. In addition, they warned that the overall message of the advertisement must not contradict the warnings about potential money losses set out above.</p>
<p>Ads must rigorously explain the risks and benefits associated with the cryptocurrency product or service they offer.</p>
<h2>Misleading Advertising Based on Past Performance Prohibited</h2>
<p>Another important aspect of the new guidelines is that crypto-related companies must not use exaggerated or misleading claims in their advertising. This includes making claims of high returns or low risks without providing any evidence to back them up.</p>
<p>Companies must also be transparent about their fees and charges and clearly communicate any risks or limitations associated with their products or services. According to the ARB, the advertisement of crypto-related services must clearly state that &#8220;past performance&#8221; is not indicative of the future returns that cryptocurrencies may experience. This is in line with the broader regulations applied to financial services, as any publicity for financial products must have a similar disclosure.</p>
<p>Similarly, they noted that those not registered as credit providers &#8220;should not encourage the purchase of crypto assets on credit.&#8221; However, they may promote information about payment methods used by crypto asset service providers.</p>
<h2>Influencers and Ambassadors Must Share Factual Information Only</h2>
<p>As for ambassadors and influencers, the ARB determined that such persons may only promote a product if they comply with the regulators&#8217; requirements.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lionel-messi-signs-a-20m-deal-to-become-the-global-ambassador-of-socios/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ambassadors</a> or influencers who do not meet the regulator&#8217;s criteria for qualified investors &#8220;may only share factual information&#8221; without giving additional advice on crypto asset trading or investment. This is a response to the controversy that arose during the bitcoin bull run when many crypto businesses released several controversial ads featuring famous worldwide celebrities to attract as many customers as possible.</p>
<p>For example, Crypto.com launched one of the most aggressive <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocom-buys-ad-space-super-bowl-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">ad campaign</a> in the ecosystem with the participation of actor Matt Damon, who invited his millions of followers to invest in the platform under the slogan &#8220;Fortune favors the brave.&#8221;</p>
<p>Following the massive crash of the crypto market and the losses of thousands of investors, South Park launched a video mocking Matt Damon, Gwyneth Paltrow, investor Larry David and tennis player Naomi Osaka, who used their image to promote this type of investment.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">New South Park movie aired tonight.</p>
<p>They made fun of Matt Damon selling out for Crypto and </p>
<p>uh</p>
<p>well <a href="https://t.co/FTIXSbRRbL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/FTIXSbRRbL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Dyme (@CryptoParadyme) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoParadyme/status/1547088449022222336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 13, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Some found it funny, but the ARB started to take things seriously.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-africa-regulator-takes-action-against-false-crypto-advertising-claims/" rel="nofollow">South Africa Regulator Takes Action Against False Crypto Advertising Claims</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lazarus Group Suspected as Culprits for $100 Million Harmony Bridge Hack</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-suspected-as-culprits-for-100-million-harmony-bridge-hack/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 23:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Harmony Protocol (ONE)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234589</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Hacking-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Hacking-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[More details about the transfer of funds following Harmony’s hack in June have been revealed. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">MistTrack – a crypto tracking and compliance platform – has published updates on its investigation of the Harmony bridge hack that compromised $100 million last June. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">They found that the infamous North Korean hacking organization, The Lazarus Group, are likely behind the theft. </span></p>
<h2>The Movement of Funds</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/MistTrack_io/status/1617521823067025408" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Twitter thread</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Monday, MistTrack said Lazarus passed the stolen funds through multiple exchanges and blockchains while attempting to cover their on-chain tracks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, the platform discovered that many funds were transferred to exchanges including Huobi, Binance, and OKX. Those funds were then “quickly converted to BTC” before being withdrawn from the exchanges. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Next, the BTC underwent “several multi-layer transfers,” before some of the funds were returned to exchanges. Meanwhile, others were bridges to Avalanche through multiple cross-chain exchanges for USDT and USDD – stablecoins pegged to the U.S. dollar. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other funds were transferred to Ethereum, and then eventually to Tron, where the recipient addresses were related to a “USDT mixed network.”</span></p>
<h2>Blockchain Bridges</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A bridge allows users to transfer assets that are otherwise native to one blockchain (ex. BTC for Bitcoin; ETH for Ethereum) over to other chains. This is usually accomplished by having users lock their tokens at a special address on the source blockchain, while tokenized equivalents are minted in equal measure on the other chain. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Unfortunately, bridges have become popular targets for hackers, bearing witness to some of the most catastrophic crimes in DeFi history. One such theft was the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/harmony-bridge-hacked-100-million-worth-of-ethereum-lost/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Harmony bridge hack</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> itself, which saw $100 million worth of ETH stolen in June. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Months prior, an independent researcher named “Ape Dev” on Twitter </span><a href="https://twitter.com/_apedev/status/1510007663832223751" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">warned</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Harmony could lose all of its funds if just two of the four private keys controlling the bridge’s wallet were compromised, potentially for up to $330 million. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other terrific hacks last year included the $600 million + </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ronin-hackers-have-moved-the-stolen-625m-to-bitcoin-network-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ronin bridge hack</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, which drained the entire Axie Infinity treasury. In this instance, 5 of 9 keys controlling the bridge were compromised, allowing for over 170,000 ETH and 25 million USDC to be taken. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">These funds were also stolen by the Lazarus group, from whom just 5% of the funds have been recovered since. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire recently tweeted about an upcoming </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-cross-chain-protocol-approaches-launch-date/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">blockchain bridge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for USDC. Unlike other bridges, this one will not contain a large honeypot targetable by hackers. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-suspected-as-culprits-for-100-million-harmony-bridge-hack/" rel="nofollow">Lazarus Group Suspected as Culprits for $100 Million Harmony Bridge Hack</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Definitely Nifty: NFTs Sold Topped 67% YoY Growth in 2022</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/definitely-nifty-nfts-sold-topped-67-yoy-growth-in-2022/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 23:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234328</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/nft_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/nft_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The total sales of NFTs increased by a whopping 67% YoY in 2022.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Ethereum, BNB Coin, Solana, and other DeFi altcoins kept running this week. New data in a report out from DappRadar reveals there were more NFTs sold in 2022 than the year before.</p>
<h2>DappRadar: NFTs Sales in 2022 Soared</h2>
<p>In more good news for cryptocurrency&#8217;s DeFi platforms, NFTs sold last year topped sales numbers from the year before. A new <a href="https://dappradar.com/blog/blockchain-and-dapp-adoption-report-2022" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> from on-chain analytics firm, DappRadar, reveals the extent that NFTs are reshaping digital ownership in the 2020s.</p>
<p>101 million nonfungible tokens <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/video/did-nfts-fare-2022-160045623.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">were sold in 2022</a>. That was a staggering 67% increase over the number of NFTs sold in 2021.</p>
<p>These figures are extremely revealing of the popularity and staying power of NFTs. Just like Bitcoin and smart contract blockchains before them, NFTs&#8217; critics in 2021 said the blockchain product was a passing fad. They said most of these <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible tokens</a> would eventually be worthless.</p>
<p>Furthermore, they said that the blockchain sector would eventually stop minting new NFTs, and the supply would collapse. Even with the crypto winter, production and units sold by the entire sector ramped up. They <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-09-28/nft-volumes-tumble-97-from-2022-highs-as-frenzy-fades-chart" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">warned</a> that NFTs&#8217; sales volumes were flatlining.</p>
<h2>Revenues Declined</h2>
<p>So it&#8217;s important to correct the perception of flatlining non-fungible token sales for the record. Because NFTs did have some down months in 2022, but overall, blockchainers minted and sold more new NFTs in 2022 than any year before it. Moreover, the growth in non-fungible token sales year-over-year was absolutely massive in 2022.</p>
<p>Revenue from NFT sales did decline in 2022, but not by much. Last year&#8217;s exchange in non-fungibles saw $24 billion in trading volume. The year before, NFTs changed hands for $25 billion in sales revenue.</p>
<p>So the market barely missed hitting the same sales revenue volume as the year before in the depths of crypto winter.</p>
<p>The highest volume trading day for NFTs in history was in 2022. It happened on May 1, 2022, before crypto winter had gotten really bad but when prices had all been slipping for months.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/definitely-nifty-nfts-sold-topped-67-yoy-growth-in-2022/" rel="nofollow">Definitely Nifty: NFTs Sold Topped 67% YoY Growth in 2022</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vitalik Buterin Weighs in on Stealth Address to Bring Privacy to Blockchain Transactions</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-weighs-in-on-stealth-address-to-bring-privacy-to-blockchain-transactions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 21:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tornado Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234503</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Stealth addresses can be registered on Ethereum Name Services (ENS) and can help in obfuscating the peer-to-peer transactions of digital assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Privacy tools have always been heralded as a key to financial freedom in the crypto industry. In the Ethereum ecosystem, discussions surrounding the subject matter have revolved mostly around privacy-preserving transfers of ETH and mainstream ERC20 tokens.</p>
<p>In a bid to improve the state of privacy on the network, its co-founder Vitalik Buterin has proposed a stealth address system.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Last Remaining Challenge for Ethereum&#8221;</h2>
<p>The concept of Stealth addresses using elliptic curve cryptography was first introduced in the context of Bitcoin by BTC core developer Peter Todd in 2014 to obscure transaction details. In the latest <a href="https://vitalik.ca/general/2023/01/20/stealth.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post,</a> Buterin acknowledged that privacy is &#8220;one of the largest remaining challenges in the Ethereum ecosystem&#8221; while highlighting the need for a privacy solution because &#8220;anything that goes onto a public blockchain is public.&#8221;</p>
<p>Stealth addresses, on the other hand, can help in this regard. Buterin noted that such a mechanism in place will enable the Ethereum wallet to generate stealth addresses to receive funds privately and access them using a special code called a &#8220;spending key.&#8221;</p>
<p>The proposed stealth addresses can be generated by either party, but they can only be controlled by one of them. The user receiving the assets generates the stealth address and keeps secret a spending key, which will then be used to generate a stealth meta-address that can be passed on to the sender.</p>
<p>This allows the sender to perform a computation on this meta-address to initiate a stealth address belonging to the receiver. The sender can then send any assets they want to send to this address, while the receiver will have full control. Along with the transfer, the sender publishes some extra cryptographic data on-chain confirming that the stealth address belongs to the receiver.</p>
<p>Buterin asserted that stealth addresses give the same privacy properties as a user generating a fresh address for each transaction.</p>
<h2>Stealth Address Vs. Tornado Cash</h2>
<p>Several methods have been employed in recent years to obfuscate transactional details. This includes Tornado Cash which was recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-tornado-cashs-activity-didnt-cease-completely-post-ofac-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">sanctioned</a> by the OFAC. Buterin, for one, said the proposed concept of stealth address provides a different kind of privacy to that of the popular Ethereum-based coin mixer. He explained,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Tornado Cash can hide transfers of mainstream fungible assets such as ETH or major ERC20s (though it&#8217;s most easily useful for privately sending to yourself), but it&#8217;s very weak at adding privacy to transfers of obscure ERC20s, and it cannot add privacy to NFT transfers at all.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-weighs-in-on-stealth-address-to-bring-privacy-to-blockchain-transactions/" rel="nofollow">Vitalik Buterin Weighs in on Stealth Address to Bring Privacy to Blockchain Transactions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>IMF Recommends 5-Point Crypto Regulation Scheme</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/imf-recommends-5-point-crypto-regulation-scheme/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 20:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234341</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cryptocurrency_imf_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cryptocurrency_imf_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund issued a five-point cryptocurrency recommendation scheme.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As global influencers rubbed elbows at Davos, the IMF issued recommendations for crypto to global regulators. Depending on who you ask, crypto regulation could hurt the industry or open up vast new markets for normie investors.</p>
<p>In a note published over the week, the International Monetary Fund <a href="https://www.imf.org/en/Blogs/Articles/2023/01/18/crypto-contagion-underscores-why-global-regulators-must-act-fast-to-stem-risk" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;During times of stress, we’ve seen market failures of stablecoins, crypto-focused hedge funds, and crypto exchanges, which in turn raised serious concerns about market integrity and user protection. And with growing and deeper links with the core financial system, there could also be concerns about systemic risk and financial stability in the near future.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The IMF&#8217;s preferred approach to counter these concerns is increasing global crypto regulation:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Many of these concerns can be addressed by strengthening financial regulation and supervision, and by developing global standards that can be implemented consistently by national regulatory authorities.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The recommendations are:</p>
<p>1) License, register, and authorize crypto asset providers. 2) Prohibit crypto entities from carrying out multiple functions in one business that create conflicts of interest. 3) Apply strong, bank-type regulation to stablecoin issuers. 4) Impose clear requirements on traditional financial institutions for exposure or engagement with crypto. 5) Create a consistent global approach to crypto regulation and oversight.</p>
<h2>Posing a Threat?</h2>
<p>While it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chinas-ban-made-bitcoin-even-stronger-says-edward-snowden/" data-wpel-link="internal">seems unlikely</a> that the <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/cryptocurrency-regulations-around-the-world-5202122" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">entire world</a> could agree on crypto regulations, the possibility of a global regulatory regime seems stifling. After all, Bitcoin was invented in the first place to side-step the global financial system.</p>
<p>In the view of Bitcoin&#8217;s creators and earliest adopters, it was the global financial system that was the contagion with spillover risk. Regulations did nothing to stop a financial downturn much bigger than the crypto winter from shocking global markets in 2008.</p>
<p>In fact, it&#8217;s even possible that financial regulations are what led to the 2008 financial crisis. The central bank&#8217;s regulation of the money supply was dovish in the years leading up to that. This encouraged rampant speculation in exotic instruments with borrowed money at low-interest rates.</p>
<h2>For Better or Worse?</h2>
<p>As the money velocity of the economy churned and revalued each dollar according to the constantly growing new supply of USD, the same thing happened <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-lesson-in-alameda-ftx-about-government-regulation-and-crypto-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">to Wall Street that happened to Alameda-FTX</a>. They were holding on to all these assets that weren&#8217;t really worth what they said on paper.</p>
<p>A global regulatory regime with inflexible, one-size-fits-all rules put together by committees could easily squash a project as important as Bitcoin before it has a chance to get started.</p>
<p>Or perhaps just as easily inspire one and cede control to an ecosystem of peer-to-peer network governance cobbled together ad hoc by developers, entrepreneurs, and the markets they serve.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/imf-recommends-5-point-crypto-regulation-scheme/" rel="nofollow">IMF Recommends 5-Point Crypto Regulation Scheme</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle Cross-Chain Protocol Approaches Launch Date</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circle-cross-chain-protocol-approaches-launch-date/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 18:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234563</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/circlenyse.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/circlenyse.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Circle’s Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol lets users burn USDC on one chain while Circle sends them newly minted USDC on another. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Circle – the issuer of the second largest stablecoin by market cap, USDC – is preparing to launch a permissionless protocol for letting users transfer their stablecoins between blockchains. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The company said the protocol can be embedded into dapps, and provide the most “capital efficient” path for cross-chain USDC transfers.</span></p>
<h2>Bridging USDC</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/jerallaire/status/1616912607407149057?t=72cy9wJ0mmJ4gWU_Bpnm6A&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on Monday, Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire said the Cross-Chain Transfer Protocol (CCTP) will “help foster more scalable, efficient, secure and user friendly apps built on USDC.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">USDC, a stablecoin, is value pegged to the U.S. dollar. Each token holds its “stable” price by maintaining 1:1 convertibility for $1.00 at all times through Circle’s reserves, which are </span><a href="https://www.circle.com/en/transparency#stability" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">comprised</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of over $43 billion in cash and U.S. Treasuries. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Stablecoins are a core element of the Defi economy, which would otherwise be difficult to interact with given the volatility of other cryptocurrencies. With a cross-chain bridge for the second-largest of the bunch, Circle’s new tool is aimed toward “unifying liquidity across the ecosystem and simplifying user experience,” per its </span><a href="https://developers.circle.com/stablecoin/docs/cctp-getting-started" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CCTP intends to feature more functionality than the typical blockchain bridge, however, due to being exposed to smart contracts. For instance, developers may build flows that let users can move USDC across chains and directly into a given defi protocol to begin generating yield, in what feels like one seamless transaction. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To use the protocol, users begin by burning their USDC tokens on their source chain. This burn is later observed and attested to by Circle, which then mints a new batch of USDC on the destination chain, and sends it to the user’s provided address. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Developers can leverage CCTP to build novel cross-chain apps that stack together the various functionalities of trading, lending, payments, NFTs, gaming and more – all while abstracting complexity away from users,” explained the company. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Circle’s Expanding Network</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In November, Circle </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-integrates-apple-pay-for-existing-merchants/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">integrated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with Apple Pay for its existing merchants, letting its customers check out from apps like Safari without the burden of filling out lengthy forms. Businesses need only a Circle account and Apple developer account to use the service. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The company also </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blocks-tbd-partners-with-circle-to-create-global-fiat-crypto-bridges/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">partnered</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with TBD, a subsidiary of Jack Dorsey’s Block, in September, with the mission of creating global fiat-to-crypto bridges. Block intends to use these bridges as part of its mission to form a decentralized Bitcoin exchange – an asset that is mostly confined to trade with help from CeFi institutions. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-cross-chain-protocol-approaches-launch-date/" rel="nofollow">Circle Cross-Chain Protocol Approaches Launch Date</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Is Up Nearly 30% Since Peter Schiff, Jim Cramer Said Get Out of Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-is-up-nearly-30-since-peter-schiff-jim-cramer-said-get-out-of-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 16:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234470</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cramer_Schiff_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Cramer_Schiff_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Contrary to Peter Schiff's and Jim Cramer's pessimistic predictions, bitcoin continued its price expansion.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the biggest critics of the cryptocurrency industry &#8211; Peter Schiff &#8211; expected bitcoin&#8217;s spike at the start of the year to cease shortly after it began and advised investors to sell their holdings when the asset was trading at around $18,000. The uptrend, though, continued, and BTC currently stands at $22,800 &#8211; a 27% increase since the American financial commentator shared his views.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another famous person whose grim prediction has failed as of the moment is Jim Cramer. He urged people to cash out their &#8220;awful&#8221; crypto positions at the beginning of December last year, while bitcoin is up 33% since that statement.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Schiff&#8217;s Forecast: a Catalyst for BTC&#8217;s Rise?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO of Euro Pacific Capital &#8211; Peter Schiff &#8211; is among the most vocal opponents of the cryptocurrency sector and often cautions investors to stay away from it. He opined on January 12 that bitcoin&#8217;s surge to above $18,000 (at that time) was an &#8220;excellent opportunity&#8221; for HODLers to sell their ownings. As usual, Schiff claimed investing in gold is a much better option. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> is trading above $18K, its highest level in 3 weeks, an excellent opportunity for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/HOLDers?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#HOLDers</a> to sell ahead of the release of the Dec. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CPI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#CPI</a>. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Gold?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Gold</a> is only up $10, trading at an 8-month high. While Bitcoin has already broken down, gold has broken out. Time to drop Bitcoin.</p>
<p>— Peter Schiff (@PeterSchiff) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeterSchiff/status/1613507494541770752?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Luckily for those who did not part with their holdings, bitcoin&#8217;s run continued in the following days, hitting <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/300m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-soars-to-18-week-high/" data-wpel-link="internal">a 5-month high</a> of nearly $23,300 (according to CoinGecko&#8217;s data) on January 21. This represented an almost 30% price increase compared to the day when Schiff shared his view. Currently, BTC is worth approximately $22,800, or a 27% spike.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American, known as a huge proponent of gold, expected to see a significant price expansion for the precious metal. Nonetheless, it has risen by a mere 1.3% over the past ten days.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Cramer Effect</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jim Cramer &#8211; the host of CNBC&#8217;s Mad Money show &#8211; has jumped from a huge supporter of the industry to an outspoken critic over the past several years. He is also often mocked by the crypto community since many of his predictions have been proven wrong.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/jim-cramer-urges-for-caution-in-the-cryptocurrency-market-amid-evergrande-saga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">advised</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> investors to sell their bitcoin holdings in September 2021 when the Evergrande debt crisis in China seemed to play a major role in the asset&#8217;s future performance. Bitcoin reached an all-time high of nearly $70,000 two months later.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cnbcs-jim-cramer-believes-bitcoin-and-ethereums-selloff-could-be-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">argued</a> in January last year that the BTC correction could be over, meaning people should reconsider jumping on the bandwagon. Contrary to that expectation, bitcoin lost over 60% of its valuation throughout 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cramer&#8217;s latest advice came on December 6 when he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bull-market-signal-jim-cramer-advises-crypto-investors-to-sell/" data-wpel-link="internal">told</a> investors they still have time to sell their &#8220;awful&#8221; positions. He specifically outlined Ripple (XRP), Dogecoin (DOGE), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC) as the most speculative tokens that could crash to zero. All four still exist and, apart from DOGE, are in a much better condition since the beginning of last month. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-is-up-nearly-30-since-peter-schiff-jim-cramer-said-get-out-of-crypto/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Is Up Nearly 30% Since Peter Schiff, Jim Cramer Said Get Out of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Today in 2014: Ethereum Was Announced by Vitalik Buterin on Bitcointalk</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/today-in-2014-ethereum-was-announced-by-vitalik-buterin-on-bitcointalk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234477</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereum_Dark.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Ethereum_Dark.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nine years ago, on this day, Vitalik Buterin announced Ethereum on the popular Bitcointalk forum.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vitalik Buterin&#8217;s first tryst with the Bitcoin community dates back to 2011. He began participating in &#8216;Bitcointalk,&#8217; a forum created by Satoshi Nakamoto. It was then that he co-founded and started writing articles for Bitcoin magazine. He began traveling to speak with BTC developers around the world in a bid to construct a new, potentially superior iteration of the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p>In late 2013, Buterin described the idea of yet another digital currency in a white paper and sent it to a few of his friends. The vision was to develop a blockchain with a built-in programming language and platform for decentralized applications, an &#8220;android of the cryptocurrency world&#8221; of sorts.</p>
<p>Subsequently, Ethereum was officially <a href="https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=428589" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> on Bitcointalk on January 23rd, 2014. It has been exactly nine years since then. The blockchain&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-history-from-whitepaper-to-hardforks-and-the-eth-merge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">story</a>, from the whitepaper to the DAO attack, to the hard fork, scalability issues, and more recent Merge, has been anything but ordinary.</p>
<h2>&#8220;Welcome to the New Beginning&#8221;</h2>
<p>Buterin revealed that the primary core devs along with him were Gavin Wood, Charles Hoskinson, and Jeffrey Wilcke, while Anthony Di Iorio, Mihai Alisie, Joseph Lubin, and Stephan Tual were named as primary non-development members. Buterin&#8217;s commentary, titled &#8220;Welcome to the New Beginning, noted,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Ethereum is a modular, stateful, Turing-complete contract scripting system married to a blockchain and developed with a philosophy of simplicity, universal accessibility, and generalization. Our goal is to provide a platform for decentralized applications &#8211; an android of the cryptocurrency world, where all efforts can share a common set of APIs, trustless interactions, and no compromises.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>While explaining his brainchild, Buterin then called for the community to join the new ecosystem as volunteers, developers, investors, and evangelists. The focus was to enable a &#8220;fundamentally different paradigm for the internet and the relationships it provides.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Challenging the Idea of &#8216;Bitcoin Dominance Maximalism&#8217;</h2>
<p>The same year, Buterin challenged the Bitcoin Dominance Maximalism, a school of thought that is still very much relevant in the crypto ecosystem. His treatise essentially separated people who simply want to improve Bitcoin from those who can be called &#8220;Bitcoin domination maximalists,&#8221; often categorized as aggressive, hostile, and toxic.</p>
<p>This was the first time he questioned the ideology. Since then, Ethereum itself has become the most consistent and high-profile target of criticism by the proud &#8220;Bitcoin Maximalist.&#8221; Despite the differences in culture and workings, Ethereum has still managed to retain its position as the second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, almost a decade after its existence, even as most prominent altcoins faded away.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/today-in-2014-ethereum-was-announced-by-vitalik-buterin-on-bitcointalk/" rel="nofollow">Today in 2014: Ethereum Was Announced by Vitalik Buterin on Bitcointalk</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
