<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 06:35:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BingX Launches Special Events for P2P Crypto-Fiat Traders]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bingx-launches-special-events-for-p2p-crypto-fiat-traders</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bing-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bing-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bing-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:49:23 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bingx-launches-special-events-for-p2p-crypto-fiat-traders</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s leading social trading platform, BingX, announced the launch of a peer-to-peer trading feature which allows users to buy and sell crypto directly with P2P merchants. </p>
<p>BingX, the world&rsquo;s leading social trading platform, announced the launch of its innovative peer-to-peer (P2P) trading feature. The company&rsquo;s latest offering allows users to buy and sell cryptocurrencies directly with P2P merchants at agreed-upon prices.</p>
<p>In a press release, the firm said with BingX P2P, traders will receive rewards for their first trades. The platform further said:</p>

<p>With BingX P2P, traders can enjoy reduced fees, enhanced trust and security, community interaction, and competitive pricing, making it the go-to platform for seamless and rewarding crypto trading experiences.</p>

<p>The platform is advantageous as P2P trading, using its platform, reduces fees compared to traditional centralized exchanges. In a P2P system, intermediaries are eliminated, and users can save on various instances, including trading fees, withdrawal fees, and other related costs, maximizing the user&rsquo;s potential profits.</p>
<p>BingX has also ensured secure transactions, stating:</p>

<p>To ensure secure transactions, BingX P2P trading employs advanced security measures. These systems hold funds in neutral accounts until both parties fulfil their obligations, effectively reducing the risk of fraud or disputes and enhancing trust and security.</p>

BingX P2P Foster Community Building
<p>The platform also boasts a &ldquo;vibrant and supportive trading community&rdquo;, which creates a network for traders to connect.</p>

<p>In addition, BingX P2P fosters a vibrant and supportive trading community. Traders can connect with fellow enthusiasts, share knowledge, and exchange experiences directly, creating an engaging and collaborative environment.</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s emphasis on community building sets BingX apart from traditional exchanges and adds value to the overall trading experience.</p>

<p>BingX P2P is also unique in that it offers competitive pricing:</p>

<p>BingX P2P trading also offers competitive pricing, allowing sellers to set their own prices while providing buyers the freedom to choose from a variety of attractive offers.</p>
<p>This direct nature of transactions ensures favourable pricing for both parties, giving traders an edge compared to centralized exchanges that may impose fees or less competitive rates.</p>

BingX Offers Over 30 Fiat Options
<p>The platform boasts an impressive 30 fiat options, including USD, &nbsp;EUR, IDR and additional support for nearly 300 payment methods worldwide. The company said it would continually expand its fiat currency offering to cater for the needs of its growing user base.</p>
From Bingbon to BingX
<p>The digital asset exchange announced to complete corporate rebrand in 2021, changing its name from Bingbon to BingX.</p>
<p>The platform, which has offered a crypto spot and derivative services since 2018, said that under its new name, it &ldquo;hopes to continue accelerating open value transfer and empowering an accessible, engaging crypto trading experience via innovative social trading solutions.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s leading social trading platform, BingX, announced the launch of a peer-to-peer trading feature which allows users to buy and sell crypto directly with P2P merchants. </p>
<p>BingX, the world&rsquo;s leading social trading platform, announced the launch of its innovative peer-to-peer (P2P) trading feature. The company&rsquo;s latest offering allows users to buy and sell cryptocurrencies directly with P2P merchants at agreed-upon prices.</p>
<p>In a press release, the firm said with BingX P2P, traders will receive rewards for their first trades. The platform further said:</p>

<p>With BingX P2P, traders can enjoy reduced fees, enhanced trust and security, community interaction, and competitive pricing, making it the go-to platform for seamless and rewarding crypto trading experiences.</p>

<p>The platform is advantageous as P2P trading, using its platform, reduces fees compared to traditional centralized exchanges. In a P2P system, intermediaries are eliminated, and users can save on various instances, including trading fees, withdrawal fees, and other related costs, maximizing the user&rsquo;s potential profits.</p>
<p>BingX has also ensured secure transactions, stating:</p>

<p>To ensure secure transactions, BingX P2P trading employs advanced security measures. These systems hold funds in neutral accounts until both parties fulfil their obligations, effectively reducing the risk of fraud or disputes and enhancing trust and security.</p>

BingX P2P Foster Community Building
<p>The platform also boasts a &ldquo;vibrant and supportive trading community&rdquo;, which creates a network for traders to connect.</p>

<p>In addition, BingX P2P fosters a vibrant and supportive trading community. Traders can connect with fellow enthusiasts, share knowledge, and exchange experiences directly, creating an engaging and collaborative environment.</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s emphasis on community building sets BingX apart from traditional exchanges and adds value to the overall trading experience.</p>

<p>BingX P2P is also unique in that it offers competitive pricing:</p>

<p>BingX P2P trading also offers competitive pricing, allowing sellers to set their own prices while providing buyers the freedom to choose from a variety of attractive offers.</p>
<p>This direct nature of transactions ensures favourable pricing for both parties, giving traders an edge compared to centralized exchanges that may impose fees or less competitive rates.</p>

BingX Offers Over 30 Fiat Options
<p>The platform boasts an impressive 30 fiat options, including USD, &nbsp;EUR, IDR and additional support for nearly 300 payment methods worldwide. The company said it would continually expand its fiat currency offering to cater for the needs of its growing user base.</p>
From Bingbon to BingX
<p>The digital asset exchange announced to complete corporate rebrand in 2021, changing its name from Bingbon to BingX.</p>
<p>The platform, which has offered a crypto spot and derivative services since 2018, said that under its new name, it &ldquo;hopes to continue accelerating open value transfer and empowering an accessible, engaging crypto trading experience via innovative social trading solutions.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[XRP: Public Awaits The Release Of The Hinman Documents]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/xrp-public-awaits-the-release-of-the-hinman-documents</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:56:07 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/xrp-public-awaits-the-release-of-the-hinman-documents</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Ripple executives and the broader crypto industry eagerly await the Hinman documents&rsquo; public release. </p>
Hinman Documents Expected to Be Unsealed by June 13
<p>The highly anticipated public release of the Hinman speech documents and emails is reportedly set for June 13, 2023. Before these documents can be unsealed, one of Ripple&rsquo;s most notable executives, Susan Friedman, Ripple&rsquo;s head of policy, is focusing on a crucial hearing linked to the crypto industry ahead of the public release of the Hinman documents.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">While the upcoming June 13 HFSC hearing is an important one for crypto, the one being held next week by @HouseAgGOP is equally so. @CongressmanGT has been a steadfast supporter of the call for clarity in this space. https://t.co/DLLUjDzhQr</p>
&mdash; Susan Friedman (@ss_friedman) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The crypto industry and Ripple executives such as Susan Friedman eagerly await June 6 hearing that the House Committee on Agriculture is organizing. The hearing entitled &ldquo;The Future of Digital Assets: Providing Clarity for Digital Asset Spot Markets&rdquo; will delve into the nuances of crypto markets and provide some much-needed clarity for the crypto spot market.</p>
June 6 Hearing is Crucial Before The Hinman Documents Can Be Unsealed
<p>Key to note here is that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) falls under the jurisdiction of the House Agriculture Committee. The CFTC and the SEC have been the two leading agencies actively cracking down on the crypto industry and pushing regulatory charges around digital assets-linked firms.</p>
<p>The SEC, in particular, have been accused of not providing clear rules for the market. It was recently sued by crypto exchange Coinbase for allegedly ignoring its petition for clear crypto guidance.</p>
<p>The June 6 hearing by the House Committee on Agriculture comes as a crucial time, just a month before the highly anticipated release of the Hinman speech and emails.</p>
<p>The Hinman documents also include unredacted versions of cross-motions for summary judgement and accompanying exhibits in the XRP lawsuit, Coingape reports.</p>
The Hinman Documents &ndash; What do they entail?
<p>Ripple gained a small victory in October in its ongoing case with the SEC, when the latter was forced to give up the Hinman documents, which could help Ripple prove in its case that XRP is, in fact, not a security.</p>
<p>The documents include discovery material proving that the former Director of Corporation Finance, Willian Hinman, delivered a speech in which he clearly stated that neither Bitcoin (BTC) nor Ether (ETH) is securities.</p>
<p>Video evidence of Hinman claiming that neither tokens are a security emerged. In the recording, Hinman states:</p>

<p>Based on my understanding of the present state of Ether, the Ethereum network and its decentralized structure, current offers and sales of Ether are not securities transactions.</p>

Ripple CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, Remains Confident - Market Reacted Well
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s chief executive Brad Garlinghouse told Forbes he predicts the case, dragging on since 2020, will conclude in &ldquo;weeks, not months.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Garlinghouse&rsquo;s statement shot XRP&rsquo;s price up by over 10% over last week, and it currently trades at $0.51, according to data by CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>XRP has tested the critical resistance at $0.5, but many wonders if the rally will continue.</p>
<p>Technical analysis from news agency CryptoPotato indicates that XRP has shown a consistent upward trend after being rejected from its 200-day moving average at around $0.4. XRP also managed to surpass its 50-day moving average of approximately $0.45 and seems to target its resistance zone at $0.6 in the short term. &nbsp;</p>
<p>If XRP successfully breaks through the $0.6 level, it would likely spur a bullish phase, with prices potentially reaching highs of $0.9 mid-term.</p>
<p>Investors should, however, be cautious as the Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates we are in an overbought market, suggesting a pullback or a period of consolidation may be seen in the next few days.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse further told Tai Panich, the chief executive of SCB 10x, in a YouTube interview:</p>

<p>I feel very confident that we&rsquo;ll see a decision from the courts this year.</p>

<p>Adding:</p>

<p>In fact, I think I would guess that it will be in weeks, not months.</p>

<p>The Ripple CEO also commented on the decision for the Hinman documents to be made public.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Another win for transparency! Unredacted Hinman emails to be publicly available soon - stay tuned as the lawyers work through the mechanics to make that happen. https://t.co/o6puPypRHd https://t.co/qmaLVeQaP8</p>
&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) May 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>He told Forbes:</p>

<p>The court just ruled last week that the notes in the emails associated with that are going to be made public, and should be public around June 13. So I think that&rsquo;s a huge win for transparency. But what it really calls out is, there really hasn&rsquo;t been clarity, despite calls and demands from leaders across the crypto industry.</p>

<p>Forbes further reports that while crypto exchange Kraken and crypto lenders such as BlockFi chose to settle with the SEC, Ripple decided to fight it and go to court.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p>Ripple decided to lean in and fight this fight, both for Ripple and the whole industry. We&rsquo;ve spent a lot of money defending it. And I think what we&rsquo;ve called out is the government in the United States, and the SEC particularly, is putting politics ahead of smart policy.</p>

Things Are Looking Up for Ripple
<p>A recent Messari report revealed that XRP surged by over 55% in Q1 2023, outperforming the overall crypto market. The report further shows that XRP&rsquo;s market cap increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to an impressive $27.4 billion on March 31, representing a Q1 surge of 59.9%.</p>
<p>Ripple further announced it made a&nbsp;$250 million acquisition of Metaco&nbsp;&ndash; a well-known crypto custodian. Seen as a positive sign for the future of both Ripple and Metaco, the move sees Ripple take on sole responsibility at Metaco while still allowing current CEO Adrien Traccani to manage operations independently.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today, we are proud to announce Ripple has acquired @metaco_sa, becoming the sole shareholder of the Swiss-based provider of digital asset custody and tokenization technology.Learn more: https://t.co/GrI3u13iDT</p>
&mdash; Ripple (@Ripple) May 17, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple executives and the broader crypto industry eagerly await the Hinman documents&rsquo; public release. </p>
Hinman Documents Expected to Be Unsealed by June 13
<p>The highly anticipated public release of the Hinman speech documents and emails is reportedly set for June 13, 2023. Before these documents can be unsealed, one of Ripple&rsquo;s most notable executives, Susan Friedman, Ripple&rsquo;s head of policy, is focusing on a crucial hearing linked to the crypto industry ahead of the public release of the Hinman documents.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">While the upcoming June 13 HFSC hearing is an important one for crypto, the one being held next week by @HouseAgGOP is equally so. @CongressmanGT has been a steadfast supporter of the call for clarity in this space. https://t.co/DLLUjDzhQr</p>
&mdash; Susan Friedman (@ss_friedman) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The crypto industry and Ripple executives such as Susan Friedman eagerly await June 6 hearing that the House Committee on Agriculture is organizing. The hearing entitled &ldquo;The Future of Digital Assets: Providing Clarity for Digital Asset Spot Markets&rdquo; will delve into the nuances of crypto markets and provide some much-needed clarity for the crypto spot market.</p>
June 6 Hearing is Crucial Before The Hinman Documents Can Be Unsealed
<p>Key to note here is that the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) falls under the jurisdiction of the House Agriculture Committee. The CFTC and the SEC have been the two leading agencies actively cracking down on the crypto industry and pushing regulatory charges around digital assets-linked firms.</p>
<p>The SEC, in particular, have been accused of not providing clear rules for the market. It was recently sued by crypto exchange Coinbase for allegedly ignoring its petition for clear crypto guidance.</p>
<p>The June 6 hearing by the House Committee on Agriculture comes as a crucial time, just a month before the highly anticipated release of the Hinman speech and emails.</p>
<p>The Hinman documents also include unredacted versions of cross-motions for summary judgement and accompanying exhibits in the XRP lawsuit, Coingape reports.</p>
The Hinman Documents &ndash; What do they entail?
<p>Ripple gained a small victory in October in its ongoing case with the SEC, when the latter was forced to give up the Hinman documents, which could help Ripple prove in its case that XRP is, in fact, not a security.</p>
<p>The documents include discovery material proving that the former Director of Corporation Finance, Willian Hinman, delivered a speech in which he clearly stated that neither Bitcoin (BTC) nor Ether (ETH) is securities.</p>
<p>Video evidence of Hinman claiming that neither tokens are a security emerged. In the recording, Hinman states:</p>

<p>Based on my understanding of the present state of Ether, the Ethereum network and its decentralized structure, current offers and sales of Ether are not securities transactions.</p>

Ripple CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, Remains Confident - Market Reacted Well
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s chief executive Brad Garlinghouse told Forbes he predicts the case, dragging on since 2020, will conclude in &ldquo;weeks, not months.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Garlinghouse&rsquo;s statement shot XRP&rsquo;s price up by over 10% over last week, and it currently trades at $0.51, according to data by CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>XRP has tested the critical resistance at $0.5, but many wonders if the rally will continue.</p>
<p>Technical analysis from news agency CryptoPotato indicates that XRP has shown a consistent upward trend after being rejected from its 200-day moving average at around $0.4. XRP also managed to surpass its 50-day moving average of approximately $0.45 and seems to target its resistance zone at $0.6 in the short term. &nbsp;</p>
<p>If XRP successfully breaks through the $0.6 level, it would likely spur a bullish phase, with prices potentially reaching highs of $0.9 mid-term.</p>
<p>Investors should, however, be cautious as the Relative Strength Index (RSI) indicates we are in an overbought market, suggesting a pullback or a period of consolidation may be seen in the next few days.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse further told Tai Panich, the chief executive of SCB 10x, in a YouTube interview:</p>

<p>I feel very confident that we&rsquo;ll see a decision from the courts this year.</p>

<p>Adding:</p>

<p>In fact, I think I would guess that it will be in weeks, not months.</p>

<p>The Ripple CEO also commented on the decision for the Hinman documents to be made public.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Another win for transparency! Unredacted Hinman emails to be publicly available soon - stay tuned as the lawyers work through the mechanics to make that happen. https://t.co/o6puPypRHd https://t.co/qmaLVeQaP8</p>
&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) May 16, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>He told Forbes:</p>

<p>The court just ruled last week that the notes in the emails associated with that are going to be made public, and should be public around June 13. So I think that&rsquo;s a huge win for transparency. But what it really calls out is, there really hasn&rsquo;t been clarity, despite calls and demands from leaders across the crypto industry.</p>

<p>Forbes further reports that while crypto exchange Kraken and crypto lenders such as BlockFi chose to settle with the SEC, Ripple decided to fight it and go to court.</p>
<p>Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p>Ripple decided to lean in and fight this fight, both for Ripple and the whole industry. We&rsquo;ve spent a lot of money defending it. And I think what we&rsquo;ve called out is the government in the United States, and the SEC particularly, is putting politics ahead of smart policy.</p>

Things Are Looking Up for Ripple
<p>A recent Messari report revealed that XRP surged by over 55% in Q1 2023, outperforming the overall crypto market. The report further shows that XRP&rsquo;s market cap increased from $17.4 billion on January 1 to an impressive $27.4 billion on March 31, representing a Q1 surge of 59.9%.</p>
<p>Ripple further announced it made a&nbsp;$250 million acquisition of Metaco&nbsp;&ndash; a well-known crypto custodian. Seen as a positive sign for the future of both Ripple and Metaco, the move sees Ripple take on sole responsibility at Metaco while still allowing current CEO Adrien Traccani to manage operations independently.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today, we are proud to announce Ripple has acquired @metaco_sa, becoming the sole shareholder of the Swiss-based provider of digital asset custody and tokenization technology.Learn more: https://t.co/GrI3u13iDT</p>
&mdash; Ripple (@Ripple) May 17, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Magic Web3 Wallet Raises $52m In Strategic Funding]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/magic-web3-wallet-raises-52m-in-strategic-funding-updated</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/magic-web3-wallet-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/magic-web3-wallet-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/magic-web3-wallet-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/magic-web3-wallet-raises-52m-in-strategic-funding-updated</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Wallet-as-a-service provider Magic has successfully raised $52 million in a strategic funding round led by PayPal Ventures.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The investment will support Magic's expansion plans within the European Union and Asia-Pacific region, as well as the development of additional use cases. Magic offers non-custodial wallet infrastructure to enterprise clients, enabling them to securely onboard customers into the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Participants in the funding round inccluded Cherubic, Synchrony, KX, Northzone, and Volt Capital. With this latest funding, Magic's total raised capital now exceeds $80 million. The San Francisco-based company, founded in 2018, provides enterprise-grade solutions that simplify the adoption of Web3 technology for large enterprises in various sectors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Magic's non-custodial wallet creation infrastructure utilizes a software development kit (SDK), allowing companies to seamlessly integrate wallet creation into their applications. Users can create wallets instantly using existing email, social media accounts, or SMS. To date, Magic has generated over 20 million unique wallets, and its SDK is widely used by more than 130,000 developers. Notable clients of Magic include Mattel, Macy's, Xsolla, and Immutable.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alan Du, a partner at PayPal Ventures, expressed his confidence in Magic's wallet creation service, highlighting its ability to onboard new users to Web3 and enable global brands to explore diverse use cases within the growing Web3 landscape. Magic's CEO, Sean Li, stated that the company has observed a steady increase in Web3 adoption among large enterprises, with global brands leveraging blockchain technology to engage customers and monetize their experiences in innovative ways.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Our vision is to ignite new economic opportunities by enabling authentic digital ownership for everyone - starting with building the necessary infrastructure to onboard the next billion users to web3." Li shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The strategic funding will allow Magic to further expand its functionality and provide increased value to its customers. The company aims to deepen its integration within the European Union and Asia-Pacific markets. Magic's vision is to enable widespread economic opportunities by creating the necessary infrastructure to onboard billions of users into the Web3 ecosystem. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Magic's solutions are designed to simplify the migration to Web3, providing enterprise-grade, low-effort solutions for various applications such as customer loyalty programs, digital collectibles, employee recognition, ticketing, and memberships. The company's success lies in its commitment to secure and seamless non-custodial wallet creation, offering users complete control over their assets. Magic's scalability and compliance with industry standards differentiate it from other wallet-as-a-service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership between Magic and PayPal Ventures reflects the increasing interest and recognition of the potential of blockchain technology by established companies. While Magic continues to facilitate the onboarding of users into Web3, the funding and expansion plans will position the company to bridge the gap between traditional businesses and the evolving Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Wallet-as-a-service provider Magic has successfully raised $52 million in a strategic funding round led by PayPal Ventures.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The investment will support Magic's expansion plans within the European Union and Asia-Pacific region, as well as the development of additional use cases. Magic offers non-custodial wallet infrastructure to enterprise clients, enabling them to securely onboard customers into the Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Participants in the funding round inccluded Cherubic, Synchrony, KX, Northzone, and Volt Capital. With this latest funding, Magic's total raised capital now exceeds $80 million. The San Francisco-based company, founded in 2018, provides enterprise-grade solutions that simplify the adoption of Web3 technology for large enterprises in various sectors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Magic's non-custodial wallet creation infrastructure utilizes a software development kit (SDK), allowing companies to seamlessly integrate wallet creation into their applications. Users can create wallets instantly using existing email, social media accounts, or SMS. To date, Magic has generated over 20 million unique wallets, and its SDK is widely used by more than 130,000 developers. Notable clients of Magic include Mattel, Macy's, Xsolla, and Immutable.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Alan Du, a partner at PayPal Ventures, expressed his confidence in Magic's wallet creation service, highlighting its ability to onboard new users to Web3 and enable global brands to explore diverse use cases within the growing Web3 landscape. Magic's CEO, Sean Li, stated that the company has observed a steady increase in Web3 adoption among large enterprises, with global brands leveraging blockchain technology to engage customers and monetize their experiences in innovative ways.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Our vision is to ignite new economic opportunities by enabling authentic digital ownership for everyone - starting with building the necessary infrastructure to onboard the next billion users to web3." Li shares.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The strategic funding will allow Magic to further expand its functionality and provide increased value to its customers. The company aims to deepen its integration within the European Union and Asia-Pacific markets. Magic's vision is to enable widespread economic opportunities by creating the necessary infrastructure to onboard billions of users into the Web3 ecosystem. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Magic's solutions are designed to simplify the migration to Web3, providing enterprise-grade, low-effort solutions for various applications such as customer loyalty programs, digital collectibles, employee recognition, ticketing, and memberships. The company's success lies in its commitment to secure and seamless non-custodial wallet creation, offering users complete control over their assets. Magic's scalability and compliance with industry standards differentiate it from other wallet-as-a-service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership between Magic and PayPal Ventures reflects the increasing interest and recognition of the potential of blockchain technology by established companies. While Magic continues to facilitate the onboarding of users into Web3, the funding and expansion plans will position the company to bridge the gap between traditional businesses and the evolving Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Brings In Deutsche Telekom As Node Validator]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-brings-in-deutsche-telekom-as-node-validator</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-dt-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-dt-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-x-dt-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 02:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/polygon-brings-in-deutsche-telekom-as-node-validator</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Germany's Deutsche Telekom has joined Polygon as a validator, signaling its support for the Ethereum layer-2 scaling protocol and expanding its involvement in the blockchain technology space. Deutsche Telekom aims to explore new revenue streams and enhance network security through its participation as a validator.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The company's subsidiary, Deutsche Telekom MMS, will operate as a validator for Polygon, contributing to the security, governance, and decentralization of the platform. As a validator, Deutsche Telekom will run a full node, produce blocks, validate transactions, and participate in the consensus process. This move strengthens the overall integrity and interoperability of the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Dirk R&ouml;der, Head of the Blockchain Solutions Center at Deutsche Telekom, views the collaboration with Polygon as a significant milestone for the company's aspiration to become a key player in Web3 infrastructure. Deutsche Telekom aims to serve institutional clients as a reliable enterprise-grade staking provider and leverage the existing infrastructure to monetize the native token of the underlying blockchain network. This strategic move allows Deutsche Telekom to tap into the growing potential of blockchain technology and establish a foothold in the evolving digital economy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The involvement of mainstream telecommunications companies like Deutsche Telekom in the Web3 space can contribute to the greater decentralization of proof-of-stake blockchains. R&ouml;der emphasizes the importance of having a diverse and reliable validator set in a decentralized ecosystem. Other telecommunications companies are also exploring opportunities in this domain, fostering a more robust network infrastructure for blockchain platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Michael Blank, CEO of Polygon Labs, believes that collaborations between blockchain projects and mainstream businesses like Deutsche Telekom can pave the way for wider adoption of blockchain technology across various industries. The partnership not only strengthens Polygon's network security and governance but also showcases the practical applications of blockchain beyond cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon's blockchain ecosystem offers a suite of protocols for developers to access major scaling solutions, including zero-knowledge rollups, sidechains, app-specific chains, and data availability protocols. As a validator, Deutsche Telekom MMS will contribute to the security and decentralization of Polygon's proof-of-stake sidechain and Supernets app-chains. Currently, Polygon's PoS chain hosts numerous decentralized applications, processing millions of daily transactions and locking over $1.2 billion in Total Value Locked.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Deutsche Telekom's participation as a validator on Polygon demonstrates the increasing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology by established companies in the telecommunications industry. This collaboration strengthens Polygon's network infrastructure while bridging the gap between traditional businesses and the blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership between Deutsche Telekom and Polygon highlights the continued growth and integration of blockchain technology into mainstream operations. Such collaborations between traditional industry firms and blockchain companies advance the possibilities for transformative applications and advancements in the digital landscape, merging new horizons to expand the use case and adoption of blockchain technologies beyond crypto.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Germany's Deutsche Telekom has joined Polygon as a validator, signaling its support for the Ethereum layer-2 scaling protocol and expanding its involvement in the blockchain technology space. Deutsche Telekom aims to explore new revenue streams and enhance network security through its participation as a validator.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The company's subsidiary, Deutsche Telekom MMS, will operate as a validator for Polygon, contributing to the security, governance, and decentralization of the platform. As a validator, Deutsche Telekom will run a full node, produce blocks, validate transactions, and participate in the consensus process. This move strengthens the overall integrity and interoperability of the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Dirk R&ouml;der, Head of the Blockchain Solutions Center at Deutsche Telekom, views the collaboration with Polygon as a significant milestone for the company's aspiration to become a key player in Web3 infrastructure. Deutsche Telekom aims to serve institutional clients as a reliable enterprise-grade staking provider and leverage the existing infrastructure to monetize the native token of the underlying blockchain network. This strategic move allows Deutsche Telekom to tap into the growing potential of blockchain technology and establish a foothold in the evolving digital economy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The involvement of mainstream telecommunications companies like Deutsche Telekom in the Web3 space can contribute to the greater decentralization of proof-of-stake blockchains. R&ouml;der emphasizes the importance of having a diverse and reliable validator set in a decentralized ecosystem. Other telecommunications companies are also exploring opportunities in this domain, fostering a more robust network infrastructure for blockchain platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Michael Blank, CEO of Polygon Labs, believes that collaborations between blockchain projects and mainstream businesses like Deutsche Telekom can pave the way for wider adoption of blockchain technology across various industries. The partnership not only strengthens Polygon's network security and governance but also showcases the practical applications of blockchain beyond cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon's blockchain ecosystem offers a suite of protocols for developers to access major scaling solutions, including zero-knowledge rollups, sidechains, app-specific chains, and data availability protocols. As a validator, Deutsche Telekom MMS will contribute to the security and decentralization of Polygon's proof-of-stake sidechain and Supernets app-chains. Currently, Polygon's PoS chain hosts numerous decentralized applications, processing millions of daily transactions and locking over $1.2 billion in Total Value Locked.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Deutsche Telekom's participation as a validator on Polygon demonstrates the increasing recognition of the potential of blockchain technology by established companies in the telecommunications industry. This collaboration strengthens Polygon's network infrastructure while bridging the gap between traditional businesses and the blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership between Deutsche Telekom and Polygon highlights the continued growth and integration of blockchain technology into mainstream operations. Such collaborations between traditional industry firms and blockchain companies advance the possibilities for transformative applications and advancements in the digital landscape, merging new horizons to expand the use case and adoption of blockchain technologies beyond crypto.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sparklo (SPRK) Becomes the Most Sought-After Token as Uniswap (UNI) And Stellar (XLM) See Varying Price Trends]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sparklo-sprk-becomes-the-most-sought-after-token-as-uniswap-uni-and-stellar-xlm-see-varying-price-trends</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-627.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-627.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-627.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/sparklo-sprk-becomes-the-most-sought-after-token-as-uniswap-uni-and-stellar-xlm-see-varying-price-trends</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a market filled with thousands of tokens, Sparklo prides itself as one of the most sought-after tokens at the moment, with more investors looking to capitalize on the project's high potential.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it has been a day of varying price actions for tokens like Uniswap (UNI) and Stellar (XLM) as both look to scale past their support level.&nbsp;</p>
<p>More investors join the Sparklo (SPRK) project as the ongoing token presale gains more ground</p>
<p>The Sparklo project has caught the eye of investors as more numbers join the project amid an imminent positive price trajectory. Sparklo is an innovative investment opportunity on the blockchain which allows investors to invest in valuable solid treasures like Silver, Gold and Platinum. These timeless treasures can be traded using fractionalized NFTs that act as digital placeholders.</p>
<p>The SPRK token is looking to replicate the growth of Bitcoin as crypto experts suggest an over 2,000% growth in the price value of the SPRK token before the end of the year. Investors will get the SPRK token at the price of only $0.030 per token currently. Early investors will also get a 50% bonus offer which lasts until the 2nd of June 2023. This means you have unlimited time to join the project and benefit from this opportunity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is worth noting that Sparklo has passed its audit with Interfi Network. The BlockAudit Report Team has also approved the project's KYC. To prevent a rug pull and ensure the safety of investors' assets, the liquidity of the SPRK token will be locked for 100 years. This is the time to invest in this project that has the potential to become the next blue-chip crypto. As such, we recommend you join this opportunity now. You can click the link to invest.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKEN HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) sees a slight price slump</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) is a decentralized protocol that facilitates the automation of crypto trading while also solving liquidity issues on its network. Within the last 24 hours, Uniswap's (UNI) price has been stagnant, with the coin losing only&nbsp; 0.53% of its value. As a result, Uniswap (UNI) is currently trading at the price of $5.03. The trading volume of Uniswap (UNI) took a deep dive as it lost 23.32% in trading volume and is currently at $29,377,114.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has shown stability in recent days, with the Uniswap (UNI) coin gaining 2% in the last 48 hours. Uniswap (UNI) is one of the few promising tokens in the crypto market at the moment. However, Uniswap (UNI) coin holders have joined the ongoing Sparklo presale, which crypto experts project will offer a better return on investment. Crypto experts already predict that the Sparklo token will rise exponentially in the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) shines as it witnesses a significant price rally</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized network that works on a peer-to-peer basis to connect financial systems with individuals in need of it for swift payment transactions. Stellar (XLM) is gearing up to become the base layer for the thrilling-dollar stablecoin market which will see it provide fast and secure payments in real time. This development was made known in a published article on the Stellar (XLM) official website, which also highlighted fundamental ideas that should be considered when backing a fiat-backed stablecoin.</p>
<p>&nbsp;Stellar (XLM) has seen a 2.06% price increase in the last 24 hours. This has raised the price of Stellar (XLM) to $0.092 currently.&nbsp; However, the trading volume of Stellar (XLM) declined to 16.12% within the last 24 hours. The last 48 hours' price chart of Stellar (XLM) is also bullish. While Stellar (XLM) investors hope that the coin continues its bullish price movement, some have joined the ongoing Sparklo presale to make gains. Sparklo is presently offering a 50% bonus on token purchases which will end in a few hours. Investors are joining to benefit from it.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Sparklo presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a market filled with thousands of tokens, Sparklo prides itself as one of the most sought-after tokens at the moment, with more investors looking to capitalize on the project's high potential.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Meanwhile, it has been a day of varying price actions for tokens like Uniswap (UNI) and Stellar (XLM) as both look to scale past their support level.&nbsp;</p>
<p>More investors join the Sparklo (SPRK) project as the ongoing token presale gains more ground</p>
<p>The Sparklo project has caught the eye of investors as more numbers join the project amid an imminent positive price trajectory. Sparklo is an innovative investment opportunity on the blockchain which allows investors to invest in valuable solid treasures like Silver, Gold and Platinum. These timeless treasures can be traded using fractionalized NFTs that act as digital placeholders.</p>
<p>The SPRK token is looking to replicate the growth of Bitcoin as crypto experts suggest an over 2,000% growth in the price value of the SPRK token before the end of the year. Investors will get the SPRK token at the price of only $0.030 per token currently. Early investors will also get a 50% bonus offer which lasts until the 2nd of June 2023. This means you have unlimited time to join the project and benefit from this opportunity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is worth noting that Sparklo has passed its audit with Interfi Network. The BlockAudit Report Team has also approved the project's KYC. To prevent a rug pull and ensure the safety of investors' assets, the liquidity of the SPRK token will be locked for 100 years. This is the time to invest in this project that has the potential to become the next blue-chip crypto. As such, we recommend you join this opportunity now. You can click the link to invest.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKEN HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) sees a slight price slump</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) is a decentralized protocol that facilitates the automation of crypto trading while also solving liquidity issues on its network. Within the last 24 hours, Uniswap's (UNI) price has been stagnant, with the coin losing only&nbsp; 0.53% of its value. As a result, Uniswap (UNI) is currently trading at the price of $5.03. The trading volume of Uniswap (UNI) took a deep dive as it lost 23.32% in trading volume and is currently at $29,377,114.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap (UNI) has shown stability in recent days, with the Uniswap (UNI) coin gaining 2% in the last 48 hours. Uniswap (UNI) is one of the few promising tokens in the crypto market at the moment. However, Uniswap (UNI) coin holders have joined the ongoing Sparklo presale, which crypto experts project will offer a better return on investment. Crypto experts already predict that the Sparklo token will rise exponentially in the year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) shines as it witnesses a significant price rally</p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) is a decentralized network that works on a peer-to-peer basis to connect financial systems with individuals in need of it for swift payment transactions. Stellar (XLM) is gearing up to become the base layer for the thrilling-dollar stablecoin market which will see it provide fast and secure payments in real time. This development was made known in a published article on the Stellar (XLM) official website, which also highlighted fundamental ideas that should be considered when backing a fiat-backed stablecoin.</p>
<p>&nbsp;Stellar (XLM) has seen a 2.06% price increase in the last 24 hours. This has raised the price of Stellar (XLM) to $0.092 currently.&nbsp; However, the trading volume of Stellar (XLM) declined to 16.12% within the last 24 hours. The last 48 hours' price chart of Stellar (XLM) is also bullish. While Stellar (XLM) investors hope that the coin continues its bullish price movement, some have joined the ongoing Sparklo presale to make gains. Sparklo is presently offering a 50% bonus on token purchases which will end in a few hours. Investors are joining to benefit from it.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Sparklo presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKX Proposes Industry-First BRC-30 Token Standard to Enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 Token Staking]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Discover_the_Power_of_BRC_30_Learn_Now__1200x628_n_168562839915xuMuCflZ.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Discover_the_Power_of_BRC_30_Learn_Now__1200x628_n_168562839915xuMuCflZ.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Discover_the_Power_of_BRC_30_Learn_Now__1200x628_n_168562839915xuMuCflZ.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 21:12:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/okx-proposes-industry-first-brc-30-token-standard-to-enable-bitcoin-and-brc-20-token-staking</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>SAN FRANCISCO, UNITED STATES, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><ul><li>With BRC-30, OKX Wallet users will soon be able to stake BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin to earn passive income on their digital assets</li></ul><p>OKX, a leading Web3 company, today introduced its proposal for a new, open-source BRC-30 protocol that enables staking of BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin in order to earn BRC-30 tokens. The protocol is open-source and available for all developers to build upon.</p><p>OKX Wallet will add support for the BRC-30 standard according to the protocol, enabling users to earn passive income by staking BRC-20 tokens or Bitcoin on Web3 Earn without actively trading. This complements the existing range of curated DeFi earning products already available through the platform.</p><p>The introduction of BRC-30 and its staking functionalities is driven by OKX's goal to provide users with additional opportunities to participate in the Bitcoin ecosystem and earn passive income.</p>OKX Chief Innovation Officer Jason Lau said: "We're thrilled to have proposed and pioneered the BRC-30 standard to enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 token staking. With the OKX Wallet soon to incorporate BRC-30 support, users will be able to access Bitcoin staking and earn opportunities across multiple-chains. With the Bitcoin ecosystem seeing an explosion of new development, we're proud to work with developers and projects across the community to contribute to the growth of the wider ecosystem."<p>OKX is a longstanding supporter of Bitcoin, having integrated the Lightning Network to its centralized exchange over two years ago. OKX Wallet is also the first multi-chain wallet to support BRC-20 trading with the launch of its Ordinals Marketplace, as well as the viewing and transfer of Bitcoin Ordinals.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace, DEX and Web3 Earn.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX believes in challenging the status quo. The company recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>Disclaimer</p><p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION. THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS. OKX IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH ANY PARTICULAR DEFI PROTOCOL, MAKES NO WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR UNDERTAKINGS RELATING TO ANY DEFI PROTOCOL&rsquo;S OFFERINGS, AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS OR OTHER DAMAGE ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. OKX WALLET IS AN AGGREGATOR; ALL DISPLAYED ESTIMATED RETURN RATES ARE PROVIDED BY THE DEFI PROTOCOL, AND ARE NOT GUARANTEED NOR INDICATIVE OF FUTURE RETURNS. PLEASE CONDUCT YOUR OWN DUE DILIGENCE BEFORE INVESTING IN ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>ContactOKXmedia@okx.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SAN FRANCISCO, UNITED STATES, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><ul><li>With BRC-30, OKX Wallet users will soon be able to stake BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin to earn passive income on their digital assets</li></ul><p>OKX, a leading Web3 company, today introduced its proposal for a new, open-source BRC-30 protocol that enables staking of BRC-20 tokens and Bitcoin in order to earn BRC-30 tokens. The protocol is open-source and available for all developers to build upon.</p><p>OKX Wallet will add support for the BRC-30 standard according to the protocol, enabling users to earn passive income by staking BRC-20 tokens or Bitcoin on Web3 Earn without actively trading. This complements the existing range of curated DeFi earning products already available through the platform.</p><p>The introduction of BRC-30 and its staking functionalities is driven by OKX's goal to provide users with additional opportunities to participate in the Bitcoin ecosystem and earn passive income.</p>OKX Chief Innovation Officer Jason Lau said: "We're thrilled to have proposed and pioneered the BRC-30 standard to enable Bitcoin and BRC-20 token staking. With the OKX Wallet soon to incorporate BRC-30 support, users will be able to access Bitcoin staking and earn opportunities across multiple-chains. With the Bitcoin ecosystem seeing an explosion of new development, we're proud to work with developers and projects across the community to contribute to the growth of the wider ecosystem."<p>OKX is a longstanding supporter of Bitcoin, having integrated the Lightning Network to its centralized exchange over two years ago. OKX Wallet is also the first multi-chain wallet to support BRC-20 trading with the launch of its Ordinals Marketplace, as well as the viewing and transfer of Bitcoin Ordinals.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>A leading global technology company driving the future of Web3, OKX provides a comprehensive suite of products to meet the needs of beginners and experts alike, including the OKX Wallet, NFT Marketplace, DEX and Web3 Earn.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world's top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>As a leader building innovative technology products, OKX believes in challenging the status quo. The company recently launched a global brand campaign entitled, The System Needs a Rewrite, which advocates for a new paradigm led by Web3 self-managed technology to replace existing centralized systems.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>Disclaimer</p><p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION. THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS. OKX IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH ANY PARTICULAR DEFI PROTOCOL, MAKES NO WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR UNDERTAKINGS RELATING TO ANY DEFI PROTOCOL&rsquo;S OFFERINGS, AND IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS OR OTHER DAMAGE ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. OKX WALLET IS AN AGGREGATOR; ALL DISPLAYED ESTIMATED RETURN RATES ARE PROVIDED BY THE DEFI PROTOCOL, AND ARE NOT GUARANTEED NOR INDICATIVE OF FUTURE RETURNS. PLEASE CONDUCT YOUR OWN DUE DILIGENCE BEFORE INVESTING IN ANY DEFI PROTOCOL. PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>ContactOKXmedia@okx.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto.com Secures Major Payment Institution License from MAS]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cryptocom-secures-major-payment-institution-license-from-mas</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cro-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cro-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cro-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 20:05:21 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cryptocom-secures-major-payment-institution-license-from-mas</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Crypto.com announced it had been granted a Major Payment Institution license (MPI) for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services from Singapore&rsquo;s MAS. </p>
<p>On Thursday, Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com announced that it received its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We're excited to share our latest regulatory achievement in one of the world's leading crypto hubs, #Singapore https://t.co/vCNztATSCO has been granted the Major Payment Institution Licence by The Monetary Authority of Singapore @MAS_sg Learn more:https://t.co/4PwkuGgsnr pic.twitter.com/AklwjP2Z4C</p>
&mdash; Crypto.com (@cryptocom) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a press release, company CEO Kris Marszalek said:</p>

<p>The Monetary Authority of&nbsp;Singapore&nbsp;is recognized globally as a regulator that ensures responsible innovation of the digital assets sector. We are proud to receive the licence from a regulator that prioritizes consumer protection, safety, and security.</p>
<p>We look forward to continuing to collaborate with MAS and leading at the forefront of&nbsp;crypto&nbsp;in our home market of&nbsp;Singapore.</p>

<p>The announcement comes a year after the exchange received in-principle approval from MAS in June 2022. Securing this license means Crypto.com can continue offering its DPT service to Singaporean customers.</p>
Crypto.com Bags Another Regulatory Greenlight
<p>The regulatory approval from Singapore&rsquo;s MAS adds to the exchanges list of regulatory permission. Crypto.com received a Payment Institution License from Brazil&rsquo;s central bank in December. In its announcement, the exchange also detailed its global regulatory status:</p>

<p>In recent months, Crypto.com has received in-principle approval of its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), regulatory approval as a Digital Asset Service Provider by the Autorit&eacute; des march&eacute;s financiers (AMF) in France, registration approval as a cryptoasset business from the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), provisional approval of its Virtual Asset License from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA), Electronic Financial Transaction Act and Virtual Asset Service Provider registration in South Korea, a pre-registration undertaking with the Ontario Securities Administration in Canada, among others.</p>

Crypto.com Forced to Cut Staff Following FTX Collapse
<p>The collapse of the crypto exchange FTX caused widespread industry turmoil, and Crypto.com was not immune.</p>
<p>In January, the exchange announced that it would cut its staff by 20% due to the &ldquo;significant damage&rdquo; caused by FTX. The company further cited economic difficulties spurred by the overall market downturn as the reason for its decision.</p>
<p>Kris Marszalek said at the time:</p>

<p>We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Crypto.com announced it had been granted a Major Payment Institution license (MPI) for Digital Payment Token (DPT) services from Singapore&rsquo;s MAS. </p>
<p>On Thursday, Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com announced that it received its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS).</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We're excited to share our latest regulatory achievement in one of the world's leading crypto hubs, #Singapore https://t.co/vCNztATSCO has been granted the Major Payment Institution Licence by The Monetary Authority of Singapore @MAS_sg Learn more:https://t.co/4PwkuGgsnr pic.twitter.com/AklwjP2Z4C</p>
&mdash; Crypto.com (@cryptocom) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a press release, company CEO Kris Marszalek said:</p>

<p>The Monetary Authority of&nbsp;Singapore&nbsp;is recognized globally as a regulator that ensures responsible innovation of the digital assets sector. We are proud to receive the licence from a regulator that prioritizes consumer protection, safety, and security.</p>
<p>We look forward to continuing to collaborate with MAS and leading at the forefront of&nbsp;crypto&nbsp;in our home market of&nbsp;Singapore.</p>

<p>The announcement comes a year after the exchange received in-principle approval from MAS in June 2022. Securing this license means Crypto.com can continue offering its DPT service to Singaporean customers.</p>
Crypto.com Bags Another Regulatory Greenlight
<p>The regulatory approval from Singapore&rsquo;s MAS adds to the exchanges list of regulatory permission. Crypto.com received a Payment Institution License from Brazil&rsquo;s central bank in December. In its announcement, the exchange also detailed its global regulatory status:</p>

<p>In recent months, Crypto.com has received in-principle approval of its Major Payment Institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS), regulatory approval as a Digital Asset Service Provider by the Autorit&eacute; des march&eacute;s financiers (AMF) in France, registration approval as a cryptoasset business from the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), provisional approval of its Virtual Asset License from the Dubai Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA), Electronic Financial Transaction Act and Virtual Asset Service Provider registration in South Korea, a pre-registration undertaking with the Ontario Securities Administration in Canada, among others.</p>

Crypto.com Forced to Cut Staff Following FTX Collapse
<p>The collapse of the crypto exchange FTX caused widespread industry turmoil, and Crypto.com was not immune.</p>
<p>In January, the exchange announced that it would cut its staff by 20% due to the &ldquo;significant damage&rdquo; caused by FTX. The company further cited economic difficulties spurred by the overall market downturn as the reason for its decision.</p>
<p>Kris Marszalek said at the time:</p>

<p>We grew ambitiously at the start of 2022, building on our incredible momentum and aligning with the trajectory of the broader industry. That trajectory changed rapidly with a confluence of negative economic developments.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[IoTeX DAO votes in proposal to share gas fees with dApps and bolster its ecosystem]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/iotex-dao-votes-in-proposal-to-share-gas-fees-with-dapps-and-bolster-its-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-01-182631.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-01-182631.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-06-01-182631.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/iotex-dao-votes-in-proposal-to-share-gas-fees-with-dapps-and-bolster-its-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the rapidly evolving Web3 space, the success of any blockchain platform hinges on the creativity and ingenuity of its dApp creators. Recognizing developers' pivotal role in driving adoption, the IoTeX community has voted massively in favor of IoTeX's Improvement Proposal 15 (IIP-15) for Sharing of Gas-Fee with dApps (SGD).</p>
<p>With its groundbreaking IIP-15, IoTeX aims to unlock a new era of high-level innovation, engagement, and sustainable growth. By sharing a portion of transaction gas fees with dApp developers, IoTeX sets the stage for an ecosystem where creativity thrives, users are captivated, and developers are incentivized like never before.</p>
<p>The IoTeX community has passed the groundbreaking IIP-15 with 98.5% in favor, and 1.5% against the proposal. A total of 224 wallets participated with nearly 157.4 million IOTX staked. The IoTeX Foundation will distribute 224 Soulbound Tokens (SBTs) to reward those who participated in the IIP-15 DAO governance vote.</p>
<p>Becoming the DePIN leader</p>

<p>&ldquo;The significance of IIP-15 cannot be overstated,&rdquo; said IoTeX CEO and Co-Founder Raullen Chai. &ldquo;For IoTeX, it represents another step toward becoming the leader within the burgeoning Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) space. It also represents a paradigm shift in how blockchain platforms value and compensate their development community.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;By proposing the revenue-sharing mechanism through SGD, IoTeX opens the doors for community members to actively participate in shaping the platform's future and fostering a vibrant ecosystem,&rdquo; Chai said.</p>

<p>Striking a fair balance</p>
<p>As users interact with dApps on the IoTeX blockchain, a portion of the transaction gas fees is automatically accrued in the SGD treasury. The proposal recommends that 30% of the gas fees be reallocated to the SGD treasury to strike a fair balance and incentivize sustainable growth. At the same time, the remaining portion continues to contribute to the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) rewarding pool. The actual ratio may be subject to adjustment through governance voting.</p>
<p>DApp owners can withdraw their accumulated revenue by initiating a claim action. The SGD treasury verifies the eligibility criteria, including transaction volume and time deployed on the chain, through the SGD registry.</p>
<p>Once the criteria are met, the treasury issues the corresponding rewards. To maintain the integrity and quality of the ecosystem, the IoTeX Foundation implements a review process, approving dApps based on their performance and adherence to guidelines.</p>
<p>Transparency and efficiency</p>
<p>The SGD initiative comprises two main components to ensure transparency and efficient management: the SGD Treasury and the SGD Registry. The treasury module handles gas fee distribution, accounting, and the SGD rewards claims process.</p>
<p>The registry consists of a system contract and an indexer. dApp owners utilize the system contract to register their dApp contracts and reward addresses, while the indexer keeps track of SGD contract addresses, owners, and the number of contract calls.</p>
<p>Implementing this fee-sharing model requires careful consideration to prevent potential abuses. To address this concern, the IoTeX Foundation has set eligibility criteria to qualify for revenue sharing.</p>
<p>DApps must have completed at least 100,000 IoTeX Layer 1 blockchain transactions, have been deployed and running smoothly for at least one month, and receive approval from the IoTeX Foundation.</p>
<p>The Foundation reserves the right to disapprove dApps involved in spam transactions or illegitimate activities, thereby safeguarding the integrity of the SGD program and protecting users' interests.</p>
<p>Driving innovation</p>
<p>Implementing the SGD feature will be part of an upcoming hard fork, ensuring backward compatibility with existing applications and infrastructure. With this forward-thinking proposal, IoTeX joins a growing movement for blockchain platforms to actively reward their dApp creators, driving a virtuous cycle of innovation, user engagement, and overall ecosystem growth.</p>
<p>As IoTeX continues to expand its reach and influence, IIP-15 solidifies its position as a trailblazer in blockchain technology. Through this revenue-sharing model, IoTeX sets the stage for a new dApp development era that rewards creativity, nurtures innovation, and fosters a new and exciting design space for Web3 applications.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the rapidly evolving Web3 space, the success of any blockchain platform hinges on the creativity and ingenuity of its dApp creators. Recognizing developers' pivotal role in driving adoption, the IoTeX community has voted massively in favor of IoTeX's Improvement Proposal 15 (IIP-15) for Sharing of Gas-Fee with dApps (SGD).</p>
<p>With its groundbreaking IIP-15, IoTeX aims to unlock a new era of high-level innovation, engagement, and sustainable growth. By sharing a portion of transaction gas fees with dApp developers, IoTeX sets the stage for an ecosystem where creativity thrives, users are captivated, and developers are incentivized like never before.</p>
<p>The IoTeX community has passed the groundbreaking IIP-15 with 98.5% in favor, and 1.5% against the proposal. A total of 224 wallets participated with nearly 157.4 million IOTX staked. The IoTeX Foundation will distribute 224 Soulbound Tokens (SBTs) to reward those who participated in the IIP-15 DAO governance vote.</p>
<p>Becoming the DePIN leader</p>

<p>&ldquo;The significance of IIP-15 cannot be overstated,&rdquo; said IoTeX CEO and Co-Founder Raullen Chai. &ldquo;For IoTeX, it represents another step toward becoming the leader within the burgeoning Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) space. It also represents a paradigm shift in how blockchain platforms value and compensate their development community.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;By proposing the revenue-sharing mechanism through SGD, IoTeX opens the doors for community members to actively participate in shaping the platform's future and fostering a vibrant ecosystem,&rdquo; Chai said.</p>

<p>Striking a fair balance</p>
<p>As users interact with dApps on the IoTeX blockchain, a portion of the transaction gas fees is automatically accrued in the SGD treasury. The proposal recommends that 30% of the gas fees be reallocated to the SGD treasury to strike a fair balance and incentivize sustainable growth. At the same time, the remaining portion continues to contribute to the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) rewarding pool. The actual ratio may be subject to adjustment through governance voting.</p>
<p>DApp owners can withdraw their accumulated revenue by initiating a claim action. The SGD treasury verifies the eligibility criteria, including transaction volume and time deployed on the chain, through the SGD registry.</p>
<p>Once the criteria are met, the treasury issues the corresponding rewards. To maintain the integrity and quality of the ecosystem, the IoTeX Foundation implements a review process, approving dApps based on their performance and adherence to guidelines.</p>
<p>Transparency and efficiency</p>
<p>The SGD initiative comprises two main components to ensure transparency and efficient management: the SGD Treasury and the SGD Registry. The treasury module handles gas fee distribution, accounting, and the SGD rewards claims process.</p>
<p>The registry consists of a system contract and an indexer. dApp owners utilize the system contract to register their dApp contracts and reward addresses, while the indexer keeps track of SGD contract addresses, owners, and the number of contract calls.</p>
<p>Implementing this fee-sharing model requires careful consideration to prevent potential abuses. To address this concern, the IoTeX Foundation has set eligibility criteria to qualify for revenue sharing.</p>
<p>DApps must have completed at least 100,000 IoTeX Layer 1 blockchain transactions, have been deployed and running smoothly for at least one month, and receive approval from the IoTeX Foundation.</p>
<p>The Foundation reserves the right to disapprove dApps involved in spam transactions or illegitimate activities, thereby safeguarding the integrity of the SGD program and protecting users' interests.</p>
<p>Driving innovation</p>
<p>Implementing the SGD feature will be part of an upcoming hard fork, ensuring backward compatibility with existing applications and infrastructure. With this forward-thinking proposal, IoTeX joins a growing movement for blockchain platforms to actively reward their dApp creators, driving a virtuous cycle of innovation, user engagement, and overall ecosystem growth.</p>
<p>As IoTeX continues to expand its reach and influence, IIP-15 solidifies its position as a trailblazer in blockchain technology. Through this revenue-sharing model, IoTeX sets the stage for a new dApp development era that rewards creativity, nurtures innovation, and fosters a new and exciting design space for Web3 applications.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Avalanche reaches 1 Million Monthly Active Users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/avalanche-reaches-1-million-monthly-active-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ava-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ava-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ava-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:11:25 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/avalanche-reaches-1-million-monthly-active-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In an impressive milestone for the Avalanche (AVAX) ecosystem, the platform has successfully surpassed the coveted one million monthly active users (MAUs) mark.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Avalanche's achievement not only solidifies its position as a major player in the rapidly evolving crypto landscape but also signifies the growing popularity and adoption of its innovative blockchain technology.</p>
Avalanche's Meteoric Rise
<p>Since its arrival on the scene, Avalanche has revolutionised the blockchain industry by addressing the scalability and speed limitations that have plagued other platforms. With a strong emphasis on decentralisation, scaling, and incredibly fast finality, Avalanche has managed to capture the attention of users and developers alike.</p>
Scalability
<p>One of the primary factors propelling Avalanche's success is its ability to handle a massive number of transactions per second (TPS). By utilising a unique consensus protocol called Avalanche Consensus, the platform achieves impressive TPS rates, ensuring smooth and efficient operation even during peak network activity.</p>
Interoperability&nbsp;
<p>Avalanche's interoperability capabilities have played a vital role in its growth. The platform enables seamless communication and asset transfers between different blockchains, unlocking cross-chain liquidity and expanding its potential use cases. This flexibility has garnered significant interest from developers and users looking for a comprehensive blockchain solution.</p>
User-Friendly&nbsp;
<p>Avalanche has prioritised user experience, making it accessible and intuitive for both crypto veterans and newcomers. The platform's user-friendly interfaces, robust development tools, and extensive documentation have lowered entry barriers, attracting a diverse user base and driving widespread adoption. However, a big issue still to be solved is the high cost of becoming a validator. Until this cost is lowered dramatically, smaller projects are being priced out.&nbsp;</p>
The Path Ahead
<p>With Avalanche crossing the one million MAU milestone, the platform's trajectory looks promising. Avalanche continues to foster innovation through ongoing partnerships, collaborations, and development initiatives. If the platform can resolve its issues of high costs if will climb to the next million users in a far shorter time scale.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an impressive milestone for the Avalanche (AVAX) ecosystem, the platform has successfully surpassed the coveted one million monthly active users (MAUs) mark.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Avalanche's achievement not only solidifies its position as a major player in the rapidly evolving crypto landscape but also signifies the growing popularity and adoption of its innovative blockchain technology.</p>
Avalanche's Meteoric Rise
<p>Since its arrival on the scene, Avalanche has revolutionised the blockchain industry by addressing the scalability and speed limitations that have plagued other platforms. With a strong emphasis on decentralisation, scaling, and incredibly fast finality, Avalanche has managed to capture the attention of users and developers alike.</p>
Scalability
<p>One of the primary factors propelling Avalanche's success is its ability to handle a massive number of transactions per second (TPS). By utilising a unique consensus protocol called Avalanche Consensus, the platform achieves impressive TPS rates, ensuring smooth and efficient operation even during peak network activity.</p>
Interoperability&nbsp;
<p>Avalanche's interoperability capabilities have played a vital role in its growth. The platform enables seamless communication and asset transfers between different blockchains, unlocking cross-chain liquidity and expanding its potential use cases. This flexibility has garnered significant interest from developers and users looking for a comprehensive blockchain solution.</p>
User-Friendly&nbsp;
<p>Avalanche has prioritised user experience, making it accessible and intuitive for both crypto veterans and newcomers. The platform's user-friendly interfaces, robust development tools, and extensive documentation have lowered entry barriers, attracting a diverse user base and driving widespread adoption. However, a big issue still to be solved is the high cost of becoming a validator. Until this cost is lowered dramatically, smaller projects are being priced out.&nbsp;</p>
The Path Ahead
<p>With Avalanche crossing the one million MAU milestone, the platform's trajectory looks promising. Avalanche continues to foster innovation through ongoing partnerships, collaborations, and development initiatives. If the platform can resolve its issues of high costs if will climb to the next million users in a far shorter time scale.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Is Reportedly Conducting Large Scale Layoffs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binance-is-reportedly-conducting-large-scale-layoffs</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-usd-suspension-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-usd-suspension-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-usd-suspension-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:57:43 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/binance-is-reportedly-conducting-large-scale-layoffs</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Reports emerged on Wednesday that crypto exchange Binance is undertaking sizable layoffs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Wednesday, a report by independent journalist Colin Wu claimed Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, may have cut its staff by as much as 20%.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">SCOOP: According to multiple sources who confirmed to WuBlockchain, Binance has started layoffs, and the proportion is still uncertain. The total number of Binance employees is about 8,000, market rumors that the proportion of layoffs in June was about 20%. As of press time,&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Patrick Hillmann, Binance&rsquo;s Chief Communication Officer, clarified the matter via a Twitter thread.</p>
<p>Hillmann said the exchange is not cutting 20% of its employees as a cost-cutting measure but said it would &ldquo;streamline&rdquo; after experiencing exponential growth over the past five years.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Let me provide some additional clarity via . Binance is not cutting 20% of employees as a cost-cutting measure. @binance experienced true exponential growth these past 5 years &mdash; and grew its staff accordingly. This was a historic operational challenge to overcome. https://t.co/Awmh8PdT8j</p>
&mdash; Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The exchange has faced unprecedented regulatory action in recent months and has seen a decline in market share, The Block reports. However, the company said in March that it is not planning layoffs but would grow its headcount even further. Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao, said at the time it planned to expand its staff by between 15% and 30%.</p>
Binance CEO Clarifies
<p>In response to the report, Zhao took to Twitter to explain the situation. The company&rsquo;s CEO wrote Wu&rsquo;s claims off as FUD, saying the exchange has a &ldquo;bottom out&rdquo; program where it continually greets employees it deems &ldquo;not strong fits with the company.&rdquo; Zhao further noted that many of these are &ldquo;great people or high performers, but may not fit our unique culture/situation.&rdquo; &nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. Another day, another FUD. On rumors of layoffs.Binance has a "bottom out" (we should probably rename it to something else) program. We constantly say goodbye to people who are not strong fits with the company. Many of them are great people or high performers, but may not fit&hellip; https://t.co/YGnZILzd5C</p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Zhao reiterated that the company is still appointing new employees.</p>
Binance Creates Japanese Trading Platform
<p>Despite a declining market share, the exchange does not appear to be slowing operations. Most recently, Binance announced the launch of a fully compliant crypto trading platform for Japanese residents.</p>
<p>As part of the transition to Binance Japan, the company said it would discontinue its crypto services for Japanese residents through its global platform by November 30. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Reports emerged on Wednesday that crypto exchange Binance is undertaking sizable layoffs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Wednesday, a report by independent journalist Colin Wu claimed Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, may have cut its staff by as much as 20%.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">SCOOP: According to multiple sources who confirmed to WuBlockchain, Binance has started layoffs, and the proportion is still uncertain. The total number of Binance employees is about 8,000, market rumors that the proportion of layoffs in June was about 20%. As of press time,&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Patrick Hillmann, Binance&rsquo;s Chief Communication Officer, clarified the matter via a Twitter thread.</p>
<p>Hillmann said the exchange is not cutting 20% of its employees as a cost-cutting measure but said it would &ldquo;streamline&rdquo; after experiencing exponential growth over the past five years.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Let me provide some additional clarity via . Binance is not cutting 20% of employees as a cost-cutting measure. @binance experienced true exponential growth these past 5 years &mdash; and grew its staff accordingly. This was a historic operational challenge to overcome. https://t.co/Awmh8PdT8j</p>
&mdash; Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>The exchange has faced unprecedented regulatory action in recent months and has seen a decline in market share, The Block reports. However, the company said in March that it is not planning layoffs but would grow its headcount even further. Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao, said at the time it planned to expand its staff by between 15% and 30%.</p>
Binance CEO Clarifies
<p>In response to the report, Zhao took to Twitter to explain the situation. The company&rsquo;s CEO wrote Wu&rsquo;s claims off as FUD, saying the exchange has a &ldquo;bottom out&rdquo; program where it continually greets employees it deems &ldquo;not strong fits with the company.&rdquo; Zhao further noted that many of these are &ldquo;great people or high performers, but may not fit our unique culture/situation.&rdquo; &nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. Another day, another FUD. On rumors of layoffs.Binance has a "bottom out" (we should probably rename it to something else) program. We constantly say goodbye to people who are not strong fits with the company. Many of them are great people or high performers, but may not fit&hellip; https://t.co/YGnZILzd5C</p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) May 31, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Zhao reiterated that the company is still appointing new employees.</p>
Binance Creates Japanese Trading Platform
<p>Despite a declining market share, the exchange does not appear to be slowing operations. Most recently, Binance announced the launch of a fully compliant crypto trading platform for Japanese residents.</p>
<p>As part of the transition to Binance Japan, the company said it would discontinue its crypto services for Japanese residents through its global platform by November 30. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Devour & Alterverse Partner to Bring the World's First Web3 Food Ordering Marketplace to the Metaverse]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/devour-alterverse-partner-to-bring-the-worlds-first-web3-food-ordering-marketplace-to-the-metaverse</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/DevourGO_in_Sky_City_1685562348d4O0CbJDeI.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/DevourGO_in_Sky_City_1685562348d4O0CbJDeI.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/DevourGO_in_Sky_City_1685562348d4O0CbJDeI.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:57:26 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/devour-alterverse-partner-to-bring-the-worlds-first-web3-food-ordering-marketplace-to-the-metaverse</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Phoenix, AZ, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Devour, a pioneering restaurant engagement technology company, is thrilled to announce its strategic partnership with AlterVerse, an innovative force in the gaming industry. The collaboration aims to revolutionize the restaurant and gaming experience by expanding DevourGO, Devour's web3 enabled guest engagement platform, to the upcoming release of AlterVerse's Sky City gaming Metaverse.</p><p>DevourGO has emerged as a prominent player in token-gating food ordering experiences. It is gaining swift recognition for its innovative approach, which allows users to unlock these experiences by utilizing their digital assets and the native token, DevourPAY ($DPAY), for payments and exclusive rewards on the platform. With this new partnership, DevourGO will extend its offering to include real world food delivery orders coming from storefronts within AlterVerse&rsquo;s stunning photorealistic metaverse, Sky City. The integration with AlterVerse will allow DevourGO to unlock a whole new level of immersive restaurant experiences for customers and restaurant brands.</p><p>The visionary AlterVerse team, backed by notable entities such as Binance Labs, Polygon Ventures, and Gate.io Labs, is actively building a vibrant global community of gaming enthusiasts. With Sky City, built on Unreal Engine 5, AlterVerse offers an extensive range of experiences that go beyond traditional gaming. Users can play countless games and challenges, design their own homes, engage in high stakes competition, and shop at many restaurants and retail shops in the central hub. The metaverse is blockchain-driven allowing users to create, own and sell in-game creations in support of its fun-first gaming mantra.</p><p>As part of this partnership, Devour will integrate its DevourGO order platform into Sky City, enabling users to seamlessly order food and beverages from participating restaurants within the virtual realm. As the partnership evolves,&nbsp;players will not only receive real world food, but their avatars will gain valuable increases in their hunger and thirst meters, which players need to maintain in order to progress in the game. Because the Alterverse community is Global, players will be able to seamlessly order from restaurants local to their physical location.</p><p>"We are thrilled to partner with Alterverse and expand the reach of DevourGO to the exciting world of AlterVerse's Sky City metaverse," said Shelly Rupel, CEO at Devour. "This collaboration represents a significant step forward in enhancing guest engagement for restaurant brands. By combining the immersive experiences of Alterverse with the convenience and efficiency of DevourGO, we are enabling restaurant guests to seamlessly order, dine, and engage in an entirely new way.&rdquo; </p><p>As the release of AlterVerse's Sky City approaches, Devour and AlterVerse will work closely to ensure a seamless integration of DevourGO with the metaverse. Restaurant brands will have the opportunity to leverage the combined power of Devour's technology and AlterVerse's immersive gaming environment to create unforgettable guest experiences and maximize their reach in the gaming community.</p><p>About Devour</p><p>Devour Inc is a next-gen restaurant engagement technology company dedicated to transforming the way restaurants connect with their guests. Their DevourGO platform utilizes web3 technology to provide community-focused delivery and pick-up ordering services for restaurant brands of all sizes, with on-premise ordering, reservations, and more digital guest engagement solutions coming soon. Included in the Devour ecosystem is DevourPAY $DPAY (https://devour.io/devourpay), the native utility token of the platform, and The Industry Pass (https://devour.io/theindustry), offering exclusive perks and benefits to its community members.&nbsp;</p><p>More information can be found at https://devour.io</p><p>About AlterVerse</p><p>AlterVerse is a pioneering force in the gaming industry, creating a four-phase metaverse intricately built on Unreal Engine 5. Their upcoming Sky City gaming metaverse offers users the ability to play mini-games and adventures, fly a &lsquo;Copter over the shrouded planet, race a Violator around the Sky City track, and monetize their in-game creations within an expansive, interconnected ecosystem. The metaverse is powered by blockchain technology, VR compatible, and provides players with opportunities for both immersive gameplay and financial reward.</p><p>More information can be found at https://www.alterverse.com</p><p>Disclaimer: This press release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>ContactCEOShelly RupelDevour Incshelly@devour.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Phoenix, AZ, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Devour, a pioneering restaurant engagement technology company, is thrilled to announce its strategic partnership with AlterVerse, an innovative force in the gaming industry. The collaboration aims to revolutionize the restaurant and gaming experience by expanding DevourGO, Devour's web3 enabled guest engagement platform, to the upcoming release of AlterVerse's Sky City gaming Metaverse.</p><p>DevourGO has emerged as a prominent player in token-gating food ordering experiences. It is gaining swift recognition for its innovative approach, which allows users to unlock these experiences by utilizing their digital assets and the native token, DevourPAY ($DPAY), for payments and exclusive rewards on the platform. With this new partnership, DevourGO will extend its offering to include real world food delivery orders coming from storefronts within AlterVerse&rsquo;s stunning photorealistic metaverse, Sky City. The integration with AlterVerse will allow DevourGO to unlock a whole new level of immersive restaurant experiences for customers and restaurant brands.</p><p>The visionary AlterVerse team, backed by notable entities such as Binance Labs, Polygon Ventures, and Gate.io Labs, is actively building a vibrant global community of gaming enthusiasts. With Sky City, built on Unreal Engine 5, AlterVerse offers an extensive range of experiences that go beyond traditional gaming. Users can play countless games and challenges, design their own homes, engage in high stakes competition, and shop at many restaurants and retail shops in the central hub. The metaverse is blockchain-driven allowing users to create, own and sell in-game creations in support of its fun-first gaming mantra.</p><p>As part of this partnership, Devour will integrate its DevourGO order platform into Sky City, enabling users to seamlessly order food and beverages from participating restaurants within the virtual realm. As the partnership evolves,&nbsp;players will not only receive real world food, but their avatars will gain valuable increases in their hunger and thirst meters, which players need to maintain in order to progress in the game. Because the Alterverse community is Global, players will be able to seamlessly order from restaurants local to their physical location.</p><p>"We are thrilled to partner with Alterverse and expand the reach of DevourGO to the exciting world of AlterVerse's Sky City metaverse," said Shelly Rupel, CEO at Devour. "This collaboration represents a significant step forward in enhancing guest engagement for restaurant brands. By combining the immersive experiences of Alterverse with the convenience and efficiency of DevourGO, we are enabling restaurant guests to seamlessly order, dine, and engage in an entirely new way.&rdquo; </p><p>As the release of AlterVerse's Sky City approaches, Devour and AlterVerse will work closely to ensure a seamless integration of DevourGO with the metaverse. Restaurant brands will have the opportunity to leverage the combined power of Devour's technology and AlterVerse's immersive gaming environment to create unforgettable guest experiences and maximize their reach in the gaming community.</p><p>About Devour</p><p>Devour Inc is a next-gen restaurant engagement technology company dedicated to transforming the way restaurants connect with their guests. Their DevourGO platform utilizes web3 technology to provide community-focused delivery and pick-up ordering services for restaurant brands of all sizes, with on-premise ordering, reservations, and more digital guest engagement solutions coming soon. Included in the Devour ecosystem is DevourPAY $DPAY (https://devour.io/devourpay), the native utility token of the platform, and The Industry Pass (https://devour.io/theindustry), offering exclusive perks and benefits to its community members.&nbsp;</p><p>More information can be found at https://devour.io</p><p>About AlterVerse</p><p>AlterVerse is a pioneering force in the gaming industry, creating a four-phase metaverse intricately built on Unreal Engine 5. Their upcoming Sky City gaming metaverse offers users the ability to play mini-games and adventures, fly a &lsquo;Copter over the shrouded planet, race a Violator around the Sky City track, and monetize their in-game creations within an expansive, interconnected ecosystem. The metaverse is powered by blockchain technology, VR compatible, and provides players with opportunities for both immersive gameplay and financial reward.</p><p>More information can be found at https://www.alterverse.com</p><p>Disclaimer: This press release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>ContactCEOShelly RupelDevour Incshelly@devour.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  7.1% Weaker in May - 2 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-seven-point-one-per-cent-weaker-in-may-2-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-1-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-seven-point-one-per-cent-weaker-in-may-2-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Off 7.1% in May:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent weakness early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 27000 figure following an acute move lower from the 27360.31 area that was reversed around the 26615 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 26744.31 area, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that intensified around the 27875 area.&nbsp; Large Stops were recently elected below the 27477.07 area during the depreciation, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25864.35 to 28473.93.&nbsp; Downside price objectives linked to the 28057.23 and 27875 levels include the 26526, 26335, and 25675 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 26422 level.&nbsp; BTC/USD depreciated approximately 7.1% in May and has appreciated approximately 64.5% year-to-date.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27011.61 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26988.19.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Off 7.1% in May:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 2 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended recent weakness early in the Asian session as the pair traded below the 27000 figure following an acute move lower from the 27360.31 area that was reversed around the 26615 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 26744.31 area, a downside price objective associated with selling pressure that intensified around the 27875 area.&nbsp; Large Stops were recently elected below the 27477.07 area during the depreciation, representing the 38.2% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25864.35 to 28473.93.&nbsp; Downside price objectives linked to the 28057.23 and 27875 levels include the 26526, 26335, and 25675 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 26422 level.&nbsp; BTC/USD depreciated approximately 7.1% in May and has appreciated approximately 64.5% year-to-date.</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27011.61 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26988.19.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Google Bard Shiba Inu prediction Tradecurve price increased by 25%]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/google-bard-shiba-inu-prediction-tradecurve-price-increased-by-25</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-162815.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-162815.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-162815.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/google-bard-shiba-inu-prediction-tradecurve-price-increased-by-25</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The AI tool built by Google, known as Bard, has made waves across the Web3 space as a lot of users are using it for price prediction. One of the most notable altcoins to get a significant level of attention due to the bullish outlook of Google Bard is Shiba Inu, and today, we will explore why it thinks that the crypto has high-growth potential.</p>
<p class="s5">The presale-stage project Tradecurve has increased by 25% in the past week, and it has its own AI system as well that can change the way investors make decisions when trading.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s8">Google Bard Makes Prediction Surrounding Shiba Inu&rsquo;s Future Value</p>
<p class="s5">Google Bard was consulted to get the price predictions for the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency, as users on a global scale are using AI to check the future value of their favorite cryptocurrencies. Note that the price predictions that are made by the Google Bard AI might not always be 100% accurate or correct. However, they will provide much-needed insights into the potential future direction a cryptocurrency's value might be headed to. When Shiba Inu was released in 2020, it was dubbed the "Dogecoin Killer" and experienced a massive 1,500% increase after it was released. This excessive increase resulted in the crypto community speculating on the different scenarios, and one of them predicted that SHIB could climb to $1.</p>
<p class="s5">However, according to Google Bard, $1 is highly unlikely at this point. Bard's projection for the future of Shiba Inu is still optimistic, however. As of May 29, 2023, Shiba Inu trades at $0.00000883. Bard predicts that the maximum value for the cryptocurrency in 2023 is at $0.0000259, an increase of 193.32%. Aside from Shiba Inu, one other cryptocurrency caught the attention of crypto traders as well, and that project is Tradecurve.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s8">Tradecurve Already Sees an Increase of 25% And Can Spike By 100x At Launch</p>
<p class="s5">Tradecurve has transitioned from Stage 2 of its presale, where one TCRV token was worth $0.012, to Stage 3, where its price increased by 25%, and now trades at $0.015. Analysts and investors are eyeing the Tradecurve platform as it also implements AI to make trades, users can access hundreds of algorithmic and AI-driven trading systems and create AI-oriented bots to optimize the performance of their portfolio.</p>
<p class="s5">This hybrid platform requires no KYC, features Proof of Reserves (PoR), and allows anyone to make trades just by depositing crypto and then using it as collateral when trading other cryptocurrencies or any other derivative.</p>
<p class="s5">According to the Tradecurve whitepaper, the platform will feature high leverage beginning at 500:1, a VIP account service, zero requirements for FIAT payments, exclusive deposit bonuses, a dedicated Trading academy, and negative balance protection.</p>
<p class="s5">The team estimates that they will make $20 million during the presale and that they can onboard 100,000 new users at launch. TCRV will also get listed on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and as a result, Google Bard predicts that TCRV can climb 100x by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV utility token at the links below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">The AI tool built by Google, known as Bard, has made waves across the Web3 space as a lot of users are using it for price prediction. One of the most notable altcoins to get a significant level of attention due to the bullish outlook of Google Bard is Shiba Inu, and today, we will explore why it thinks that the crypto has high-growth potential.</p>
<p class="s5">The presale-stage project Tradecurve has increased by 25% in the past week, and it has its own AI system as well that can change the way investors make decisions when trading.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s8">Google Bard Makes Prediction Surrounding Shiba Inu&rsquo;s Future Value</p>
<p class="s5">Google Bard was consulted to get the price predictions for the Shiba Inu cryptocurrency, as users on a global scale are using AI to check the future value of their favorite cryptocurrencies. Note that the price predictions that are made by the Google Bard AI might not always be 100% accurate or correct. However, they will provide much-needed insights into the potential future direction a cryptocurrency's value might be headed to. When Shiba Inu was released in 2020, it was dubbed the "Dogecoin Killer" and experienced a massive 1,500% increase after it was released. This excessive increase resulted in the crypto community speculating on the different scenarios, and one of them predicted that SHIB could climb to $1.</p>
<p class="s5">However, according to Google Bard, $1 is highly unlikely at this point. Bard's projection for the future of Shiba Inu is still optimistic, however. As of May 29, 2023, Shiba Inu trades at $0.00000883. Bard predicts that the maximum value for the cryptocurrency in 2023 is at $0.0000259, an increase of 193.32%. Aside from Shiba Inu, one other cryptocurrency caught the attention of crypto traders as well, and that project is Tradecurve.</p>
<p></p>
<p class="s8">Tradecurve Already Sees an Increase of 25% And Can Spike By 100x At Launch</p>
<p class="s5">Tradecurve has transitioned from Stage 2 of its presale, where one TCRV token was worth $0.012, to Stage 3, where its price increased by 25%, and now trades at $0.015. Analysts and investors are eyeing the Tradecurve platform as it also implements AI to make trades, users can access hundreds of algorithmic and AI-driven trading systems and create AI-oriented bots to optimize the performance of their portfolio.</p>
<p class="s5">This hybrid platform requires no KYC, features Proof of Reserves (PoR), and allows anyone to make trades just by depositing crypto and then using it as collateral when trading other cryptocurrencies or any other derivative.</p>
<p class="s5">According to the Tradecurve whitepaper, the platform will feature high leverage beginning at 500:1, a VIP account service, zero requirements for FIAT payments, exclusive deposit bonuses, a dedicated Trading academy, and negative balance protection.</p>
<p class="s5">The team estimates that they will make $20 million during the presale and that they can onboard 100,000 new users at launch. TCRV will also get listed on Tier-1 exchanges and on Uniswap, and as a result, Google Bard predicts that TCRV can climb 100x by the end of 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Learn more about Tradecurve and the TCRV utility token at the links below:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uphold Launches New Uphold Institutional OTC Trading and Research Services]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uphold-launches-new-uphold-institutional-otc-trading-and-research-services</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-150043.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-150043.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-01-at-150043.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/uphold-launches-new-uphold-institutional-otc-trading-and-research-services</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Valley Conference, Rotkreuz, Switzerland, June 1, 2023&nbsp; - Uphold, the Web3 financial platform, today announced a new offering for all classes of institutional investors trading digital assets. This is the first solution to provide institutional grade research, optimal OTC execution, superior product breadth - offering more than 280 assets - and settlement in multiple currencies.</p>
<p>The OTC Platform: Branded Uphold Ascent, the customizable OTC trading platform is designed for optimal execution, handling large orders with minimal price impact and competitive&nbsp; pricing.</p>
<ul>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Superior Liquidity: with connection to 29 trading venues, Ascent allows traders to smart route orders to centralized exchanges, decentralized exchanges and Layer 2 networks.</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Expansive Digital Asset Coverage: Uphold has set a high bar in the industry for depth of product, offering more than 280 tokens, including access to many assets unavailable on other OTC platforms</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Trading Expertise: our team is comprised of CeFi, DeFi and high-frequency trading experts</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Fully Customizable trading tools and order management interface</li>
</ul>

<p>&ldquo;Whether institutional investors are trading digital assets now, or looking to get into the space, our new Ascent OTC platform and in-depth research will provide them access to comprehensive and extensive insights and the deepest liquidity pool in digital asset management through which to execute trades,&rdquo; said Simon McLoughlin, Chief Executive Officer of Uphold.</p>

<p>Token Discovery: Uphold Intelligence, digital asset research, has proven to identify meaningful assets early. With Dr. Martin Hiesbock, Head of Research at Uphold Institutional, clients gain direct access to first-hand knowledge of what is happening and about to happen in the market.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sort through the assets with just flash from those that have fundamental value for our clients,&rdquo; said Scott Kaplan, Chief Executive Officer of Uphold Securities. &ldquo;We identify important digital assets early based on sound methodology intended to spot fundamental long term value.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Uphold</p>
<p>Ranked #1 in the San Francisco Business Times Fast 100 List, Uphold is committed to making Web3 easy. As a Web3 financial platform, Uphold serves over 10 million customers in more than 180 countries. It provides businesses and consumers with easy access to financial technology and services. Uphold&rsquo;s patented &ldquo;Anything to Anything&rdquo; platform gives end users seamless access to and between digital assets and national currencies and precious metals. To learn more about Uphold&rsquo;s products and services visit uphold.com.</p>
<ul>
<li>Certain currencies and assets are not available in all jurisdictions ###</li>
</ul>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto Valley Conference, Rotkreuz, Switzerland, June 1, 2023&nbsp; - Uphold, the Web3 financial platform, today announced a new offering for all classes of institutional investors trading digital assets. This is the first solution to provide institutional grade research, optimal OTC execution, superior product breadth - offering more than 280 assets - and settlement in multiple currencies.</p>
<p>The OTC Platform: Branded Uphold Ascent, the customizable OTC trading platform is designed for optimal execution, handling large orders with minimal price impact and competitive&nbsp; pricing.</p>
<ul>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Superior Liquidity: with connection to 29 trading venues, Ascent allows traders to smart route orders to centralized exchanges, decentralized exchanges and Layer 2 networks.</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Expansive Digital Asset Coverage: Uphold has set a high bar in the industry for depth of product, offering more than 280 tokens, including access to many assets unavailable on other OTC platforms</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Trading Expertise: our team is comprised of CeFi, DeFi and high-frequency trading experts</li>
<li> &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; Fully Customizable trading tools and order management interface</li>
</ul>

<p>&ldquo;Whether institutional investors are trading digital assets now, or looking to get into the space, our new Ascent OTC platform and in-depth research will provide them access to comprehensive and extensive insights and the deepest liquidity pool in digital asset management through which to execute trades,&rdquo; said Simon McLoughlin, Chief Executive Officer of Uphold.</p>

<p>Token Discovery: Uphold Intelligence, digital asset research, has proven to identify meaningful assets early. With Dr. Martin Hiesbock, Head of Research at Uphold Institutional, clients gain direct access to first-hand knowledge of what is happening and about to happen in the market.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sort through the assets with just flash from those that have fundamental value for our clients,&rdquo; said Scott Kaplan, Chief Executive Officer of Uphold Securities. &ldquo;We identify important digital assets early based on sound methodology intended to spot fundamental long term value.&rdquo;</p>

<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>About Uphold</p>
<p>Ranked #1 in the San Francisco Business Times Fast 100 List, Uphold is committed to making Web3 easy. As a Web3 financial platform, Uphold serves over 10 million customers in more than 180 countries. It provides businesses and consumers with easy access to financial technology and services. Uphold&rsquo;s patented &ldquo;Anything to Anything&rdquo; platform gives end users seamless access to and between digital assets and national currencies and precious metals. To learn more about Uphold&rsquo;s products and services visit uphold.com.</p>
<ul>
<li>Certain currencies and assets are not available in all jurisdictions ###</li>
</ul>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p></p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[First Digital Rolls Out FDUSD Amid HK Crypto Regulation]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/first-digital-rolls-out-fusd-amid-hk-crypto-regulation</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-kong-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/first-digital-rolls-out-fusd-amid-hk-crypto-regulation</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong-based First Digital Group has announced the introduction of a new stablecoin that will be pegged to the United States Dollar but regulated in Asia.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes shortly after Hong Kong announced the introduction of a new regulatory framework for digital assets in its jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
The First Digital USD
<p>The new stablecoin christened the &ldquo;First Digital USD&rdquo; or FDUSD, is intended to be backed on a 1:1 basis with the USD or an asset of equivalent fair value. First Digital also added that the reserves backing the stablecoin would be held in segregated accounts at different institutions in Asia. This is to prevent the co-mingling of assets. The FDUSD stablecoin will be backed by &ldquo;high-quality reserves&rdquo; and issued by the First Digital Trust, a trust company registered under Hong Kong&rsquo;s Trust ordinance. The stablecoin has been issued on BNB and Ethereum, with the company in discussions with major exchanges for a listing. First Digital, in its statement, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;First Digital Labs will work closely with local and overseas regulatory authorities to ensure full compliance with current and future applicable laws and regulations, and First Digital Labs will participate in the shaping of their evolution, including the shaping of any regulatory regimes that FDUSD and/or First Digital may fall under in the foreseeable future. Stablecoins provide increased stability, a form of remittance, a hedge against central bank policymakers who seek to influence their domestic currencies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The CEO of First Digital, Vincent Chok, stated that the launch represented a major stride forward in providing an efficient and secure digital currency integrated into transactions.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The launch of this stablecoin represents a major stride forward in our mission to provide a secure and efficient digital currency that can be seamlessly integrated into everyday transactions.&rdquo;</p>

Hong Kong Enacts Guidelines&nbsp;
<p>The announcement comes at a time when Hong Kong&rsquo;s &ldquo;Guidelines for Virtual Asset Trading Platform Operators&rdquo; that are becoming effective on the 1st of June 2023. The new rules define clear standards for the safe custody of assets, avoidance of conflict of interest, segregation of client assets, and cybersecurity standards that are expected from licensed trading platforms.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Providing clear regulatory expectations is the key to fostering responsible development. Hong Kong&rsquo;s comprehensive virtual assets regulatory framework follows the principle of &lsquo;same business, same risks, same rules&rsquo; and aims to provide robust investor protection and manage key risks. This will enable the industry to develop sustainably and support innovation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) will also provide additional guidance on the new regulatory requirements and other implementation details, such as license application procedures and information about transitional arrangements. Regulators in Hong Kong have stated that stablecoins should not be allowed for trading by investors until the proposed rules for the asset class are implemented in its jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
Regulatory Uncertainty In The US Continues&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, regulatory uncertainty in the United States is continuing and has pushed major players to warn regulators that it could lose its position as a leader in the sector. The warning comes as many firms in the country are weighing their options and looking to shift to friendlier jurisdictions. According to Brian Armstrong, Coinbase CEO, with the regulatory uncertainty in the US, it was not surprising that Hong Kong was positioning itself as a crypto hub.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong-based First Digital Group has announced the introduction of a new stablecoin that will be pegged to the United States Dollar but regulated in Asia.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes shortly after Hong Kong announced the introduction of a new regulatory framework for digital assets in its jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
The First Digital USD
<p>The new stablecoin christened the &ldquo;First Digital USD&rdquo; or FDUSD, is intended to be backed on a 1:1 basis with the USD or an asset of equivalent fair value. First Digital also added that the reserves backing the stablecoin would be held in segregated accounts at different institutions in Asia. This is to prevent the co-mingling of assets. The FDUSD stablecoin will be backed by &ldquo;high-quality reserves&rdquo; and issued by the First Digital Trust, a trust company registered under Hong Kong&rsquo;s Trust ordinance. The stablecoin has been issued on BNB and Ethereum, with the company in discussions with major exchanges for a listing. First Digital, in its statement, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;First Digital Labs will work closely with local and overseas regulatory authorities to ensure full compliance with current and future applicable laws and regulations, and First Digital Labs will participate in the shaping of their evolution, including the shaping of any regulatory regimes that FDUSD and/or First Digital may fall under in the foreseeable future. Stablecoins provide increased stability, a form of remittance, a hedge against central bank policymakers who seek to influence their domestic currencies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The CEO of First Digital, Vincent Chok, stated that the launch represented a major stride forward in providing an efficient and secure digital currency integrated into transactions.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The launch of this stablecoin represents a major stride forward in our mission to provide a secure and efficient digital currency that can be seamlessly integrated into everyday transactions.&rdquo;</p>

Hong Kong Enacts Guidelines&nbsp;
<p>The announcement comes at a time when Hong Kong&rsquo;s &ldquo;Guidelines for Virtual Asset Trading Platform Operators&rdquo; that are becoming effective on the 1st of June 2023. The new rules define clear standards for the safe custody of assets, avoidance of conflict of interest, segregation of client assets, and cybersecurity standards that are expected from licensed trading platforms.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Providing clear regulatory expectations is the key to fostering responsible development. Hong Kong&rsquo;s comprehensive virtual assets regulatory framework follows the principle of &lsquo;same business, same risks, same rules&rsquo; and aims to provide robust investor protection and manage key risks. This will enable the industry to develop sustainably and support innovation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) will also provide additional guidance on the new regulatory requirements and other implementation details, such as license application procedures and information about transitional arrangements. Regulators in Hong Kong have stated that stablecoins should not be allowed for trading by investors until the proposed rules for the asset class are implemented in its jurisdiction.&nbsp;</p>
Regulatory Uncertainty In The US Continues&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, regulatory uncertainty in the United States is continuing and has pushed major players to warn regulators that it could lose its position as a leader in the sector. The warning comes as many firms in the country are weighing their options and looking to shift to friendlier jurisdictions. According to Brian Armstrong, Coinbase CEO, with the regulatory uncertainty in the US, it was not surprising that Hong Kong was positioning itself as a crypto hub.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Gemini Seeks UAE License]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-exchange-gemini-seeks-uae-license</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gemini-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:53:33 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/crypto-exchange-gemini-seeks-uae-license</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>US-based crypto exchange Gemini announced it seeks a crypto license in the United Arab Emirates, citing &ldquo;hostility and [a] lack of clarity&rdquo; on US regulations. </p>
<p>Gemini, the cryptocurrency exchange owned by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, announced on Wednesday that it will &ldquo;soon&rdquo; start the process of obtaining a crypto service license for customers in the United Arab Emirates (UAE).</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ We&rsquo;re coming to the UAE! We&rsquo;re thrilled to announce that Gemini will soon begin the process of acquiring a crypto license to serve customers based in the United Arab Emirates (UAE). pic.twitter.com/Ycdj9RxMbE</p>
&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a blog post, the exchange said the UAE, as a forward-thinking, global financial hub, is fast establishing itself as a crypto hub. The company said its team has met with stakeholders throughout the region to learn more about local regulatory requirements, further stating that it aims for the &ldquo;adoption of crypto globally across 20 countries.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Gemini said:</p>

<p>By applying for a license, we will be taking another step towards making Gemini a truly global company.</p>

<p>It is not yet clear where Gemini&rsquo;s base operations will be located, but Cointelegraph reports that the exchange has hinted at establishing headquarters in Dubai and Abu Dhabi.</p>
<p>Gemini co-CEOs, the Winklevoss twins, also told media outlet Zaywa that its decision was prompted by &ldquo;hostility and a lack of clarity&rdquo; regarding crypto regulations in the US.</p>
<p>The exchange announced last week that it plans to establish its European operations out of Dublin, Ireland.</p>
UAE Residents Have Bought More Crypto Than US Residents
<p>In Gemini&rsquo;s Global State of Crypto Report for 2022, data revealed more than 35% of those surveyed in the UAE purchased crypto, compared to only 20% in the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4/As part of Gemini&rsquo;s 2022 Global State of Crypto Report, we found that those in the UAE were rapidly acquiring crypto and putting it to use making in-person purchases. We also found high intent to purchase crypto among those who were not yet ownershttps://t.co/EIB1ji2uBP pic.twitter.com/Ay9pfzkJk4</p>
&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Data further revealed that almost 32% of those in the UAE who do not own crypto are likely to purchase some in the next year. Compared to just 19% of global crypto owners, 33% of holders in the UAE said they plan to use crypto to make in-person purchases at brick-and-mortar retailers.</p>
Gemini Launches Offshore Crypto Derivatives Exchange
<p>Gemini has rapidly expanded its offerings by launching Gemini Foundation, an offshore crypto derivatives platform. The platform launched in 30 countries but is not available to US, UK, or European Union users.</p>
<p>Gemini Foundation allows users to begin trading with Bitcoin perpetual contracts denominated in Gemini Dollars (GUSD) and offers 100x leverage.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US-based crypto exchange Gemini announced it seeks a crypto license in the United Arab Emirates, citing &ldquo;hostility and [a] lack of clarity&rdquo; on US regulations. </p>
<p>Gemini, the cryptocurrency exchange owned by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, announced on Wednesday that it will &ldquo;soon&rdquo; start the process of obtaining a crypto service license for customers in the United Arab Emirates (UAE).</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ We&rsquo;re coming to the UAE! We&rsquo;re thrilled to announce that Gemini will soon begin the process of acquiring a crypto license to serve customers based in the United Arab Emirates (UAE). pic.twitter.com/Ycdj9RxMbE</p>
&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a blog post, the exchange said the UAE, as a forward-thinking, global financial hub, is fast establishing itself as a crypto hub. The company said its team has met with stakeholders throughout the region to learn more about local regulatory requirements, further stating that it aims for the &ldquo;adoption of crypto globally across 20 countries.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Gemini said:</p>

<p>By applying for a license, we will be taking another step towards making Gemini a truly global company.</p>

<p>It is not yet clear where Gemini&rsquo;s base operations will be located, but Cointelegraph reports that the exchange has hinted at establishing headquarters in Dubai and Abu Dhabi.</p>
<p>Gemini co-CEOs, the Winklevoss twins, also told media outlet Zaywa that its decision was prompted by &ldquo;hostility and a lack of clarity&rdquo; regarding crypto regulations in the US.</p>
<p>The exchange announced last week that it plans to establish its European operations out of Dublin, Ireland.</p>
UAE Residents Have Bought More Crypto Than US Residents
<p>In Gemini&rsquo;s Global State of Crypto Report for 2022, data revealed more than 35% of those surveyed in the UAE purchased crypto, compared to only 20% in the US.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4/As part of Gemini&rsquo;s 2022 Global State of Crypto Report, we found that those in the UAE were rapidly acquiring crypto and putting it to use making in-person purchases. We also found high intent to purchase crypto among those who were not yet ownershttps://t.co/EIB1ji2uBP pic.twitter.com/Ay9pfzkJk4</p>
&mdash; Gemini (@Gemini) June 1, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Data further revealed that almost 32% of those in the UAE who do not own crypto are likely to purchase some in the next year. Compared to just 19% of global crypto owners, 33% of holders in the UAE said they plan to use crypto to make in-person purchases at brick-and-mortar retailers.</p>
Gemini Launches Offshore Crypto Derivatives Exchange
<p>Gemini has rapidly expanded its offerings by launching Gemini Foundation, an offshore crypto derivatives platform. The platform launched in 30 countries but is not available to US, UK, or European Union users.</p>
<p>Gemini Foundation allows users to begin trading with Bitcoin perpetual contracts denominated in Gemini Dollars (GUSD) and offers 100x leverage.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Labs Invests in Sparkle Ventures to Ignite Innovation in Web3]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-invests-in-sparkle-ventures-to-ignite-innovation-in-web3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1685621381rWklztAwW8.JPEG" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1685621381rWklztAwW8.JPEG" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/1280X1280_1685621381rWklztAwW8.JPEG" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-labs-invests-in-sparkle-ventures-to-ignite-innovation-in-web3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, a leading blockchain venture fund, is pleased to announce an investment in Sparkle Ventures, a prominent fund manager based in Luxembourg. The strategic investment aims to foster innovation and support the growth of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures on a global scale.</p><p>LBank Labs, known for its protocol and exchange-agnostic approach, is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. With $100 million in assets under management (AUM), the venture capitalist arm of global cryptocurrency exchange LBank has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. Besides direct investments, the team aims to build a strong fund network via investing in global top funds to support portfolios from the network in both financial and resource value-add. Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, is also personally LP to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund and Lemniscap, while Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank is LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II and FOF, and IOSG Ventures.&nbsp;</p><p>Sparkle Ventures, acting as the strategic fund manager in conjunction with Animoca Brands, has gained recognition for its investments in cutting-edge technologies, supporting early-stage Web3 infrastructure enablers globally. Among the General Partners of Sparkle Ventures are industry veterans like Sebastien Borget, Co-Founder and COO of The Sandbox, Yat Siu, Founder and Chairman of Animoca Brands, Julien Pageaud, former head of strategic investments and tech lead at Nomura Digital, and Thibaut Chess&eacute;, former head of tech adoption for the Tezos blockchain protocol.</p><p>Notable projects backed by Sparkle Ventures include institutional-grade DeFi SaaS platform Kiln.fi, data analytics software AbsoluteLabs.io, and ZKP systems Polyhedra.network and OAS.gg. Their co-investors include market giants such as Accel, BinanceLabs, Coinbase, Consensys, Matrix Partners, Polychain, and Sequoia.</p><p>By investing in Sparkle Ventures, LBank Labs aims to leverage their combined expertise, networks, and resources to drive innovation in NFT, gaming and metaverse infra to advance the creation of highly scalable businesses and technologies that will shape the future of Web3.</p>"We are thrilled to invest in Sparkle Ventures to support our shared mission to accelerate the growth of transformative technologies in the Web3 space," said Jiayu Gao, Head of FOF investment at LBank Labs. "We believe this investment will empower entrepreneurs and developers to bring their ideas to life, pushing the boundaries of what is possible in the realm of Web3,&rdquo; she added.<p>With $100 million assets under management, LBank Labs brings extensive financial resources and a vast global network to Sparke Ventures. In turn, Sparkle Ventures will reciprocate by contributing significant value to LBank Labs, leveraging their expertise, strategic insights, and innovative approach to fuel mutual growth and success.</p><p>The venture fund also aims to forge its commitment by building a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, designed to enhance the performance and diversification of its portfolios while emphasizing the inherent value of its ecosystem network. Labs&rsquo; presence in seven global regions, including San Francisco, Dubai, and Shanghai, positions them as a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation across borders.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, British Virgin Islands, June 1st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank Labs, a leading blockchain venture fund, is pleased to announce an investment in Sparkle Ventures, a prominent fund manager based in Luxembourg. The strategic investment aims to foster innovation and support the growth of highly-scalable Web3 infrastructures on a global scale.</p><p>LBank Labs, known for its protocol and exchange-agnostic approach, is committed to supporting projects through direct funding, acceleration, incubation, and extensive networking. With $100 million in assets under management (AUM), the venture capitalist arm of global cryptocurrency exchange LBank has a strong track record of nurturing startups and helping them thrive. Besides direct investments, the team aims to build a strong fund network via investing in global top funds to support portfolios from the network in both financial and resource value-add. Czhang Lin, IC board member of Labs, is also personally LP to NGC, Blockchain Founders Fund and Lemniscap, while Eric He, Co-Founder of LBank is LP to SevenX Ventures fund I, II and FOF, and IOSG Ventures.&nbsp;</p><p>Sparkle Ventures, acting as the strategic fund manager in conjunction with Animoca Brands, has gained recognition for its investments in cutting-edge technologies, supporting early-stage Web3 infrastructure enablers globally. Among the General Partners of Sparkle Ventures are industry veterans like Sebastien Borget, Co-Founder and COO of The Sandbox, Yat Siu, Founder and Chairman of Animoca Brands, Julien Pageaud, former head of strategic investments and tech lead at Nomura Digital, and Thibaut Chess&eacute;, former head of tech adoption for the Tezos blockchain protocol.</p><p>Notable projects backed by Sparkle Ventures include institutional-grade DeFi SaaS platform Kiln.fi, data analytics software AbsoluteLabs.io, and ZKP systems Polyhedra.network and OAS.gg. Their co-investors include market giants such as Accel, BinanceLabs, Coinbase, Consensys, Matrix Partners, Polychain, and Sequoia.</p><p>By investing in Sparkle Ventures, LBank Labs aims to leverage their combined expertise, networks, and resources to drive innovation in NFT, gaming and metaverse infra to advance the creation of highly scalable businesses and technologies that will shape the future of Web3.</p>"We are thrilled to invest in Sparkle Ventures to support our shared mission to accelerate the growth of transformative technologies in the Web3 space," said Jiayu Gao, Head of FOF investment at LBank Labs. "We believe this investment will empower entrepreneurs and developers to bring their ideas to life, pushing the boundaries of what is possible in the realm of Web3,&rdquo; she added.<p>With $100 million assets under management, LBank Labs brings extensive financial resources and a vast global network to Sparke Ventures. In turn, Sparkle Ventures will reciprocate by contributing significant value to LBank Labs, leveraging their expertise, strategic insights, and innovative approach to fuel mutual growth and success.</p><p>The venture fund also aims to forge its commitment by building a comprehensive network of Fund of Funds, designed to enhance the performance and diversification of its portfolios while emphasizing the inherent value of its ecosystem network. Labs&rsquo; presence in seven global regions, including San Francisco, Dubai, and Shanghai, positions them as a powerhouse for fostering collaboration and innovation across borders.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[L3 Platform Orbs Introduces dLIMIT To Enhance Trading on DEXs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/l3-platform-orbs-introduces-dlimit-to-enhance-trading-on-dexs</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-248.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-248.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-248.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/l3-platform-orbs-introduces-dlimit-to-enhance-trading-on-dexs</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized blockchain infrastructure Orbs announced the launch of dLIMIT, an innovative decentralized limit order solution for decentralized exchanges (DEXs), this Thursday. The dLIMIT platform is built atop Orbs&rsquo; unique Layer 3 infrastructure, which provides a separate decentralized execution layer between existing Layer 1 and Layer 2 solutions and the application layer.</p>
<p>The new dLIMIT platform joins a chain of new products launched on Orbs to enhance decentralization, privacy, and security. Additionally, the platform will guarantee users an optimal and reliable execution layer for limit orders on decentralized exchanges.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"The Orbs dLIMIT smart contract offers DEX users an unprecedented ability to execute limit orders at optimal prices with fair fees," says Ran Hammer, Vice President of Business Development for Orbs.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Notwithstanding, the novel technology also provides a user interface template, &ldquo;designed for seamless integration and customization by any DEX&rdquo; building an intuitive, user-friendly and informative trading experience, Hammer added.&nbsp;</p>
<p>dLIMIT platform joins novel technologies built on Orbs infrastructure including the decentralized time-weighted average price platform (dTWAP) that provides a decentralized algorithmic TWAP order tool for DEXs. The latest innovation is built on Orbs&rsquo; dTWAP protocol and leverages the latter&rsquo;s price oracles, which have previously been used on several top DEXs such as Quickswap and Spookyswap.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>

<p>"dLIMIT, backed by Orbs' robust network infrastructure and smart contract, offers DEXs an optimal limit order solution that ensures decentralization, redundancy, reliability, and user protection," a spokesperson from the Orbs&rsquo; team adds.</p>

<p>Orbs launched in 2017 intending to offer users a public, open, decentralized blockchain infrastructure powered by a network of permissionless validators (Guardians) using Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus. The Orbs L3 infrastructure is the backbone of the dLIMIT solution.&nbsp; It allows developers to design applications that extend the capabilities of their smart contracts without relying on traditional centralized server solutions.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Guardians on Orbs will validate and approve transactions on dLIMIT. Simply, the Guardians run a tailored function utilizing ORBS-Lambda that acts as the single honest bidder, or "taker", required for the dLIMIT protocol to run optimally. To enhance decentralization, the validators will monitor and validate the transactions on the dLIMIT smart contract and submit an honest bid when an order is open for bids.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will enable traders and users to get minimal transaction and gas fees while the platform finds the DEXs with the best prices. This provides assurance that the limit order set will track spot market prices as closely as possible when being executed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lastly, the statement confirms that the latest innovation from Orbs is gaining &ldquo;significant interest&rdquo; from leading DEXs with multiple integrations in progress</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized blockchain infrastructure Orbs announced the launch of dLIMIT, an innovative decentralized limit order solution for decentralized exchanges (DEXs), this Thursday. The dLIMIT platform is built atop Orbs&rsquo; unique Layer 3 infrastructure, which provides a separate decentralized execution layer between existing Layer 1 and Layer 2 solutions and the application layer.</p>
<p>The new dLIMIT platform joins a chain of new products launched on Orbs to enhance decentralization, privacy, and security. Additionally, the platform will guarantee users an optimal and reliable execution layer for limit orders on decentralized exchanges.&nbsp;</p>

<p>"The Orbs dLIMIT smart contract offers DEX users an unprecedented ability to execute limit orders at optimal prices with fair fees," says Ran Hammer, Vice President of Business Development for Orbs.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Notwithstanding, the novel technology also provides a user interface template, &ldquo;designed for seamless integration and customization by any DEX&rdquo; building an intuitive, user-friendly and informative trading experience, Hammer added.&nbsp;</p>
<p>dLIMIT platform joins novel technologies built on Orbs infrastructure including the decentralized time-weighted average price platform (dTWAP) that provides a decentralized algorithmic TWAP order tool for DEXs. The latest innovation is built on Orbs&rsquo; dTWAP protocol and leverages the latter&rsquo;s price oracles, which have previously been used on several top DEXs such as Quickswap and Spookyswap.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>

<p>"dLIMIT, backed by Orbs' robust network infrastructure and smart contract, offers DEXs an optimal limit order solution that ensures decentralization, redundancy, reliability, and user protection," a spokesperson from the Orbs&rsquo; team adds.</p>

<p>Orbs launched in 2017 intending to offer users a public, open, decentralized blockchain infrastructure powered by a network of permissionless validators (Guardians) using Proof-of-Stake (PoS) consensus. The Orbs L3 infrastructure is the backbone of the dLIMIT solution.&nbsp; It allows developers to design applications that extend the capabilities of their smart contracts without relying on traditional centralized server solutions.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Guardians on Orbs will validate and approve transactions on dLIMIT. Simply, the Guardians run a tailored function utilizing ORBS-Lambda that acts as the single honest bidder, or "taker", required for the dLIMIT protocol to run optimally. To enhance decentralization, the validators will monitor and validate the transactions on the dLIMIT smart contract and submit an honest bid when an order is open for bids.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will enable traders and users to get minimal transaction and gas fees while the platform finds the DEXs with the best prices. This provides assurance that the limit order set will track spot market prices as closely as possible when being executed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Lastly, the statement confirms that the latest innovation from Orbs is gaining &ldquo;significant interest&rdquo; from leading DEXs with multiple integrations in progress</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mass media outlet compares crypto unfavourably with AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/mass-media-outlet-compares-crypto-unfavourably-with-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/media.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/media.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/media.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:57:01 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/mass-media-outlet-compares-crypto-unfavourably-with-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto bashing in the mainstream media continues unabated as Reuters writer bigs up AI at the expense of the crypto sector.</p>
A mainstream media narrative
<p>Mainstream media generally appears to back the narrative that crypto has no intrinsic value, and that it will go to zero much sooner than later. This is the narrative put out by governments, bank leaders, and global traditional financial agencies.</p>
<p>Everyone has their view of crypto, and both sides of the argument have prominent economists and financial experts with widely differing opinions. However, what is not in doubt is that the large mainstream media outlets are gunning for crypto, often with little fundamental sense behind their articles.</p>
<p>For example, an article published today by a Reuters columnist expounds the view that the current &ldquo;AI craze&rdquo; leaves crypto for dead, and states how AI is gathering momentum while crypto is gathering dust.</p>
<p>No one can deny that artificial intelligence (AI) is arguably the biggest technological breakthrough that the human race has ever seen. The potential for this technology is as breathtaking as it is alarming.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto and AI complement each other
<p>However, comparing it with crypto is quite ridiculous. It&rsquo;s like comparing apples and oranges. Both have their place, and the two of them complement each other, as can be seen with crypto projects such as Render, Ocean, SingularityNET, and others that are harnessing the power of AI.</p>
<p>Crypto is either extremely misunderstood, or there are malicious actors involved in trying to drive this anti-crypto narrative out to the masses. Of course, in calling a spade a spade, the vast majority of cryptocurrencies will probably eventually fail and go to zero, but some of these projects are revolutionary, and this space is coming up with financial innovations such as DeFi, NFTs, payments, and many other uses that can change our world for the better.</p>
Bitcoin is an exit from debasing fiat currencies
<p>Bitcoin is the preeminent cryptocurrency, and it serves as a hard money exit out of the failing fiat-based monetary system. Artificial intelligence with properly defined boundaries can complement this people&rsquo;s money and be used to make life easier for all.</p>
<p>Just throwing mud at a technology is never a good idea. Balanced arguments are always needed. Crypto is a technology that seems to threaten governments, banks, and central planners in general.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Being able to have total control has become the raison d&rsquo;&ecirc;tre of governments instead of being a servant of the people. Crypto challenges this misuse of power, and it is to be hoped that AI will not be used to strengthen governmental oppression of freedoms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto bashing in the mainstream media continues unabated as Reuters writer bigs up AI at the expense of the crypto sector.</p>
A mainstream media narrative
<p>Mainstream media generally appears to back the narrative that crypto has no intrinsic value, and that it will go to zero much sooner than later. This is the narrative put out by governments, bank leaders, and global traditional financial agencies.</p>
<p>Everyone has their view of crypto, and both sides of the argument have prominent economists and financial experts with widely differing opinions. However, what is not in doubt is that the large mainstream media outlets are gunning for crypto, often with little fundamental sense behind their articles.</p>
<p>For example, an article published today by a Reuters columnist expounds the view that the current &ldquo;AI craze&rdquo; leaves crypto for dead, and states how AI is gathering momentum while crypto is gathering dust.</p>
<p>No one can deny that artificial intelligence (AI) is arguably the biggest technological breakthrough that the human race has ever seen. The potential for this technology is as breathtaking as it is alarming.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto and AI complement each other
<p>However, comparing it with crypto is quite ridiculous. It&rsquo;s like comparing apples and oranges. Both have their place, and the two of them complement each other, as can be seen with crypto projects such as Render, Ocean, SingularityNET, and others that are harnessing the power of AI.</p>
<p>Crypto is either extremely misunderstood, or there are malicious actors involved in trying to drive this anti-crypto narrative out to the masses. Of course, in calling a spade a spade, the vast majority of cryptocurrencies will probably eventually fail and go to zero, but some of these projects are revolutionary, and this space is coming up with financial innovations such as DeFi, NFTs, payments, and many other uses that can change our world for the better.</p>
Bitcoin is an exit from debasing fiat currencies
<p>Bitcoin is the preeminent cryptocurrency, and it serves as a hard money exit out of the failing fiat-based monetary system. Artificial intelligence with properly defined boundaries can complement this people&rsquo;s money and be used to make life easier for all.</p>
<p>Just throwing mud at a technology is never a good idea. Balanced arguments are always needed. Crypto is a technology that seems to threaten governments, banks, and central planners in general.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Being able to have total control has become the raison d&rsquo;&ecirc;tre of governments instead of being a servant of the people. Crypto challenges this misuse of power, and it is to be hoped that AI will not be used to strengthen governmental oppression of freedoms.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[EU Officially Enacts New Crypto Regulations]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/eu-officially-enacts-new-crypto-regulations</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/eu-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/eu-officially-enacts-new-crypto-regulations</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The European Union (EU) has formally signed new legislation on crypto licensing and money laundering rules into law.&nbsp;</p>
MiCA Signed Into Law
<p>After months of discussions and negotiations, on May 31, 2023, the EU formally signed the landmark Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) into law. The legislation introduces a comprehensive framework for licensing and regulating cryptocurrency businesses operating within the EU member states. The goal is to establish clear guidelines for crypto-related activities and strengthen the integrity of the digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p>It marks the beginning of a new era of crypto regulation and is expected to enhance consumer protection, prevent money laundering, and foster a more transparent and secure crypto market. These developments signal a notable shift in the EU's stance towards digital currencies.</p>
AML Laws Also Enforced
<p>The European Parliament President, Roberta Metsola, and Swedish Rural Affairs Minister, Peter Kullgren, signed the MiCA law into action. They also formally enacted another law on anti-money laundering (AML), which mandates cryptocurrency providers to authenticate their customers' identities when conducting fund transfers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Swedish government, currently holding the EU presidency and overseeing legislative discussions, made the announcement on Twitter. A spokesperson from the parliament verified that the laws mentioned encompass MiCA, the transfer of funds regulations, and two additional regulations unrelated to trade with Ukraine.&nbsp;</p>
EU Regulating Exchanges And Wallets
<p>Crypto exchanges and wallet providers looking to operate across the 27-nation bloc will be able to do so with a license issued under MiCA, which will likely be truly enforced in June after being published in the official EU journal. The MiCA rules also mandate that stablecoin issuers must hold appropriate reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Proposed by the European Commission in 2020, MiCA sparked controversy due to lawmakers considering environmentally focused provisions that could have effectively banned Bitcoin's proof-of-work technology. While the industry largely welcomed these provisions, there is now a growing focus on the next phase of EU crypto regulation. Future laws may include other elements of the industry, like staking, non-fungible tokens, and decentralized finance.</p>
Critics Question &ldquo;Excessive Regulation&rdquo;
<p>The EU's move to regulate cryptocurrencies reflects a growing recognition of the importance of digital assets and their potential impact on the global financial system. Other regulatory bodies like the SEC have already applauded MiCA.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, critics argue that excessive regulations could stifle innovation and drive crypto businesses away from the EU. In addition, concerns have been raised about the potential burden of compliance costs and the impact on smaller crypto startups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Striking the right balance between regulation and innovation will be crucial in order to support the growth of the digital asset industry while addressing legitimate concerns regarding money laundering and consumer protection.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The European Union (EU) has formally signed new legislation on crypto licensing and money laundering rules into law.&nbsp;</p>
MiCA Signed Into Law
<p>After months of discussions and negotiations, on May 31, 2023, the EU formally signed the landmark Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) into law. The legislation introduces a comprehensive framework for licensing and regulating cryptocurrency businesses operating within the EU member states. The goal is to establish clear guidelines for crypto-related activities and strengthen the integrity of the digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p>It marks the beginning of a new era of crypto regulation and is expected to enhance consumer protection, prevent money laundering, and foster a more transparent and secure crypto market. These developments signal a notable shift in the EU's stance towards digital currencies.</p>
AML Laws Also Enforced
<p>The European Parliament President, Roberta Metsola, and Swedish Rural Affairs Minister, Peter Kullgren, signed the MiCA law into action. They also formally enacted another law on anti-money laundering (AML), which mandates cryptocurrency providers to authenticate their customers' identities when conducting fund transfers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Swedish government, currently holding the EU presidency and overseeing legislative discussions, made the announcement on Twitter. A spokesperson from the parliament verified that the laws mentioned encompass MiCA, the transfer of funds regulations, and two additional regulations unrelated to trade with Ukraine.&nbsp;</p>
EU Regulating Exchanges And Wallets
<p>Crypto exchanges and wallet providers looking to operate across the 27-nation bloc will be able to do so with a license issued under MiCA, which will likely be truly enforced in June after being published in the official EU journal. The MiCA rules also mandate that stablecoin issuers must hold appropriate reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Proposed by the European Commission in 2020, MiCA sparked controversy due to lawmakers considering environmentally focused provisions that could have effectively banned Bitcoin's proof-of-work technology. While the industry largely welcomed these provisions, there is now a growing focus on the next phase of EU crypto regulation. Future laws may include other elements of the industry, like staking, non-fungible tokens, and decentralized finance.</p>
Critics Question &ldquo;Excessive Regulation&rdquo;
<p>The EU's move to regulate cryptocurrencies reflects a growing recognition of the importance of digital assets and their potential impact on the global financial system. Other regulatory bodies like the SEC have already applauded MiCA.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, critics argue that excessive regulations could stifle innovation and drive crypto businesses away from the EU. In addition, concerns have been raised about the potential burden of compliance costs and the impact on smaller crypto startups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Striking the right balance between regulation and innovation will be crucial in order to support the growth of the digital asset industry while addressing legitimate concerns regarding money laundering and consumer protection.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
