<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 14:28:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Want to Become an Ethereum Validator? You Have to Wait 45 Days and Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/want-to-become-an-ethereum-validator-you-have-to-wait-45-days-and-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 20:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum 2.0]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253683</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Ethereum validator enter queue has extended to a whopping 45 days. Here's why. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This year, Ethereum&#8217;s network officially transitioned to a Proof-of-Stake consensus algorithm, leaving Proof-of-Work forever behind.</p>
<p>One of the multiple implications <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">The Merge</a> has had on the protocol is that there are no longer Ethereum miners. Validators secure the network now, and the path to becoming one is supposed to be tremendously simplified &#8211; deposit 32 ETH to the staking contract and run the appropriate software.</p>
<p>But it turns out that there&#8217;s quite a queue for validators lined up, and becoming one might take some time.</p>
<h2>45 Days to Become an Ethereum Validator</h2>
<p>You read that right &#8211; if you have ETH to spare and you want to invest in securing the network and earn rewards for this important task, you&#8217;d have to wait&#8230; a lot.</p>
<p>It appears that becoming a validator is something so sought after that the queue keeps on increasing.</p>
<p>Data from <em>WenMerge </em><a href="https://wenmerge.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> that there are 92,536 validators currently waiting to enter the network. This will take approximately 45 days to clean up.</p>
<p>The competition is so high, and it appears that practically nobody wants to exit. The exit queue currently consists of only 4 validators.</p>
<h2>Celsius Enters the Queue</h2>
<p>The embattled cryptocurrency lender is part of the reason why the queue is stretched out.</p>
<p>Throughout the past couple of days, Celsius Network has moved some $600 million worth of ETH into the staking contract and this rate shows no signs of slowing down, according to Arkham Intelligence.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Celsius is making moves to stake all the ETH they currently hold, representing movements totalling almost $1B in on-chain flows.</p>
<p>Over the past 24 hours, they have staked over $600M of ETH, with their rate of deposits showing no sign of slowing. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/8bW3xB15UH" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/8bW3xB15UH</a></p>
<p>— Arkham (@ArkhamIntel) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1664669447880048644?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>At current prices, the above is made up of around 316K ETH added to the validator enter queue.</p>
<p>Recall that back in April, <em>CryptoPotato </em>reported that leading US-based cryptocurrency exchanges &#8211; Coinbase and Gemini &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-and-gemini-join-bid-race-for-celsius-networks-assets-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">joined</a> the bid for the lender&#8217;s assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/want-to-become-an-ethereum-validator-you-have-to-wait-45-days-and-heres-why/" rel="nofollow">Want to Become an Ethereum Validator? You Have to Wait 45 Days and Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Ways Aritficial Intelligence (AI) Will Change Our Lives by 2030: ChatGPT Predicts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/6-ways-aritficial-intelligence-ai-will-change-our-lives-by-2030-chatgpt-predicts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 15:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253694</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are six ways ChatGPT thinks AI can change our lives in the next 7 years. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Artificial intelligence (AI) continues to be a booming topic amongst tech aficionados and beyond.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve had our fair share of articles where we talk to ChatGPT &#8211; arguably the most popular AI-based chatbot &#8211; on various topics. These include:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-which-5-cryptos-will-survive-in-10-years-the-answer-might-surprise-you/" data-wpel-link="internal">Which 5 Cryptocurrencies Will Survive in 10 Years?</a></li>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-after-ai-these-4-emerging-technologies-can-cause-cryptos-next-big-boom/" data-wpel-link="internal">What Are the Next Emerging Technologies to Disrupt Crypto?</a></li>
</ul>
<p>The list goes on. For this one, we decided to have another conversation but this time on a more general topic. We asked ChatGPT: how will AI impact our lives by 2030?</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253696" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg" alt="chatgpt_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/chatgpt_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>6 Ways AI Will Impact Our Lives by 2030</h2>
<p>ChatGPT didn&#8217;t shy away with an answer:</p>
<blockquote><p>AI is expected to have a significant impact on various aspects of our lives by 2030. Here are a few potential ones:</p></blockquote>
<h3>Automation and Job Market</h3>
<p>According to the chatbot, artificial intelligence has the potential to conveniently automate repetitive tasks and augment human capabilities in different industries.</p>
<p>The AI argued that it could lead to some job displacement, but it can also create a lot of new job opportunities in the areas that are related to AI development, human-AI collaboration, and data analysis.</p>
<p>The bit about human-AI collaboration already sounds a bit scary. We recently published a piece on the dangers of artificial intelligence, as seen by one of the most influential specialists in the field &#8211; Geoffrey Hinton. You can <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fears-for-humanity-and-the-dangers-of-artificial-intelligence-according-to-geoffrey-hinton/" data-wpel-link="internal">read it here</a>.</p>
<h3>Healthcare</h3>
<p>Artificial intelligence is capable of improving our lives by fine-tuning diagnostics, personalized medicine, and drug discovery.</p>
<p>ChatGPT says that AI-powered algorithms can analyze medical images, genetic data, and patient records. This could help doctors to make precise diagnoses and craft better treatment plans.</p>
<h3>Transportation</h3>
<p>According to the language model:</p>
<blockquote><p>AI is already being employed in self-driving cars, and by 2030, autnomous vehicles may become more common. This could potentially enhance road safety, reduce traffic congestion, and improve transportation efficiency.</p></blockquote>
<h3>Education</h3>
<p>Education is another field where AI can substantially impact our lives by personalizing learning experiences while also providing intelligent tutoring and automating most administrative tasks.</p>
<p>Virtual tutors that are powered by artificial intelligence and adaptive learning platforms might be able to help students learn at their very own pace and receive personalized support.</p>
<h3>Customer Service</h3>
<p>This is something that&#8217;s already being disrupted by artificial intelligence. Chatbots and virtual assistants powered by the technology are being used by many companies today.</p>
<blockquote><p>By 2030, these AI systems may become even more advanced and capable of handling complex inquiries, offering personalized recommendations, and providing better customer experiences. &#8211; argued ChatGPT.</p></blockquote>
<h3>Smart Homes and Cities</h3>
<p>Artificial intelligence is capable of empowering the development of smart homes and cities.</p>
<p>Interconnected devices and systems could work together to optimize energy consumption, enhance security, and improve the overall quality of life.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s another concept that&#8217;s commonly referred to as the Internet of Things (IoT).</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>All in all, ChatGPT seems to be of the opinion that the development of AI will continue and that the technology will play an increasing role in our future.</p>
<p>And by the pace AI advances today, it&#8217;s hard to see a reason that won&#8217;t hold true. Already people are using ChatGPT and related extensions to boast productivity by handling routine tasks quicker and easier.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/6-ways-aritficial-intelligence-ai-will-change-our-lives-by-2030-chatgpt-predicts/" rel="nofollow">6 Ways Aritficial Intelligence (AI) Will Change Our Lives by 2030: ChatGPT Predicts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Ethereum Miner CoreWeave Inks an AI Deal With Microsoft</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/former-ethereum-miner-coreweave-inks-an-ai-deal-with-microsoft/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253680</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/microsoft_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/microsoft_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Microsoft has repotedly signed a deal with former Ethereum miner - CoreWeave. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry continues to comingle with that of artificial intelligence in what is reported as a new deal between tech heavyweight Microsoft and former Ethereum miner &#8211; CoreWeave.</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/01/microsoft-inks-deal-with-coreweave-to-meet-openai-cloud-demand.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to recent coverage by CNBC, Microsoft has signed a deal with the former Ethereum miner &#8211; CoreWeave.</li>
<li>It&#8217;s worth noting that CoreWeave has spun up its usage of cloud computing infrastructure from Ethereum mining and is currently one of the rapidly developing providers.</li>
<li>It recently attained a valuation of $2 billion.</li>
<li>The financials of the deal with Microsoft haven&#8217;t been disclosed, but according to sources familiar with the matter and cited by CNBC, the tech behemoth has agreed to spend &#8220;potentially billions of dollars over multiple years.&#8221;</li>
<li>At the beginning of 2023, Microsoft also <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-23/microsoft-makes-multibillion-dollar-investment-in-openai" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">invested</a> a whopping $10 billion in OpenAI &#8211; the firm behind the popular AI-based chatbot ChatGPT.</li>
<li>Sam Altman &#8211; the CEO of OpenAI &#8211; in turn, is now spearheading a cryptocurrency project called Worldcoin. He was successful in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/115m-for-worldcoin-secured-chatgpt-openai-ceo-closes-successful-fundraiser/" data-wpel-link="internal">securing</a> funding of $115 million to build the project, which involves high-precision retina scans and is backed by crypto&#8217;s most prominent VCs.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Featured image courtesy of CNET</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ethereum-miner-coreweave-inks-an-ai-deal-with-microsoft/" rel="nofollow">Former Ethereum Miner CoreWeave Inks an AI Deal With Microsoft</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reasons AI Could be Dangerous for Humanity According to Geoffrey Hinton</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fears-for-humanity-and-the-dangers-of-artificial-intelligence-according-to-geoffrey-hinton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253660</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/geoffrey_hinton.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/geoffrey_hinton.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Will AI be a turning point for humanity? Geoffrey Hinton talks about the dangers of artificial intelligence. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry has been widely impacted by the advance in artificial intelligence technology. More specifically, the increasing po polarity of AI-based chatbots like ChatGPT and Google Bard has spawned a subsection of cryptocurrencies themed around that field.</p>
<p>There is a myriad of coins in the market that saw exponential growth because of the soaring interest in AI.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve also tapped ChatGPT on numerous topics, such as:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-if-ethereums-price-can-flip-bitcoin-in-the-next-5-years-heres-the-answer/" data-wpel-link="internal">Will Ethereum Flip Bitcoin in the Next Five Years? </a></li>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-which-5-cryptos-will-survive-in-10-years-the-answer-might-surprise-you/" data-wpel-link="internal">Which 5 Cryptocurrencies Will Survive in 10 Years?</a></li>
<li><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-after-ai-these-4-emerging-technologies-can-cause-cryptos-next-big-boom/" data-wpel-link="internal">What Are the Next Emerging Techs to Disrupt Crypto?</a></li>
</ul>
<p>And while it&#8217;s exciting to chat with an AI on topics that you would normally discuss with your fellow peers, there&#8217;s also another side to it, and Geoffrey Hinton speaks of it loud and clear.</p>
<h2>The Godfather of Artificial Intelligence</h2>
<p>Geoffrey Hinton is a British-Canadian cognitive psychologist and computer scientist who was born in 1947 in Wimbledon, London.</p>
<p>He is most noted for his work on artificial neural networks and is a former employee of Google. He left the company in May 2023 in a big public exit, voicing public concerns about the risks of artificial intelligence (AI) technology.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253666" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253666" style="width: 1120px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253666" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton.jpg" alt="jeff_hinton" width="1120" height="621" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton.jpg 1120w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton-300x166.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton-1024x568.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton-768x426.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/jeff_hinton-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1120px) 100vw, 1120px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253666" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Technology Review via Linda Nylind / Eyevine Via Redux</figcaption></figure>
<p>Hinton is the first winner of the Rumelhart Prize in 2001 and is internationally renowned for his work on artificial neural nets, especially in relation to how they can be designed to learn without the need for a human teacher. He also won the 2018 ACM A.M. Turing Award for conceptual and engineering breakthroughs in the field.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s also commonly referred to as one of the godfathers of AI. And now, he has some concerns.</p>
<h2>We&#8217;ve Discovered the Secret of Immortality, but There&#8217;s a Catch</h2>
<p>In an <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2023/may/05/geoffrey-hinton-godfather-of-ai-fears-for-humanity" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> for <em>The Guardian, </em>Hinton made it clear that he left Google on good terms and that he has no objections to what the company is doing or has done.</p>
<p>In the article, he compares biological intelligence (human brain) to digital intelligence, outlining the inefficiencies faced by people. He says that our brain runs at low power, but our approach is quite inefficient in terms of information transfer. Digital intelligence, on the other hand, is different.</p>
<blockquote><p>You pay an enormous cost in terms of energy, but when one of them learns something, all of them know it, and you can easily store more copies. So the good news is, we&#8217;ve discovered the secret of immortality. The bad news is, it&#8217;s not for us.</p></blockquote>
<p>In essence, Hinton came to the conclusion that humans are building intelligence that has the potential to outthink humanity.</p>
<blockquote><p>I thought it would happen eventually, but we had plenty of time: 30 to 50 years. I don&#8217;t think that anymore. And I don&#8217;t know any examples of more intelligent things being controlled by less intelligent things.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>To make the comparison more comprehensible, the computer scientist pinned us (humans) against frogs while also adding:</p>
<blockquote><p>And it (AI) is going to learn from the web, it&#8217;s going to have read every single book that&#8217;s ever been written on how to manipulate people, and also seen it in practice.&#8221;</p>
<figure id="attachment_253676" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253676" style="width: 1600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253676" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3.jpg" alt="Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3" width="1600" height="900" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3.jpg 1600w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ex-Machina-2015-featured-3-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253676" class="wp-caption-text">Snip from the Movie Ex Machina. Source: Movie House Memories</figcaption></figure></blockquote>
<h2>Fears for Humanity</h2>
<p>Citing a recent report by Hinton, reports <a href="https://mpost.io/jeff-hinton-explores-two-paths-to-intelligence-and-the-dangers-of-ai-in-recent-talk/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">outline</a> the potential dangers of the so-called superintelligence.</p>
<p>The Godfather of AI outlines scenarios where an AI may seek to gain control over numerous aspects of its own environment in pursuit of solving complex problems. These aspects even include human manipulation. The scientist believes that the AI wouldn&#8217;t even need an explicit goal of achieving power or destruction to leverage its ability to mimic human behavior.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not all doom and gloom, though. He believes that there are ways to mitigate catastrophic scenarios, but he&#8217;s also of the <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/geoffrey-hinton-ai-chatgpt-dangers/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">opinion</a> that we&#8217;ve passed the point of no return and stopping AI development is downright impossible, nor that it should be stopped.</p>
<blockquote><p>I think we should continue to develop it because it could do wonderful things. But we should put equal effort into mitigating or preventing the possible bad consequences.</p></blockquote>
<p>How close are we to those bad consequences? Closer than you might think.</p>
<blockquote><p>I&#8217;ve got huge uncertainty at present. It is possible that large language models, having consumed all the documents on the web, won&#8217;t be able to go much further unless they can get access to all our private data as well. I don&#8217;t want to rule things like that out &#8211; I think people who are confident in this situation are crazy.</p>
<p>The right way to think about the odds of a disaster is closer to a simple coin toss than we might like.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Closing Thoughts</h2>
<p>Artificial Intelligence is likely to play an increasing role in our lives. In fact, according to ChatGPT (oh, the irony) itself, some of the fields it will impact in the next 7 years include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Healthcare</li>
<li>Automation</li>
<li>Transportation</li>
<li>Education</li>
<li>Smart Homes</li>
<li>Customer Service</li>
</ul>
<p>Since voicing his concerns, Hinton has come under fire by many that he didn&#8217;t follow some of his colleagues who quit earlier. It&#8217;s easy to come to that conclusion, but it&#8217;s also easy to oversee the complexity of the problem, which touches on multiple technological, philosophical, and ethical principles.</p>
<p>I guess all Hinton is trying to say is that AI&#8217;s impact on humanity, whether it&#8217;d be good or bad, is likely much closer than most of us seem to think.</p>
<p><em>Featured image courtesy of CBC, submitted to them by Geoffrey Hinton. </em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fears-for-humanity-and-the-dangers-of-artificial-intelligence-according-to-geoffrey-hinton/" rel="nofollow">The Reasons AI Could be Dangerous for Humanity According to Geoffrey Hinton</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Warning! Peter Schiff&#8217;s Twitter Account Compromised, Lures to Phishing Site</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/warning-peter-schiffs-twitter-account-compromised-lures-to-phishing-site/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peter Schiff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253667</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/peter_schiff_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/peter_schiff_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Peter Schiff's Twitter has been hijacked, reportedly linking to a phishing website.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Long-term gold proponent and arguably the most popular full-time Bitcoin basher &#8211; Peter Schiff &#8211; has had his Twitter account comrpomised.</p>
<ul>
<li style="list-style-type: none;">
<ul>
<li>According to Blockfence, Peter Schiff&#8217;s Twitter account has been compromised and hijacked.</li>
<li>The perpetrator already published a tweet that leads to a phishing website. It&#8217;s advised not to click or interact with the link.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a0.png" alt="⚠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />Warning<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a0.png" alt="⚠" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://twitter.com/PeterSchiff?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@PeterSchiff</a>&#8216;s twitter got compromised. Scammers are using it to promote a fake <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24GOLD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$GOLD</a> presale. However, note that a presale smart contract is likely not an EOA (Externally Owned Account) as been detected by Blockfence. Confirming this tx would lead to a wallet drain! <a href="https://t.co/Nvzc3xuWFj" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Nvzc3xuWFj</a></p>
<p>— Blockfence (@blockfence_io) <a href="https://twitter.com/blockfence_io/status/1664919019357458434?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>In fact, there are multiple tweets currently present on Schiff&#8217;s tweet, and all users are highly advised not to interact with them.</li>
<li>Blockfence has confirmed that the transactions from that link would lead to a wallet drain.</li>
<li>The security firm explains the details of the attack:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>Scammers are using it to promote a fake gold presale. However, note that the presale smart contract is likely not an EOA (externally Owned Account) as been detected by Blockfence. Confirming this tx would lead to a wallet drain.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/warning-peter-schiffs-twitter-account-compromised-lures-to-phishing-site/" rel="nofollow">Warning! Peter Schiff&#8217;s Twitter Account Compromised, Lures to Phishing Site</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron Explodes 10% Daily, Bitcoin Stable at $27K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tron-explodes-10-daily-bitcoin-stable-at-27k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 08:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253658</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Green_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Green_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aside from TRX, LDO is another notable gainer, having surge to almost $2.3.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has settled at around $27,000 after dipping below that level on a few occasions during the working week.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also quiet today, aside from Tron, which has skyrocketed by double digits.</p>
<h2>BTC Calm at $27K</h2>
<p>Although Monday started on a highly positive note, after the US government&#8217;s debt ceiling deal and BTC skyrocketed to a two-week high at $28,500, the week didn&#8217;t turn out all that well for the asset.</p>
<p>It was rejected there, which brought it back down to $28,000 at first. However, a one-grand price dump followed, which pushed it south to $27,000. The following two days delivered a few more price dips, the second of which took BTC to a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-ldo-and-aptos-apt-soar-by-7-btc-remains-shaky-at-27k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">weekly low</a> of $26,500 on Friday.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, BTC managed to bounce off rather rapidly and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-leads-with-11-gains-bitcoin-struggles-with-27k-injective-inj-explodes-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">reclaimed</a> $27,000 by the end of the day. It has remained relatively still since then and currently sits inches above that line.</p>
<p>As such, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s market capitalization has remained at the same level as yesterday &#8211; just over $525 billion. Its dominance over the alts, though, has taken another minor hit and is down under 46%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253659" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253659" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253659" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-2-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253659" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>TRX Steals the Spotlight</h2>
<p>The altcoins have also calmed on a 24-hour scale, similar to bitcoin. Ethereum went on a trip south of $1,900 during the week but has managed to reclaim that level after a few consecutive minor daily increases.</p>
<p>Ripple and Cardano have jumped by around 1-2% in the past 24 hours, while DOGE, SOL, LTC, and DOT are up by under 1%.</p>
<p>Tron, on the other hand, has taken the spotlight with a massive 10% daily surge. As a result, TRX trades at almost $0.085.</p>
<p>Lido DAO&#8217;s native token has also jumped by an impressive percentage &#8211; 5%. Consequently, LDO has neared $2.3.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has added around $10 billion in a day and is close to $1.150 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253661" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253661" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253661" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="850" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1-1024x463.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1-768x347.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1-1536x695.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-1-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253661" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-explodes-10-daily-bitcoin-stable-at-27k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Tron Explodes 10% Daily, Bitcoin Stable at $27K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Crowns zkPass as Winner of its First Web3 Reality Show &#8216;Build The Block&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-crowns-zkpass-as-winner-of-its-first-web3-reality-show-build-the-block/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253591</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BinanceENS.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BinanceENS.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Winning Binance's Metaverse-based reality show allows zkPass to receive funding from Binance Labs.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, has just concluded its first metaverse reality show dubbed &#8220;Build The Block.&#8221; The show ends with the blockchain project zkPass emerging as the winner, opening the way to several awards from the exchange.</p>
<p><a href="https://zkpass.org/home" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">zkPass</a> is a decentralized privacy-protecting identity protocol that harnesses Multi-party Computation (MPC) and Zero-knowledge Proof (ZKP) technology to enable users to prove their verifiable data in the Web2 and Web3 networks.</p>
<h2>zkPass to Receive Funding From Binance Labs</h2>
<p>According to a press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Binance awarded zkPass as the winner of its show after the protocol&#8217;s founding members received the highest votes throughout the seven-episode competition featuring 12 finalists. The purpose of the metaverse-hosted show is to search for the next big Web3 business tycoon.</p>
<p>Bagging an investment from Binance Labs, zkPass co-founder Joshua Peng said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are not only thrilled to be a part of the first pitch ever done in a real time metaverse series, but especially honored to win Build The Block and have the opportunity to work closer with Binance Labs. This investment helps us immensely on our journey to be the infrastructure of this decentralized world.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Other Projects Get Rewarded</h2>
<p>Aside from zkPass, four other projects that partook in the &#8220;Build The Block&#8221; contest were rewarded with investments from Binance Labs.</p>
<p>The finalist blockchain projects were Mind Network, Kryptoskatt, Bracket Labs, and DappOS. They emerged as the runners-up from a list of over 900 applications received by the show moderators.</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s commitment to fostering the development of emerging blockchain startups is exemplified by its recent initiative, which builds upon its previous <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-introduces-a-500-million-fund-to-focus-on-web3-companies/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of a $500 million fund dedicated to nurturing Web3 companies.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-crowns-zkpass-as-winner-of-its-first-web3-reality-show-build-the-block/" rel="nofollow">Binance Crowns zkPass as Winner of its First Web3 Reality Show &#8216;Build The Block&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elon Musk Sued for Insider Trading With Dogecoin Using &#8220;Publicity Stunts&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-sued-for-insider-trading-with-dogecoin-using-publicity-stunts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 23:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253649</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ElonMusk2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ElonMusk2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s tweets often influence Dogecoin’s price, but allegations from investors suggest that Musk traded around his social media activity. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tesla boss Elon Musk is guilty of insider trading against his followers using Dogecoin (DOGE), alleged memecoin investors in a court filing against the tech entrepreneur on Wednesday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The accusations are a follow-up to a $258 billion class action lawsuit filed by the same group in June 2022, accusing Musk and his companies of causing hundreds of billions in losses for Dogecoin holders.   </span></p>
<h2>Elon Musk Dogecoin Agenda</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per the </span><a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.581639/gov.uscourts.nysd.581639.74.1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">amended filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in a Manhattan federal court on May 31, Elon Musk engaged in “a deliberate course of carnival barking market manipulation,” through a “publicity circus” intended to pump Dogecoin’s price. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">These stunts include his </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sell-the-news-dogecoin-drops-20-after-elon-musk-snl/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">public appearances</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and social media activity hyping up  Dogecoin dating back to April 2019. These stunts boosted Dogecoin’s price by 36,000% to $0.70+ by May 2021. Today, DOGE trades 90% down from that high. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Musk’s pretense that promotion of Dogecoin was just well-meaning fun—not meant to be taken seriously—is not credible,” read the filing, labeling the tycoon an “apex predator,” and his millions of Twitter followers as prey. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The lawsuit noted that numerous studies have already demonstrated the effect of Elon Musk’s tweets on the price of Dogecoin. Indeed, Musk’s announcements that he would begin </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-spikes-15-as-elon-musk-says-spacex-will-soon-accept-it-for-merch-payments/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">accepting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Dogecoin at SpaceX in 2021, and his </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-skyrockets-22-as-elon-musk-visited-twitter-hq-ahead-of-purchase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">visit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to Twitter HQ after taking over the company last year, have each contributed to DOGE’s changing price. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Musk exercised his influence again by changing Twitter’s blue bird logo to a picture of the Doge meme’s Shiba Inu for three days, helping </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-explodes-25-after-elon-musk-changes-twitter-icon-to-doge-meme/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pump</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the coin’s price by 30%. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing added that Musk and Tesla traded profitably around the billionaire’s “intended moves,” citing blockchain records as evidence. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Specifically, the lawsuit claims to have tracked down a wallet address – DH5ya – allegedly belonged to Musk, and became the largest single holder of Dogecoin by February 2021. That wallet then sold millions of dollars worth of Dogecoin at multiple times throughout April 2021.</span></p>
<h2>Securities Fraud?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A key part of the lawsuit is the presupposition that Dogecoin is an unregistered security under existing standards from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Musk was founded by Dogecoin creators Billy Markus and Jackson Palmer back in 2013 – but they have remained uninvolved in the development of the project for years. Markus himself often jokes with Elon Musk on Twitter, both of whom often provide lighthearted commentary about crypto over Twitter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When the original lawsuit was filed last year, Musk’s lawyers said the lawsuit was fanciful. “There is nothing unlawful about tweeting words of support for, or funny pictures about, a legitimate cryptocurrency that continues to hold a market cap of nearly $10 billion,&#8221; they said.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-sued-for-insider-trading-with-dogecoin-using-publicity-stunts/" rel="nofollow">Elon Musk Sued for Insider Trading With Dogecoin Using &#8220;Publicity Stunts&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Contracts for Institutional Investors on June 5 </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-launch-bitcoin-and-ether-futures-contracts-for-institutional-investors-on-june-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Futures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253535</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/coinbase_bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/coinbase_bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The move marks a shift in Coinbase’s focus away from retail trade, an area of increased regulatory scrutiny in recent months. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Popular crypto exchange Coinbase will launch Bitcoin and Ethereum futures contracts for institutional investors on June 5, the company said on its website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company will launch these products through CFTC-regulated Coinbase Derivative Exchange, promising lower fees than other US-regulated derivatives exchanges. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTI and ETI for Institutional Investors </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span></h2>
<p>Coinbase has partnered with leading FCMs (Futures Commission Merchants), brokers, and front-end providers to enable institutional clients seamless access to these contracts.</p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“The Coinbase Bitcoin (BTI) and Coinbase Ether (ETI) futures contracts will be accessible through leading third-party institutional futures commission merchants (FCMs) and brokers,” the <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-derivatives-exchange-will-launch-institutional-sized-bitcoin-and" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a> said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To help investors manage their portfolios effectively, BTI and ETI will be available in 1 Bitcoin and 10 Ether contracts.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decision to launch these futures contracts followed the release of nano bitcoin (BIT) and nano Ether (ET) contracts earlier. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“With the launch of these institutional-sized USD-settled contracts, we look to empower institutional participants with greater precision in managing crypto exposure, expressing directional views, or tracking Bitcoin and Ether returns in a capital-efficient way,” Coinbase said. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase Looking Beyond US</span></h2>
<p>Over the past two months, Coinbase was in the news for exploring friendlier jurisdictions for its entire range of offerings. As part of this endeavor, it secured a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/securing-us-alternatives-coinbase-obtains-a-license-in-bermuda/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">license</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in Bermuda, where a crypto regulation has been in place since 2018.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Based in Bermuda, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> the Coinbase International Exchange for non-US institutional investors, a derivatives exchange offering perpetual futures contracts. Furthermore, Coinbase is believed to evaluate options in European Union and the UK for setting its base.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Although Coinbase says it’s committed to the US, its disillusionment with the world’s largest crypto market came recently when the regulators signaled that they might investigate the company’s staking services, calling them unregulated securities.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Coinbase has <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/we-asked-the-sec-for-reasonable-crypto-rules-for-americans-we-got-legal" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">refuted</a> these claims, the regulatory scrutiny of crypto firms in the US has become more intense in the past few months, especially after FTX’s collapse. With the prolonged downturn keeping crypto firms under check, big entities like Coinbase must look beyond the US to retain their leadership position in the crypto business. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-launch-bitcoin-and-ether-futures-contracts-for-institutional-investors-on-june-5/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase to Launch Bitcoin and Ether Futures Contracts for Institutional Investors on June 5 </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As the Meme Coin Craze Shows No Signs of Slowing Down, Here Are 3 Tokens That Could Explode Next</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-meme-coin-craze-shows-no-signs-of-slowing-down-here-are-3-tokens-that-could-explode-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253614</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin market has taken a hit in recent weeks, with most tokens suffering double-digit value drops. Investors are now looking elsewhere for returns potential, given the current state of meme coin stalwarts like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu. However, despite this red wave, several tokens are withstanding the tide and producing stellar results – [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin market has taken a hit in recent weeks, with most tokens suffering double-digit value drops.</p>
<p>Investors are now looking elsewhere for returns potential, given the current state of meme coin stalwarts like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu.</p>
<p>However, despite this red wave, several tokens are withstanding the tide and producing stellar results – providing a glimmer of hope for meme coin enthusiasts.</p>
<h2>Waning Enthusiasm Hits the Meme Coin Market Hard</h2>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap reveals that total meme coin trading volume is down by 17% over the past day – highlighting the lack of excitement around these crypto assets.</p>
<p>Individual trading volumes are down across the board, with the main culprits being $DOGE, $SHIB, $PEPE, and $FLOKI. All four of these tokens have seen waning interest over the past week – with $DOGE being the only one providing signs of a reversal.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253617" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="199" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2-300x99.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-2-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Meme coins seem to be following the market trajectory set by big players like Bitcoin and Ethereum. Both of these coins have posted losses in the past few days, dragging down their peers.</p>
<p>Moreover, the buzz around the meme coin niche has mostly faded with the dramatic fall of popular tokens like $PEPE and $WOJAK.</p>
<p>Investors in these coins have opted to cash in rather than wait for price to bounce back – leading to the dramatic value drops experienced in recent weeks.</p>
<p>Finally, there has also been an evident lack of innovation within the space since the breakthrough of Pepe in mid-April. Although many copycat coins have entered the fray, none were able to match Pepe&#8217;s impact, prompting investors to return to more established cryptos.</p>
<p>All told, these factors paint a bleak picture for the meme coin niche in the short term.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Ignites Hope After Raising $2.7 Million</h2>
<p>Fortunately, several projects have begun to gain traction over the past week – with investors hopeful that they can spark the meme coin market back into life.</p>
<p>Leading the way in this regard is<a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a>, a brand-new meme coin from the creators of the ultra-successful Wall St Bulls NFT collection.</p>
<p>In 2021, this NFT collection made headlines when it sold out all 10,000 pieces in 32 minutes and raised $2.5 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">According</a> to OpenSea, 1,864 ETH worth of these NFTs have been traded since the collection launched – equating to over $3.5 million based on today’s exchange rate.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253618" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="305" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-1-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This collection&#8217;s incredible success led to the formation of a colossal community around Wall Street Memes, evidenced by the 523,000+ “degens” that follow the official Instagram account.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; community benefits from an indirect link to the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/wallstreetbets/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">WallStreetBets subreddit</a>. This subreddit played a significant role in the GameStop short squeeze, a market-rocking event two years ago</p>
<p>Now, Wall Street Memes&#8217; team is looking to give back to the community by launching the $WSM token – allowing holders to benefit as the community grows.</p>
<p>Early investors can now <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">buy $WSM tokens</a> through the Wall Street Memes presale, which has raised over $2.7 million in just one week.</p>
<p>Clearly, Wall Street Memes stands as a beacon of potential amidst the current meme coin gloom – making it an exciting time to be a $WSM investor.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>AiDoge Redefining Meme Coin Landscape After Selling Out $15m Presale</h2>
<p>Another meme coin that’s still making headway amidst the current market turmoil is<a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> AiDoge ($AI)</a>.</p>
<p>As its name suggests, AiDoge is an innovative meme coin that blends artificial intelligence (AI) concepts with a Doge-like theme – creating a unique and intriguing proposition for meme coin enthusiasts.</p>
<p>AiDoge’s flagship feature is its groundbreaking meme generator, which uses cutting-edge AI algorithms to create hilarious images using text-based prompts.</p>
<p>AiDoge users can easily capitalize on trending topics by instantly uploading these images to social media sites like Reddit and Twitter.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253619" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2-300x122.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-2-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Per the project’s <a href="https://aidoge.com/assets/documents/Aidoge_Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, users can also earn tokenized rewards by uploading their memes to AiDoge’s public wall, where they will be voted on by other community members.</p>
<p>Central to the AiDoge ecosystem is $AI – the project’s native transactional token.</p>
<p>Users must buy $AI to use the meme generator, although many eager investors opted to purchase tokens through the project’s presale phase to gain financial exposure to AiDoge’s growth.</p>
<p>This led to AiDoge’s presale hitting its funding target of $14.9 million – although the development team is offering one final chance for investors to get involved before $AI is listed on major exchanges on June 19.</p>
<p>Investors can <a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">buy $AI</a> through the project&#8217;s website for $0.0000336, which will be the token&#8217;s official listing price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Website</strong></a></p>
<h2>Baby Doge Coin Acts as Beacon of Resilience for Investors</h2>
<p>Lastly, Baby Doge Coin is also performing remarkably well, making it one of the few meme coins to post gains in the past week.</p>
<p>Per CoinGecko, Baby Doge Coin is up by 0.5% over the past seven days. Although this is a minor value increase, it’s a far cry from the sharp price drops experienced by most projects in the meme coin niche.</p>
<p>Moreover, $BABYDOGE is now the fifth-largest meme coin in the world, according to CoinMarketCap, boasting a market cap of nearly $300 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253620" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="281" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-300x140.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Naturally, most of the hype surrounding Baby Doge Coin is fuelled by its branding. Although it has no direct link to the Dogecoin project, many meme coin investors are opting to purchase tokens to capitalize on the association with $DOGE.</p>
<p>However, Baby Doge Coin is distinguishing itself with a focus on real-world utility. The project offers a custom-built DEX that allows community members to swap any token on the Binance Smart Chain.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the steady performance and rise in market cap of $BABYDOGE indicate that it&#8217;s captured the attention of meme coin lovers – making it an intriguing contender within the market.</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-meme-coin-craze-shows-no-signs-of-slowing-down-here-are-3-tokens-that-could-explode-next/" rel="nofollow">As the Meme Coin Craze Shows No Signs of Slowing Down, Here Are 3 Tokens That Could Explode Next</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
