<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:54:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>El Salvador’s Alejandra Guajardo Walks Miss Universe Stage in Glowing Bitcoin Suit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-alejandra-guajardo-walks-miss-universe-stage-in-glowing-bitcoin-suit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 01:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232917</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The moment came during the national costume show in the preliminary competition round. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Miss Universe 2023 contest had various show-stopper moments during its National Costume Competition today. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">But for the cryptocurrency sector, it came when El Salvador’s Alejandra Guajardo sashayed the stage in a Bitcoin suit. </span></p>
<figure id="attachment_232951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232951" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-232951" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo.jpg" alt="Alejandra Guajardo" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alejandra-Guajardo-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232951" class="wp-caption-text">Alejandra Guajardo. Source: Reddit</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTC on Miss Universe Stage </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 27-year-old actress and model showcased the evolution of her country’s currency through a dress she wore at the Miss Universe contest. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She came on stage in a golden bitcoin outfit, holding a scepter with a BTC logo. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a striking resemblance to the BTC logo, her outfit had three prominent colors &#8211; gold, silver, and bronze. Guajardo sported a big coin model on the back, with her country’s name engraved on it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Guajardo’s bitcoin outfit quickly became the <a href="https://elsalvadorgram.com/2023/01/alejandra-guajardo-sorprende-con-su-traje-de-bitcoin-en-miss-universo/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">talking</a> point in the cryptosphere. It was designed by El Salvadoran artist and fashion designer Francisco Guerrero. According to him, the dress describes the evolution of currency in his country &#8211; from cocoa to colón, the US dollar, and BTC. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The finale of the ongoing 71st Miss Universe competition, which is taking place in New Orleans, Louisiana, is scheduled for January 14. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Beauty with Substance </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Earlier, in a statement seeking support from her fans in her campaign for the Miss Universe title, she said, “Transformational leadership is when you work harmoniously with others with similar objectives for the betterment of everyone else’s.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In her profile, Miss Universe’s official website <a href="https://www.missuniverse.com/delegates/alejandra-guajardo-sada" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">says</a>, “Alejandra Guajardo takes every opportunity close to her heart. She is immensely grateful for all the motivation and love she receives from her loved ones and supporters. She has a degree in International Business, and her profound sales skills date back to when she was just five years old and began selling hand-crafted stones to her neighbors.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">El Salvador’s BTC Strategy </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Guajardo wearing a bitcoin dress at the Miss Universe event today <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-backed-bonds-inch-closer-after-greenlighting-digital-asset-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">coincides </a>with her country’s Legislative Assembly passing a law that allows the issuance of sovereign Bitcoin Bond. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recently, El Salvador’s President Nayib Bukele <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-president-lashes-out-on-mainstream-media-over-bitcoin-attacks/" data-wpel-link="internal">lashed out</a> at mainstream media for attacking his campaign to buy more bitcoins, also through the upcoming Volcano Bond. Going ahead with the bitcoin strategy, Bukele’s government <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-launches-a-national-bitcoin-office-onbtc/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a national bitcoin office in November to coordinate various bitcoin and cryptocurrency-related initiatives both within the country and globally. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The country also decided to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-to-start-buying-1-bitcoin-per-day-says-bukele/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy</a> one bitcoin every day to benefit from the dip, as BTC is down nearly 65% since its all-time high in November 2021.  </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-alejandra-guajardo-walks-miss-universe-stage-in-glowing-bitcoin-suit/" rel="nofollow">El Salvador’s Alejandra Guajardo Walks Miss Universe Stage in Glowing Bitcoin Suit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Study Claims Chinese Crypto Traders Are Price Gouging Korean Buyers, But They&#8217;re Not (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-study-claims-chinese-crypto-traders-are-price-gouging-korean-buyers-but-theyre-not-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232835</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Are Chinese crypto traders exploiting the Kimchi premium, or is it just free-market behavior?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s a crypto study out of South Korea recently of Chinese Bitcoin arbitrage traders and Korea&#8217;s &#8220;kimchi premium&#8221; on Bitcoin prices. Its characterization of the cross-border Bitcoin trade and recommendations miss some key economic foundations.</p>
<p>A recently published <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1544612322004056?via%3Dihub" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">crypto study</a> by Incheon National University and the Bank of Korea is making the rounds. The authors found a strong correlation between the &#8220;kimchi premium&#8221; and international remittances to China.</p>
<h2>&#8216;Kimchi Premium&#8217; Is The Persistently Higher Bitcoin Price in South Korea</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.cnbctv18.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-kimchi-premium-and-why-it-exists-explained-14370162.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">kimchi premium</a> is the higher Bitcoin and crypto prices in South Korea. That&#8217;s because of the higher relative demand for Bitcoin within the Korean economy against fiat payments. It&#8217;s also a result of lower BTC supply.</p>
<p>The paper&#8217;s authors infer that Chinese arbitrage traders are selling Bitcoin to South Koreans. They suggest it is because the Chinese Bitcoin sellers are going after the kimchi premium. They&#8217;re selling it to South Korean crypto traders specifically to get a higher price.</p>
<p>The paper&#8217;s authors frame this as Chinese crypto traders taking advantage of Korean crypto traders. They call South Korea a &#8220;target&#8221; and say Chinese crypt traders are &#8220;exploiting excess demand.&#8221; Moreover, they also call for international standards of regulation of cryptocurrency to protect investors.</p>
<p>But Chinese crypto traders aren&#8217;t fleecing South Korean crypto traders. The South Korean Bitcoin buyers don&#8217;t mind being fleeced if that&#8217;s what it is. They are willing to pay higher prices to get ahold of more Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Chinese Are Serving the Higher Demand</h2>
<p>The study originated from the economics department of Incheon National. But the paper itself isn&#8217;t very economical. The author does not seem to consider the cross-border trade of bitcoin economically.</p>
<p>Higher prices specifically exist to attract more sellers. That&#8217;s how markets work to coordinate supply and demand. There isn&#8217;t as much Bitcoin in South Korea as people in the market for it there <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-re-enter-south-korea-by-acquiring-local-exchange-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">would like</a>.</p>
<p>So they are willing to pay a higher price to get more Bitcoin. That is a free market. It&#8217;s not exploitation. This is how prices distribute resources to where people want them most in the fair trade-offs we all make.</p>
<p>The Chinese traders getting the kimchi premium are responding to an incentive. Bitcoin buyers in Korea raise that incentive with their own money. They use the higher price they&#8217;re willing to pay as BTC bait.</p>
<p>Ironically, the paper calls for policy intervention. That&#8217;s ironic because it&#8217;s policy (<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/monitoring-crypto-whales-korean-regulators-with-new-legislation-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">strict Korean capital controls</a>) that creates the Bitcoin shortage in South Korea. That shortage of BTC is the cause of the kimchi premium.</p>
<p>A decrease in government controls on financial markets could be more apt to cut the premium. The mutually beneficial trade relationship between Chinese and Korean crypto traders is not exploitation. It&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-study-claims-chinese-crypto-traders-are-price-gouging-korean-buyers-but-theyre-not-opinion/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Study Claims Chinese Crypto Traders Are Price Gouging Korean Buyers, But They&#8217;re Not (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Lesson in Alameda-FTX About Government Regulation and Crypto (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-lesson-in-alameda-ftx-about-government-regulation-and-crypto-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232985</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[For as long as modern finance existed, there have been bank runs and insolvencies. The lesson in the Alameda-FTX bankruptcy is actually that government regulation is no good for crypto markets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The scale of the financial damage to crypto investors last year was colossal. Not just from FTX International going under but also the rest of them: Three Arrow Capital, Celsius, Genesis, Gemini, Voyager Digital, and BlockFi.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin price still hasn&#8217;t recovered from the ongoing streak of crypto bankruptcies, although it deleted some of the losses from the FTX fiasco. Over crypto exchanges, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-price-winter-continue-in-2023-8-key-considerations/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC kept taking steep discounts</a> all year. Every new bankruptcy headline plunged the Bitcoin price lower.</p>
<p>There&#8217;s no telling whether the most recent Bitcoin price rally to $21K is a breakout or a January bull trap. Meanwhile, last year&#8217;s insolvencies continue to unravel in bankruptcy and criminal court.</p>
<p>Bankruptcy lawyers said Wednesday that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-locates-5-billion-in-assets-attorney-says-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX has found $5 billion</a> in liquid assets. While under house arrest on a $250 million bail bond, <a href="https://sambf.substack.com/p/ftx-pre-mortem-overview" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Sam Bankman-Fried began blogging</a> on Substack on Jan 12. He wrote in a post entitled &#8220;FTX Pre-Mortem Overview&#8221; that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In November 2022, an extreme, quick, targeted crash precipitated by the CEO of Binance made Alameda insolvent.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Notice the concluding point of SBF&#8217;s &#8220;post-mortem&#8221; is not that FTX didn&#8217;t have their customer&#8217;s money. It&#8217;s that a competitor&#8217;s CEO told the public that FTX didn&#8217;t have their customer&#8217;s money.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried wasn&#8217;t some unregulated cowboy on the digital frontier. Satoshi Nakamoto was. SBF was, in fact, a political megadonor who nurtured cozy relations with the U.S. regulatory regime.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the TradFi attitude toward finance that plagued crypto last year is exactly why we need crypto. Bitcoin is supposed to fix this. So are other open-source, peer-to-peer ledgers.</p>
<h2>How Wall Street TradFi Bros Ransacked The Buzz Surrounding Crypto</h2>
<p>At the close of the year, Bloomberg Businessweek published <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2022-the-crypto-story-FTX-collapse-matt-levine/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">a sequel</a> to its Oct 2022 long-form presentation, &#8220;The Crypto Story.&#8221;</p>
<p>The follow-up piece was about Sam Bankman-Fried and the Alameda FTX foibles. The story is entitled &#8220;How Not To Play The Game.&#8221; The article deftly diagnoses the problem of TradFi imports to crypto:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;You might find yourself building out a snazzy user interface and a fast, clever trading algorithm, because those are fun and profitable things to do, but you might find yourself neglecting the accounting department, because that&#8217;s boring. You might get really good at attracting customer money, with your snazzy interface and your sense of fun, but also really bad at keeping track of the customer money with your lack of accountants and your sense of fun.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto is fundamentally a no-nonsense, hard-money, anti-Wall Street industry. But the TradFi bros turned it into Wall Street&#8217;s evil twin. They created a parallel crypto menagerie of financial shenanigans and accounting horrors:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;One imperfect but useful way to think about crypto is that it allowed for the creation of a toy financial system. There was already a regular financial system, a set of abstractions and procedures&#8230; And then crypto came along with a new set of stuff to do finance to.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>But the way veteran financial columnist Matt Levine describes it: Crypto needs <em>more</em> regulation. Where the article gets it wrong is leaving the influence of government out of the picture. Because the story does not address the influence of government regulation on the insolvency crises of the past year.</p>
<p>The way &#8220;How Not To Play The Game&#8221; tells it, the government was not at play in this game. But that is not exactly the case. The article itself advances some of the evidence against this characterization.</p>
<p>Because in it, the author tells about how &#8220;crypto&#8221; businesses resold the worst excesses of Wall Street as crypto products. These bad business ideas did not originate on Wall Street in a vacuum. They happened with the permission and even the support and design of regulators:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This game was played by young people who came from the world of traditional finance, from banks and hedge funds and quantitative proprietary trading firms, people who already liked finance and wanted to play with a toy version of it they could shape however they wanted.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Could the picture be any clearer? Crypto&#8217;s bubble was not driven by the humble miner running their ASIC rigs. It was driven by these Wall Street entrants who brought along with them the heavily regulated Wall Street&#8217;s reckless financial culture.</p>
<p>What else should investors expect from any substantial interventions by the government into crypto markets but more misaligned incentives and unintended consequences?</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-233267" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover.jpg" alt="sbf_alameda_ftx_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_alameda_ftx_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>It&#8217;s U.S. TradFi Regulation That Hurts Investor Finances</h2>
<p>It was the U.S. financial regulatory regime that allowed the Dot Com bubble in 1999 and 2000. Regulators let people trade dot com stocks with huge market caps for glorified home pages.</p>
<p>The advocate itching to regulate cryptos looks and sees that 91% of altcoins from 2014 are now defunct and sees a reason to pass more rules for cryptos.</p>
<p>But they want regulation from the same authorities that incentivized the Dot Com bubble. They conveniently forget the track record of regulated securities performing the exact way that the crypto sector did in 2020 &#8211; 2022. For example, they ignore the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_companies_affected_by_the_dot-com_bubble" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Dot Com companies that</a> spent hundreds of millions of dollars on their way to bankruptcy.</p>
<p>Moreover, it was regulators asleep at the wheel in the housing savings and loans crisis. That created a real estate and financial bubble from 2005 until 2007. By 2008 it had shaken the entire world economy into recession.</p>
<p>Vast government-sponsored enterprises, financial institutions like Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, fueled the madness with low-interest loans for subprime mortgage customers.</p>
<p>Wall Street giants, with close regulatory partnerships with the government, invented mortgage-backed securities as an exotic fixed-income derivative for big financials to sell back and forth to each other.</p>
<p>By 2007 the chickens had come home to roost. Housing prices began to crater. At that point, the regulated traditional finance sector&#8217;s involvement with the bubble was beyond insane. It was unethical.</p>
<p>Berkshire Hathaway&#8217;s Warren Buffett and Charlie Munger would call it decadent and immoral. Well ahead of the housing bubble&#8217;s inevitable crash, Buffett and Munger warned about it.</p>
<p>In 2005, <a href="https://money.cnn.com/2005/05/01/news/fortune500/buffett_talks/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">they considered</a> the residential real estate bubble and the destabilizing effect of hedge funds on financial markets to be the biggest threats to America after a nuclear terrorist strike.</p>
<h2>How Did Regulation Prevent The Above?</h2>
<p>It was on the U.S. financial regulators&#8217; watch that these crises formed. And it was in traditional finance companies that were compliant with regulation if not directly responding to regulatory incentives.</p>
<p>The damage done to investors and household finances lasts to this day. The U.S. Treasury <a href="https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/frontline/article/how-much-did-the-financial-crisis-cost/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">estimates the housing crash cost</a> the economy $19 trillion in household wealth.</p>
<p>Furthermore, it is the SEC that allows algorithmic trading logjams, arcane derivatives, and insane leveraged trading. That TradFi mess dressed up as &#8220;crypto&#8221; and made a ton of money while damaging many people&#8217;s finances. So that doesn&#8217;t make what FTX did the same as what Bitcoin created the crypto segment for.</p>
<p>Crypto is supposed to be a movement toward financial sanity, propriety, and honor. While the traditional finance world was going through the shocks of 2000 and 2008, so much for regulation, the world was blissfully unaware that Bitcoin would be one answer to solve the problems of finance in our modern, connected, global world.</p>
<p>It was inevitable that forces of reaction would appropriate the good reputation and glamor of cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin. But these so-called crypto projects that conduct the funny money business as usual are counterfeit crypto, not the real thing.</p>
<h2>What Happens When Crypto Gets Cozy With Government and Regulation</h2>
<p>The crypto businesses that went under worst of all were those with the most government influence.</p>
<p>There were, of course, many reports that SBF was very active in U.S. federal politics after the FTX collapse. The non-profit group, Open Secrets, which keeps track of public federal election donation records, <a href="https://www.opensecrets.org/news/2022/11/megadonor-no-more-sam-bankman-fried-spent-his-way-into-the-good-graces-of-washington-then-lost-it-all/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported in November</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of the cryptocurrency exchange platform FTX, was a darling in some Washington D.C. policy circles. He proselytized for digital assets in testimony on Capitol Hill and gave more than $990,000 to candidates plus an additional $38.8 million to outside groups this election cycle, making him the sixth biggest individual donor of the 2022 midterms.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Before the fortunes of Alameda-FTX turned, SBF had planned to give over $1 billion to support his chosen candidates and issues in the 2024 elections.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss brothers and their Gemini exchange are also very cozy with Washington. Like SBF, they bring the big finance mindset to crypto and are very active in lobbying and talking to regulators. <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/10/winklevoss-twins-advice-to-zuckerberg-and-libra-work-with-regulators.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Their advice</a> to Mark Zuckerberg back when Facebook was working on Libra was:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Work with regulators. Talk with them. You know, we definitely went through the front door, and we tried to educate the regulators and shape the regulation in a thoughtful manner because if you get the regulation wrong it can stifle innovation, but the right regulation allows for innovation to flourish, and we think we have achieved that right balance with New York.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>So there have been plenty of reports of the involvement of these businesses with regulators. But has anyone drawn the connection that the TradFi regulatory mindset is what caused the insolvencies?</p>
<p>The regulatory mindset isn&#8217;t a business mindset. It&#8217;s a control function. It is not concerned with how to produce anything. It&#8217;s concerned with how to control an already productive system and how to freeze it against competition from new entrants to give it time to grow.</p>
<p>Crypto&#8217;s ethos is that it doesn&#8217;t need special treatment and protection. It doesn&#8217;t need regulatory entrenchment to thrive. Crypto thrives on openness and freedom, not barriers and regulation.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s community hopes its great-grandchildren will use the money and that it will be more valuable than ever. It&#8217;s a currency started by a borderless, nationless online community. So it doesn&#8217;t see its future resting on TradFi government regulation. It sees its future in the code working as is.</p>
<h2>Governance Through Trustless Code, Not Through Trusting Regulation</h2>
<p>Cryptocurrencies are something that can be subject to government regulation. Government can make laws outright banning crypto, as China has. But crypto is not an agent of the government.</p>
<p>Companies, even private companies, are agents of the government. They register with the government, ostensibly comply with its regulations, and pay taxes out of payroll and profits.</p>
<p>While a cryptocurrency platform or its monies may be an object of government action, they are not a subject of government. They are more like commodity goods (like gold or oil) that way than like joint stock corporations.</p>
<p>Cryptos like Bitcoin are not constituted the way private, and public companies are. They are simply software scripts and databases of information that serve the platform&#8217;s users.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s origin is not in regulation but in code and a market economy. A market economy is regulated automatically and naturally by its realities and the self-direction of its participants.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, crypto companies like FTX or Binance are agents of government and subject to its regulation the day they register with a government to engage in commerce. While Bitcoin and most cryptos are open-source projects, FTX, Genesis, Gemini, Three Arrows, Voyager, (etc.) were regulated private companies.</p>
<p>Now, that doesn&#8217;t mean they&#8217;re doomed from the start. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/if-people-withdrew-everything-from-binance-us-we-would-still-have-millions-in-assets-ceo-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance has remained solvent</a>, and it&#8217;s a regulated private company. It&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-receives-initial-approval-to-acquire-voyager-digitals-assets-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">even buying its rivals</a> that failed in the insolvency crisis.</p>
<p>Many of the world&#8217;s most beloved brands and greatest fortunes were created by private and public companies under the direction of government regulation.</p>
<p>But Bitcoin is just one of the amazing new products that represent a complete paradigm shift away from government regulation. It belongs to a paradigm shift called open source, and the open source movement is just beginning to create exciting new possibilities for the world.</p>
<p>In open source, the greatest solutions to age-old human problems will be found in autonomous network governance.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-lesson-in-alameda-ftx-about-government-regulation-and-crypto-opinion/" rel="nofollow">The Lesson in Alameda-FTX About Government Regulation and Crypto (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining 2022 Review: A Tough Year for Public Miners</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-2022-review-a-tough-year-for-public-miners/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 19:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232833</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A closer look at how much more difficult 2022 was for Bitcoin miners than the year prior. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The mining data site Hashrate Index has released a report reflecting on the state of the Bitcoin mining industry throughout 2022. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The analysis examines the steep decline in mining profitability in 2022 compared to 2021 amid plummeting Bitcoin prices and a rising hash rate. </span></p>
<h2>The Hardest Hitting Bear Market</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Per the </span><a href="https://hashrateindex.com/blog/hashrate-index-2022-bitcoin-mining-year-in-review/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> published on Wednesday, Bitcoin’s hashprice reached an all-time low of $55.94/PH/day in November of last year. Hashprice is a dollar-denominated measure of miner revenue for each unit of hashing power used. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The 2022 yearly average hashprice was $123.88/PH/day, a steep decline from the $314.61/PH/day average in 2021. The steep decline was driven largely by the onset of Bitcoin’s bear market but also by an average 16% increase in energy costs across the United States in 2022. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“35 states have lower average industrial electricity rates than the S19 Pro’s current break-even electricity price of $92 per MWh,” explained the report. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Rising energy costs also caused the cost of hosting services to spike. Whereas a “reasonable contract” may have offered prices at $0.05-$0.06/kWh before 2022, it’s now “not uncommon” to see rates around $0.08-0.09/kWh. “Anything below $0.075/kWh is considered  “a steal” given market conditions,” the report continued. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meanwhile, the trade on ASICs– the specialized machines used to efficiently mine Bitcoin – has plummeted. Rigs of all new, mid, and old generations each saw their returns fall by over 80%, causing the premium on the S19 XP to increase throughout the year. </span></p>
<h2>Public Miners Suffer</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public Bitcoin miners have suffered major losses within this environment, with most pure-play Bitcoin mining stocks plummeting over 90% in 2022. One of the world’s largest miners – Core Scientific (CORZ) – fell 99% as worrying rumors swelled about the firm’s solvency, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">culminating</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in an official bankruptcy filing towards the year’s end. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The second-worst performing mining stock was  Greenidge Generation (GREE), which fell 98% as it struggled to pay off high-interest debt collateralized with its own ASIC machines. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Other miners like Iris Energy have also suffered under the weight of such loans, with Iris being forced to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/iris-energy-slashes-bitcoin-mining-capacity-due-to-a-requested-loan/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">slash</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> its mining capacity to pay back its debt to NYDIG in November. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Public miners were incentivized to expand as quickly as possible during the 2021 bull market, causing them to expand their hashrate dominance further from 14% to 19% over private miners. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2022, Bitcoin’s overall hashrate rose by another 41%. This, too, was largely driven by public miners, which increased their cumulative hashrate by 59% versus a 19% increase among their private counterparts. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally, 2022 marked a year in which Bitcoin mining became “the only proof of work game in town.” Its only major rival, Ethereum, changed its consensus mechanism to proof of stake in mid-September, thus killing Ethereum’s mining industry with one upgrade. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Despite Ethereum’s three and a half months without proof of work, miners on the network still produced nearly as much revenue as Bitcoin miners last year ($8.87 billion vs. $9.55 billion). Today, Ethereum miners have been replaced by staking validators, which produce new ETH at a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eths-supply-change-after-the-merge-and-will-it-ever-be-deflationary/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">far slower rate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> than miners did pre-merge. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Staking validator revenue is a shadow of mining revenue,” stated the report. </span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-2022-review-a-tough-year-for-public-miners/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Mining 2022 Review: A Tough Year for Public Miners</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Staying Vigilant in 2023: 91% of Cryptocurrencies From 2014 Are Dead</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/staying-vigilant-in-2023-91-of-cryptocurrencies-from-2014-are-dead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233121</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/darker_light_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/darker_light_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the market rallies, it's essential to remain vigilant and informed. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two weeks into the year, and crypto markets are rebounding. The Bitcoin and Ether price are each up some 20% on the seven-day chart. But a recent study of altcoins aims to give crypto investors pause before they go trading the rally.</p>
<p>When the market makes a move like this, crypto traders often shuffle. They make trades to scoop profits, make hedges, or take long positions in the coin they think will gain the most next.</p>
<p>This can result in an increase in volatility in crypto exchange markets. Furthermore, traders anticipate each other&#8217;s moves. As a result, the market can become increasingly volatile with self-fulfilling, short-range expectations. While this may seem complicated, crypto trading is worth a world of difference in ROI.</p>
<h2>There is a Broad Range of Risks and Reward</h2>
<p>For example, while the top three cryptos by market cap gained 20% in the last week, here&#8217;s what some altcoins gained: Cardano (ADA) gained 26%. Solana (SOL) gained 70%. Avalanche (AVAX) gained 42%. Lido DAO (LDO) surged by 42%. Aptos (APT) skyrocketed by 94%.</p>
<p>Cardano is up because <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-possible-reasons-why-cardano-skyrocketed-30-in-7-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">ADA&#8217;s fundamentals surged</a> in volume. the TVL (Total Value Locked) has soared. TVL in Cardano for staking has soared in Jan. Trading on its DeFi protocols swelled as well. There&#8217;s also buzz around a new ADA stablecoin and dev toolkit for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-launches-toolkit-for-custom-sidechain-creation/" data-wpel-link="internal">ADA custom sidechain deployment</a>.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Citi notes that Solana blockchain activity is high. AWS <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/11/aws-partners-with-avalanche-to-scale-blockchain-solutions-for-enterprises-governments/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">has partnered</a> with Avalanche to bring its blockchain solutions to enterprises and governments.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-lido-dao-soars-to-2-month-high-btc-touched-17k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Lido DAO keeps pushing</a> forward in an exciting race with MakerDAO. Solana peer Aptos is doing well because of investor excitement over its fast throughput.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s easy to see why it&#8217;s tempting to go altcoin shopping. But before you whip out your credit card with your eyes full of big numbers with dollar signs on them, don&#8217;t forget to stay vigilant against the downsides. While your principal investment could appreciate by 35 or 84% in a week&#8217;s time, it could also all disappear as quickly.</p>
<h2>91% of Cryptos Launched in 2014 Are Gone</h2>
<p>A recent study <a href="https://coinkickoff.com/dead-crypto-coins/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">found that</a> 91% of cryptos launched in 2014 are now defunct. 704 now-dead cryptocurrencies were released in 2017. And 2018 was the worst year of crypto extinctions, with 751 coins dying on their holders:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We reviewed data on over 2,400 dead coins from Coinopsy, compiling data on the current status of each coin. We then analyzed the performance of each coin over the last 10 years, noting when coins were killed off and why.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The study found some common themes in dead coins: scams, jokes, short-lived ICOs, and ones that were abandoned or had no volume. Here are some red flags to look out for based on past failed cryptos: <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rug-pulls-how-to-avoid/" data-wpel-link="internal">How to avoid crypto rug pulls</a>. And here are six suggestions for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/6-ways-to-avoid-losing-your-funds-to-defi-scams-in-2021/" data-wpel-link="internal">how to avoid DeFi scams</a>.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting, though, that the number of failed cryptos should not at all give the impression that cryptocurrency is especially risky or difficult. This is a failure rate similar to those across the economy. New restaurants <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2016/01/20/heres-the-real-reason-why-most-restaurants-fail.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">have a similar</a> failure rate. New websites died during the Dot Com era <a>and still do</a>.</p>
<p>This distribution goes beyond commerce as well. Most of the outputs of most systems are the result of a small minority of the system&#8217;s factors. Crypto is hardly unique in this regard.</p>
<p>It doesn&#8217;t mean crypto is too difficult or risky to learn how to use. But it does underscore the importance of staying informed, taking it seriously, and knowing what you&#8217;re doing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/staying-vigilant-in-2023-91-of-cryptocurrencies-from-2014-are-dead/" rel="nofollow">Staying Vigilant in 2023: 91% of Cryptocurrencies From 2014 Are Dead</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Market Cap Taps $1 Trillion as SOL, DOT Explode Double Digits</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-taps-1-trillion-as-solana-polkadot-explode-double-digits/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Total Market Cap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233286</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Market_Cap.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Market_Cap.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Double-digit price surges from SOL, DOT, MATIC, and a few more have helped the market cap increase. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rally from the past two weeks has pushed the cumulative market cap of all crypto assets to above $1 trillion for the first time since the FTX debacle.</p>
<p>This comes amid the massive price surge from several altcoins, such as Solana, Polkadot, Polygon, Avalanche, and others.</p>
<ul>
<li>The start of 2023 has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/600m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-skyrockets-to-21k/" data-wpel-link="internal">quite spectacular</a> for the cryptocurrency market following the painful 2022. The largest digital asset went from around $16,500 to over $21,000 in about two weeks.</li>
<li>This 27% increase meant that the asset <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-fully-recovers-from-ftx-crash-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">recovered</a> all losses that came from the FTX collapse in November. It also helped BTC&#8217;s market cap to touch $400 billion, and its dominance is up to almost 41% after dropping to 39% last week.</li>
<li>Although bitcoin&#8217;s dominance is on the rise in the past few days, several altcoins have actually outperformed it. Solana is a prime example. SOL was among the most harmed asset following the FTX crash due to its affiliation with the former empire led by SBF.</li>
<li>This culminated in a drop below $8 at the end of 2022. However, things started to change following some positive words by Ethereum&#8217;s co-founder Vitalik Buterik, and SOL went on a roll. It almost tripled its value in the span of a few weeks and surged above $23 earlier today.</li>
<li>NEAR Protocol is another massive daily gainer, following a 28% surge. MATIC, DOT, TRX, AVAX, and CRO are among the other larger-cap altcoins with double-digit price pumps.</li>
<li>This rally has pushed the crypto market cap to above $1 trillion on CoinGecko for the first time in over two months. This means the metric has added more than $200 billion since the start of 2023.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_233288" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233288" style="width: 1831px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233288" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Capitalization. Source: CoinGecko" width="1831" height="549" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123.jpg 1831w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123-300x90.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123-1024x307.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123-768x230.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123-1536x461.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/123-50x15.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1831px) 100vw, 1831px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233288" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Capitalization. Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-cap-taps-1-trillion-as-solana-polkadot-explode-double-digits/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Market Cap Taps $1 Trillion as SOL, DOT Explode Double Digits</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Illicit Crypto Transactions in 2022 Surpassed $20 Billion for the First Time: Chainalysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/illicit-crypto-transactions-in-2022-surpassed-20-billion-for-the-first-time-chainalysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232946</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crime_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crime_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Criminal transactions involving digital currencies in 2022 supposedly totaled $20.1 billion, a $2 billion increase compared to 2021.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Illegal financial transactions involving cryptocurrencies in 2022 have reportedly surged for a second consecutive year, tapping an all-time high of $20.1 billion. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The previous record was in 2021, when digital assets facilitated criminal proceedings worth $18 billion.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Going Up Amid the Bear Market</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from the significant market decline, the numerous bankruptcies, and scandals, 2022 will be remembered as a flourishing year for illicit cryptocurrency transactions. According to Chainalysis&#8217; recent <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2023-crypto-crime-report-introduction/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">study</a>, the total value received by illegal crypto addresses hit $20.1 billion during the past 12 months.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The blockchain data platform noted that last year&#8217;s events made the forming of the latest report a bit &#8220;tricky.&#8221; It also explained that the figure includes only cryptocurrency-related crimes and not other offenses, such as employing digital currencies in drug trafficking or prostitution.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We have to stress that this is a lower bound estimate &#8211; our measure of illicit transaction volume is sure to grow over time.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Chainalysis outlined that transactions associated with sanctioned organizations soared over 100,000-fold in 2022, compared to 2021, and made up 44% of last year&#8217;s total criminal activity.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_232961" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232961" style="width: 980px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232961" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis.png" alt="Chainalysis" width="980" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis-300x122.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis-768x314.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Chainalysis-50x20.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 980px) 100vw, 980px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232961" class="wp-caption-text">Chainalysis figures, Source: Chainalysis</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Russia-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Garantex &#8211; is one such example. The Office of Foreign Control (OFAC) sanctioned it in April (a few months after Vladimir Putin launched his &#8220;special military operation&#8221; in Ukraine), but the platform continued operating.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cryptocurrency scams have also played a significant role, accounting for around 20% of the total illicit transactions. Still, crypto proceedings from fraudulent schemes last year were much less than the ones recorded in 2021. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The market downturn may be one reason for this. We&#8217;ve found in the past that crypto scams, for instance, take in less revenue during bear markets, likely because users are more pessimistic and less likely to believe a scam&#8217;s promises of high returns at times when asset prices are declining.</span></p>
<p>In general, less money in crypto overall tends to correlate with less money associated with crypto crime,&#8221; Chainalysis explained.</p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fewer Darknet Transactions</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Illicit deals on the  Darknet market involving cryptocurrencies have also been on a decline compared to 2021 (during the bull run). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-authorities-arrested-bitcoin-fogs-operator-for-laundering-336m-in-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">arrested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Russian-Swedish citizen &#8211; Roman Sterlingov &#8211; in April 2021, claiming he laundered over $330 million worth of bitcoin. He was the leader of Bitcoin Fog &#8211; an Internet service operating in the Darknet.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The officials doubled down in August, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/darknet-drug-dealer-accused-of-laundering-136m-worth-of-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">accusing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Baltimore resident – Ryan Farace &#8211; of laundering nearly 3,000 BTC on the Dark Web.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One such example last year was the investigation against the Russian Darknet marketplace &#8211; Hydra Market. Germany&#8217;s law enforcement agents </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/germany-halts-russian-darknet-marketplace-hydra-confiscates-25-million-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shut down</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the entity&#8217;s server infrastructure in April and confiscated 543 BTC from it. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/illicit-crypto-transactions-in-2022-surpassed-20-billion-for-the-first-time-chainalysis/" rel="nofollow">Illicit Crypto Transactions in 2022 Surpassed $20 Billion for the First Time: Chainalysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin’s Yearly Start May Signal an Incoming Bull Market: Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 12:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232847</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/bullbitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/bullbitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Glassnode’s lead analyst said that periods of low market activity are often followed by volatility storms. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Glassnode released its first on-chain video report of 2023 on Tuesday, reviewing what could be data-based indicators of an emerging crypto bull market. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The firm noted that both Bitcoin and Ether’s price and on-chain activity have seen little volatility since the year began – a period like others that have historically preceded “explosive market moves.”</span></p>
<h2>Starting Off Slow</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m5oo9b8Tsr4&amp;ab_channel=glassnode" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">explained</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> by Glassnode’s lead analyst James Check, Bitcoin has been stuck trading within a roughly $550 range since December 17. That’s a mere 3.4% trading range for almost an entire month. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“It really is quite remarkable, and there are very few instances in history where Bitcoin and any digital asset really goes to sleep to this level on a volatility framework,” said Check. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the few times in history when volatility ran lower than its current level, Bitcoin has experienced massive volatility spikes in the aftermath – in both directions. For example, in November 2018, both Bitcoin and Ethereum fell by over 50% after a period of flat trading. Likewise, a similarly slow period was quickly followed by a market rally starting in April 2019 from $4000 to $14,000 within three months. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking at on-chain activity, Check noted that “new address momentum” flipped positive for the first time since May 2021 in the aftermath of FTX’s collapse. This refers to when the monthly average generation of new blockchain addresses flips above the yearly average, indicating relatively high on-chain activity at that time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The analyst believes this may show a reversal in on-chain momentum, similar to what was seen at the beginning of 2019 – but could still fail and go lower. “That’s really a proxy for what’s going on in terms of demand and the userbase,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At present, Bitcoin is facing virtually no fee pressure, meaning there is little demand for block space to process transactions. Meanwhile, the network’s transfer volume has been in “free fall” since the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-locates-5-billion-in-assets-attorney-says-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">FTX</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> collapse, processing roughly $65 billion per day before the collapse and only $5 billion at present. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, large entities transacting in volumes worth $10 million or more have become far less dominant over total volume than they were in 2021 and most of 2022. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“There was a lot of transaction volume going on that was associated with the FTX-Alameda entity, and it is likely that a reasonable chuck of this had something to do with them,” said Check. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Realized Dominance</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The analyst concluded by examining Bitcoin and Ether’s Realized Cap Dominance. The metric compares the total value of Bitcoin and Ether combined based on the last time at which units of those cryptos were transacted and observes Bitcoin and Ether’s share of that pie.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This differs from traditional market cap/ market dominance metrics, which unfairly value certain coins on certain networks. Examples include the many lost Bitcoin believed to belong to Satoshi and unmoved coins from the Ethereum ICO, which many consider unlikely to ever move again. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Check claimed that the magnitude of the drawdown in each coin’s realized cap “provides us with a measuring tool for the magnitude of the prevailing bear market.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At present, there is relatively more realized value flowing into Ethereum than Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin’s Yearly Start May Signal an Incoming Bull Market: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Fully Recovers From FTX Crash: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-fully-recovers-from-ftx-crash-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 09:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233255</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Full_Circle.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Full_Circle.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price completed full circle from the FTX crash over two months ago.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has taken bitcoin just a little over two months to recover from the damages done by the collapse of SBF&#8217;s former crypto empire, as the asset skyrocketed to over $21,000 earlier today.</p>
<p>Most alternative coins saw an equally if not more impressive rally in the past week or so, culminating in double-digit price surges on Friday and early Saturday.</p>
<h2>BTC Topped $21K</h2>
<p>After a violent year, which saw the demise of former crypto giants such as Terra, 3AC, and Celsius, the end of 2022 witnessed the loud and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">rapid debacle of FTX, Alameda Research</a>, and countless firms related to them.</p>
<p>Being some of the most prominent names in the industry up to that point, their crash resulted in massive price drops for the entire market. Bitcoin dropped from over $21,000 to under $16,000 in days. It spent the following weeks around the latter with brief attempts to recover some ground but to no avail.</p>
<p>It was at the start of the new year that the cryptocurrency finally saw some relief and broke above $17,000 earlier this week. This turned out to be a key moment as BTC kept climbing and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-tests-20k-as-end-of-week-rally-continues/" data-wpel-link="internal">neared $20,000</a> yesterday evening.</p>
<p>The bulls really stepped on the gas at this point and pushed the asset to above $20,000 and even to<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/600m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-skyrockets-to-21k/" data-wpel-link="internal"> just over $21,000</a> earlier today. This meant a full circle for bitcoin from the FTX collapse in roughly two months.</p>
<p>Although BTC has retraced by several hundred dollars since then, it still hovers well above $20,000, and its market capitalization stands close to $400 billion. Its dominance over the alts has exploded in the past 24 hours and is up to 40.8% after being down to 39% last week.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233256" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233256" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233256" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-14-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233256" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SOL Steals the Show</h2>
<p>The altcoins have also been impressive since the start of the year, and the past 24 hours have only solidified this. Solana, for instance, had dumped below $8 at the end of 2022. However, it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-reasons-solana-regained-its-december-losses-in-a-new-year-rally/" data-wpel-link="internal">went on a roll</a> in the following weeks, resulting in a price surge to above $23 earlier today. This meant that the asset almost tripled its USD valuation in about two weeks.</p>
<p>Ethereum skyrocketed to over $1,500 for the first time in months as well. Binance Coin&#8217;s 6% daily increase has helped it to overcome $300.</p>
<p>Green dominates the entire altcoin landscape, with Dogecoin, Polygon, OKB, Polkadot, Tron, and Uniswap posting gains of up to 11% in a day.</p>
<p>Overall, the crypto market cap added $80 billion daily and came inches away from touching the coveted $1 trillion line.</p>
<figure id="attachment_233257" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233257" style="width: 1858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233257" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1858" height="654" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9.jpg 1858w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9-300x106.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9-1024x360.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9-768x270.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9-1536x541.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-9-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1858px) 100vw, 1858px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233257" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-fully-recovers-from-ftx-crash-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Fully Recovers From FTX Crash: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$600M Shorts Liquidated as Bitcoin Skyrockets to $21K</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/600m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-skyrockets-to-21k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233244</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/rocket_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/rocket_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Almost $600 million out of the $650 million in total are short positions. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In one of its most impressive rallies in about a year, bitcoin skyrocketed by double digits, charting a two-month high above $21,000.</p>
<p>Most alternative coins have followed suit, resulting in over $650 million in liquidations on a 24-hour scale, the majority of which were from short positions.</p>
<ul>
<li>It&#8217;s safe to say that the start of the year has been quite favorable for the cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin, for one, stood around $16,500 on January 1. After a quiet first few days, it began to add value and broke above $17,000 earlier this week.</li>
<li>However, that was just the start, as the asset kept breaking into forgotten ground in the following days and finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-tests-20k-as-end-of-week-rally-continues/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached</a> $20,000 late last night.</li>
<li>It continued climbing and jumped to $21,240 (on Bitstamp) for the first time since the FTX collapse unfolded at the beginning of November.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_233245" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-233245" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-233245" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-13-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-233245" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li>Several altcoins have skyrocketed even more in the past 24 hours. Solana has stolen the show with a massive 40% rally, driving it to a multi-month high of its own at above $23.</li>
<li>Polkadot (20%), Shiba Inu (14%), Ethereum (10.5%), Cardano (11%), Dogecoin (11%), Polygon (10%), and OKB (10%) are just some of the examples of double-digit price gainers.</li>
<li>This has resulted in the overall crypto market cap nearing $1 trillion for the first time in months on CoinMarketCap.</li>
<li>Short traders have felt the pain of this impressive rally, according to CoinGlass. The total value of<a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> liquidated positions</a> in the past day stands at $650 million, but $590 million are from shorts.</li>
<li>More than 110,000 traders have been wrecked in the same timeframe, with the largest single order happening on Huobi, which was worth over $6.5 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/600m-shorts-liquidated-as-bitcoin-skyrockets-to-21k/" rel="nofollow">$600M Shorts Liquidated as Bitcoin Skyrockets to $21K</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
