<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood’s Ark Amends Bitcoin Spot ETF Application To Copy BlackRock</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-amends-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-to-copy-blackrock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 23:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257619</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ARK’s modification may make it the first to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States, beating BlackRock.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood’s ARK Invest has amended its Bitcoin Spot ETF filing to include a new surveillance sharing agreement, taking cues from the filing presented by investment giant BlackRock earlier this month.</p>
<p>The modification may give ARK a better chance of getting its product approved by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), which has denied every flavor of the product thus far.</p>
<h2>ARK’s Crucial Change</h2>
<p>According to ARK’s modified <a href="https://cdn.cboe.com/resources/regulation/rule_filings/pending/2023/SR-CboeBZX-2023-028-Amendment-No-1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">19b-4 filing</a>, the proposal suggests that the Cboe BZX Exchange – on which the Ark’s 21 Shares ETF would be listed – will enter a surveillance sharing agreement (SSA) with “an operator of a United States-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin.”</p>
<p>ARK didn’t name which specific spot exchange it would partner with, but claimed it represented a “substantial portion of US-based Bitcoin trading.”</p>
<p>“ This Spot BTC SSA, in combination with the information available through [Intermarket Surveillance Group] related to CME Bitcoin Futures, which the Exchange believes on its own represents a regulated market of significant size, would further strengthen the Exchange’s ability to detect and deter manipulation of the Shares,” wrote Ark.</p>
<p>The inability to form a sufficient surveillance-sharing agreement related to Bitcoin spot trading is what caused Ark’s last ETF application to be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-the-sec-once-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">rejected</a> in January.</p>
<p>While Ark and other firms – such as Grayscale – have proposed entering this agreement with CME Bitcoin Futures, the SEC claims this market isn’t closely connected enough to spot Bitcoin trading.</p>
<p>Ark stood by its defense for using CME Bitcoin Futures, arguing that other ETFs have been approved for commodities that use their relevant CME futures market as a “regulated market of significant size.” Furthermore, many of these commodity and currency-based ETFs had unregulated spot markets, including for gold, silver, platinum, palladium, and copper.</p>
<h2>BlackRock’s Filing</h2>
<p>BlackRock’s own <a href="https://listingcenter.nasdaq.com/assets/rulebook/NASDAQ/filings/SR-NASDAQ-2023-016.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">19-b4 filing</a> included the same passage as Ark about its respective stock exchange, Nasdaq, entering an SSA with a spot Bitcoin exchange in the United States.</p>
<p>According to Bloomberg ETF analyst Eric Balchunas, Ark’s filing puts the firm in a position to be approved before Blackrock, since it filed first.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This adds another twist to the plot bc SEC decision due on this in August, if they delay it is bad sign for approval unless, they delay and then approve BlackRock, which shows favoritism. Grayscale decision announcement also plays into timing of all this. GRAB THE POPCORN.</p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1674057257565208576?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Balchunas added that BlackRock may have prevented Coinbase from participating in Ark’s SSA, since the investment giant is already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with Coinbase for its own product.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-amends-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-to-copy-blackrock/" rel="nofollow">Cathie Wood’s Ark Amends Bitcoin Spot ETF Application To Copy BlackRock</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum-Based DeFi Project Chibi Finance Rug Pulled: Over $1 Million Drained</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arbitrum-based-defi-project-chibi-finance-rug-pulled-over-1-million-drained/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257344</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The CHIBI token nosedived by 99.4% since the incident. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In yet another case of a rug pull, Arbitrum-based Chibi Finance reportedly siphoned more than $1 million worth of various crypto assets. Notably, the protocol went live on Tuesday, but the developers managed to launder the stolen funds to other networks shortly after.</p>
<ul>
<li>On-chain analysis conducted by blockchain security platform CertiK <a href="https://twitter.com/CertiKAlert/status/1673639936631734272" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that Chibi devs deployed a malicious contract that enabled them to steal user funds from the protocol&#8217;s smart contracts.</li>
<li>These funds were then sold for 555 Ether and <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1673615238758006786" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">transferred</a> from Arbitrum to Ethereum on the same day, as per another security firm PeckShield, before being funneled to the coin mixing service Tornado Cash to conceal transaction trails.</li>
<li>Following the rug pull, Chibi Finance&#8217;s Twitter and Telegram profiles were disabled, and the website was deleted.</li>
<li>CertiK said that the latest exit scam is the 12th incident the platform recorded on Arbitrum in 2023.</li>
<li>A series of exit scams have emerged on Arbitrum as well as the wider Ethereum Layer 2 ecosystem recently, with the most recent being Swaprum.</li>
<li>As reported earlier, the developers behind the decentralized exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swaprum-dex-drained-in-3m-crypto-rugpull/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">drained</a> $3 million worth of Ether from the protocol.</li>
<li>A recent report by Beosin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-rug-pull-losses-outpaced-defi-exploits-in-may-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the total amount of crypto assets lost to exit scams and rug pulls exceeded the amount pilfered from decentralized finance projects through exploits and attacks last month.</li>
<li>More than $45 million of crypto assets were stolen via rug pulls in May across six incidents, while other exploits in DeFi amounted to $19.6 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arbitrum-based-defi-project-chibi-finance-rug-pulled-over-1-million-drained/" rel="nofollow">Arbitrum-Based DeFi Project Chibi Finance Rug Pulled: Over $1 Million Drained</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Combining the Incongruous: From Cryptocurrencies to Organics with Cannafarm</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/combining-the-incongruous-from-cryptocurrencies-to-organics-with-cannafarm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257606</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cannafarm_cover.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/cannafarm_cover.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[For the last couple of decades, we have been fighting a number of ecological challenges that threaten human health and well-being: polluted air, water poisoned with runoff, and pesticides on foods are real dangers. Sometimes it feels like technological and scientific advancement is poorly matched with a move toward more organic, natural, and healthier products. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the last couple of decades, we have been fighting a number of ecological challenges that threaten human health and well-being: polluted air, water poisoned with runoff, and pesticides on foods are <em>real dangers</em>.</p>
<p>Sometimes it feels like technological and scientific advancement is poorly matched with a move toward more organic, natural, and healthier products. Each attempt only contaminates the environment more.</p>
<p>Well, this is no longer true. The Cannafarm company has managed to combine two things that, at first glance, seem incompatible: the newest technology and nature, cryptocurrencies, and the most advanced equipment. Organically pure <em>medical grade cannabis</em>.</p>
<p>Now you can be a part of this project, not only to get dividends via your investment but to help produce medicines made of natural components, which are vitally important for the future of medicine.</p>
<h2>How Cannafarm Operates</h2>
<p>Cannafarm has established its own organic, <em>eco-friendly</em> medical cannabis plantations in 9 countries worldwide using <strong><em>safe</em></strong>, accelerated cultivation techniques.</p>
<p>Today, the efforts of automated equipment and over 2,000 specialists on these plantations produce year-round harvests, which become the basis for pharmaceuticals such as:</p>
<p>&#8211; Dronabinol and Nabilone, used as antiemetics for patients being treated with chemotherapy;</p>
<p>&#8211; Nabiximols, used as a painkiller for patients with cancer and neuropathic pain;</p>
<p>&#8211; Epidiolex, which is effective as an anticonvulsant for patients with epilepsy.</p>
<p>All of these medications have been clinically tested. They are approved in many European countries and have successfully been used in evidence-based medicine.</p>
<h2>How do Cryptocurrencies Fit In?</h2>
<p>If you want to be part of Cannafarm&#8217;s company, then you can join and choose one of the company&#8217;s investment plans. Raised oney goes to expand the production and sponsorship of research and development work, while profits are generated through the distribution of organic raw materials to pharmaceutical manufacturers.</p>
<p>Users can invest as little as $50 and potentially enjoy up to 15% monthly income in cryptocurrencies. The digital assets for deposit and interest income make investments in Cannafarm accessible to residents of many countries and especially attractive to cryptocurrency enthusiasts. <em>Five different cryptocurrencies</em> are available: Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, Binance Coin, and USDT.</p>
<p>This is not just a way to invest in the field of organic herbal components but also a way to help popularize cryptocurrency as an ecological sector by taking this tool into various business spheres, including the medical and healthcare sectors. Today It is already possible for anyone to join <a href="https://cannafarm.ltd/?refsysis=potato@cryptopotato.com" rel="nofollow sponsored noopener" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Cannafarm</a>.</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/combining-the-incongruous-from-cryptocurrencies-to-organics-with-cannafarm/" rel="nofollow">Combining the Incongruous: From Cryptocurrencies to Organics with Cannafarm</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>VC Firm Paradigm Remains Interested in Crypto and AI</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vc-firm-paradigm-remains-interested-in-crypto-and-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 20:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paradigm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257424</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/paradigm_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/paradigm_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["We’ve never been more excited about crypto and we continue to invest," Huang said. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paradigm’s co-founder &#8211; Matt Huang &#8211; said the company “has never been more dedicated to crypto.”</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The venture capital firm has been involved in the industry for years by making substantial investments and leading numerous fundraisers.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">’Excited About Crypto’ </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Huang <a href="https://twitter.com/matthuang/status/1673786399252955137" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">assured</a> in a new post on Twitter that Paradigm remains committed to the cryptocurrency sector. The VC giant will continue “to invest across all stages, publish original research, help portfolio companies develop mechanisms, ship open source projects, advocate for good policy, and more.” </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also said that Paradigm is interested in the advancement of artificial intelligence (AI). </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">”We’re also a group of curious nerds, and the developments in AI are too interesting to ignore.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exec opposed the thesis that crypto vs. AI is a zero-sum competition. The latter is a popular term in finance, describing a business deal where one person’s gain is another one&#8217;s loss.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">”It seems trendy to frame crypto vs. AI as a zero-sum competition. But we don’t buy it. Both are interesting and will have plenty of overlap. We’re excited to continue exploring,” he concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paradigm’s Crypto Efforts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of Paradigm’s first major interactions with the sector occurred in 2019 when it invested as much as $1 million in Uniswap. It was also among the financial backers of the latter’s <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2022/10/13/uniswap-labs-raises-165-million-in-new-funding/?guccounter=1&amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAGH1gf2JqySvomtyTgtzx9QqusiZUrKkO6sawUUg2002ChmdSxeBFZ9w1xeSuYj1a63xgt3F-CyZShG39xcBa0OQhbkac0ZA-hmyZoIZib1OV983jogPX_woUnvq6EOFlfv8wZcoHKlIao9KdyAupXcekxjnNuY9-buxlDHu2SDF" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$165 million fundraiser</a> in 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The VC firm made the headlines during the bull market of 2021 when it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-co-founder-led-paradigm-announces-2-5b-bombshell-venture-fund/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> a whopping $2.5 billion fund to further invest in the digital asset industry. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Paradigm also had a hand in the launch of the new cryptocurrency exchange EDX Markets. It put its name in the list of prominent companies that financially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-backed-cryptocurrency-exchange-edx-goes-live/" data-wpel-link="internal">supported</a> the marketplace, such as Fidelity Digital Assets, Citadel Securities, Sequoia Capital, Charles Schwab, and Virtu Financial.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Alongside its successful efforts, Paradigm was caught up in the FTX domino effect due to its previous engagement with the now-bankrupt exchange. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It lost over $270 million following the demise. Co-Founder Huang </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/matthuang/status/1592595241453776896" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> he feels “shocked” by the event, arguing it will prompt firms and individuals to investigate more before distributing funds to projects.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several months later, Paradigm, Sequoia Capital, Thoma Bravo, and other finance giants with exposure to FTX were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sequoia-capital-paradigm-thoma-bravo-accused-of-promoting-the-legitimacy-of-ftx-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> of popularizing the trading venue in a marketing campaign in 2021. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vc-firm-paradigm-remains-interested-in-crypto-and-ai/" rel="nofollow">VC Firm Paradigm Remains Interested in Crypto and AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin Introduces Mandatory KYC Checks For All Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kucoin-introduces-mandatory-kyc-checks-for-all-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bybit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257534</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/KuCoin_Metaverse.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/KuCoin_Metaverse.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The KYC status will have no affect on fund withdrawals. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seychelles-based crypto exchange KuCoin is pushing for mandatory KYC upgrades as its competitors face regulatory challenges across various jurisdictions.</p>
<p>In a bid to embrace global compliance requirements, KuCoin announced an upgrade of its KYC authentication rules and systems from next month onwards.</p>
<h2>Beefing Up KYC Measures</h2>
<p>The new rules mandate all newly registered users to complete KYC starting July 15 to access KuCoin&#8217;s full suite of products and services to ensure a &#8220;high level of accountability and transparency&#8221; within the platform. Existing users failing to complete the KYC process will be offered limited access to certain features, the company said in a <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20230628022769/en/KuCoin-Introduces-Compulsory-KYC-in-Move-to-Embrace-Regulation" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>.</p>
<p>As such, spot trading sell orders, futures trading deleveraging, margin trading deleveraging, KuCoin Earn redemption, and ETF redemption will be accessible, but deposit services will be unavailable for users with non-KYC status. Fund withdrawals, on the other hand, will remain unaffected.</p>
<p>KuCoin CEO Johnny Lyu said that the platform has been closely monitoring digital asset policies of various countries and compliance requirements. He went on to add,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the development of the cryptocurrency industry, crypto has gradually moved from a geek towards mass adoption. However, this process has also brought about certain security issues concerning on-chain assets. In light of this, KuCoin has strengthened our KYC system to comply with regulatory requirements worldwide and better protect the asset security of all cryptocurrency users through enhanced KYC rules.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>KuCoin isn&#8217;t the only one to roll out mandatory KYC checks in a move to embrace regulation. Dubai-headquartered Bybit also stepped up to reduce risks associated with users&#8217; accounts by <a href="https://www.bybit.com/en-US/help-center/s/article/Individual-KYC-FAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">introducing</a> compulsory KYC verification for both new and existing users.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Alleged KYC Faux Pas</h2>
<p>The push for KYC comes amid heightened regulatory scrutiny against crypto giant Binance whose employees and &#8220;angels&#8221; were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-employees-trained-users-to-bypass-kyc-and-aml-rules-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> to have allegedly helped users evade KYC and AML controls earlier this year. This sparked concerns about Binance’s ability to comply with regulations. The exchange issued a statement saying that it was investigating the report shortly after.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kucoin-introduces-mandatory-kyc-checks-for-all-users/" rel="nofollow">KuCoin Introduces Mandatory KYC Checks For All Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will Bitcoin Surge to $35K in July? Matrixport Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-surge-to-35k-in-july-matrixport-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257560</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The report said that Bitcoin's year-end target is $45,000. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin surging past the $31,000 psychological level was crucial in many ways. For one, the world&#8217;s premier cryptocurrency hit a one-year high amidst the incessant bear market.</p>
<p>But the gains may not stop here. Historically, July has been a month for strong rallies, according to the digital asset platform Matrixport.</p>
<ul>
<li>In its latest <a href="https://twitter.com/realMatrixport/status/1673897657096630272" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">analysis</a>, Bitcoin bulls are gearing up for the &#8220;seasonal surge&#8221; as prices tend to rally in July.</li>
<li>Throughout the last decade, Matrixport observed that the crypto-asset has rallied by an average of more than 11% in the month. Interestingly, 7 out of 10 observations showed positive returns (70%).</li>
<li>Moreover, the previous three Julys have seen returns of over 27%, 20%, and 24%, respectively.</li>
<li>The report also noted that summer typically marks a period of consolidation for Bitcoin. However, a strong July tends to be followed by a mediocre August and a sell-off in September.</li>
<li>As per the firm&#8217;s year-end target of $45,000, Bitcoin price is speculated to rally towards $35,000 before encountering a selling-off session and ultimately retracing to $30,000 before attempting another crucial resistance point of $40,000.</li>
<li>The latest surge came after BlackRock <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-blackrock-two-more-asset-managers-file-to-launch-a-btc-etf-in-the-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> an application for a spot Bitcoin ETF, followed by Invesco and WisdomTree, which refiled their submissions.</li>
<li>The ETF filings demonstrated the commitment of high-profile institutional investors to the digital asset space, thereby raising <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1673823232745680896" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">expectations</a> of an institutionally driven price rally.</li>
<li>Furthermore, Glassnode <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1674051382423216128" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> that the &#8216;Bitcoin Illiquid Supply Change&#8217; metric continued to hover extremely elevated near cycle highs depicting the prominence of &#8216;hodling&#8217; despite a surge in price.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-surge-to-35k-in-july-matrixport-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Will Bitcoin Surge to $35K in July? Matrixport Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sony Strengthens Web3 Foothold With $3.5M Seed Funding in Startale Labs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sony-strengthens-web3-foothold-with-3-5m-seed-funding-in-startale-labs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257458</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/0025627.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/0025627.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The latest capital partnership is aimed at building a global infrastructure to advance web3 adoption.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sony&#8217;s wholly-owned subsidiary &#8211; Sony Network Communications &#8211; has injected $3.5 million in a seed round for Singapore Web3 tech giant, Startale Labs in addition to yet another strategic collaboration. The deal was conducted via a private placement of new shares and did not have any other investors.</p>
<p>Both firms have announced appointing Jun Watanabe, President and Representative Director of Sony Network Communications Inc., as a director of Startale Labs as part of the partnership.</p>
<h2>Sony&#8217;s Capital Partnership</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://startale.org/blog/startale-and-sony-network-communications-form-capital-38815" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, Startale Labs and Sony Network Communications plan on working towards setting up the necessary infrastructure to back the global adoption of Web3 with the help of the latter&#8217;s &#8220;extensive knowledge and experience&#8221; in creating crucial solutions across telecommunications and other sectors.</p>
<p>Besides, the new capital infusion will be poured into hiring new talent for the development of products and services across the Web3 space. Jun Watanabe, President, and Representative Director of Sony Network Communications Inc., was quoted saying,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With this capital partnership, we are merging Startale Labs’ knowledge and technical capabilities in Web3 with the experience and business fields cultivated by Sony Network Communications to create the infrastructure necessary to facilitate global Web3 adoption. We believe this partnership will contribute to the creation of new killer Web3 use cases and deliver unprecedented levels of value.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The move is part of Startale&#8217;s broader mission to create &#8220;Web3 for Billions,&#8221; which it aims to achieve by facilitating users and businesses in Japan to embrace blockchain technology, the Web3 startup&#8217;s official statement read.</p>
<h2>Sony&#8217;s Web3 Boost</h2>
<p>The subsidiary of the Japanese tech and entertainment giant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sony-network-and-astar-network-to-co-host-a-web3-incubation-program/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">tapped</a> Polkadot’s innovation hub &#8211; Astar Network &#8211; to host incubation programs jointly with Startale Labs for Web3 advancement in February this year.</p>
<p>The initiative focused on offering tech support, resources, and financial assistance for projects in the Web 3 spectrum looking to generate viability for non-fungible tokens (NFTs) as well as decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs).</p>
<p>The Web3 incubation program was slated for mid-March to mid-June, for any users interested across the globe.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sony-strengthens-web3-foothold-with-3-5m-seed-funding-in-startale-labs/" rel="nofollow">Sony Strengthens Web3 Foothold With $3.5M Seed Funding in Startale Labs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can PEPE Be the Next Shiba Inu? Analyst Chips In While Wall Street Memes Dominates</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cana-pepe-be-the-next-shiba-inu-analyst-chips-in-while-wall-street-memes-dominates/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257586</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_pepe_cover-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_pepe_cover-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Pepe ($PEPE) is back in the green after the token&#8217;s price soared nearly 100% last week. With investors now scrambling to buy $PEPE before the next upwards push, market commentators are deliberating whether the token can move past Shiba Inu ($SHIB) – and even rival Dogecoin ($DOGE) However, it&#8217;s not just Pepe making moves, with [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pepe ($PEPE) is back in the green after the token&#8217;s price soared nearly 100% last week.</p>
<p>With investors now scrambling to buy $PEPE before the next upwards push, market commentators are deliberating whether the token can move past Shiba Inu ($SHIB) – and even rival Dogecoin ($DOGE)</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s not just Pepe making moves, with trailblazing meme coin Wall Street Memes ($WSM) continuing to turn heads during its ongoing presale phase.</p>
<h2>Huge $PEPE Trading Volume Fuels Speculation of $SHIB Takeover</h2>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">reveals</a> that the total $PEPE trading volume hit $167 million in the past 24 hours – 51% higher than the $SHIB trading volume.</p>
<p>This metric highlights just how popular $PEPE really is and adds credence to the hypothesis that the token could take the number two spot in the meme coin market.</p>
<p>For this to happen, $PEPE would need to exceed Shiba Inu’s $4.3 billion market cap – which means the token would have to more than 7x in size from its current position.</p>
<p>Although this might seem like a tall order, many market commentators believe it could be possible.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257590" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-21.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="328" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-21-300x163.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-21-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>In fact, just last month, crypto analyst cryptunez <a href="https://twitter.com/cryptunez/status/1655758974673727488?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">tweeted</a> that he “fully expects” $PEPE to flip $SHIB within one year.</p>
<p>Additionally, YouTuber Crypto Millie released a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HKhggchmaHo&amp;pp=ygUOcGVwZSBzaGliYSBpbnU%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video analysis</a> of $PEPE, speculating that the token could surpass $SHIB’s valuation before 2025.</p>
<p>However, even though some analysts are highly bullish on $PEPE’s prospects, it’s unlikely that the token could rival Dogecoin anytime soon.</p>
<p>Dogecoin&#8217;s market cap is nearly 15 times larger than Pepe&#8217;s – meaning the latter&#8217;s tokenomics would have to drastically change for it to topple $DOGE&#8217;s dominance.</p>
<h2>Pepe Comeback Shows No Signs of Stopping as NFT Sales Skyrocket</h2>
<p>Regardless, $PEPE is undoubtedly back on the right track following a period of sustained bearish momentum.</p>
<p>The token’s comeback has inspired an array of new meme coins to enter the market and attempt to mirror $PEPE’s returns.</p>
<p>Pepe 2.0, the latest competitor to $PEPE’s throne, has burst onto the scene in the past 24 hours – generating over $10.8 million worth of trading volume, per CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-28.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257589" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-28.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="180" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-28.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-28-300x90.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-28-50x15.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Although Pepe 2.0 has no actual use cases, the token has still benefited from the speculative nature of the crypto market and the vast community interest in $PEPE.</p>
<p>However, the good news for $PEPE holders is that these copycat coins are ultimately reinforcing the popularity and appeal of the original meme coin.</p>
<p>Another factor playing into $PEPE&#8217;s comeback is the recent launch of Pepe Elementals – a brand-new NFT collection hosted on the Ethereum blockchain.</p>
<p><a href="https://opensea.io/collection/pepe-elementals" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">According</a> to OpenSea, 104 ETH worth of these NFTs has exchanged hands in the past day, equating to a remarkable $192,631.</p>
<h2>Which Other Meme Coins Could Dominate the Market?</h2>
<p>Alongside $PEPE, several other meme coins are emerging and vying for market dominance.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes, a new project inspired by the WallStreetBets Reddit movement, is one of these meme coins – and has now raised nearly $11 million in early funding.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Presale Stirs Investor Excitement After Raising Nearly $11m</h2>
<p>At the time of writing, <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is in Stage 19 of its 30-stage presale phase, meaning nearly two-thirds of the token allocation has already been snapped up.</p>
<p>Investors worldwide have been coming in droves to get their hands on $WSM tokens, given that they&#8217;re being offered at a discounted price relative to the future CEX listing price.</p>
<p>Not only that, but investors have also been clamoring to participate in Wall Street Meme&#8217;s airdrop event – which will see $50,000 worth of $WSM split between five lucky winners.</p>
<p>To participate in this event, investors must join the <a href="https://discord.com/invite/4E538pzeGX" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">official Discord server</a> and complete several social media-related tasks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-26.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257588" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-26.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="364" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-26.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-26-300x181.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-26-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This airdrop event has contributed to the buzz around Wall Street Memes, which has already reached fever pitch.</p>
<p>Twitter influencer Crypto Jamie has <a href="https://twitter.com/RealCryptoJamie" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">become</a> a brand ambassador, while nearly 10,000 people have opted to join the Wall Street Memes <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a>.</p>
<p>These factors provide a solid foundation for price growth once $WSM is launched on exchanges in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Although there’s no telling where price could go, the signs are already there that $WSM could rival $PEPE in the meme coin market during the latter half of 2023.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cana-pepe-be-the-next-shiba-inu-analyst-chips-in-while-wall-street-memes-dominates/" rel="nofollow">Can PEPE Be the Next Shiba Inu? Analyst Chips In While Wall Street Memes Dominates</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is XRP In Trouble or Will The Bulls Finally Reclaim $0.5 For Good? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/is-xrp-in-trouble-or-will-the-bulls-finally-reclaim-0-5-for-good-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 14:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257555</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price has remained relatively stagnant, displaying minimal fluctuations within a narrow range for the past couple of weeks. However, the BTC-paired chart offers a more intriguing perspective. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: The price of Ripple has been consolidating above the 50-day moving average against USDT, which is located around $0.48, after [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price has remained relatively stagnant, displaying minimal fluctuations within a narrow range for the past couple of weeks. However, the BTC-paired chart offers a more intriguing perspective.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>The price of Ripple has been consolidating above the 50-day moving average against USDT, which is located around $0.48, after facing rejection at the $0.6 resistance level once again.</p>
<p>A potential breakdown of the 50-day moving average may lead to a decline toward the $0.43 support level, accompanied by the 200-day moving average.</p>
<p>If these support levels are breached, there is a likelihood of a significant drop towards the $0.3 range. However, it is premature to adopt such a pessimistic outlook, as there remains a possibility for a price rebound and another attempt at testing the $0.6 level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257558" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257558" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257558 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2806231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257558" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</strong></h3>
<p>The price of Ripple against BTC has been experiencing a continuous decline in recent weeks.</p>
<p>Both the 200-day and 50-day moving averages have been breached downward, with the price currently testing the support level at 1500 SAT.</p>
<p>If there is a rebound from the support zone, the initial targets for XRP would be the converging 200-day and 50-day moving averages around the 1800 SAT resistance level.</p>
<p>Additionally, the RSI indicator suggests an oversold condition, implying the potential for a short-term pullback or rebound.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257558" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257558" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257558 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2806232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-Jun-28-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257558" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-xrp-in-trouble-or-will-the-bulls-finally-reclaim-0-5-for-good-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Is XRP In Trouble or Will The Bulls Finally Reclaim $0.5 For Good? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Collaborates With Georgia to Place the Country as a Global Blockchain Hub</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-collaborates-with-georgia-to-place-the-country-as-a-global-blockchain-hub/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 13:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257494</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Georgia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Georgia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The partners will create a designated fund for local startups to support the advancement of blockchain technology in the region.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether &#8211; the company behind the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin USDT &#8211; signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with Georgia&#8217;s government.</p>
<p>The partnership reinforces the firm&#8217;s position as &#8220;a pioneering infrastructure partner for cities and nations globally&#8221; and will assist the country in its effort to become a global center for blockchain technology.</p>
<h2>Georgia Strengthens its Position in the Crypto World</h2>
<p>According to a document seen by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the signed collaboration could positively affect both Tether and Georgia. Paolo Ardoino &#8211; CTO of the stablecoin-issuer &#8211; described the move as &#8220;a significant milestone&#8221; that could help his organization in its goal to diversify its offerings.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With a deep understanding of the potential of cryptocurrencies, Tether aims to empower cities and facilitate the adoption of blockchain technologies such as bitcoin as well as peer-to-peer technology solutions such as Keet and Holepunch,&#8221; he added.</p></blockquote>
<p>At the same time, the Memorandum of Understanding will focus on the establishment of a thriving startup ecosystem in Georgia and stimulate the country&#8217;s push in the world of crypto. Both Tether and the government of Georgia praised the nation&#8217;s high quality of life and favorable working conditions that could attract international investments.</p>
<p>Irakli Nadareishvili &#8211; Deputy Minister of Economy and Sustainable Development &#8211; said Tether is interested in investing in the region. As such, the company will introduce a fund for domestic startups to assist in the development of blockchain technology and position Georgia as a leader in the field.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We also agreed on cooperation in the educational field regarding blockchain technology, which will contribute to the development of local blockchain technologies in the country, as well as the introduction of companies operating in this sector in Georgia,” – the official revealed.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Tether&#8217;s Participation in Lugano</h2>
<p>Besides its involvement in Georgia, the company has previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-city-lugano-to-make-bitcoin-and-tether-its-official-de-facto-currency/" data-wpel-link="internal">shaken hands</a> with the authorities of the Swiss city of Lugano.</p>
<p>The deal, inked last year, aimed to scale the town&#8217;s blockchain capabilities and make Bitcoin (BTC) and USDT legal tender in the area.</p>
<p>CTO Ardoino praised the initiative, highlighting the success El Salvador had after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-months-later-bitcoin-now-officially-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">declaring</a> the primary cryptocurrency official payment method inside its borders:</p>
<blockquote><p>“El Salvador’s GDP increased by 10% and its tourism by 30% after declaring Bitcoin a legal tender. Imagine what we can do in a city at the center of Europe.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-collaborates-with-georgia-to-place-the-country-as-a-global-blockchain-hub/" rel="nofollow">Tether Collaborates With Georgia to Place the Country as a Global Blockchain Hub</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
