<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Marathon Digital Mined 21% Less BTC in June due to Extreme Weather Conditions in Texas</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/marathon-digital-mined-21-less-btc-in-june-due-to-extreme-weather-conditions-in-texas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 21:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258911</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BitcoinMarathon.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BitcoinMarathon.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The organization has increased its BTC production level by almost 600% year-over-year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the leading cryptocurrency mining companies &#8211; Marathon Digital &#8211; produced 979 BTC in June, 21% less than the 1,245 BTC mined in May.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As of the end of last month, the company owned 12,538 BTC, making it one of the biggest corporate holders of the primary digital asset.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The June Figures</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US-based BTC miner </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/07/05/2699990/0/en/Marathon-Digital-Holdings-Announces-Bitcoin-Production-and-Mining-Operation-Updates-for-June-2023.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the extremely hot weather in Texas last month and the emergence of Ordinals, which &#8220;significantly increased transaction fees,&#8221; have negatively impacted the bitcoin production.</span></p>
<p>Recall that temperatures in the Lone Star State exceeded 35 degrees (Celsius) during the second part of June, which <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-06-27/extreme-heat-causes-texas-bitcoin-miners-to-cut-back-video" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">caused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> some local cryptocurrency mining firms to temporarily halt activities to preserve the electricity network.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the reduced production, CEO Fred Thiel explained that Marathon Digital increased its operational hash rate by 16% month-over-month to 17.7 exahashes and its installed hash rate to 21.8 exahashes.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The final steps to achieving our 23 EH/s goal are in Ellendale, ND, and Garden City, TX. The final building in Ellendale is expected to come online this month, and final Garden City tie-in is also expected within that same period,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company also added 18,500 BTC miners at Applied Digital&#8217;s facilities in Ellendale, North Dakota, thus increasing the total fleet to 149,900 machines. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Marathon Digital usually sticks to a HODL strategy. However, it parted with 700 BTC in June and displayed intentions to sell more of its assets in the future &#8220;to support monthly operations, manage its treasury, and for general corporate purposes.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As of the end of last month, the firm had 12,538 BTC (equaling over $385 million at current prices). It ended June with $113.7 million in unrestricted cash and cash equivalents on its balance sheet.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Big Success in Q1</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Marathon Digital experienced operational difficulties throughout 2022, prompted by the prolonged bear market, massive storms, and exposure to the distressed data center – Compute North.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, it started the new year on the right foot, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/marathon-digital-announces-a-record-bitcoin-production-in-q1-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">mining</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 2,195 BTC during the first quarter (significantly more than the 1,259 BTC mined in Q1, 2022).</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;During the first quarter of 2023, we made notable progress executing our two primary initiatives for the year, which are to energize our previously purchased mining rigs to reach our target of 23 exahashes by the middle of this year and to optimize our performance so that we are both more effective and more efficient.&#8221; – CEO Thiel stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Marathon Digital also reduced its debt by $50 million and terminated its credit facilities with the collapsed Silvergate Bank during Q1.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/marathon-digital-mined-21-less-btc-in-june-due-to-extreme-weather-conditions-in-texas/" rel="nofollow">Marathon Digital Mined 21% Less BTC in June due to Extreme Weather Conditions in Texas</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>British Man Lost $100K in a Crypto Scam but There was a Happy End (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/british-man-lost-100k-in-a-crypto-scam-but-there-was-a-happy-end-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259023</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As in other previous cases, the man's investment was initially successful before plunging to zero.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Simon Hoadley &#8211; a 66-year-old retired financial advisor who lives in East Sussex, the UK &#8211; has reportedly become a victim of a &#8220;horrendous&#8221; cryptocurrency scam that drained nearly $100,000 from him.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fortunately, legal experts managed to recover nearly all the lost funds.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scammers Have No Mercy</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/money/retired-financial-advisor-lost-80000-30395486" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Mirror, Hoadley was looking to earn some extra money during the COVID-19 pandemic as his dad was dying from cancer, whereas his wife was living in a care home. At that point, he was contacted by a company that claimed to be comprised of investment specialists and advised him to distribute his savings into digital currencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hoadley agreed, and he saw a return on his investment at first. However, the person he was in touch with stopped replying to him at one point while his portfolio started rapidly declining. In the aftermath, the man handed more than $100,000 to the wrongdoers. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It was horrendous. My dad was dying of cancer, and I was living alone because my wife is in a care facility three hours away,&#8221; Hoadley said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Once realizing he had been lured, he went to his local bank to find a way to get his money back. The financial institution urged him to reveal everything to his family because the case could not have been resolved without the police&#8217;s efforts.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;ve got four grown-up children who were devastated when they found out. They had always looked up to me, but over a year, I just completely changed. It was really tough for them to see,&#8221; Hoadly stated. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlike other previous scams, which resulted in total losses for investors, the legal experts managed to return over $95,000 of the sum to the man. Hoadley said he used the money to buy a mobile home close to where his wife lives.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Such Cases in the UK</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United Kingdom has recently turned into a hotbed for cryptocurrency scams, with some people losing significant amounts of funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A British man, whose name was not disclosed, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/love-hurts-british-man-loses-200k-in-a-bitcoin-romance-scam-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">parted with</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $200,000 after a woman portraying herself as a successful cryptocurrency investor with &#8220;inside knowledge&#8221; conned him. She also told him they could build a wealthy lifestyle together with the promised profits from the dubious investment. The man was so devastated after the loss that he even contemplated committing suicide.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I recognized I needed help straight away and went straight round to see my mum. If I didn&#8217;t have that support, I wouldn&#8217;t be here. I was going to do something that wouldn&#8217;t leave me here anymore,&#8221; he revealed.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another woman who lives in Nottinghamshire </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-woman-lost-over-200k-in-a-crypto-romance-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the same sum after an unfamiliar man who introduced himself as a US Army surgeon urged her to transfer him funds in a particular bitcoin wallet so he could end his contract and unite with her. As it turned out, it was simply a romance scam, and the scammer never arrived.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The local police teamed up with the woman&#8217;s bank and managed to restore more than half of the lost money. Still, the pensioner urged others to be utterly careful when dating online. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/british-man-lost-100k-in-a-crypto-scam-but-there-was-a-happy-end-report/" rel="nofollow">British Man Lost $100K in a Crypto Scam but There was a Happy End (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As Race for Spot BTC ETF Hots Up, CEO Cathie Wood Says Ark Invest is First in the Queue</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-race-for-spot-btc-etf-hots-up-ceo-cathie-wood-says-ark-invest-is-first-in-the-queue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259265</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Refiled applications boast a surveillance-sharing agreement that allows sharing of trading, clearing, and identity details with the regulators. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The first Bitcoin ETF application was filed way back in 2013 by Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss. However, the US regulators have not approved any such application to date. </span></p>
<p>But now, they are seemingly under tremendous pressure, with some of the biggest players in traditional finance throwing their hats in the ring.</p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Race for BTC ETF Hots Up </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the latest, the world’s largest fund manager &#8211; BlackRock &#8211; filed on June 15 for a spot Bitcoin investment trust fund through iShares, the company that manages its family of ETFs. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In less than two weeks, several other companies, including rival asset management giant Fidelity, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">refiled</a> for spot Bitcoin ETFs. The other prominent names include Invesco, WisdomTree, Valkyrie Investments, and VanEck. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">These companies have tried to address the SEC’s concerns, as reflected in the regulator&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase. For example, the BlackRock application features a surveillance-sharing clause, a first for spot Bitcoin ETF applications. Ten days after the SEC’s lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase, BlackRock added a surveillance-sharing clause to its application. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Under the surveillance-sharing agreement, the fund manager will share trading, clearing, and customer identity details with the regulators to avoid fraud and manipulation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, news reports hinted that the SEC found BlackRock’s application inadequate and lacking specific details. Subsequently, the asset manager refiled the application stating that it had appointed Coinbase as its surveillance <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-btc-etf-filing-could-democratize-crypto-ceo-larry-fink-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">partner</a>.   </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ark Invest, which filed its spot Bitcoin ETF application with the investment company 21Shares in April, amended its filing on June 28 to add a surveillance-sharing clause. Ark Invest is also likely to have Coinbase as its surveillance-sharing partner. </span></p>
<p>The soaring interest of big players in spot BTC ETF has galvanized the entire crypto market, with BTC maintaining its price of around $30K.</p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ark Invest First in Line: CEO Cathie Wood</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Now, if the SEC grants the green light, whose application it will approve first is being debated. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cathie Wood, CEO of ARK Investment, argued that her company is first in the line if the SEC approval comes, Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-26/cathie-wood-s-ark-says-it-s-first-in-line-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-btc#xj4y7vzkg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>. She said the agency can take up to mid-January for Ark Invest&#8217;s and up to March for Black Rock’s spot BTC ETF applications to either approve or reject them. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">But clarity will be available much before when the court delivers its verdict, expected in August, in Grayscale’s lawsuit against the SEC’s decision to reject its spot Bitcoin ETF application.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Grayscale Bitcoin ETF proposes to be fully backed by BTC in cold storage. Wood argued that approving Bitcoin Futures ETF, which involves swaps, and not greenlighting a fully-backed Spot ETF is contradictory.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Considering all these factors, BlackRock has no edge over Ark Invest, the Ark Invest CEO claims. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-race-for-spot-btc-etf-hots-up-ceo-cathie-wood-says-ark-invest-is-first-in-the-queue/" rel="nofollow">As Race for Spot BTC ETF Hots Up, CEO Cathie Wood Says Ark Invest is First in the Queue</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Vs. BTC Companies: What&#8217;s The Better Buy?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-vs-btc-companies-whats-the-better-buy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 11:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259403</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitcoin_Wall_Street.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitcoin_Wall_Street.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Many Bitcoin-adjacent companies are outperforming the asset itself since the start of the year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) has treated its faithful well in 2023, having appreciated over 80% year to date. However, there may be better ways for investors to capitalize on the asset’s success besides stacking actual sats.</p>
<p>Here’s a look at how some Bitcoin-related assets and companies are performing next to BTC, from financial companies to mining stocks.</p>
<h2>Mining Stocks Are Booming</h2>
<p>Shares for multiple publicly traded Bitcoin miners surged on Friday, including CleanSpark (CLSK; 11.32%), Riot Platforms (RIOT; 14.33%), and Hut 8 (HUT; 6.14%). Bitcoin, by contrast, only rose by 1.42%.</p>
<p>This year alone, all three miners have seen their share prices at least triple in value. Rival mining firm Iris Energy, which rose 9.5% on Friday, is up a whopping 48% since January 1.</p>
<p>Miners’ balance sheets and revenue are directly connected to Bitcoin’s price, as such firms receive a fixed number of Bitcoin every ten minutes as newly minted coins from the network.</p>
<p>Many such miners have made <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-firm-riot-secures-33280-mining-rigs-ahead-of-halving/" data-wpel-link="internal">major infrastructure investments</a> this year in preparation for the “halving” – an event that cuts Bitcoin’s network emissions in half and is widely thought to catalyze Bitcoin bull markets.</p>
<p>While the industry’s upside looks promising, it can also encounter even greater downside volatility than BTC. Core Scientific (CORZQ), for example, saw its share price collapse over 80% in a single day in October after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/large-bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-could-file-for-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealing</a> it was not in a position to pay back its debt.</p>
<h2>Exchanges and ETFs</h2>
<p>Another publicly traded firm outpacing Bitcoin this year is Coinbase (COIN) – up 134% YTD. Though the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued the exchange last month, Bitcoin’s positive price action, Coinbase&#8217;s optimistic <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal">Q1 earnings numbers</a>, and a partnership with BlackRock for a planned Bitcoin spot ETF all spell good fortune for the company.</p>
<p>BlackRock’s filing has markets more optimistic that a spot ETF could finally get past the SEC, paving the way for other firms to follow suit.</p>
<p>This makes the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) another enticing buy: Shares for the fund have traded at a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gbtc-discount-narrows-to-27-for-the-first-time-since-may-2022-heres-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">discount</a> well below the value of its underlying Bitcoin for years. However, if its effort to convert into a spot ETF proves successful, that discount will immediately be restored to parity, creating added value for investors. The discount currently stands at 27%.</p>
<p>Until a Bitcoin spot ETF is approved, MicroStrategy (MSTR) is one of the better alternatives that are available, up 162% YTD. The software company – whose balance sheet includes over <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-12333-btc-for-350-million-at-28k-per-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">150,000 BTC</a> – frequently issues stock to buy more Bitcoin, much like an ETF.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-vs-btc-companies-whats-the-better-buy/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Vs. BTC Companies: What&#8217;s The Better Buy?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Shoots Up 12% Daily, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $30K: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-sol-shoots-up-12-daily-bitcoin-btc-maintains-30k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 08:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259418</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Solana_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Solana_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aside from SOL, the other notable gainer from the larger-cap alts is Avalanche (AVAX).]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin went through a volatile end of the week in which it posted a new 13-month high before it slipped under $30,000 but has managed to defend that level.</p>
<p>The altcoins are calmer on a daily scale, aside from SOL, AVAX, LEO, ARB, and a few others, which have added some value.</p>
<h2>BTC Defends $30K</h2>
<p>The past weekend was quite uneventful, even though BTC went through a rollercoaster that drove it from $31,000 to $29,500 and back up to $30,500 in a matter of hours on Friday. Saturday and Sunday, though, were calm, with BTC remaining at just over $30,000.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t until early Tuesday morning when the landscape changed, and BTC pushed above $31,000 once again. It was rejected there, but the bulls went on the offensive once again on Thursday, and this time, they managed to drive bitcoin north to $31,500 (on Bitstamp) for the first time in 13 months.</p>
<p>However, the asset failed there again and plummeted to $29,700 by Friday morning. Nevertheless, it bounced off and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-defends-30k-after-blackrock-refiled-its-spot-bitcoin-etf-application-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">reclaimed</a> the coveted $30,000 in the following hours and has remained just above that line since then.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization still stands at $585 billion, and its dominance over the alternative coins is just shy of 50%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259420" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259420" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259420" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-8-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259420" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SOL, AVAX on the Rise</h2>
<p>The altcoins also experienced enhanced volatility in the past few days, but most have calmed on a daily scale. Ethereum had neared $2,000 at one point but was sharply rejected yesterday and currently stands roughly $150 away from that level.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, Litecoin, Tron, Polkadot, and Polygon are slightly in the green from the larger-cap alts.</p>
<p>Avalanche and Solana have stolen the show with gains of 7.5% and 13%, respectively. As a result, AVAX stands above $13, while SOL is north of $22.</p>
<p>Overall, the cumulative market cap of all crypto assets has managed to reclaim just over $10 billion in a day and sits above $1.8 trillion. Recall that the metric <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-shed-50b-daily-as-btc-dipped-below-30k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">dumped</a> by $50 billion yesterday alone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259421" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259421" style="width: 1882px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259421" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1882" height="790" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.jpg 1882w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-1024x430.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-768x322.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-1536x645.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1882px) 100vw, 1882px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259421" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-sol-shoots-up-12-daily-bitcoin-btc-maintains-30k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Solana (SOL) Shoots Up 12% Daily, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $30K: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prop Firm HyroTrader Is Seeking Talented Crypto Traders</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/prop-firm-hyrotrader-is-seeking-talented-crypto-traders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 07:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259407</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/HyroTrader_funding_1688728906OIBhBF7CuL.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/HyroTrader_funding_1688728906OIBhBF7CuL.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Prague, Czech Republic, July 8th, 2023] Leading proprietary trading firm HyroTrader is actively seeking talented crypto traders to join its team and take advantage of the opportunity to get funded. With a proven track record and a commitment to ongoing success, HyroTrader offers a lucrative platform for traders to showcase their skills, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Prague, Czech Republic, July 8th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Leading proprietary trading firm <a href="https://www.hyrotrader.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">HyroTrader</a> is actively seeking talented crypto traders to join its team and take advantage of the opportunity to get funded. With a proven track record and a commitment to ongoing success, HyroTrader offers a lucrative platform for traders to showcase their skills, earn profits, and advance their trading career.</p>
<p>HyroTrader’s offer is open to crypto traders looking to take their skills to the next level. It provides an opportunity for talented traders to prove their prowess and secure funding to progress.</p>
<p>The journey to becoming a funded trader starts with the HyroTrader Challenge. This rigorous assessment is designed to evaluate the applicant’s trading skills and discipline. The challenge spans 30 days, during which they must demonstrate their ability to achieve a minimum of 10% profit on their initial balance.</p>
<p>The HyroTrader Challenge serves as the gateway to the Verification stage, where traders are given the opportunity to showcase their trading acumen and solidify their path to success. In the Verification stage, traders must achieve a minimum of 20% profit on their initial balance within 60 days to proceed to the final step.</p>
<p>Upon successfully completing the evaluation process, graduates will join the ranks of HyroTrader&#8217;s elite traders as a member of their proprietary trading firm. As a HyroTrader pro, they&#8217;ll have access to a range of benefits and support to fuel their trading journey.</p>
<p><strong>Leverage and Trading Platforms:</strong> Members can enjoy leverage of up to 100x and gain access to popular trading platforms such as Binance, ByBit, and HyroTrade. They can take advantage of cutting-edge trading tools and technologies to execute their trading strategies with precision and efficiency.</p>
<p><strong>Dedicated Support:</strong> Traders benefit from personalized support from HyroTrader&#8217;s dedicated customer service team, available round the clock. They can get their questions answered, receive guidance, and stay informed about the latest market trends and opportunities.</p>
<p><strong>Profit Sharing:</strong> HyroTrader believes in rewarding its traders for their hard work and success. Traders can retain up to 90% of their profits, ensuring that their efforts are duly recognized and financially rewarded.</p>
<p><strong>Weekly Profit Payouts:</strong> Unlike many other prop trading firms, HyroTrader provides traders with weekly profit payouts. This allows them to secure their earnings promptly and reinvest them in their trading activities or personal financial goals.</p>
<p>This recruitment campaign provides an opportunity to join the ranks of successful traders who have propelled their careers to new heights with HyroTrader. Those who seize the chance to demonstrate their trading skills and pass the test can get funded immediately.</p>
<p>For more information, visit the HyroTrader <a href="https://www.hyrotrader.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">website</a> or contact their dedicated team at support@hyrotrader.com</p>
<h2>About HyroTrader</h2>
<p>HyroTrader is a leading crypto proprietary trading firm dedicated to empowering traders and providing them with the resources they need to succeed in the competitive world of cryptocurrency trading. With a rigorous evaluation process, advanced trading platforms, and ongoing support, HyroTrader offers traders an unparalleled opportunity to grow their skills, achieve profitability, and reach their trading goals.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/prop-firm-hyrotrader-is-seeking-talented-crypto-traders/" rel="nofollow">Prop Firm HyroTrader Is Seeking Talented Crypto Traders</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lightning Labs Unveils Toolkit to Enable AI Transact in Bitcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-unveils-toolkit-to-enable-ai-transact-in-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 04:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_lightning_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_lightning_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The tools aim to connect the Bitcoin network with the growing field of AI.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hype surrounding Artificial Intelligence (AI) is taking multiple industries by storm, and the digital assets industry appears to be readily embracing the tech.</p>
<p>Lightning Labs has become the latest platform to tap the space. The team behind the Bitcoin Lightning Network announced the release of a new set of developer tools to enable the Lightning and AI developer communities to interact with Bitcoin seamlessly.</p>
<h2>Lightning Labs Taps AI</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://lightning.engineering/posts/2023-07-05-l402-langchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, the newly released toolkit assists AI applications such as OpenAI&#8217;s ChatGPT to interact with the Bitcoin network to send, receive, and hold the crypto-asset. Lightning Labs explained that the new tools are built on a Lightning native authentication mechanism &#8211; L402 protocol. It also uses a popular library called &#8220;Langchain.&#8221;</p>
<p>The firm also highlighted the problem of rising deployment costs that serves as a barrier due to the current billing paradigm, a crucial aspect that Lightning and the L402 protocol seek to address. As such, leveraging the L402 protocol, any entity with an internet-connected device will be able to receive or acquire Bitcoin instantly. Owing to the Lightning Network, high-volume payments can also be carried out while retaining privacy.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’re extremely excited about the new wave of innovation brought about with the latest wave of LLM models. With the L402 protocol and LangChainBitcoin, we’re able to ensure the open models can be accessed using an open payment system, connected to the world’s set of open APIs. In the end, open source will win, and we’re working to provide the tooling to enable greater accessibility to AI for humans and agents alike.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>LN Growth</h2>
<p>Despite a slow start, Lightning Network has been increasingly embraced by crypto entities. The scaling solution witnessed tremendous growth as measured by the amount of BTC locked within it. The latest <a href="https://1ml.com/statistics" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> shows that there are now more than 5.4k BTC on the Lightning Network.</p>
<p>Binance recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/keep-building-binance-starts-running-bitcoin-lightning-network-nodes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that it would start running multiple Lightning nodes to leverage the layer-2 scaling solution in a bid to enable cheaper BTC deposits and withdrawals on its platform.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-unveils-toolkit-to-enable-ai-transact-in-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Lightning Labs Unveils Toolkit to Enable AI Transact in Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap V4 Release Hinges on Ethereum&#8217;s Cancun Upgrade and Audit Completion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-v4-release-hinges-on-ethereums-cancun-upgrade-and-audit-completion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 23:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259112</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Uniswap.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Uniswap.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Uniswap had earlier invited community feedback to discuss potential areas of concern and opportunities for V4 improvement.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Uniswap Labs has shared some detail about its much-anticipated v4 release, which is currently undergoing active development. In a new post, the team behind the DeFi juggernaut Uniswap said it is thinking about the launch of the upcoming version in terms of three milestones.</p>
<p>If no security issues or delays with respect Cancun hard fork and audit process occur, V4 is likely to be launched later this year.</p>
<h2>Updates on Uniswap V4</h2>
<p>According to Uniswap Foundation&#8217;s governance lead, Erin Koen, the first step in the timeline includes publishing of protocol code which was achieved on June 13th. It involved the opening of the protocol repo for public view and contribution, a move meant to underscore Uniswap&#8217;s dedication to decentralization.</p>
<p>One of the main factors that V4&#8217;s <a href="https://gov.uniswap.org/t/uniswap-v4-and-the-dao/21626" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">launch</a> relies on is the completion of the audit process, which, in turn, depends on the successful integration of EIP-1153 into Ethereum&#8217;s Cancun. The upcoming upgrade is expected to occur in September-end.</p>
<p>Following Cancun, the devs will focus on an extensive auditing process of the v4 codebase before being deployed. The process is estimated to range anywhere between one to four months. Despite providing the timeline, Koen admitted,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The above timeline is purely indicative and it should be noted that the Cancun hard fork could be delayed, the audit process could be extended, and the protocol could be subjected to other security testing.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>What’s New in V4?</h2>
<p>The V4 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-upgrades-to-v4-heres-whats-new/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">upgrade</a> is expected to expand on the DEX&#8217;s coin-swapping capabilities by introducing &#8220;hooks&#8221; and custom liquidity pools. According to Uniswap Labs CEO Hayden Adams, hooks can be described as &#8220;plugins to customize how pools, swaps, fees, and LP positions interact.&#8221;</p>
<p>The new functionality aims to implement features such as on-chain limit orders and dynamic fees that might be accessible on more traditional exchange platforms but are not easy to bring in a blockchain setting that consists of no centralized infrastructures. Among other features, the pool creation cost on Uniswap v4 will also be slashed by 99% since all pools live within a single contract.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-v4-release-hinges-on-ethereums-cancun-upgrade-and-audit-completion/" rel="nofollow">Uniswap V4 Release Hinges on Ethereum&#8217;s Cancun Upgrade and Audit Completion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis&#8217; Clash With FTX Over Funds Likely to Delay its Creditor Payout: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-clash-with-ftx-over-funds-likely-to-delay-its-creditor-payout-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259277</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In the Battle of the Bankruptcies, who will come out on top?
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to US Bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane, Genesis, whose repayment plan was pending approval, will first have to resolve its outstanding issues with FTX.</p>
<p>The announcement came mere hours after Cameron Winklevoss’ <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-issues-3-day-ultimatum-to-dcgs-barry-silbert-threatens-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">ultimatum</a> to DCG CEO Barry Silbert expired, meaning yet another lawsuit against Genesis’ parent company is also on the horizon. A response to said ultimatum, which would have forced DCG to stick to a repayment plan, may now be out of DCG&#8217;s control to begin with.</p>
<h2>Awfully Optimistic</h2>
<p>During a preliminary hearing concerning Genesis’ creditor repayment plan, Manhattan-based Bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane stated that any further hearings regarding this proposal are likely to be delayed until the firm’ legal dispute with FTX was resolved, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-06/genesis-s-2-billion-spat-with-ftx-may-delay-creditor-payouts" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Bloomberg.</p>
<blockquote><p>“That schedule is looking awfully optimistic. My understanding is these deadlines were likely to slip.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, a final ruling on the payment plan is still not out of the question. The two parties proposed “duel procedures” in order to settle FTX’s claim, a request that was denied by Judge Lane.</p>
<p>Also rejected by the judge were a second request from FTX to sue Genesis in a Delaware court and another from the former for a hearing to decide whether the claim is legitimate in the first place.</p>
<h2>Right to Confidentiality</h2>
<p>Genesis’ debt to FTX has been outright denied by the company in earlier hearings with Judge Lane, who outright <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-judge-denies-ftxs-bid-to-participate-in-confidential-mediation-sessions-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">refused</a> access to its confidential mediation sessions to the exchange&#8217;s legal counsel.</p>
<blockquote><p>“There will be a certain amount of radio silence because mediation needs that to work. Shortening the mediation does not shorten the case.”</p></blockquote>
<p>FTX originally claimed that Genesis owed it nearly $4 billion, a claim which has since been revised to only $2 billion. This, in turn, indicates that FTX is overestimating the scope of its business deal with its fellow crypto lending platform at best and simply grasping at straws at worst. As far as Genesis is concerned, FTX “is entitled to claims totaling $0.00.”</p>
<p>Judge Lane has ordered the two platforms to exchange information regarding the alleged debt and to report back at a later date. Until then, the court will refrain from ruling on whether FTX is even allowed to sue Genesis in the first place.</p>
<p>Once the parties have exchanged the necessary information, the court may schedule the hearing requested by Genesis regarding the size of its debt to FTX – assuming it exists in the first place.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-clash-with-ftx-over-funds-likely-to-delay-its-creditor-payout-report/" rel="nofollow">Genesis&#8217; Clash With FTX Over Funds Likely to Delay its Creditor Payout: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price &#038; Other Major Cryptos Are Stalling, But Traders Remain Bullish on These Tokens</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 20:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259368</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the crypto landscape continues to change, recent days have seen Bitcoin ($BTC), along with several other cryptos, experience a notable downturn. This downturn has caused ripples of concern throughout the market, with many traders now pondering whether the bullish momentum is over for now. However, despite the slump, several new tokens are emerging, offering [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the crypto landscape continues to change, recent days have seen Bitcoin ($BTC), along with several other cryptos, experience a notable downturn.</p>
<p>This downturn has caused ripples of concern throughout the market, with many traders now pondering whether the bullish momentum is over for now.</p>
<p>However, despite the slump, several new tokens are emerging, offering a silver lining.</p>
<h2>Red Week for Crypto As Bitcoin Price Stumbles</h2>
<p>It’s been a difficult week for crypto traders thus far, with most major coins and tokens experiencing a significant selloff.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, the world’s largest cryptocurrency, has seen its price drop 4% in the past day – and has now closed in the red for three days in a row.</p>
<p>This surprise turnaround in fortunes comes after a period of sustained momentum for $BTC, which saw the coin’s price soar by 27% over the past month.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259378" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="287" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-300x143.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>However, this bullish momentum appears to have been halted, with $BTC struggling to surpass the crucial $31,000 level.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, $BTC is retesting $30,000 – a vital psychological level that has often served as support and resistance in previous market cycles.</p>
<p>If it fails to hold, further downward momentum could be on the cards.</p>
<h2>Market Uncertainty Dampens Crypto Enthusiasm</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s not just Bitcoin experiencing a price dip – major altcoins like Ethereum ($ETH) are also seeing the bears take control.</p>
<p>The $ETH price has dipped over 5% from Monday’s high, with the token now trading around the $1,860 level.</p>
<p>A quick glance at the Coin360 <a href="https://coin360.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">heatmap</a> shows a sea of red, with big hitters like Ripple ($XRP) and Binance Coin ($BNB) also experiencing a sharp price drop.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259377" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-1.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="602" height="279" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-1-300x139.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-1-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>It appears that uncertainty is rippling throughout the crypto market following the <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/d3b06ad6-6b96-42bb-9fac-ebe1b8dc7fa6" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">release</a> of the Federal Reserve’s FOMC meeting minutes, which indicate that another rate hike could be in the works for July.</p>
<p>This is bearish news for the crypto market since higher interest rates can make riskier assets, like cryptocurrencies, less attractive to investors.</p>
<p>As a result, investor funds may be redirected towards “safer” financial instruments and away from cryptos, leading to a broad decline in coin/token values.</p>
<p>Despite the current headwinds, many traders still hope for a rebound – although time will tell whether they&#8217;re correct in their predictions.</p>
<h2>Which Tokens Are Traders Still Bullish On?</h2>
<p>However, it’s not all doom and gloom in the crypto market, with several new projects gaining traction and turning heads.</p>
<p>Two of these projects are Wall Street Memes and Thug Life, which are gearing up for major exchange listings once their respective presales conclude.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Gears Up for Major CEX Listings &amp; Hits $13.2m Presale Raise</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is a new meme token that aims to capture the spirit of the r/WallStreetBets subreddit and the GameStop saga, where retail investors challenged the big hitters on Wall Street.</p>
<p>The $WSM token is community-driven and aims to reward holders for showing faith in the Wall Street Memes brand – which is backed by over 1.1 million people worldwide.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes’ scale can be traced to the success of the <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall St Bulls NFT</a> collection, which launched in 2021 and sold out in 32 minutes.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259376" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-1.jpg" alt="Picture8" width="602" height="179" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-1-300x89.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-1-50x15.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The collection’s popularity has prompted the creators to turn their attention to the crypto market, launching $WSM and hoping to capitalize on the ongoing meme coin craze.</p>
<p>This decision already appears to be bearing fruit, with high-profile names like <a href="https://twitter.com/RealCryptoJamie" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Crypto Jamie</a> opting to join the project as a brand ambassador.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes is now in Stage 21 out of 30 during its presale phase, which has already raised $13.2 million.</p>
<p>Investors who get in early can purchase $WSM tokens at the appealing price of just $0.031.</p>
<p>While the exact price for the intended CEX listing remains undisclosed, it&#8217;s anticipated that the currently-offered price will be a discount on the eventual listing price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Thug Life Aims to Be “Baller’s Meme Coin” &amp; Raises $600,000 in One Week</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a> is another new meme token that many believe is set to explode in the crypto market.</p>
<p>As its name suggests, Thug Life is a project that embraces a bold and edgy persona in the world of finance – setting it apart from most other low-cap cryptos.</p>
<p>Thug Life’s branding features a variety of well-known memes and celebrities, including Snoop Dogg and Pepe the Frog, which looks set to appeal to a broad demographic of retail investors.</p>
<p>Not only that, but Thug Life’s team encourages investors to adopt a “gangsta” attitude and “pimp out” their money game.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259375" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-1.jpg" alt="Picture9" width="602" height="301" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-1-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture9-1-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>As these statements highlight, Thug Life aims to fuel a community-driven movement through humor and trolling – an approach that seems to be working, given the huge influx of new members to the official <a href="https://t.me/thuglifetoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>Like Wall Street Memes, Thug Life is in its presale phase, which has already raised over $600,000 in just one week.</p>
<p>The presale price of $THUG is $0.0007, fixed for the duration of the offering, ensuring that early investors can secure their tokens at a stable price.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-other-major-cryptos-are-stalling-but-traders-remain-bullish-on-these-tokens/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price &#038; Other Major Cryptos Are Stalling, But Traders Remain Bullish on These Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
