<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 03:22:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Akon's Akoin Vs DPA Token DPAT: The battle to be Africa's coin]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/akons-akoin-vs-dpa-token-dpat-the-battle-to-be-africas-coin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-192351.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/akons-akoin-vs-dpa-token-dpat-the-battle-to-be-africas-coin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The traditional banking and finance system is in danger because of how the cryptocurrency market works and the pace of global adoption. With over twenty thousand cryptocurrencies in the world today and an average of 100 cryptocurrencies created daily, it is surprising that Africa has a very small share in this market. African countries regularly rank in the top 10 of searches on Google Trends for the term &ldquo;cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, two asset-backed projects are setting the pace for the African continent, hoping to inspire other crypto projects springing up across the vast region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this article, we shall seek to compare Akoin, the project launched by popular hip hop artist Akon, and the Direct Property Africa Token DPAT to see which one can become Africa&rsquo;s coin. It all comes down to which project can balance providing access for a global investor market eager to profit from a lucrative and untapped location in a safe and transparent way, while giving Africans access to the global financial system needed for expansion and growth.</p>
<p>Use Cases</p>
<p>The Akoin token is meant to be used by all 54 African countries as a single currency. This means that Akoin will be operating as a multi-national currency that allows Africans to trade amongst themselves without having to worry about exchange rates or bank charges. The token is also designed to be used as the official currency for Akon City, a futuristic city yet to break ground, designed and created by the pop star.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, DPA Token DPAT is designed with the aim of creating an infrastructure token to help real estate developers, critical infrastructure builders, private/public initiatives and housing schemes access alternative capital from a truly global investor base allowing the international investor to access the lucrative African market in a transparent and decentralized way while helping to build a continent to spearhead growth by unlocking the clear potential of the people across the continent.</p>
<p>The token is backed by real estate and infrastructure projects run by trusted local developers in major African cities like Jacob West Ghana with the recently launched Khari project in Accra. The DPA Token team have built a custom platform so investors can purchase fractional shares in the form of NFTs representing the land under development and receive profits when the project or NFT is sold. Holders of the native DPAT coin will also receive natural price lifts as word of Africa's infrastructure token spreads.</p>
<p>Market Size</p>
<p>Africa's population is growing rapidly. Currently, the continent has 1.2 billion people and will soon reach 2 billion. As a result, Africa is the world's youngest continent&mdash;with more than half of its population under age 25&mdash;and it's one of the fastest urbanizing regions in the world with an estimated 200 million people expected to move to cities over the next five years.</p>
<p>This all bodes well for both projects especially considering DPAT is seeking to partner with global investors unsure of how to access lucrative African markets safely and securely. The projects funded and cities built will change the image of Africa and become crypto hubs for enthusiasts from all over the world to travel to build the next layer of the cryptoverse and spend their DPA Tokens.</p>
<p>Conclusion&nbsp;</p>
<p>Taking into account the above-listed and discussed points, it is safe to say that both projects have separate utilities but share the same goal to help Africa grow and spread crypto adoption. There is more than enough space for useful projects that help develop the engine of the world and promote a positive image of a continent growing at an incredible pace.</p>
<p>Although the Akoin project is bigger and more popular, dpatoken.io is not far behind and its international base of backers believe Africa is just the start of a global shift where the community get to decide what gets built - by whom, for whom, and where. Analysts are all saying DPAT is undervalued and is primed for huge growth in 2023. In the next few years, it is likely to build a fortune for many crypto lovers across the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You can learn more and support the project here.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The traditional banking and finance system is in danger because of how the cryptocurrency market works and the pace of global adoption. With over twenty thousand cryptocurrencies in the world today and an average of 100 cryptocurrencies created daily, it is surprising that Africa has a very small share in this market. African countries regularly rank in the top 10 of searches on Google Trends for the term &ldquo;cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>
<p>However, two asset-backed projects are setting the pace for the African continent, hoping to inspire other crypto projects springing up across the vast region.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In this article, we shall seek to compare Akoin, the project launched by popular hip hop artist Akon, and the Direct Property Africa Token DPAT to see which one can become Africa&rsquo;s coin. It all comes down to which project can balance providing access for a global investor market eager to profit from a lucrative and untapped location in a safe and transparent way, while giving Africans access to the global financial system needed for expansion and growth.</p>
<p>Use Cases</p>
<p>The Akoin token is meant to be used by all 54 African countries as a single currency. This means that Akoin will be operating as a multi-national currency that allows Africans to trade amongst themselves without having to worry about exchange rates or bank charges. The token is also designed to be used as the official currency for Akon City, a futuristic city yet to break ground, designed and created by the pop star.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, DPA Token DPAT is designed with the aim of creating an infrastructure token to help real estate developers, critical infrastructure builders, private/public initiatives and housing schemes access alternative capital from a truly global investor base allowing the international investor to access the lucrative African market in a transparent and decentralized way while helping to build a continent to spearhead growth by unlocking the clear potential of the people across the continent.</p>
<p>The token is backed by real estate and infrastructure projects run by trusted local developers in major African cities like Jacob West Ghana with the recently launched Khari project in Accra. The DPA Token team have built a custom platform so investors can purchase fractional shares in the form of NFTs representing the land under development and receive profits when the project or NFT is sold. Holders of the native DPAT coin will also receive natural price lifts as word of Africa's infrastructure token spreads.</p>
<p>Market Size</p>
<p>Africa's population is growing rapidly. Currently, the continent has 1.2 billion people and will soon reach 2 billion. As a result, Africa is the world's youngest continent&mdash;with more than half of its population under age 25&mdash;and it's one of the fastest urbanizing regions in the world with an estimated 200 million people expected to move to cities over the next five years.</p>
<p>This all bodes well for both projects especially considering DPAT is seeking to partner with global investors unsure of how to access lucrative African markets safely and securely. The projects funded and cities built will change the image of Africa and become crypto hubs for enthusiasts from all over the world to travel to build the next layer of the cryptoverse and spend their DPA Tokens.</p>
<p>Conclusion&nbsp;</p>
<p>Taking into account the above-listed and discussed points, it is safe to say that both projects have separate utilities but share the same goal to help Africa grow and spread crypto adoption. There is more than enough space for useful projects that help develop the engine of the world and promote a positive image of a continent growing at an incredible pace.</p>
<p>Although the Akoin project is bigger and more popular, dpatoken.io is not far behind and its international base of backers believe Africa is just the start of a global shift where the community get to decide what gets built - by whom, for whom, and where. Analysts are all saying DPAT is undervalued and is primed for huge growth in 2023. In the next few years, it is likely to build a fortune for many crypto lovers across the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>You can learn more and support the project here.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OKB, Flow (FLOW) and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Touted as Best Crypto Investments for 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/okb-flow-flow-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-touted-as-best-crypto-investments-for-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-01-08-at-192136.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/okb-flow-flow-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-touted-as-best-crypto-investments-for-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the collapse of FTX behind us, OKB, the native token of rival cryptocurrency exchange OKX seems to outperform most other digital assets. Furthermore, we have Dapper Lab&rsquo;s FLOW token down over 97% from its all-time high but with great partnerships in place, and last but not least, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), a newcomer that managed to skyrocket over 805% in December of which analysts now predict it will surge by as much as 6,000% in Q1 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>OKB Shines Bright After FTX Collapse Causes FTT Token to Drop Like a Brick</p>
<p>OKB, OKX&rsquo;s native token, enjoyed a significant uptrend from around $22 to over $27 last week. When compared to most other cryptocurrencies, OKB is one of the digital assets that seems to be the most stable in value, still trading at about half of its all-time high whilst other cryptocurrencies are trading at 80 to 90 percent discounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that OKX is rapidly gaining users and its trading volume is increasing, it might be wise to add OKB to your cryptocurrency portfolio, especially because OKB reduces payable trading fees on the cryptocurrency exchange and allows investors to earn a passive income through staking.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With this in mind, OKB has seen increased attention as many investors flock to OKB for 2023. Along with its utility as an exchange token, OKB is likely to see further growth as time goes on.</p>
<p>Dapper Lab&rsquo;s Flow (FLOW) Down 97% Makes for Great Long-Term Buy</p>
<p>Flow (FLOW), the native currency of the Flow network and the keystone for a new, inclusive, and borderless digital economy, is currently trading at a whopping 97% discount compared to last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Although FLOW is designed as a payment method and a long-term reserve asset for the Flow economy, to be used by both validators and developers, it couldn&rsquo;t withstand the hefty blows dealt by the FTX collapse, and its price took a nosedive, so to speak.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, don&rsquo;t let its low price of a mere $0.65 per token fool you! Dapper Labs, the creator of the Flow blockchain as well as the famous NFT project Cryptokitties, has partnerships in place with big and well-known names such as the NBA, Warner Music Group, and UFC. Notable investors in the project include Andreessen Horowitz, Coinbase, Zynga, and Google Ventures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With these strong fundamentals, Flow (FLOW) makes for a great long-term buy going into 2023, and our experts predict the token to recover sooner rather than later.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) - The Crypto Project That Will Disrupt Crowdfunding and Venture Capital Markets in 2023</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is gaining momentum and making headlines left, right, and sideways ever since it managed to skyrocket over 805% in December during the first two phases of its pre-sale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) aims to disrupt the crowdfunding and venture capital markets through the use of fractionalized NFTs. If a start-up company wants to raise funds through Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), they can mint equity-backed NFTs that represent investments in the start-up.</p>
<p>Users of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) can then buy these NFTs from as little as $1 and reap the rewards of early seed investing. For start-ups, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) greatly reduces costs and allows them to be in direct contact with their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will use a Fill-or-Kill mechanism that ensures all investors get a refund whenever a start-up fails to reach its funding goal, which takes the guesswork out of the equation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The project&rsquo;s native ORBN token is set to provide holders with benefits like staking bonuses, transaction fee discounts and governance rights. Investors can participate in the pre-sale at a price of $0.0362 per token, however based on ORBN&rsquo;s performance thus far analysts predict that ORBN will see a 6000% price increase to $0.24 in the coming months.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the collapse of FTX behind us, OKB, the native token of rival cryptocurrency exchange OKX seems to outperform most other digital assets. Furthermore, we have Dapper Lab&rsquo;s FLOW token down over 97% from its all-time high but with great partnerships in place, and last but not least, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), a newcomer that managed to skyrocket over 805% in December of which analysts now predict it will surge by as much as 6,000% in Q1 2023.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>OKB Shines Bright After FTX Collapse Causes FTT Token to Drop Like a Brick</p>
<p>OKB, OKX&rsquo;s native token, enjoyed a significant uptrend from around $22 to over $27 last week. When compared to most other cryptocurrencies, OKB is one of the digital assets that seems to be the most stable in value, still trading at about half of its all-time high whilst other cryptocurrencies are trading at 80 to 90 percent discounts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Given that OKX is rapidly gaining users and its trading volume is increasing, it might be wise to add OKB to your cryptocurrency portfolio, especially because OKB reduces payable trading fees on the cryptocurrency exchange and allows investors to earn a passive income through staking.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With this in mind, OKB has seen increased attention as many investors flock to OKB for 2023. Along with its utility as an exchange token, OKB is likely to see further growth as time goes on.</p>
<p>Dapper Lab&rsquo;s Flow (FLOW) Down 97% Makes for Great Long-Term Buy</p>
<p>Flow (FLOW), the native currency of the Flow network and the keystone for a new, inclusive, and borderless digital economy, is currently trading at a whopping 97% discount compared to last year.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Although FLOW is designed as a payment method and a long-term reserve asset for the Flow economy, to be used by both validators and developers, it couldn&rsquo;t withstand the hefty blows dealt by the FTX collapse, and its price took a nosedive, so to speak.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, don&rsquo;t let its low price of a mere $0.65 per token fool you! Dapper Labs, the creator of the Flow blockchain as well as the famous NFT project Cryptokitties, has partnerships in place with big and well-known names such as the NBA, Warner Music Group, and UFC. Notable investors in the project include Andreessen Horowitz, Coinbase, Zynga, and Google Ventures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With these strong fundamentals, Flow (FLOW) makes for a great long-term buy going into 2023, and our experts predict the token to recover sooner rather than later.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) - The Crypto Project That Will Disrupt Crowdfunding and Venture Capital Markets in 2023</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is gaining momentum and making headlines left, right, and sideways ever since it managed to skyrocket over 805% in December during the first two phases of its pre-sale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) aims to disrupt the crowdfunding and venture capital markets through the use of fractionalized NFTs. If a start-up company wants to raise funds through Orbeon Protocol (ORBN), they can mint equity-backed NFTs that represent investments in the start-up.</p>
<p>Users of the Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) can then buy these NFTs from as little as $1 and reap the rewards of early seed investing. For start-ups, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) greatly reduces costs and allows them to be in direct contact with their backers.</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) will use a Fill-or-Kill mechanism that ensures all investors get a refund whenever a start-up fails to reach its funding goal, which takes the guesswork out of the equation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The project&rsquo;s native ORBN token is set to provide holders with benefits like staking bonuses, transaction fee discounts and governance rights. Investors can participate in the pre-sale at a price of $0.0362 per token, however based on ORBN&rsquo;s performance thus far analysts predict that ORBN will see a 6000% price increase to $0.24 in the coming months.</p>
<p>Find Out More About The Orbeon Protocol Presale</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Jetshare JETT$ Price Prediction (2023)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/jetshare-jett-price-prediction-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-01-08-191414.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/jetshare-jett-price-prediction-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Jetshare is one of the most exciting cryptocurrency projects on the blockchain today. With the fractional NFT concept fast becoming a craze for cryptocurrency lovers, there has been a high demand for the project in recent weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are still doubts about how big the Jetshare token can grow in the coming years. In this article, we take a look at Jetshare&rsquo;s price prediction for the next two years. This price prediction is based on current market movement and the strengths of the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Market Opportunities Available</p>
<p>With the average rate for private Jet hires sitting at between $1,300 and $3,000 hourly, one would expect that very few people will have an interest in using these flights.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, contrary to that, research shows that private Jet rentals have soared in numbers over the past years. Partly because of the effects of the COVID-19 pandemic and also for the ultimate desire for privacy, most people are now turning towards private Jets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most would think these people are either celebrities, millionaires, billionaires, or successful businessmen, however groups of private individuals are more likely to pull funds together to travel across the globe in comfort.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the industry moves to a more sustainable future with the advent of electrical systems and hybrid-electric propulsion over the coming years, one can only expect the demand for private Jets to go in an upward trajectory.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will in turn increase the demand for Jetshare&rsquo;s native token JETT$. In the end, the underlying Jets for the project will see real-life usage, while the tokens themselves will also appreciate in price as holders use the token to book Jet charters, pay at private terminals and access international aviation events.</p>
<p>Actual Price Predictions</p>
<p>The big question again remains: How high can the price of JETT$ get? It is expected that when the Jetshare project officially launches after its pre-sales, the price of the token will take off at around 0.08USD landing somewhere close to $5 by year end.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, this value is expected as the token gets listed on other exchanges over the coming months and receives more attention from the general investing public.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the subsequent months, as the project adds more Jets to its fleet and announces partnerships with airports, charter businesses and flying schools around the globe, it is expected that more investors will get interested in the project and increase the buying pressure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is expected to cause some positive price action in the market. Based on this intel, Jetshare should see a price increase of between 300% to 350% within 18 months.</p>
<p>By the end of 2024, the price of the token is likely to be on its way to the moon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The best way to make money from cryptocurrency is to invest in projects that have real value and are backed with assets. In today&rsquo;s crypto market, what's better than a token that allows you to fly where you want.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the price prediction in this post, you can already see where this project is headed in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click here to register now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Follow on twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jetshare is one of the most exciting cryptocurrency projects on the blockchain today. With the fractional NFT concept fast becoming a craze for cryptocurrency lovers, there has been a high demand for the project in recent weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there are still doubts about how big the Jetshare token can grow in the coming years. In this article, we take a look at Jetshare&rsquo;s price prediction for the next two years. This price prediction is based on current market movement and the strengths of the project.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Market Opportunities Available</p>
<p>With the average rate for private Jet hires sitting at between $1,300 and $3,000 hourly, one would expect that very few people will have an interest in using these flights.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, contrary to that, research shows that private Jet rentals have soared in numbers over the past years. Partly because of the effects of the COVID-19 pandemic and also for the ultimate desire for privacy, most people are now turning towards private Jets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most would think these people are either celebrities, millionaires, billionaires, or successful businessmen, however groups of private individuals are more likely to pull funds together to travel across the globe in comfort.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the industry moves to a more sustainable future with the advent of electrical systems and hybrid-electric propulsion over the coming years, one can only expect the demand for private Jets to go in an upward trajectory.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This will in turn increase the demand for Jetshare&rsquo;s native token JETT$. In the end, the underlying Jets for the project will see real-life usage, while the tokens themselves will also appreciate in price as holders use the token to book Jet charters, pay at private terminals and access international aviation events.</p>
<p>Actual Price Predictions</p>
<p>The big question again remains: How high can the price of JETT$ get? It is expected that when the Jetshare project officially launches after its pre-sales, the price of the token will take off at around 0.08USD landing somewhere close to $5 by year end.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, this value is expected as the token gets listed on other exchanges over the coming months and receives more attention from the general investing public.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the subsequent months, as the project adds more Jets to its fleet and announces partnerships with airports, charter businesses and flying schools around the globe, it is expected that more investors will get interested in the project and increase the buying pressure.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This is expected to cause some positive price action in the market. Based on this intel, Jetshare should see a price increase of between 300% to 350% within 18 months.</p>
<p>By the end of 2024, the price of the token is likely to be on its way to the moon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The best way to make money from cryptocurrency is to invest in projects that have real value and are backed with assets. In today&rsquo;s crypto market, what's better than a token that allows you to fly where you want.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With the price prediction in this post, you can already see where this project is headed in the near future.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Click here to register now.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Follow on twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Lifted from 16903 - 9 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-16903-9-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-8-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-lifted-from-16903-9-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Retains Bullish Bias:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) retained its bullish bias early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 16903.58 level after trading as high as the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;The buying pressure that emerged was right around the 78.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls seek to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.6% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16916.87 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16886.77.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Retains Bullish Bias:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 9 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) retained its bullish bias early in the Asian session as the pair encountered buying pressure around the 16903.58 level after trading as high as the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;The buying pressure that emerged was right around the 78.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 17060.86 to 16326.16.&nbsp; BTC/USD bulls seek to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.6% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16916.87 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16886.77.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: Celsius And Huobi Drama And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-weekly-roundup-celsius-and-huobi-drama-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-1-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-weekly-roundup-celsius-and-huobi-drama-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firms continue to struggle even in the first week of the new year, with businesses laying off workforces and announcing bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out how crypto has been faring in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>According to an Mt Gox announcement, base and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>Investor Michael Burry has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.</p>
<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap's newly implemented bug bounty program has uncovered and subsequently resolved an existing vulnerability in its Universal Router smart contract.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>South Korean tech giant LG Electronics has announced a partnership with the cloud-based technology platform Oorbit to bring the metaverse directly into the living room of TV viewers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A hack that exploited and drained GMX tokens from a whale enabled the perpetrator to exchange the assets for 2,627 Ether.</p>
<p>Crypto suffered its worst-ever year for hacks in 2022, with most of them affecting DeFi platforms which saw a third of all such activity in the last year.</p>
Business
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>Tron founder Justin Sun made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Customers of crypto-focused US bank Silvergate have withdrawn over $8 billion of their crypto-linked deposits, resulting in a drop in its share value.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The US government has seized hundreds of millions of dollars worth of shares in Robinhood Markets Inc. as part of the fraud case against Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>With the crypto winter showing no signs of abating, crypto payment companies Wyre and EmpireDAO have become its latest casualties.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Core Scientific has come to an agreement with Celsius Network to shut down the 37,000 mining rigs that it was hosting for the latter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Indonesia is set to launch a cryptocurrency exchange in 2023 as part of a financial reform plan,</p>
<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge.</p>
<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France, given the recent turmoil in the market.</p>
<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsk, for misrepresenting the financial condition of Celsius.</p>
<p>Fabio Panetta of the ECB has written that trading in cryptocurrencies is akin to gambling and should be treated as such by regulators.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong-led cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has reached a $100 million settlement with New York&rsquo;s Department of Financial Services (DFS).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto firms continue to struggle even in the first week of the new year, with businesses laying off workforces and announcing bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s find out how crypto has been faring in 2023.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>In the wake of the devastating winter storm in Texas in December 2022, Bitcoin miners returned up to 1,500 megawatts of energy to the grid, enough to power over 1.5 million small homes.</p>
<p>According to an Mt Gox announcement, base and intermediate payments will be moved back from July to September 2023.</p>
<p>Investor Michael Burry has said that the US will have a recession and more inflation in 2023. He thinks that inflation is currently very high, but it will not remain so.</p>
<p>Eric Voorhees, founder and CEO of crypto exchange Shapeshifter, says he cannot call the next bull market with any exactitude, but it would come in the next 6 months to 3 years.</p>
DeFi
<p>DeFi protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uniswap's newly implemented bug bounty program has uncovered and subsequently resolved an existing vulnerability in its Universal Router smart contract.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol SushiSwap has announced it would be shutting down its lending protocol, Kashi, and its token launchpad, Miso.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>South Korean tech giant LG Electronics has announced a partnership with the cloud-based technology platform Oorbit to bring the metaverse directly into the living room of TV viewers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A hack that exploited and drained GMX tokens from a whale enabled the perpetrator to exchange the assets for 2,627 Ether.</p>
<p>Crypto suffered its worst-ever year for hacks in 2022, with most of them affecting DeFi platforms which saw a third of all such activity in the last year.</p>
Business
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>Tron founder Justin Sun made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Customers of crypto-focused US bank Silvergate have withdrawn over $8 billion of their crypto-linked deposits, resulting in a drop in its share value.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the latest court ruling, Celsius Network has been rewarded the rights to interest-bearing accounts, pushing actual account holders to the end of the repayment queue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The US government has seized hundreds of millions of dollars worth of shares in Robinhood Markets Inc. as part of the fraud case against Sam Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p>With the crypto winter showing no signs of abating, crypto payment companies Wyre and EmpireDAO have become its latest casualties.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Core Scientific has come to an agreement with Celsius Network to shut down the 37,000 mining rigs that it was hosting for the latter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Indonesia is set to launch a cryptocurrency exchange in 2023 as part of a financial reform plan,</p>
<p>Lee Jung-Hoon, the former chairman of South Korea's Bithumb exchange, was declared not guilty of fraud over the failed acquisition of the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Co-founder of crypto exchange Gemini Trust Co, Cameron Winklevoss, has accused the CEO of Digital Currency Group (DCG), Barry Silbert, of negotiating in bad faith.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge.</p>
<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France, given the recent turmoil in the market.</p>
<p>Liquidators found a unique way to subpoena Three Arrows Capital co-founders Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, issuing them a copy of the subpoena via Twitter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New York Attorney General Letitia James has sued the founder and former CEO of collapsed crypto bank Celsius, Alex Mashinsk, for misrepresenting the financial condition of Celsius.</p>
<p>Fabio Panetta of the ECB has written that trading in cryptocurrencies is akin to gambling and should be treated as such by regulators.</p>
<p>Brian Armstrong-led cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has reached a $100 million settlement with New York&rsquo;s Department of Financial Services (DFS).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US still gunning for crypto exchange Binance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-still-gunning-for-crypto-exchange-binance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-crash.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 12:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/us-still-gunning-for-crypto-exchange-binance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange is still in the sights of US authorities as hedge funds are subpoenaed.</p>
<p>It was reported by Reuters last month that the long-running investigation into Binance could result in criminal charges being levied against senior executives at the crypto company, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the report also said that there could be a possible settlement in the case that sufficient evidence was not forthcoming. All this is taking place in the awful environment for crypto, which is potentially further fueling the flight of more investors from the sector.</p>
<p>An article in the Washington Post put forward the argument of Patrick Hillmann, Chief Strategy Officer for Binance. He said that Binance did have shortcomings in the past, but that the company had &ldquo;invested heavily in compliance programs&rdquo;, and that it was now working closely with law enforcement agencies around the globe. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Over the last two years, the company has completely changed its posture. Now that we have those resources, we are easily one of the most proactive parties to identify, freeze and get back funds&rdquo;</p>

<p>John Ghose, a former Justice Department prosecutor, was also featured in the Washington Post article. He stated that it was his belief that when&nbsp; he was a prosecutor Binance did not have a good reputation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In relation to whether Binance had allowed money laundering, tax evasion, or other crimes to take place on its platform, he said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The basis of those charges is whether there are U.S. customers. If there are U.S. customers, there are charges for avoiding the money laundering requirements.&rdquo;</p>

Could the Binance FUD topple crypto?
<p>Given that Binance is easily the biggest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, for it to fall would arguably have a simply huge knock-on for the rest of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>A collapse of the exchange could have dire consequences that could put the industry back years, making transacting in cryptocurrencies that much more difficult, as well as removing a very large investor in the space.</p>
<p>With all the furore surrounding the FTX debacle, the various bankruptcies of other crypto companies etc., now is a very bad time for crypto, and a very good time for authorities to turn the screw and attempt to subjugate, if not almost eliminate private digital asset transactions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s biggest crypto exchange is still in the sights of US authorities as hedge funds are subpoenaed.</p>
<p>It was reported by Reuters last month that the long-running investigation into Binance could result in criminal charges being levied against senior executives at the crypto company, including founder and CEO Changpeng Zhao.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the report also said that there could be a possible settlement in the case that sufficient evidence was not forthcoming. All this is taking place in the awful environment for crypto, which is potentially further fueling the flight of more investors from the sector.</p>
<p>An article in the Washington Post put forward the argument of Patrick Hillmann, Chief Strategy Officer for Binance. He said that Binance did have shortcomings in the past, but that the company had &ldquo;invested heavily in compliance programs&rdquo;, and that it was now working closely with law enforcement agencies around the globe. He said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Over the last two years, the company has completely changed its posture. Now that we have those resources, we are easily one of the most proactive parties to identify, freeze and get back funds&rdquo;</p>

<p>John Ghose, a former Justice Department prosecutor, was also featured in the Washington Post article. He stated that it was his belief that when&nbsp; he was a prosecutor Binance did not have a good reputation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In relation to whether Binance had allowed money laundering, tax evasion, or other crimes to take place on its platform, he said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The basis of those charges is whether there are U.S. customers. If there are U.S. customers, there are charges for avoiding the money laundering requirements.&rdquo;</p>

Could the Binance FUD topple crypto?
<p>Given that Binance is easily the biggest crypto exchange in the world by trading volume, for it to fall would arguably have a simply huge knock-on for the rest of the crypto industry.</p>
<p>A collapse of the exchange could have dire consequences that could put the industry back years, making transacting in cryptocurrencies that much more difficult, as well as removing a very large investor in the space.</p>
<p>With all the furore surrounding the FTX debacle, the various bankruptcies of other crypto companies etc., now is a very bad time for crypto, and a very good time for authorities to turn the screw and attempt to subjugate, if not almost eliminate private digital asset transactions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flares FLR Token Could Be This Years GMX]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flares-flr-token-could-be-this-years-gmx</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-229.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/flares-flr-token-could-be-this-years-gmx</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>There weren&rsquo;t many standout tokens last year &ndash; holding anything other than stablecoins was likely to see you lose 80% in dollar value &ndash; but GMX was a notable exception. The native token of Arbitrum&rsquo;s derivatives exchange, GMX is up 35% in 12 months, no mean feat when most other assets were hemorrhaging hard through 2022.</p>
<p>2023 looks like another testing year for the crypto market, but observers have already zeroed in on one token that&rsquo;s being tipped as the next GMX. Its name? FLR. The native token of Flare&rsquo;s interoperable blockchain network is finally dropping on January 9, and anticipation is mounting that FLR could shake up a stagnant market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
XRP Holders Get Their Day
<p>It&rsquo;s been over two years since a snapshot was taken of XRP balances with the goal of airdropping Flare&rsquo;s native token to them when the network launched. XRP was originally identified by Flare as being the community that would benefit the most from its interoperable EVM chain.</p>
<p>The XRP ledger, like other blockchains of that era, has no smart contract capacity, which severely limits the use cases for its eponymous asset. Step forward Flare, whose team believe they&rsquo;ve found a way to safely unlock assets on &ldquo;legacy chains&rdquo; such as Bitcoin, XRP, and Dogechain, freeing them to be used on Flare Network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Airdrop It Like It&rsquo;s Hot
<p>So what can XRP holders and the crypto community at large expect on January 9 when FLR becomes tradable? Around 15% of FLR&rsquo;s total supply will be issued to airdrop recipients on this date, with the remainder of their share vesting monthly over 36 months. XRP holders whose tokens were held on a centralized exchange at the time of the original snapshot will be able to claim their FLR tokens there.</p>
<p>Flare has published the full list of exchanges supporting the airdrop and it includes most of the major players such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi. It&rsquo;s likely that many of these exchanges will also list the FLR token as opposed to simply letting users withdraw their balance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Can Flare Reignite Crypto?
<p>There aren&rsquo;t many events to get the crypto community excited at the dawn of a new year; it&rsquo;s a time when nothing more dangerous than testnets is typically shipped. The launch of Flare&rsquo;s native token, then, should bring some cheer to airdrop recipients and give dormant traders a reason to awaken from their slumber and put their stablecoins to good use.</p>
<p>Hopes are high that Flare&rsquo;s interoperability solution will introduce a safer way to transfer value between chains. With $2 billion lost to bridge exploits last year alone, it can&rsquo;t come soon enough for DeFi users.</p>
<p>&ldquo;If information is revealed to be incorrect after transactions have been validated and assets have subsequently been reallocated to more established chains, the risk is introduced to the entire system,&rdquo; explains Flare CEO Hugo Philion. The industry will be watching closely to see whether Flare can improve on these shortcomings to deliver a secure system for cross-chain transfers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There weren&rsquo;t many standout tokens last year &ndash; holding anything other than stablecoins was likely to see you lose 80% in dollar value &ndash; but GMX was a notable exception. The native token of Arbitrum&rsquo;s derivatives exchange, GMX is up 35% in 12 months, no mean feat when most other assets were hemorrhaging hard through 2022.</p>
<p>2023 looks like another testing year for the crypto market, but observers have already zeroed in on one token that&rsquo;s being tipped as the next GMX. Its name? FLR. The native token of Flare&rsquo;s interoperable blockchain network is finally dropping on January 9, and anticipation is mounting that FLR could shake up a stagnant market.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
XRP Holders Get Their Day
<p>It&rsquo;s been over two years since a snapshot was taken of XRP balances with the goal of airdropping Flare&rsquo;s native token to them when the network launched. XRP was originally identified by Flare as being the community that would benefit the most from its interoperable EVM chain.</p>
<p>The XRP ledger, like other blockchains of that era, has no smart contract capacity, which severely limits the use cases for its eponymous asset. Step forward Flare, whose team believe they&rsquo;ve found a way to safely unlock assets on &ldquo;legacy chains&rdquo; such as Bitcoin, XRP, and Dogechain, freeing them to be used on Flare Network.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Airdrop It Like It&rsquo;s Hot
<p>So what can XRP holders and the crypto community at large expect on January 9 when FLR becomes tradable? Around 15% of FLR&rsquo;s total supply will be issued to airdrop recipients on this date, with the remainder of their share vesting monthly over 36 months. XRP holders whose tokens were held on a centralized exchange at the time of the original snapshot will be able to claim their FLR tokens there.</p>
<p>Flare has published the full list of exchanges supporting the airdrop and it includes most of the major players such as Binance, OKX, and Huobi. It&rsquo;s likely that many of these exchanges will also list the FLR token as opposed to simply letting users withdraw their balance.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Can Flare Reignite Crypto?
<p>There aren&rsquo;t many events to get the crypto community excited at the dawn of a new year; it&rsquo;s a time when nothing more dangerous than testnets is typically shipped. The launch of Flare&rsquo;s native token, then, should bring some cheer to airdrop recipients and give dormant traders a reason to awaken from their slumber and put their stablecoins to good use.</p>
<p>Hopes are high that Flare&rsquo;s interoperability solution will introduce a safer way to transfer value between chains. With $2 billion lost to bridge exploits last year alone, it can&rsquo;t come soon enough for DeFi users.</p>
<p>&ldquo;If information is revealed to be incorrect after transactions have been validated and assets have subsequently been reallocated to more established chains, the risk is introduced to the entire system,&rdquo; explains Flare CEO Hugo Philion. The industry will be watching closely to see whether Flare can improve on these shortcomings to deliver a secure system for cross-chain transfers.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wyre to continue to operate - explores options]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/wyre-to-continue-to-operate-explores-options</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/wyre.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 10:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/wyre-to-continue-to-operate-explores-options</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Beleaguered crypto payments provider Wyre is continuing to operate. The company is exploring strategic options and has set customer withdrawal limit to 90%.</p>
<p>After reports that Wyre was winding down its business, with its CEO Ioannis Giannaros, saying that the company was preparing for liquidation and that it would be potentially closing at the end of January, Tweets by Giannaros have appeared that suggest that Wyre could continue to operate.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Acting in the best interest of our community is our top priority, and we are exploring strategic options for our company that will enable us to navigate the current market environment and deliver on our mission to simplify and revolutionize the global payments ecosystem.</p>
&mdash; Wyre  (@sendwyre) January 7, 2023
<p>

</p>
Exploring options
<p>The fact that Wyre is &ldquo;exploring strategic options&rdquo;, and wants to &ldquo;deliver on [its] mission to simplify and revolutionise the global payments ecosystem&rdquo;, is not compatible with the earlier reports that the company was looking to liquidate and close down the business.</p>
<p>In another hint that Wyre would not be ending operations, the final tweet to the community stated that Wyre would continue to operate and that it would &ldquo;pursue options that would enable Wyre to flourish&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

Changes to management structure
<p>In the same tweet thread it was explained that Giannaros would be transitioning into the new role of Executive Chairman, and that Stephen Cheng, the former Chief Risk Officer, and Chief Compliance Officer, would become the interim CEO.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Beleaguered crypto payments provider Wyre is continuing to operate. The company is exploring strategic options and has set customer withdrawal limit to 90%.</p>
<p>After reports that Wyre was winding down its business, with its CEO Ioannis Giannaros, saying that the company was preparing for liquidation and that it would be potentially closing at the end of January, Tweets by Giannaros have appeared that suggest that Wyre could continue to operate.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Acting in the best interest of our community is our top priority, and we are exploring strategic options for our company that will enable us to navigate the current market environment and deliver on our mission to simplify and revolutionize the global payments ecosystem.</p>
&mdash; Wyre  (@sendwyre) January 7, 2023
<p>

</p>
Exploring options
<p>The fact that Wyre is &ldquo;exploring strategic options&rdquo;, and wants to &ldquo;deliver on [its] mission to simplify and revolutionise the global payments ecosystem&rdquo;, is not compatible with the earlier reports that the company was looking to liquidate and close down the business.</p>
<p>In another hint that Wyre would not be ending operations, the final tweet to the community stated that Wyre would continue to operate and that it would &ldquo;pursue options that would enable Wyre to flourish&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;We sincerely appreciate the support and positive sentiments from our community as well as the crypto ecosystem at large as we pursue options that will enable Wyre to flourish. Our operations continue and we will share information with the community as it is available.&rdquo;</p>

Changes to management structure
<p>In the same tweet thread it was explained that Giannaros would be transitioning into the new role of Executive Chairman, and that Stephen Cheng, the former Chief Risk Officer, and Chief Compliance Officer, would become the interim CEO.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK), Cardano (ADA), and Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Top Crypto Christmas List]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/chainlink-link-cardano-ada-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-top-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-505.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-505.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-505.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/chainlink-link-cardano-ada-and-orbeon-protocol-orbn-top-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>There are thousands of cryptocurrency projects to choose from this Christmas but three that have significantly stood out include Chainlink (LINK), Cardano (ADA), and of course Orbeon Protocol (ORBN).</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) and Cardano (ADA) are starting to look great again after entering the green zone lately but it is Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) that has created the biggest buzz in the crypto world because of the huge gains seen by its presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol is currently in phase 3 of its presale and already seeing price hikes of 805%. It is even expected to hit a 6000% price increase at the end of the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s examine the three coins to see why they are the best candidates for your December and early January investment list.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) Still Going Strong</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) is an innovative platform powered by blockchain technology that helps to build smart contracts that are universally connected.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Its major goal is to connect data from different sources outside the blockchain to smart contracts. To achieve these goals, Chainlink uses external payment methods and data feeds.</p>
<p>Despite the dominance of market bears in 2022, Chainlink (LINK) still remains resilient in the green zone with recent price hikes of up to 18%. If the trend continues, Chainlink (LINK) could potentially provide investors with a good ROI in 2023. Chainlink (LINK) is currently trading at $5.68 and&nbsp; the volume on Chainlink (LINK) currently its around $220 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) Fluctuating But Showing Signs of Growth&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most traders would say that Cardano (ADA) has been showing mixed results lately but from a long-term perspective, the token has a lot of promise. Cardano (ADA) is a third-generation platform powered by blockchain technology. It was launched in 2017.</p>
<p>Cardano&rsquo;s utility lies in building smart contracts for developing decentralized applications. Cardano (ADA) is also energy-efficient because it uses proof-of-stake consensus in its operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Cardano (ADA) has had a few dips in the past weeks in tandem with the rest of the crypto tokens, especially after the FTX downfall but has shown signs of bouncing back in 2023. It is worth keeping an eye on Cardano (ADA) as you speculate on the best coins this holiday season.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Rise of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Looks Unstoppable</p>
<p>Judging by the huge success of its current presale, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is definitely your best bet this holiday season.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The blockchain-based decentralized investment platform does what no other cryptocurrency project has managed to achieve before. It creates a great opportunity for regular people to enter the previously prohibitive venture capital industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Startups also benefit from the platform by reaching out to a wider pool of interested investors and raising capital within a shorter time than they would with traditional angel investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol provides a much-needed solution in the crowdfunding and venture capital industry that was previously dominated by the big sharks and red-tape bureaucracy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol allows retail investors to buy into promising startups through the use of its NFTs-as-a-service (NFTaas). Any company seeking to raise funds can use the service to mint equity-based NFTs that are then fractionalized and sold to investors for as low as 1 dollar.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Thanks to the practical utility of the Orbeon Protocol, its token ORBN is seeing massive gains in the first stage of its presale. Industry experts predict that the price of ORBN will attain a 6000% gain in the next few weeks when the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find Out More About the Orbeon Protocol Presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are thousands of cryptocurrency projects to choose from this Christmas but three that have significantly stood out include Chainlink (LINK), Cardano (ADA), and of course Orbeon Protocol (ORBN).</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) and Cardano (ADA) are starting to look great again after entering the green zone lately but it is Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) that has created the biggest buzz in the crypto world because of the huge gains seen by its presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol is currently in phase 3 of its presale and already seeing price hikes of 805%. It is even expected to hit a 6000% price increase at the end of the presale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Let&rsquo;s examine the three coins to see why they are the best candidates for your December and early January investment list.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) Still Going Strong</p>
<p>Chainlink (LINK) is an innovative platform powered by blockchain technology that helps to build smart contracts that are universally connected.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Its major goal is to connect data from different sources outside the blockchain to smart contracts. To achieve these goals, Chainlink uses external payment methods and data feeds.</p>
<p>Despite the dominance of market bears in 2022, Chainlink (LINK) still remains resilient in the green zone with recent price hikes of up to 18%. If the trend continues, Chainlink (LINK) could potentially provide investors with a good ROI in 2023. Chainlink (LINK) is currently trading at $5.68 and&nbsp; the volume on Chainlink (LINK) currently its around $220 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY ORBEON TOKENS HERE&lt;&lt;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) Fluctuating But Showing Signs of Growth&nbsp;</p>
<p>Most traders would say that Cardano (ADA) has been showing mixed results lately but from a long-term perspective, the token has a lot of promise. Cardano (ADA) is a third-generation platform powered by blockchain technology. It was launched in 2017.</p>
<p>Cardano&rsquo;s utility lies in building smart contracts for developing decentralized applications. Cardano (ADA) is also energy-efficient because it uses proof-of-stake consensus in its operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price of Cardano (ADA) has had a few dips in the past weeks in tandem with the rest of the crypto tokens, especially after the FTX downfall but has shown signs of bouncing back in 2023. It is worth keeping an eye on Cardano (ADA) as you speculate on the best coins this holiday season.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Rise of Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) Looks Unstoppable</p>
<p>Judging by the huge success of its current presale, Orbeon Protocol (ORBN) is definitely your best bet this holiday season.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The blockchain-based decentralized investment platform does what no other cryptocurrency project has managed to achieve before. It creates a great opportunity for regular people to enter the previously prohibitive venture capital industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Startups also benefit from the platform by reaching out to a wider pool of interested investors and raising capital within a shorter time than they would with traditional angel investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol provides a much-needed solution in the crowdfunding and venture capital industry that was previously dominated by the big sharks and red-tape bureaucracy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Orbeon Protocol allows retail investors to buy into promising startups through the use of its NFTs-as-a-service (NFTaas). Any company seeking to raise funds can use the service to mint equity-based NFTs that are then fractionalized and sold to investors for as low as 1 dollar.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Thanks to the practical utility of the Orbeon Protocol, its token ORBN is seeing massive gains in the first stage of its presale. Industry experts predict that the price of ORBN will attain a 6000% gain in the next few weeks when the presale ends.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find Out More About the Orbeon Protocol Presale:</p>
<p>Website: https://orbeonprotocol.com/</p>
<p>Presale: https://presale.orbeonprotocol.com/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/OrbeonProtocol</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mastercard Employs Polygon for Web3 Music Accelerator Program]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/mastercard-employs-polygon-for-web3-music-accelerator-program</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mastercard-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mastercard-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mastercard-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 18:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/mastercard-employs-polygon-for-web3-music-accelerator-program</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Payments giant Mastercard has expanded its reach in the blockchain sector again, this time by launching a spotlight program for emerging musical artists built atop the Polygon blockchain. </p>
<p>Mastercard announced the Mastercard Artist Accelerator program &ndash; a spotlight program for emerging musical artists to help up-and-coming creators tap into the power of Web3 and blockchain technology. The program will kick off in spring 2023 and will prepare five emerging musical artists, with the skills, access, and tools to pave their own musical paths in the digital economy. Mastercard announced the program on January 7 via a blog post that reads:</p>

<p>The artists will gain exclusive access to special events, music releases and more. A first-of-its-kind curriculum will teach the artists how to build (and own) their brand through Web3 experiences like minting NFTs, representing themselves in virtual worlds and establishing an engaged community.</p>

<p>Raja Rajamannar, Mastercard's Chief Marketing, and Communications Officer said:</p>

<p>The core of this program is providing emerging artists with the web3 tools and skills they need to excel and advance their music careers in this digital economy.</p>

<p>Mastercard has tapped the Polygon blockchain for its latest venture &ndash; a scaling blockchain built on Ethereum. Polygon Studios CEO Ryan Watt commented on the announcement saying:</p>

<p>Web3 has the potential to empower a new type of artist that can grow a fanbase, make a living, and introduce novel mediums for self-expression and connection on their own terms. The Mastercard Artists Accelerator not only shows the power of brands embracing this new space, it provides tools that can educate consumers on how to participate. This is an important step forward in opening up the benefits of Web3 to more people.</p>

Mastercard Embraces the Blockchain Space
<p>Mastercard has been very busy expanding its reach into the world of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. Most recently the company launched a program that allows mainstream banks to offer crypto trading to their customers. The payments giant also announced a collaboration between itself and Binance in Argentina. The two companies launched a prepaid reward card to help people spend crypto on everyday goods and will allow users to buy things and pay bills with Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies at more than 90 million merchants.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Payments giant Mastercard has expanded its reach in the blockchain sector again, this time by launching a spotlight program for emerging musical artists built atop the Polygon blockchain. </p>
<p>Mastercard announced the Mastercard Artist Accelerator program &ndash; a spotlight program for emerging musical artists to help up-and-coming creators tap into the power of Web3 and blockchain technology. The program will kick off in spring 2023 and will prepare five emerging musical artists, with the skills, access, and tools to pave their own musical paths in the digital economy. Mastercard announced the program on January 7 via a blog post that reads:</p>

<p>The artists will gain exclusive access to special events, music releases and more. A first-of-its-kind curriculum will teach the artists how to build (and own) their brand through Web3 experiences like minting NFTs, representing themselves in virtual worlds and establishing an engaged community.</p>

<p>Raja Rajamannar, Mastercard's Chief Marketing, and Communications Officer said:</p>

<p>The core of this program is providing emerging artists with the web3 tools and skills they need to excel and advance their music careers in this digital economy.</p>

<p>Mastercard has tapped the Polygon blockchain for its latest venture &ndash; a scaling blockchain built on Ethereum. Polygon Studios CEO Ryan Watt commented on the announcement saying:</p>

<p>Web3 has the potential to empower a new type of artist that can grow a fanbase, make a living, and introduce novel mediums for self-expression and connection on their own terms. The Mastercard Artists Accelerator not only shows the power of brands embracing this new space, it provides tools that can educate consumers on how to participate. This is an important step forward in opening up the benefits of Web3 to more people.</p>

Mastercard Embraces the Blockchain Space
<p>Mastercard has been very busy expanding its reach into the world of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. Most recently the company launched a program that allows mainstream banks to offer crypto trading to their customers. The payments giant also announced a collaboration between itself and Binance in Argentina. The two companies launched a prepaid reward card to help people spend crypto on everyday goods and will allow users to buy things and pay bills with Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies at more than 90 million merchants.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Spike to 17027 - 8 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-spike-to-17027-8-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-7-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-spike-to-17027-8-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Spikes to 17027.11:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) resumed its short-term upward bias early in the Asian session as the pair reapproached the 17000 figure after spiking to the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December 2022 and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;Bulls are looking to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.5% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16917.29 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16863.53.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Spikes to 17027.11:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 8 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) resumed its short-term upward bias early in the Asian session as the pair reapproached the 17000 figure after spiking to the 17027.11 level, its strongest print since 20 December 2022 and another test of the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 18385.36 to 16273.40.&nbsp; &nbsp;Bulls are looking to see if BTC/USD can establish a constructive base above the 16880.44 area, representing a 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp; Additional upside retracement levels in this depreciating range include the 17750, 18469, 19179, 20058, and 20190 levels.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 2.5% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16917.29 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16863.53.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Thai SEC Launches Crypto Academy to Educate Digital Investors]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/thai-sec-launches-crypto-academy-to-educate-digital-investors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/thai-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/thai-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/thai-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 14:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/thai-sec-launches-crypto-academy-to-educate-digital-investors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge. </p>
<p>The Thai SEC announced recently that it launched &ldquo;Crypto Academy,&rdquo; an initiative aimed at providing free online resources and courses on digital assets for all those wanting to invest in the sector. The SEC said the &lsquo;academy&rsquo; is aimed at equipping the public with in-depth knowledge of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology before they invest. The regulator argues:</p>

<p>The more you know your investments, the less risk you will have.</p>

Four Courses Offer Comprehensive Knowledge of Crypto
<p>The Crypto Academy offers four courses on crypto and blockchain technology. The first offers new investors a basic understanding of the digital asset market, including the definition of cryptocurrency and the principles of blockchain technology. The second educate potential investors on the key features of cryptocurrencies and the technologies that underlie them. The second course also includes information on Bitcoin, decentralisation, and peer-to-peer systems.</p>
<p>A third of the courses cover pertinent events from the past, the present, and also the future, including bitcoin halving and previous market crashes. This course further covers the digital asset ecosystem, digital tokens, NFTs, the metaverse, and the future of the crypto market. Finally, the fourth course focuses on investment strategies, portfolio diversification, investor sentiment, and basic price analysis through the use of charts and other indicators, and finally covers asset management.</p>
<p>The SEC has also taken the initiative to include a very useful tool that could potentially save many from losing their money &ndash; a Crypto Quotient (CQ). The CQ is a self-assessment for investors that they can use to test their knowledge of the crypto world to ascertain whether they are ready to enter the market.</p>
India Launches Crypto Awareness Campaign
<p>Asian countries have seemingly taken charge of informing their citizens of the cryptocurrency market and the potential dangers thereof. The Indian government is reportedly launching a similar initiative aimed at raising awareness of cryptocurrencies. India however takes a slightly different approach to Thailand, by focusing much of their campaign on the legal status of cryptocurrencies rather than purely educating its citizens on the intricacies of crypto and all that involves the digital asset market. India&rsquo;s approach seems to be aimed at discouraging citizens to invest in the sector, while Thailand tries to educate its citizens before they enter the market &ndash; providing a sense of encouragement.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Thai Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has launched a cryptocurrency academy aimed at educating those wanting to invest in digital assets free of charge. </p>
<p>The Thai SEC announced recently that it launched &ldquo;Crypto Academy,&rdquo; an initiative aimed at providing free online resources and courses on digital assets for all those wanting to invest in the sector. The SEC said the &lsquo;academy&rsquo; is aimed at equipping the public with in-depth knowledge of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology before they invest. The regulator argues:</p>

<p>The more you know your investments, the less risk you will have.</p>

Four Courses Offer Comprehensive Knowledge of Crypto
<p>The Crypto Academy offers four courses on crypto and blockchain technology. The first offers new investors a basic understanding of the digital asset market, including the definition of cryptocurrency and the principles of blockchain technology. The second educate potential investors on the key features of cryptocurrencies and the technologies that underlie them. The second course also includes information on Bitcoin, decentralisation, and peer-to-peer systems.</p>
<p>A third of the courses cover pertinent events from the past, the present, and also the future, including bitcoin halving and previous market crashes. This course further covers the digital asset ecosystem, digital tokens, NFTs, the metaverse, and the future of the crypto market. Finally, the fourth course focuses on investment strategies, portfolio diversification, investor sentiment, and basic price analysis through the use of charts and other indicators, and finally covers asset management.</p>
<p>The SEC has also taken the initiative to include a very useful tool that could potentially save many from losing their money &ndash; a Crypto Quotient (CQ). The CQ is a self-assessment for investors that they can use to test their knowledge of the crypto world to ascertain whether they are ready to enter the market.</p>
India Launches Crypto Awareness Campaign
<p>Asian countries have seemingly taken charge of informing their citizens of the cryptocurrency market and the potential dangers thereof. The Indian government is reportedly launching a similar initiative aimed at raising awareness of cryptocurrencies. India however takes a slightly different approach to Thailand, by focusing much of their campaign on the legal status of cryptocurrencies rather than purely educating its citizens on the intricacies of crypto and all that involves the digital asset market. India&rsquo;s approach seems to be aimed at discouraging citizens to invest in the sector, while Thailand tries to educate its citizens before they enter the market &ndash; providing a sense of encouragement.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Balancer Advises LPs To Pull Liquidity Due To Ongoing Issues]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/balancer-advises-lps-to-pull-liquidity-due-to-ongoing-issues</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/balancer-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/balancer-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/balancer-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/balancer-advises-lps-to-pull-liquidity-due-to-ongoing-issues</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The protocol did not specify what the issue was but added that the emergency DAO could not mitigate it.&nbsp;</p>
LPs Advised To Pull Liquidity&nbsp;
<p>The team at decentralized finance protocol Balancer has advised some LPs to pull their liquidity immediately. The warning was issued after ongoing issues related to some of the service&rsquo;s pools were discovered by the protocol. Some liquidity pools on the protocol have seen their fees set to zero by Balancer&rsquo;s emergency multisig. However, despite this measure, the team has indicated that this approach could mitigate not all effects of the issue.</p>

<p>&ldquo;IMPORTANT: Because of a related issue, LPs of the following pools should remove their liquidity ASAP as the issue cannot be mitigated by the emergency DAO.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Balancer announced the issue on Twitter on the 6th of January at 2:03 am UTC, adding that the team had set protocol fees to zero to attempt to mitigate the problem. The team further added that it would disclose more details in the near future.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Protocol fees of some Balancer pools have been set to 0 to avoid an issue that is now mitigated and will be publicly disclosed in the near future. This has been done by the emergency multisig, a 4/7 comprised of BLabs engineers and Balancer Maxis. These pools continue to function normally, so no action is needed by the LPs of those pools. They will continue to accrue swap fees, but the protocol will not take its cut from them.&rdquo;</p>

Impacted Pools&nbsp;
<p>Balancer has asked LPs to pull liquidity from specific pools because the emergency DAO has been unable to mitigate the ongoing issue. As a result, LPs on Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (MATIC), Optimism (OP), and Fantom (FTM) versions of Balancer (BAL) have been asked to remove liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Ethereum, the issue has impacted the DOLA/bb-a-USD pool, which has a current Total Value Locked (TVL) of $3.6 million in equivalent. On Polygon, LPs were advised to remove liquidity from the bb-am-USD/miMATIC pool. On Optimism, the problem has impacted the MAI Life and Smells Like Spartan Spirit Pools. Furthermore, users of the Fantom-based &ldquo;friendly fork&rdquo; of Balancer were advised to remove $1.9 million from the Tenacious Dollar Liquidity Pool. The pools on Arbitrum, according to Fernando Martinelli, remain unaffected by the issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Balancer also stated that if a pool&rsquo;s transaction fee has been set to zero by the emergency multisig, then LPs do not need to take any further action. The pools in question will continue to accumulate fees. However, Balancer would not be taking its cut.&nbsp;</p>
Community On Tenterhooks&nbsp;
<p>Balancer is currently the 6th largest decentralized exchange in terms of trading volume and handles around $52 million worth of crypto trades daily, according to data from DeFiLlama. The Balancer community&rsquo;s initial reaction has seen some members fearing the worst, citing the vagueness of the protocol&rsquo;s statement about the issue and what it could potentially be. The problem at Balancer comes after the Radium DEX was subject to a fee exploit, where a malicious entity utilized an admin key to change pool parameters. This allowed them to trick the pool smart contract into behaving as if the pool contained only accumulated admin fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Balancer has warned LPs on the protocol to withdraw their liquidity immediately due to an ongoing issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The protocol did not specify what the issue was but added that the emergency DAO could not mitigate it.&nbsp;</p>
LPs Advised To Pull Liquidity&nbsp;
<p>The team at decentralized finance protocol Balancer has advised some LPs to pull their liquidity immediately. The warning was issued after ongoing issues related to some of the service&rsquo;s pools were discovered by the protocol. Some liquidity pools on the protocol have seen their fees set to zero by Balancer&rsquo;s emergency multisig. However, despite this measure, the team has indicated that this approach could mitigate not all effects of the issue.</p>

<p>&ldquo;IMPORTANT: Because of a related issue, LPs of the following pools should remove their liquidity ASAP as the issue cannot be mitigated by the emergency DAO.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Balancer announced the issue on Twitter on the 6th of January at 2:03 am UTC, adding that the team had set protocol fees to zero to attempt to mitigate the problem. The team further added that it would disclose more details in the near future.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Protocol fees of some Balancer pools have been set to 0 to avoid an issue that is now mitigated and will be publicly disclosed in the near future. This has been done by the emergency multisig, a 4/7 comprised of BLabs engineers and Balancer Maxis. These pools continue to function normally, so no action is needed by the LPs of those pools. They will continue to accrue swap fees, but the protocol will not take its cut from them.&rdquo;</p>

Impacted Pools&nbsp;
<p>Balancer has asked LPs to pull liquidity from specific pools because the emergency DAO has been unable to mitigate the ongoing issue. As a result, LPs on Ethereum (ETH), Polygon (MATIC), Optimism (OP), and Fantom (FTM) versions of Balancer (BAL) have been asked to remove liquidity.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On Ethereum, the issue has impacted the DOLA/bb-a-USD pool, which has a current Total Value Locked (TVL) of $3.6 million in equivalent. On Polygon, LPs were advised to remove liquidity from the bb-am-USD/miMATIC pool. On Optimism, the problem has impacted the MAI Life and Smells Like Spartan Spirit Pools. Furthermore, users of the Fantom-based &ldquo;friendly fork&rdquo; of Balancer were advised to remove $1.9 million from the Tenacious Dollar Liquidity Pool. The pools on Arbitrum, according to Fernando Martinelli, remain unaffected by the issue.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Balancer also stated that if a pool&rsquo;s transaction fee has been set to zero by the emergency multisig, then LPs do not need to take any further action. The pools in question will continue to accumulate fees. However, Balancer would not be taking its cut.&nbsp;</p>
Community On Tenterhooks&nbsp;
<p>Balancer is currently the 6th largest decentralized exchange in terms of trading volume and handles around $52 million worth of crypto trades daily, according to data from DeFiLlama. The Balancer community&rsquo;s initial reaction has seen some members fearing the worst, citing the vagueness of the protocol&rsquo;s statement about the issue and what it could potentially be. The problem at Balancer comes after the Radium DEX was subject to a fee exploit, where a malicious entity utilized an admin key to change pool parameters. This allowed them to trick the pool smart contract into behaving as if the pool contained only accumulated admin fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Head of French Central Bank Pushes for Crypto Licensing]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/head-of-french-central-bank-pushes-for-crypto-licensing</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/france-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/head-of-french-central-bank-pushes-for-crypto-licensing</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France given the recent turmoil in the market. The head of the central bank said France should not wait for the upcoming MiCA regulation to enact obligatory licensing for local digital asset service providers (DASPs). </p>
<p>Francois Villeroy de Galhau, governor of the Bank of France, said during a speech in Paris on January 5, that the recent chaos in the crypto markets necessitates that France moves ahead with a mandatory licensing scheme for crypto firms &ldquo;as soon as possible,&rdquo; according to reports by Bloomberg. The governor said that France should not wait for the upcoming EU crypto laws &ndash; the Markets in Crypto Assets bill (MiCA), to come into effect before enacting mandatory licensing for DASPs.</p>
France Needs to Act Before MiCA Comes into Force
<p>Villeroy addressed France&rsquo;s financial industry in his speech, saying:</p>

<p>All the disorder in 2022 feeds a simple belief: it is desirable for France to move to an obligatory licensing of DASP as soon as possible, rather than just registration.</p>

<p>The European Parliament&rsquo;s MiCA is expected to potentially come into force in 2024 and will provide a crypto licensing regime for the European Union.</p>
<p>As it stands in France, the Financial Markets Authority (AMF), the nation&rsquo;s market regulator, requires &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from cryptocurrency firms offering trading and custody services. A DASP license is currently voluntary per Bloomberg, and none of the service providers hold one. The less strict &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from the AMF is held by about 60 businesses.</p>
<p>Villeroy&rsquo;s calls come after Herv&eacute; Maurey, a member of the Senate Finance Commission, in December 2022 proposed an amendment that would do away with the provision allowing businesses to operate without a license.</p>
<p>In December reports were circulating that France is considering an obligation for crypto firms to obtain a full license before they can operate. The government then already expressed concern over the lack of regulation and oversight in the crypto space in the wake of the recent bankruptcy of FTX.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The governor of the Bank of France is calling for stricter and more comprehensive licensing requirements for cryptocurrency companies in France given the recent turmoil in the market. The head of the central bank said France should not wait for the upcoming MiCA regulation to enact obligatory licensing for local digital asset service providers (DASPs). </p>
<p>Francois Villeroy de Galhau, governor of the Bank of France, said during a speech in Paris on January 5, that the recent chaos in the crypto markets necessitates that France moves ahead with a mandatory licensing scheme for crypto firms &ldquo;as soon as possible,&rdquo; according to reports by Bloomberg. The governor said that France should not wait for the upcoming EU crypto laws &ndash; the Markets in Crypto Assets bill (MiCA), to come into effect before enacting mandatory licensing for DASPs.</p>
France Needs to Act Before MiCA Comes into Force
<p>Villeroy addressed France&rsquo;s financial industry in his speech, saying:</p>

<p>All the disorder in 2022 feeds a simple belief: it is desirable for France to move to an obligatory licensing of DASP as soon as possible, rather than just registration.</p>

<p>The European Parliament&rsquo;s MiCA is expected to potentially come into force in 2024 and will provide a crypto licensing regime for the European Union.</p>
<p>As it stands in France, the Financial Markets Authority (AMF), the nation&rsquo;s market regulator, requires &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from cryptocurrency firms offering trading and custody services. A DASP license is currently voluntary per Bloomberg, and none of the service providers hold one. The less strict &ldquo;registration&rdquo; from the AMF is held by about 60 businesses.</p>
<p>Villeroy&rsquo;s calls come after Herv&eacute; Maurey, a member of the Senate Finance Commission, in December 2022 proposed an amendment that would do away with the provision allowing businesses to operate without a license.</p>
<p>In December reports were circulating that France is considering an obligation for crypto firms to obtain a full license before they can operate. The government then already expressed concern over the lack of regulation and oversight in the crypto space in the wake of the recent bankruptcy of FTX.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Heralds Major Blockchain Adoption in Turkey]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/lbank-heralds-major-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/2023-01-06_60547_1672999558OlDkfDzMFz.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/lbank-heralds-major-blockchain-adoption-in-turkey</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, 6th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, the licensed European cryptocurrency exchange, has applauded measures taken by the Turkish government to utilize blockchain technology. LBank CEO Allen Wei has highlighted a number of positive developments in Turkey including CBDC trials and regional blockchain projects.</p>
<p>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even stronger embrace of blockchain technology in 2023.</p>
"Turkey is an exciting market that ranks among the top 10 in crypto adoption globally,&rdquo; said Allen Wei, Co-Founder and CEO of LBank Exchange. &ldquo;Efforts such as these show Turkey&rsquo;s determination to push for wider blockchain integration in the country. It&rsquo;s a boost for the digital Turkish lira and a positive step from the forward-looking government.&rdquo;
<p>Since the Turkish government unveiled its plan for a national blockchain infrastructure in 2019, Turkey has had many ambitious blockchain-based goals. However, besides specific project announcements, there have been few deliverables. This looks set to change in 2023, with several promising projects at an advanced stage of development.</p>
<p>A recent statement from the CBRT revealed that &ldquo;the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully.&rdquo; It said that further advanced-stage tests will be run in the first quarter of 2023, and selected banks and financial technology companies will be chosen to be included in the expansion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The official announcement for a CBDC came in September of 2021. Initially, the CBRT did not commit to a digital Turkish lira. However, the most recent statement mentions that &ldquo;the CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Testing and successful completion of the digital Turkish lira is seen as a big step towards rolling out a digital lira,&rdquo; said Adem &Ouml;zkan &Ouml;zdil, LBank Community Manager for Turkey. Beyond Turkey&rsquo;s CBDC, the government has made other commitments, such as testing and integrating blockchain technology in public services.</p>
<p>Amid the news about the digital Turkish lira, the Vice President of Turkey, Fuat Oktay, announced plans for a blockchain-based digital identity application during the Digital Turkey 2023 event. Many public services, including residential matters and military services, will be integrated into the E-Devlet portal, which will use a blockchain-based digital identity and login system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Turkey first shared its vision to utilize blockchain technology in public services in 2019. In its Strategy 2023 presentation, Turkey&rsquo;s Ministry of Industry and Technology put blockchain and distributed ledger technology (DLT) as one of the priorities of 2020.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, the city of Konya, one of the most important cultural centers of Turkey, revealed in 2020 that it was planning to develop a &ldquo;city coin&rdquo; and use blockchain technology to fund social programs. Konya served as an initial test to see how blockchain technology works with public services on a large scale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About LBank
LBank, founded in 2015, is an innovative global trading platform for various crypto assets. The exchange provides its users with safe crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. It has become one of the most popular and trusted crypto trading platforms, with over 7 million users from more than 210 regions around the world.
&nbsp;</p>
<p>Start Trading Now</p>
<p>Community &amp; Social Media:
Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INTERNET CITY, DUBAI, 6th January, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, the licensed European cryptocurrency exchange, has applauded measures taken by the Turkish government to utilize blockchain technology. LBank CEO Allen Wei has highlighted a number of positive developments in Turkey including CBDC trials and regional blockchain projects.</p>
<p>The Central Bank of Turkey (CBRT) completed CBDC tests in December 2022 and the government is currently planning to use blockchain technology for online public services. Both signal an even stronger embrace of blockchain technology in 2023.</p>
"Turkey is an exciting market that ranks among the top 10 in crypto adoption globally,&rdquo; said Allen Wei, Co-Founder and CEO of LBank Exchange. &ldquo;Efforts such as these show Turkey&rsquo;s determination to push for wider blockchain integration in the country. It&rsquo;s a boost for the digital Turkish lira and a positive step from the forward-looking government.&rdquo;
<p>Since the Turkish government unveiled its plan for a national blockchain infrastructure in 2019, Turkey has had many ambitious blockchain-based goals. However, besides specific project announcements, there have been few deliverables. This looks set to change in 2023, with several promising projects at an advanced stage of development.</p>
<p>A recent statement from the CBRT revealed that &ldquo;the first payment transactions on the Digital Turkish Lira Network were executed successfully.&rdquo; It said that further advanced-stage tests will be run in the first quarter of 2023, and selected banks and financial technology companies will be chosen to be included in the expansion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The official announcement for a CBDC came in September of 2021. Initially, the CBRT did not commit to a digital Turkish lira. However, the most recent statement mentions that &ldquo;the CBRT will continue to run tests for authentic architectural setups designed in areas such as the use of distributed ledger technologies in payment systems and the integration of these technologies with instant payment systems.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Testing and successful completion of the digital Turkish lira is seen as a big step towards rolling out a digital lira,&rdquo; said Adem &Ouml;zkan &Ouml;zdil, LBank Community Manager for Turkey. Beyond Turkey&rsquo;s CBDC, the government has made other commitments, such as testing and integrating blockchain technology in public services.</p>
<p>Amid the news about the digital Turkish lira, the Vice President of Turkey, Fuat Oktay, announced plans for a blockchain-based digital identity application during the Digital Turkey 2023 event. Many public services, including residential matters and military services, will be integrated into the E-Devlet portal, which will use a blockchain-based digital identity and login system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Turkey first shared its vision to utilize blockchain technology in public services in 2019. In its Strategy 2023 presentation, Turkey&rsquo;s Ministry of Industry and Technology put blockchain and distributed ledger technology (DLT) as one of the priorities of 2020.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, the city of Konya, one of the most important cultural centers of Turkey, revealed in 2020 that it was planning to develop a &ldquo;city coin&rdquo; and use blockchain technology to fund social programs. Konya served as an initial test to see how blockchain technology works with public services on a large scale.&nbsp;</p>
<p>About LBank
LBank, founded in 2015, is an innovative global trading platform for various crypto assets. The exchange provides its users with safe crypto trading, specialized financial derivatives, and professional asset management services. It has become one of the most popular and trusted crypto trading platforms, with over 7 million users from more than 210 regions around the world.
&nbsp;</p>
<p>Start Trading Now</p>
<p>Community &amp; Social Media:
Telegram l Twitter l Facebook l LinkedIn l Instagram l YouTube</p>ContactLBK Blockchain Co. Limitedpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Plans Staff Layoffs, Rumors of Insolvency Hang in the Air]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/huobi-plans-staff-layoffs-rumors-of-insolvency-hang-in-the-air</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/huobi-plans-staff-layoffs-rumors-of-insolvency-hang-in-the-air</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>In the latest round of all-over cost-cutting across the crypto industry, crypto exchange Huobi today confirmed to Reuters that the firm plans to lay off about 20% of its staff. Huobi said in a statement to the news agency:</p>

<p>The planned layoff ratio is about 20%, but it is not implemented now. With the current state of the bear market, a very lean team will be maintained going forward.</p>

<p>The statement to Reuters confirms an earlier message from Tron founder Justin Sun, who said that a &ldquo;structural adjustment&rdquo; is to start in Huobi soon. Sun, who is a member of Huobi&rsquo;s global advisory board, said in an internal memo to company staff that the firm has been like &ldquo;a fire in the crypto winter&rdquo; despite the worsening macro environment. Huobi is based in Seychelles and has offices in Hong Kong, the United States, Japan, and in South Korea. The company is publicly listed on the Stock Exchange of Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Along with the layoffs, which rumours of have been running wild on Twitter, Sun has also had to address rumours of insolvency. He said in a January 5 Tweet, that business development of the exchange was &ldquo;good&rdquo; and the &ldquo;security of users&rsquo; assets will always be fully protected.&rdquo; Earlier in January, crypto journalist, Colin Wu, reported that Sun had changed employee salaries from being paid in fiat to being either paid in Tether or USD Coin. The journalist also claimed that staff who disagreed with the new payment systems faced being laid off. Sun dismissed these claims saying that Huobi will &ldquo;fully respect the legal demands of local employees.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Justin Sun's HR is communicating with all Huobi employees to change the salary form from fiat currency to USDT/USDC; employees who cannot accept it may be dismissed. The move sparked protests from some employees. Exclusive https://t.co/QB4sjDyHc7</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) January 4, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Wu also cited insiders and reported that in December Huobi cancelled end-of-year bonuses and was preparing to cut up to half of its staff.</p>
Crypto Firms Off to a Rocky Start in 2023
<p>Huobi&rsquo;s announcement does not come as the first for 2023. In the first couple of days of the year, crypto firm Genesis cut 30% of its workforce in a second round of layoffs in less than six months. Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, cut its workforce by 40% and has been forced to abandon some of its projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Huobi is planning to lay off 20% of its staff amid the crypto market downturn and the fallout from collapsed crypto exchange FTX. </p>
<p>In the latest round of all-over cost-cutting across the crypto industry, crypto exchange Huobi today confirmed to Reuters that the firm plans to lay off about 20% of its staff. Huobi said in a statement to the news agency:</p>

<p>The planned layoff ratio is about 20%, but it is not implemented now. With the current state of the bear market, a very lean team will be maintained going forward.</p>

<p>The statement to Reuters confirms an earlier message from Tron founder Justin Sun, who said that a &ldquo;structural adjustment&rdquo; is to start in Huobi soon. Sun, who is a member of Huobi&rsquo;s global advisory board, said in an internal memo to company staff that the firm has been like &ldquo;a fire in the crypto winter&rdquo; despite the worsening macro environment. Huobi is based in Seychelles and has offices in Hong Kong, the United States, Japan, and in South Korea. The company is publicly listed on the Stock Exchange of Hong Kong.</p>
<p>Along with the layoffs, which rumours of have been running wild on Twitter, Sun has also had to address rumours of insolvency. He said in a January 5 Tweet, that business development of the exchange was &ldquo;good&rdquo; and the &ldquo;security of users&rsquo; assets will always be fully protected.&rdquo; Earlier in January, crypto journalist, Colin Wu, reported that Sun had changed employee salaries from being paid in fiat to being either paid in Tether or USD Coin. The journalist also claimed that staff who disagreed with the new payment systems faced being laid off. Sun dismissed these claims saying that Huobi will &ldquo;fully respect the legal demands of local employees.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Justin Sun's HR is communicating with all Huobi employees to change the salary form from fiat currency to USDT/USDC; employees who cannot accept it may be dismissed. The move sparked protests from some employees. Exclusive https://t.co/QB4sjDyHc7</p>
&mdash; Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) January 4, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Wu also cited insiders and reported that in December Huobi cancelled end-of-year bonuses and was preparing to cut up to half of its staff.</p>
Crypto Firms Off to a Rocky Start in 2023
<p>Huobi&rsquo;s announcement does not come as the first for 2023. In the first couple of days of the year, crypto firm Genesis cut 30% of its workforce in a second round of layoffs in less than six months. Silvergate Capital Corp, a crypto-focused bank, cut its workforce by 40% and has been forced to abandon some of its projects.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[$100 million in stablecoins transferred to Huobi by Justin Sun]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/100-million-in-stablecoins-transferred-to-huobi-by-justin-sun</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/huobi-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/100-million-in-stablecoins-transferred-to-huobi-by-justin-sun</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Recently, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In an article posted by The Block earlier today, security analysts at PeckShield reported that two transactions of $50 million each of USDC and USDT were conducted at 11:10 a.m. UTC. The wallet, which can be linked to Sun through the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan, also holds $16.5 million worth of decentralised usd (USDD), a stablecoin from the Tron blockchain, and closely connected to Sun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It has been noted that the majority of the funds in the recent transactions originated from Just Lend, a Tron-based lending platform, and were transferred to the wallet through Binance before ultimately reaching Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the transactions to Huobi, some exchange users noticed the creation of a $1 million buy wall for $HT, indicating that someone was willing to purchase $1 million worth of the token at a specific price, which is possibly a strategy used to keep the token price from crashing.</p>
<p>The news comes at a time when Huobi is in the public eye, with rumours circulating about layoffs and a mandate for employees to be paid in stablecoins rather than fiat currency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there have been unconfirmed reports of internal communication platforms being shut down, which caused the price of Huobi's token ($HT) to drop to a low of $4.30 from $5.20 over the past 48 hours. $HT has since recovered to $4.64 at time of going to press.</p>
<p>In response to these rumours, Huobi's Global Head of Sales, James Hume, posted on LinkedIn that "most if not all" of them were "totally false or inaccurate." Hume went on to clarify that the exchange's internal communication platform was functioning normally and that it was "business as usual."</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, Justin Sun, the founder of Tron, made headlines when a wallet connected to him transferred $100 million worth of stablecoins to the cryptocurrency exchange Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In an article posted by The Block earlier today, security analysts at PeckShield reported that two transactions of $50 million each of USDC and USDT were conducted at 11:10 a.m. UTC. The wallet, which can be linked to Sun through the Ethereum block explorer Etherscan, also holds $16.5 million worth of decentralised usd (USDD), a stablecoin from the Tron blockchain, and closely connected to Sun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It has been noted that the majority of the funds in the recent transactions originated from Just Lend, a Tron-based lending platform, and were transferred to the wallet through Binance before ultimately reaching Huobi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the transactions to Huobi, some exchange users noticed the creation of a $1 million buy wall for $HT, indicating that someone was willing to purchase $1 million worth of the token at a specific price, which is possibly a strategy used to keep the token price from crashing.</p>
<p>The news comes at a time when Huobi is in the public eye, with rumours circulating about layoffs and a mandate for employees to be paid in stablecoins rather than fiat currency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, there have been unconfirmed reports of internal communication platforms being shut down, which caused the price of Huobi's token ($HT) to drop to a low of $4.30 from $5.20 over the past 48 hours. $HT has since recovered to $4.64 at time of going to press.</p>
<p>In response to these rumours, Huobi's Global Head of Sales, James Hume, posted on LinkedIn that "most if not all" of them were "totally false or inaccurate." Hume went on to clarify that the exchange's internal communication platform was functioning normally and that it was "business as usual."</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Given Below 16880 - 7 January 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-below-16880-7-january-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-6-january-2022-240.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/bitcoin-price-analysis-given-below-16880-7-january-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Given Below 16880:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered additional volatility early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 17000 figure after recently peaking around the 16988 level, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders lifted BTC/USD higher to the 16809.30 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average, and then BTC/USD retreated lower to the 16670.82 area, representing a test of the 200-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 1.4% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16725.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16711.39.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Given Below 16880:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 7 January 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) encountered additional volatility early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 17000 figure after recently peaking around the 16988 level, its strongest print since 20 December.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders lifted BTC/USD higher to the 16809.30 level, representing a test of the 50-hour simple moving average, and then BTC/USD retreated lower to the 16670.82 area, representing a test of the 200-hour simple moving average.&nbsp; Traders recently drove BTC/USD as low as the 16326.16 area after Stops were elected below the 16375.18 area, a downside retracement level related to selling pressure around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels.&nbsp; Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD depreciated approximately 64% in 2022, was off more than 3% in December, and is up approximately 1.4% month-to-date. Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16725.67 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16711.39.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Genesis Lays Off 30% Of Workforce]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/genesis-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/gns-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/genesis-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis On The Verge Of Bankruptcy?
<p>Less than six months after its first round of layoffs, Genesis, has been forced to cut loose around 30% of its workforce. Moreover, the word around the blockchain is that the lending platform is considering filing for bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Genesis has confirmed the news, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"As we continue to navigate unprecedented industry challenges, Genesis has made the difficult decision to reduce our headcount globally."&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to other sources, the company is working with investment bank Moelis &amp; Co to evaluate its options.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Contagion Spreads&nbsp;
<p>The biggest blow to the industry this year was the utter destruction of the FTX ecosystem. Not only did the major crypto exchange crash down dramatically, but it also took with it several significant institutions and crypto firms. For example, crypto-focused bank Silvergate Capital was also affected heavily by the FTX crash and has announced that it will slash its headcount by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the year crypto has had, Genesis would not be the first crypto firm to go down the bankruptcy route. Crypto lender BlockFi was the first to follow FTX into Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing. The market downturn has forced the hands of many crypto executives to cut costs in their respective firms by trimming the workforce fat. In many cases, declaring bankruptcy is the only option left.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis In Trouble
<p>Genesis has been treading troubled waters lately, thanks to its association with the FTX ecosystem. The company&rsquo;s interim CEO, Derar Islim, penned a client letter in which he wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe we can arrive at a solution. As a key element in this process, we have made significant progress in refining our business plans for Genesis&rsquo; client offerings. This includes reducing costs and driving efficiencies in all our business lines.'</p>

<p>In November 2022, the company closed down withdrawals. Just a week before this, it was seeking a billion-dollar emergency loan. Both these events have led to the most recent skirmish with one of the founders of the Gemini crypto exchange, Cameron Winklevoss. The latter has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group (DCG) of acting in bad faith. Winklevoss penned an open letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, claiming that the latter has been evading all attempts at consensual resolution since Genesis owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto lending platform Genesis is considering filing for bankruptcy and has laid off around 30% of its staff.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis On The Verge Of Bankruptcy?
<p>Less than six months after its first round of layoffs, Genesis, has been forced to cut loose around 30% of its workforce. Moreover, the word around the blockchain is that the lending platform is considering filing for bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Genesis has confirmed the news, saying,&nbsp;</p>

<p>"As we continue to navigate unprecedented industry challenges, Genesis has made the difficult decision to reduce our headcount globally."&nbsp;</p>

<p>According to other sources, the company is working with investment bank Moelis &amp; Co to evaluate its options.&nbsp;</p>
FTX Contagion Spreads&nbsp;
<p>The biggest blow to the industry this year was the utter destruction of the FTX ecosystem. Not only did the major crypto exchange crash down dramatically, but it also took with it several significant institutions and crypto firms. For example, crypto-focused bank Silvergate Capital was also affected heavily by the FTX crash and has announced that it will slash its headcount by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After the year crypto has had, Genesis would not be the first crypto firm to go down the bankruptcy route. Crypto lender BlockFi was the first to follow FTX into Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing. The market downturn has forced the hands of many crypto executives to cut costs in their respective firms by trimming the workforce fat. In many cases, declaring bankruptcy is the only option left.&nbsp;</p>
Genesis In Trouble
<p>Genesis has been treading troubled waters lately, thanks to its association with the FTX ecosystem. The company&rsquo;s interim CEO, Derar Islim, penned a client letter in which he wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe we can arrive at a solution. As a key element in this process, we have made significant progress in refining our business plans for Genesis&rsquo; client offerings. This includes reducing costs and driving efficiencies in all our business lines.'</p>

<p>In November 2022, the company closed down withdrawals. Just a week before this, it was seeking a billion-dollar emergency loan. Both these events have led to the most recent skirmish with one of the founders of the Gemini crypto exchange, Cameron Winklevoss. The latter has accused Genesis and the Digital Currency Group (DCG) of acting in bad faith. Winklevoss penned an open letter to DCG CEO Barry Silbert, claiming that the latter has been evading all attempts at consensual resolution since Genesis owes members of Gemini Earn around $900 million.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto and Carbon Reduction - Climate Tech Company YES WORLD is carving out a niche to solve the Global Warming Crisis. Launches Energy Efficient Glass Product Range]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-carbon-reduction-climate-tech-company-yes-world-is-carving-out-a-niche-to-solve-the-global-warming-crisis-launches-energy-efficient-glass-product-range</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/yes-world-1200-720.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/01/crypto-and-carbon-reduction-climate-tech-company-yes-world-is-carving-out-a-niche-to-solve-the-global-warming-crisis-launches-energy-efficient-glass-product-range</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain based climate tech company - YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd launches world&rsquo;s first Energy Efficient Windows Solution for home and commercial buildings. This new product line of specialized glass is part of company SAVE EARTH MISSION to reduce the carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p>The specialized glass solution includes double pane glass and sandwich glass which has a layer of patented material that reflects the 85% solar radiant heat as well as blocks 92% of UV rays from entering the building. The energy efficient glass is a see-through windows solution that blocks the majority of solar heat from entering the building and significantly reduces the energy consumption in terms of HVAC load.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The energy efficient glass product line by YES WORLD not only reduces the radiant heat, thereby reducing the greenhouse effect in the building, but also reflects 92% of the damaging UV rays back out through the window, reducing fading and sun damage.&nbsp; It also provides daytime privacy through its unique one way vision design, as well as control glare issues for sensitive eyes.</p>
<p>As a climate tech company, YES WORLD is on the world's biggest mission to SAVE EARTH, working towards a solution for the biggest problem faced by mankind - Global Warming. YES WORLD is among a very few companies that have tangible offerings towards the solution of the global warming crisis. In addition to the energy efficient windows solution, YES WORLD is also working on Carbon emission data analytics as well as tokenization service for carbon offsets. &nbsp;</p>
<p>YES WORLD TOKEN is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. YES WORLD has taken a community driven approach to generate awareness around climate change and global warming and YES is a powerful mechanism to create a strong community working towards meaningful carbon emission reduction activities while getting advantages of holding best in class utility Token in the form of $YES.</p>
<p>Launched in April 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting a lot of interest from global crypto audiences and buying interest seen across all exchanges. Based on CoinMarketCap data, it has already generated three digit returns for early adopters. YES WORLD announced launch of global utilities portal which is available in 80 countries worldwide</p>
<p>YES is a leading utility token with token&nbsp; usability available across several verticals - Gaming, Travel, NFT Marketplace, Health &amp; Fitness, Financial services as well as wide acceptance among e-commerce and brick-and-mortar stores. YES WORLD plans to onboard 10 million merchants worldwide by the global launch event scheduled in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>YES WORLD Token offers several utility services to investors and enables them to not just hold a token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. Users can make the payment by scanning the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal using the token.</p>
<p>YES WORLD Token is trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap. YES WORLD plans to be listed on over 50 leading crypto exchanges before its global launch.</p>
<p>Just last week YES WORLD announced that it crossed an important milestone of 1.5 million transactions and 100k holders on explorer - BSCScan.</p>
<p>YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Important links -</p>
<p>Twitter - https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p>CMC - https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p>Website - www.yesworld.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain based climate tech company - YES WORLD Climate Tech Pte Ltd launches world&rsquo;s first Energy Efficient Windows Solution for home and commercial buildings. This new product line of specialized glass is part of company SAVE EARTH MISSION to reduce the carbon footprint from the atmosphere.</p>
<p>The specialized glass solution includes double pane glass and sandwich glass which has a layer of patented material that reflects the 85% solar radiant heat as well as blocks 92% of UV rays from entering the building. The energy efficient glass is a see-through windows solution that blocks the majority of solar heat from entering the building and significantly reduces the energy consumption in terms of HVAC load.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>The energy efficient glass product line by YES WORLD not only reduces the radiant heat, thereby reducing the greenhouse effect in the building, but also reflects 92% of the damaging UV rays back out through the window, reducing fading and sun damage.&nbsp; It also provides daytime privacy through its unique one way vision design, as well as control glare issues for sensitive eyes.</p>
<p>As a climate tech company, YES WORLD is on the world's biggest mission to SAVE EARTH, working towards a solution for the biggest problem faced by mankind - Global Warming. YES WORLD is among a very few companies that have tangible offerings towards the solution of the global warming crisis. In addition to the energy efficient windows solution, YES WORLD is also working on Carbon emission data analytics as well as tokenization service for carbon offsets. &nbsp;</p>
<p>YES WORLD TOKEN is the native token for YES WORLD's Save Earth mission. YES WORLD has taken a community driven approach to generate awareness around climate change and global warming and YES is a powerful mechanism to create a strong community working towards meaningful carbon emission reduction activities while getting advantages of holding best in class utility Token in the form of $YES.</p>
<p>Launched in April 2022, YES WORLD Token is getting a lot of interest from global crypto audiences and buying interest seen across all exchanges. Based on CoinMarketCap data, it has already generated three digit returns for early adopters. YES WORLD announced launch of global utilities portal which is available in 80 countries worldwide</p>
<p>YES is a leading utility token with token&nbsp; usability available across several verticals - Gaming, Travel, NFT Marketplace, Health &amp; Fitness, Financial services as well as wide acceptance among e-commerce and brick-and-mortar stores. YES WORLD plans to onboard 10 million merchants worldwide by the global launch event scheduled in April 2024.</p>
<p></p>
<p>YES WORLD Token offers several utility services to investors and enables them to not just hold a token for price appreciation, but also to use it for various usability and utility services available in their countries. Users can make the payment by scanning the bar-code presented at the checkout on the POS Terminal using the token.</p>
<p>YES WORLD Token is trading on several leading centralized exchanges including XT.com and Coinsbit.io, as well as on decentralized exchange - PancakeSwap. YES WORLD plans to be listed on over 50 leading crypto exchanges before its global launch.</p>
<p>Just last week YES WORLD announced that it crossed an important milestone of 1.5 million transactions and 100k holders on explorer - BSCScan.</p>
<p>YES WORLD is inceptualized and promoted by Save Earth activist Dr Sandeep Choudhary, who has constantly been working to generate awareness of global warming and climate change impacts. Under Dr. Choudhary's vision and leadership, YES WORLD has championed a noble cause of reducing carbon footprint and bringing forth the issue of global warming and climate change.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Important links -</p>
<p>Twitter - https://twitter.com/yesworld24</p>
<p>CMC - https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/yes-world-token/</p>
<p>Website - www.yesworld.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
