<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:31:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Thai SEC to Investigate Zipmex About Violating Certain Crypto Rules (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/thai-sec-to-investigate-zipmex-about-violating-certain-crypto-rules-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thailand]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232662</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Thailand_Zipmex.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Thailand_Zipmex.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Thailand's regulator will check if Zipmex abode by local rules when providing products and services to customers.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thailand&#8217;s Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has reportedly launched an investigation against the distressed cryptocurrency platform Zipmex.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The watchdog will inspect whether the latter breached some domestic rules when offering digital asset services </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">and products.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">More Problems for Zipmex</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a Bloomberg </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/thailand-probes-embattled-crypto-exchange-zipmex-on-rule-breach-1.1868527" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the top financial regulator of Thailand will probe the bankrupt Zipmex for violating local laws and running a &#8220;digital-asset fund manager without permission.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC will investigate the platform&#8217;s ZipUP and ZipUP+ programs which enabled users to earn returns on their investments.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The watchdog previously wrote a warning letter to Zipmex&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Akalarp Yimwilai. The crypto firm has until January 12 to shed more light on its activities over the years and thus escape the regulatory scrutiny.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company was among the main victims of the prolonged bear market. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/thai-crypto-exchange-zipmex-suspends-customer-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">paused</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> customer withdrawals in July last year, citing volatile market conditions, and revealed a $53 million exposure to struggling crypto platforms &#8211; Babel Finance ($48 million) and Celsius Network ($5 million).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Zipmex </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/distressed-crypto-exchange-zipmex-in-talks-with-interested-parties-regarding-a-possible-deal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">started</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> discussing possible acquisition deals with &#8220;interested parties&#8221; that could present a rescue plan. It also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/zipmex-requests-meeting-with-thai-regulators-ahead-of-fundraise/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">asked</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for meetings with the SEC regarding an eventual recovery strategy and a multi-million fundraise that could reimburse some customers.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the efforts, Zipmex could not solve its issues and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/07/29/crypto-exchange-zipmex-files-for-bankruptcy-protection-in-singapore.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for bankruptcy protection. The firm, which operated in Thailand, Singapore, Indonesia, and Australia, was among Asia&#8217;s leading cryptocurrency exchanges.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It had over two million customers at its peak and enabled access to assets like Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Ripple (CRP), and its Zipmex token (ZMT), which has plunged over 70% since the platform announced its problems last summer.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Compared to its all-time high level of $5.30, the current valuation of around $0.17 represents a whopping 96% decline.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Buyout Offer on the Horizon</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some sources </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/zipmex-sees-buyout-offer-of-100m-as-it-secures-creditor-protection-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">informed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the Singapore-based investment firm &#8211; V Ventures &#8211; has been in &#8220;advanced talks&#8221; with Zipmex regarding a potential acquisition agreement. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If completed, the $100 million deal will give V Ventures a 90% stake in the distressed organization. The investment company will supposedly pay $30 million in cash and the remainder in cryptocurrencies. According to the court hearing, the digital assets will be later deployed to unfreeze clients&#8217; wallets by the end of Q1, 2023.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thai-sec-to-investigate-zipmex-about-violating-certain-crypto-rules-report/" rel="nofollow">Thai SEC to Investigate Zipmex About Violating Certain Crypto Rules (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Receives Initial Approval to Acquire Voyager Digital&#8217;s Assets: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-receives-initial-approval-to-acquire-voyager-digitals-assets-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 23:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232635</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Voyager_BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Voyager_BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Voyager and Binance's deal had previously received opposition from CFIUS as well as SEC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance US&#8217; plan to acquire some of Voyager Digital&#8217;s assets for $1.02 billion is one step closer as the bankrupt crypto lender received initial court approval for its proposal.</p>
<p>The United States District Judge Michael Wiles of the bankruptcy court for the Southern District of New York on January 10th approved Voyager to work out a purchase agreement with the crypto exchange and to solicit creditor votes on the sale.</p>
<h2>Uncertainty of the Deal</h2>
<p>According to the Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/voyager-seeks-expedite-national-security-review-binance-deal-2023-01-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, the deal will not become final until a future court hearing. Besides, the confirmation hearing is scheduled for March and will require the approval of Voyager&#8217;s creditors as well. If received, the sale will help Voyager customers to recover 51% of crypto assets held before the bankruptcy filing.</p>
<p>But the federal prosecutors are pursuing Binance, especially due to its proximity to its now defunct-rival FTX. As a result, Voyager is looking to speed up the national security review of the deal that could decide whether it can be set in motion.</p>
<p>The Tuesday&#8217;s hearing, Voyager attorney Joshua Sussberg confirmed that the lender is actively responding to national security concerns raised by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States (CFIUS).</p>
<p>The agency essentially reviews the national security implications of foreign investments in US-based companies or operations. Sussberg also asserted that Voyager will address any concerns that CFIUS could deem valid in opposing the transaction with Binance US.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are coordinating with Binance and their attorneys to not only deal with that inquiry but to voluntarily submit an application to move this process along.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As part of the deal, Voyager will receive a $20 million cash payment and transfer customers to Binance US’ crypto exchange. Thus, it will allow customers to withdraw their crypto assets from the platform for the first time after bankruptcy.</p>
<p>If CFIUS blocks the transaction, Voyager will have to repay its customers with crypto-assets available on hand, in which case, customers will end up receiving less payout.</p>
<h2>Opposition</h2>
<p>The latest development comes a week after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) reportedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-objects-to-binance-us-buying-voyager-digital-for-1-billion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">opposed</a> Binance US&#8217; proposal to purchase Voyager assets. The focus of the SEC&#8217;s argument was that the crypto exchange has not sufficiently demonstrated having the necessary funds required to settle the deal. The SEC added that Binance US also did not outline how it plans to secure the assets of Voyager customers.</p>
<p>Despite the pushback, Judge Glenn greenlit the deal despite citing that the Commission will have the opportunity to object to the deal receiving final approval in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-receives-initial-approval-to-acquire-voyager-digitals-assets-report/" rel="nofollow">Binance US Receives Initial Approval to Acquire Voyager Digital&#8217;s Assets: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dutch Crypto Exchange Refuses DCG&#8217;s Offer to Pay 70% of its Debt</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dutch-crypto-exchange-refuses-dcgs-offer-to-pay-70-of-its-debt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232704</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitvavo.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitvavo.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitvavo said that the repayment of just a part of the outstanding amount is "not acceptable."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dutch crypto exchange Bitvavo claimed to have received an offer from Digital Currency Group (DCG) on January 9th to repay 70% of its debt within an acceptable period.</p>
<p>However, the company refused the offer citing that the crypto conglomerate has sufficient funds available for full repayment.</p>
<ul>
<li>The development comes days after the trading platform revealed it is actively engaged in conversations with DCG to recover the resulting debt along with other creditors and advisors.</li>
<li>The official <a href="https://blog.bitvavo.com/dcg-update-statement-10-01-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The residual amount is still under discussion with DCG as they are only willing to repay part of it within a period acceptable to Bitvavo. As creditors, the latter is not acceptable because DCG has sufficient funds available for full repayment.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Digital Currency Group is currently under investigation by the US Department of Justice’s Eastern District of New York as well as the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The focus is on the internal transfers between the company and its troubled subsidiary &#8211; crypto lending firm &#8211; Genesis Global Capital.</li>
<li>The ongoing financial distress was spurred by Genesis becoming one of the companies to be affected by the FTX contagion.</li>
<li>It halted withdrawals on November 16th, citing liquidity issues, and has been involved with investment bank Moelis &amp; Company for restructuring purposes.</li>
<li>It was earlier reported that Genesis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">owes</a> $900 million to the crypto exchange Gemini. The two platforms jointly operated together a product called Gemini Earn, which enabled users to earn 8% interest on their loans.</li>
<li>Gemini also accused DCG of failing to repay Genesis, which, in turn, resulted in the failure of payments to its clients.</li>
<li>Since the unraveling, Barry Silbert, the head of DCG, has been under tremendous backlash. Cameron Winklevoss, the Gemini co-founder, claimed that Silbert has been unwilling to find a solution and even <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-for-the-removal-of-dcg-ceo-barry-silbert/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">requested</a> that the Board remove him as the CEO.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dutch-crypto-exchange-refuses-dcgs-offer-to-pay-70-of-its-debt/" rel="nofollow">Dutch Crypto Exchange Refuses DCG&#8217;s Offer to Pay 70% of its Debt</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>India&#8217;s WazirX Releases Proof-of-Reserves With Over 1:1 Liability Ratio</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/indias-wazirx-releases-proof-of-reserves-with-over-11-liability-ratio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 19:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232725</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/WazirX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/WazirX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[90% of user funds of WazirX are in Binance wallets, according to the recently published proof-of-reserve report. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Indian crypto exchange WazirX released its proof-of-reserves (PoR) report disclosing its reserves-to-liability ratio of over 1:1. Alongside the paper, published by CoinGabbar, a third-party platform that tracks crypto assets, WazirX also made its wallet addresses, and list of exchanges available to the public.</p>
<p>At press time, the Indian company <a href="https://www.coingabbar.com/en/proof-of-reserve/Wazirx" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">had</a> over $283 million of total user assets in the form of stablecoin USDT.</p>
<h2>Proof-of-Reserves</h2>
<p>WazirX, in a <a href="https://wazirx.com/blog/wazirx-proof-of-reserves/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a>, highlighted that the platform is not only India’s largest crypto exchange by volume but is also the largest in terms of reserves. According to the report, 90% of user assets are held in wallets at Binance despite a very public spat between the CEOs of the two crypto exchanges &#8211; CZ and Nischal Shetty &#8211; over WazirX&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-wazirx-promise-to-cooperate-with-ed-on-ownership-and-shady-transactions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ownership.</a></p>
<p>Meanwhile, the remaining user asset balance of 10% is stored in hot and warm wallets. This adds to nearly $257.25 million and $26.59 million, respectively.</p>
<p>The wallets used by the platform are multi-sig with multiple private keys required to perform certain tasks, thereby making it difficult to get compromised.</p>
<p>Over the last two months, several crypto exchanges have rushed to publish PoR reports in a seeming attempt to reassure clients their funds are safe after FTX&#8217;s meltdown. WazirX is the latest to hop on the trend. In case of liquidation, the company assured the customers that it has sufficient funds &#8220;till the last minute&#8221; to enable withdrawals in case of liquidation.</p>
<p>Commenting on the report, WazirX&#8217;s Vice President, Rajagopal Menon, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are committed to building India’s top crypto exchange responsibly and securely, and full transparency is a key part of that commitment. By making our wallet addresses, list of exchanges, and independent Proof of Reserves report available to the public, we hope to provide our users with the trust and security they deserve.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>WazirX&#8217;s FY&#8217;22</h2>
<p>With the market sinking, WazirX&#8217;s trading volume fell sharply by 76% in the 12 months period ending December. However, the crypto exchange raked in more than 7X growth in its scale in the fiscal year ending March 2022, most of which can be attributed to the 2021 bull market cycle.</p>
<p>Its operating revenue in FY22 was <a href="https://entrackr.com/2023/01/wazirx-crosses-100-mn-in-revenue-in-fy22-profit-grows-6-4x/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">recorded</a> to be at $108.4 million, increasing by over 632% from $14.8 million the previous fiscal year. WazirX&#8217;s largest source of revenue was commissions that originated from trading. This accounted for 94% of the collections which surged to $101.9 million in FY22 from $14.25 million in FY21.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indias-wazirx-releases-proof-of-reserves-with-over-11-liability-ratio/" rel="nofollow">India&#8217;s WazirX Releases Proof-of-Reserves With Over 1:1 Liability Ratio</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Fiasco Won&#8217;t Include Lots of Selling: Novogratz Comments on Crypto State</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-fiasco-wont-include-lots-of-selling-novogratz-comments-on-crypto-state/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232682</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Mike_Novogratz.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Mike_Novogratz.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Novogratz believes the DCG debacle will not cause any major price sell-off. He also thinks that firms cutting jobs are doing the right thing. 
 ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto proponent and CEO of Galaxy Digital, Mike Novogratz, commented on the fiasco between two industry participants &#8211; Digital Currency Group (DCG) and Gemini &#8211; and how it will affect the entire market.</p>
<p class="p2">The American investor <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/01/10/galaxy-digital-ceo-mike-novogratz-2022-was-a-grand-washout-for-crypto-and-growth-stocks.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noted</a> that although the issue &#8220;isn&#8217;t good news&#8221; for the industry, it won&#8217;t involve massive selling that will affect crypto prices as it plays out over the next quarter.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>The DCG-Gemini Fiasco</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Recall that the DCG debacle started in the wake of FTX&#8217;s insolvency in November 2022. Shortly after FTX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for bankruptcy, Genesis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-halts-withdrawals-for-its-lending-arm-following-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted</a> users&#8217; withdrawal, citing &#8220;extreme market dislocation and loss of industry confidence caused by the FTX implosion.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p2">The liquidity crunch also caused Genesis&#8217; business partner Gemini to halt withdrawals from its lending platform. According to reports, Genesis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">owes</a> Gemini Earn&#8217;s users over $900 million. Since then, problems have been piling up for Genesis and its parent company, DCG.</p>
<p class="p2">Earlier this week, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss <span class="s1"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-for-the-removal-of-dcg-ceo-barry-silbert/" data-wpel-link="internal">wrote</a> an open letter</span> to the board of DCG, demanding its CEO Barry Silbert&#8217;s immediate removal for misleading statements about Genesis&#8217;s financial status.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Crypto Is in a Transition Period: Novogratz</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Like many other crypto proponents, the Galaxy Digital CEO believes the bear market offers the industry an opportunity to heal and rebuild.</p>
<p class="p2">According to him, crypto and growth stocks experienced a &#8220;grand washout&#8221; last year, and multiple firms were hampered, leading to revenue shrinks.</p>
<p class="p2">Novogratz explained that the crypto market is neither in a good nor bad position as it is facing several experiences that have not been before. As a result, entities and individuals must cut costs to survive the period.</p>
<figure id="attachment_69888" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-69888" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-69888" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover.jpg" alt="mike_novogratz_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/mike_novogratz_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-69888" class="wp-caption-text">Mike Novogratz. Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Firms Cutting Jobs Doing the Right Thing</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Since the crypto crash in April, crypto companies have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-crypto-companies-slashed-their-workforce-since-the-market-crash-in-april/" data-wpel-link="internal">laid off</a> thousands of employees to stay afloat. The job cut trend has continued into the new year, with firms like Coinbase going into a second round of layoffs.</p>
<p class="p2">While referring to Coinbase&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" data-wpel-link="internal">decision</a> to slash its workforce <span class="s1">again</span>, Novogratz opined that the CEOs of firms that have made such a move are doing the right thing.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;2022 was a grand washout for growth stocks and for crypto and so anything associated with it…got hampered as many of the crypto stocks did. I think CEOs Brian at Coinbase and any rational CEOs are doing the right thing,&#8221; Novogratz said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Novogratz noted that 2023 would be a year of survival and upturn as the market heals.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;The outlook for crypto is not horrible but it&#8217;s not great. We&#8217;ve got regulatory headwinds we didn&#8217;t have before, we&#8217;ve got time to heal and rebuild the narrative and so people are gonna cut costs and survive this transition period,&#8221; he stated.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-fiasco-wont-include-lots-of-selling-novogratz-comments-on-crypto-state/" rel="nofollow">DCG Fiasco Won&#8217;t Include Lots of Selling: Novogratz Comments on Crypto State</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s the Next Target for Ethereum if $1,300 Holds (ETH Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-next-target-for-ethereum-if-1300-holds-eth-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232742</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price is on the verge of breaking out from a significant resistance level after testing it for quite a while. However, there are still some obstacles for the price to overcome in order for a new bullish phase to begin. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the daily timeframe, the price is [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price is on the verge of breaking out from a significant resistance level after testing it for quite a while. However, there are still some obstacles for the price to overcome in order for a new bullish phase to begin.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price is breaking above the key $1300 resistance level after finally surpassing the 50-day moving average. In case of a bullish breakout, the 200-day moving average found at around $1400 would be next in line, followed by the $1800 level.</p>
<p>The 200-day moving average is considered a benchmark used to indicate whether the market is in a bullish or bearish trend, and a breakout above it could potentially lead to a mid-term uptrend.</p>
<p>However, there is still a considerable chance for rejection, which could lead to a drop back toward the $1000 support level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232747" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232747" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232747 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_110123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-11-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232747" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour timeframe, the momentum is seemingly fading away after a few bullish days, as the price is struggling to break above the $1350 resistance level.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator, which has been flashing an overbought signal for a while now, is also demonstrating a bearish divergence between the two last price highs. Therefore, there is a significant probability of a bearish pullback or even a reversal around the current level.</p>
<p>In the event of a reversal, a rapid decline toward the $1100 support area would be expected. The $1100 level would be the bulls&#8217; last resort, which a breakdown from would likely lead to a massive crash and further elongation of the bear market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232746" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232746" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232746 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1101232" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-11-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232746" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>A bull market is always accompanied by an uptrend in the Active Addresses metric as more people get interested in cryptocurrencies when their prices jump significantly. Hence, the market faces higher activity, with more people sending and receiving coins.</p>
<p>In contrast, during the bearish stage of the market, people start to realize massive losses and leave as the prices are declining rapidly. As a result, the market faces lower activity, and the Active Addresses metric starts to plummet substantially.</p>
<p>The following chart demonstrates the Active Addresses metric(30-day MA) alongside ETH&#8217;s price. As is evident, the metric has been declining during the recent bearish stage of the market and has dropped to new yearly lows. This signifies a notable lack of activity and interest among market participants.</p>
<p>Overall, Ethereum is going through a significant capitulation state, and the next bull market won’t be anticipated unless the capitulation is over.</p>
<figure id="attachment_232748" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-232748" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-232748 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_active_addresses_chart_110123" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Active-Addresses-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-232748" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-next-target-for-ethereum-if-1300-holds-eth-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s the Next Target for Ethereum if $1,300 Holds (ETH Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s the Amount of FTX Shares Tom Brady and Gisele Bundchen Will Probably Lose</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-amount-of-ftx-shares-tom-brady-and-gisele-bundchen-will-probably-lose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 16:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kevin O'Leary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232645</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Brady_Gisele_FTX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Brady_Gisele_FTX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The list of people and firms owning FTX shares include Tom Brady, Gisele Bundchen, Kevin O'Leary, Sequoia Capital, and Thoma Bravo.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The NFL legend Tom Brady and his ex-wife Gisele Bundchen collectively own nearly 1.8 million FTX shares. Their investment will most likely be entirely wiped out due to the exchange&#8217;s demise in November.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other prominent people and companies who <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTQzNzE2Nw==&amp;id2=-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">invested</a> in the former crypto giant include the likes of Kevin O&#8217;Leary, Robert Kraft, Thoma Bravo, and Sequoia Capital.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Who Has FTX Shares?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of crypto&#8217;s most catastrophic events &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">the crash of FTX</a> &#8211; caused multi-billion financial losses to numerous clients and investors. And while those who deposited money on the platform have a slight chance to receive some sort of compensation, this is highly unlikely for the individuals who purchased shares of the exchange.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The list of prominent figures who bought an equity stake in FTX spreads far and wide, and the name of Tom Brady sits at the top. Arguably the greatest NFL athlete owns over 1.1 million common shares of FTX, while his ex-spouse &#8211; Gisele Bundchen &#8211; has 686,761 stocks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American billionaire and owner of The New England Patriots &#8211; Robert Kraft &#8211; purchased 110,000 Series B Preferred shares of FTX Trading and 479,000 common shares. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The popular TV personality and a keen proponent of the cryptocurrency industry &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Leary &#8211; comes next. Mr. Wonderful owns 139,000 Class A Common shares and 12,631 Series A Preferred shares of West Realm Shires (the firm that controls FTX US). Additionally, his investment platform &#8211; O&#8217;Leary Ventures &#8211; has 25,944 common shares and 6,486 Series B-1 Preferred shares of FTX Trading.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Canadian also served as an ambassador of the platform, for which he inked a $15 million deal. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/FredRadford/status/1590843252437299201" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">declared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in October (a few weeks before the exchange&#8217;s doom) that FTX is among the safest places for investors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">High-profile monetary organizations have also purchased FTX shares over the past few years. Sequoia Capital owns 2.3 million common shares, 572,335 Series B-1 Preferred shares, and 4.8 million Series B Preferred shares of FTX Trading.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thoma Bravo has 4.4 million Series A Preferred shares of West Realm Shire and 4.6 million Series B Preferred shares of the former crypto behemoth. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hedge fund Tiger Global owns 323,612 Series C Preferred shares of FTX Trading and 6.6 million Series A Preferred shares of West Realm Shire.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Justice Instead of Reimbursement?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former CEO of FTX &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) &#8211; and other executives stepped down at the same time when the trading venue </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for bankruptcy protection. The new boss John Ray, though, could not assure that customers will be refunded for their losses:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;At the end of the day, we&#8217;re not going to be able to recover all the losses here.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Being aware that reimbursing is an arduous task, investors could at least expect some sort of justice and jail time for the people responsible for the crash. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The alleged main culprit &#8211; SBF &#8211; spent a week in the Bahamian Fox Hill Prison before the authorities deported him to the USA a few days before Christmas. He was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">released</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on a record $250 million bond and currently lives at his parents&#8217; house.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> not guilty to the accusations that he knowingly defrauded investors and was involved in wire fraud and money laundering operations. His trial date is set for October 2. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the contrary, Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang &#8211; former executives at FTX and its sister company Alameda Research &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-alameda-crisis-caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> guilty that they had a connection to the exchange&#8217;s fall and the investor losses.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-amount-of-ftx-shares-tom-brady-and-gisele-bundchen-will-probably-lose/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s the Amount of FTX Shares Tom Brady and Gisele Bundchen Will Probably Lose</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget Launches Fund Custody Service with Dedicated Wallet to Elevate Safety</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-launches-fund-custody-service-with-dedicated-wallet-to-elevate-safety/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232770</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitget_Fund_Custody.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitget_Fund_Custody.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Users with total assets over 100,000 USDT may apply for a separate custodial wallet Victoria, Seychelles 11 Jan 2023 &#8211; Leading crypto exchange Bitget launches the Fund Custody service for professional investors and institutions. The service will provide dedicated wallets to qualified accounts to maximize protection of customers&#8217; funds [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p><em>Users with total assets over 100,000 USDT may apply for a separate custodial wallet</em></p>
<p>Victoria, Seychelles 11 Jan 2023 &#8211; Leading crypto exchange Bitget launches the <a href="https://www.bitget.com/en/support/articles/12560603776207" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Fund Custody service</a> for professional investors and institutions. The service will provide dedicated wallets to qualified accounts to maximize protection of customers&#8217; funds on the platform. The exchange also recently released the latest snapshot of its Merkle tree Proof of Reserves to reassure users that their assets are held in 1:1 reserves.</p>
<p>To be qualified for the Fund Custody service, users will have to store more than or equal to 100,000 USDT worth of combined assets (including spot, futures, Bitget Earn, fiat currency, and leverage) on the platform. Once the application is approved, the user will then be assigned a separate custodial wallet, with its own dedicated address to check and withdraw funds separated from the main reserve.</p>
<p>Storing the asset in a separate wallet prevents users&#8217; funds from being affected in case of emergencies such as an exchange run, or other cybersecurity threats. The wallet assets will be rounded on a daily basis to make sure the user still meets the required conditions.</p>
<p>Additionally, Bitget has recently updated its Merkle tree snapshot as of December 31, 2022, and the latest reserve ratio of the most popular tokens are as follows:</p>
<p>• BTC reserves are held at 650%<br />
• USDT reserves are held at 185%<br />
• ETH reserves are held at 237%</p>
<p>The exchange is committed to be fully reserved holding customers&#8217; assets on the platform at least on a 1:1 reserves ratio.</p>
<p>Gracy Chen, Managing Director of Bitget, remarks, &#8220;Protecting our customers&#8217; assets is, and always will be, our top priority at Bitget. Ever since the collapse of some bad actors in the industry, we have taken a series of initiatives for heightened protection. In addition to the security offered with our US$300 million Bitget Protection Fund and Merkle tree Proof of Reserves, we are proud to announce our Fund Custody service. The new service, equipped with industry-grade security systems and dedicated wallet addresses for qualified users, shall further foster transparency and elevate safety for our users and their funds.&#8221;</p>
<h2>About Bitget</h2>
<p>Bitget, established in 2018, is the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange with innovative products and social trading services as its key features, currently serving over 8 million users in more than 100 countries around the world.</p>
<p>The exchange is committed to providing a secure, one-stop trading solution to users and aims to increase crypto adoption by collaborations with credible partners, including legendary Argentinian footballer Lionel Messi, the Italian leading football team Juventus, and the official esports events organizer PGL.</p>
<p>To learn more about Bitget, please visit <a href="https://www.bitget.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://www.bitget.com</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-launches-fund-custody-service-with-dedicated-wallet-to-elevate-safety/" rel="nofollow">Bitget Launches Fund Custody Service with Dedicated Wallet to Elevate Safety</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Locates $5 Billion in Assets, Attorney Says: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-locates-5-billion-in-assets-attorney-says-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232743</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ftx_trial_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ftx_trial_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Over $5 billion worth of cash, liquid crypto, and other liquid assets have been located, an attorney revealed today.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a hearing from today, a bankruptcy attorney said that FTX has managed to locate over $5 billion of assets.</p>
<ul>
<li>Per a CoinDesk <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/01/11/ftx-has-recovered-over-5b-in-assets-bankruptcy-attorney-says/?utm_term=organic&amp;utm_content=editorial&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_campaign=coindesk_main" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, the attorney said that they&#8217;ve managed to locate over $5 billion of cash and liquid assets.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>We have located over $5 billion of cash, liquid cryptocurrency, and liquid investment securities measured at petition date value.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>This number doesn&#8217;t include the $450 million in cryptocurrencies that are currently held by the Securities Commission of the Bahamas.</li>
<li>In addition, they also located illiquid cryptocurrency tokens where they hold such large positions that can&#8217;t be offloaded without affecting the market for said tokens.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-locates-5-billion-in-assets-attorney-says-report/" rel="nofollow">FTX Locates $5 Billion in Assets, Attorney Says: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Secures Regulatory Approval in Sweden</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-regulatory-approval-in-sweden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 14:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Union]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sweden]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232726</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/binance_sweden_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/binance_sweden_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Sweden became the seventh EU jurisdiction where Binance received a regulatory green light.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Swedish Financial Supervisory Authority registered the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance &#8211; as a financial institution for management and trading in virtual currency in the Scandinavian country.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is the seventh EU nation where the platform has received such a license, with the previous six being Italy, France, Spain, Poland, Cyprus, and Lithuania.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/swedish-fsa-grants-binance-seventh-regulatory-approval-in-eu-1385399034980621164" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that its Swedish subsidiary &#8211; Binance Nordics AB &#8211; obtained registration from the country&#8217;s financial watchdogs after &#8220;months of constructive engagement.&#8221;</span></li>
<li>The authorization enables local consumers to access its products and services, such as buying cryptocurrencies with euro, making withdrawals against the fiat currency, trading, and staking.</li>
<li>Richard Teng &#8211; Head of Europe and MENA at Binance &#8211; said the latest registration demonstrates the company&#8217;s commitment to collaborate with regulators to &#8220;uphold global standards.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are deeply grateful for the support from the Swedish Financial Supervisory Authority throughout the application process and for the approval. Sweden is now amongst the growing list of global jurisdictions that have granted regulatory approval to Binance,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Roy van Krimpen &#8211; the Head of Benelux at the exchange &#8211; assured the trading venue had complied with all necessary AML policies to abide by Swedish law and requirements.</span></li>
<li>The exchange has previously secured regulatory greenlight from six other members of the European Union, with <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-scores-first-european-regulatory-approval-in-france/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">France</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-scores-second-european-regulatory-approval-this-time-in-italy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Italy</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and Spain being some of them.</span></li>
<li>CZ <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-wants-to-apply-for-a-crypto-license-in-germany/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year that Binance is &#8220;building a compliance team&#8221; that could help the firm obtain a license in Europe&#8217;s largest economy &#8211; Germany.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-regulatory-approval-in-sweden/" rel="nofollow">Binance Secures Regulatory Approval in Sweden</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
