<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 01:19:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SEC Files Complaint Against Gemini and Genesis for Allegedly Selling Unregistered Securities</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 01:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=233019</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/US_SEC4.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC is going against Gemini and Genesis, saying they offered unregistered securities via Gemini Earn.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a complaint against Genesis Global Capital and Gemini Trust Company for allegedly selling unregistered securities to retail investors in the US. The SEC is seeking permanent injunctive relief, disgorgement of ill-gotten gains, plus front-end interest and civil penalties.</p>
<p>Both companies raised billions of dollars by offering and selling securities to US investors through the Gemini Earn crypto asset lending program.</p>
<h2>Gemini and Genesis: A Brief Story</h2>
<p>Gemini, a US cryptocurrency exchange, and Genesis, a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group, teamed up in December 2020 to offer cryptocurrency lending services. The SEC says that Gemini charged a fee for its services that sometimes amounted to 4.29% of the returns paid by Genesis to investors.</p>
<p>In November 2022, Genesis stopped paying interest to Gemini&#8217;s clients and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">halted withdrawals</a>, claiming it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-looking-to-sell-off-some-assets-as-genesis-owes-creditors-over-3b-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">lacked sufficient liquid assets</a> to fulfill withdrawal requests due to the volatility of the crypto asset market. However, at the time, Genesis held approximately more than $900 million in assets from more than 340,000 Gemini investors, who were forced to cancel the Gemini Earn program in early January without the ability to get a refund.</p>
<p>As a consequence, SEC Chairman Gary Gensler <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-7#:~:text=%E2%80%9CToday&#039;s%20charges%20build%20on%20previous,It%20promotes%20trust%20in%20markets." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">alleged</a> that &#8220;Genesis and Gemini offered unregistered securities to the public, bypassing disclosure requirements designed to protect investors.&#8221; Gensler said the complaint aims to show that crypto lending platforms and intermediaries must comply with US securities laws.</p>
<p>Director of the SEC&#8217;s Division of Enforcement, Gurbir S. Grewal, said the recent collapse and suspension of the Genesis program highlights the need for these platforms to comply with federal securities laws. He also called on all those affected by the Genesis program or who have information about it to contact the SEC&#8217;s Whistleblower Program.</p>
<h2>The SEC Pushes For More Power Over Crypto Businesses</h2>
<p>The complaint states that Genesis and Gemini were offering securities through the Gemini Earn program without registering them, violating federal securities laws. Additionally, the complaint states that the companies failed to disclose important information about the program to investors, including the risks of lending their crypto assets and the fact that the companies would be able to use the assets as they pleased without disclosing that to investors.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the complaint also claims that Genesis and Gemini falsely stated that the program was fully collateralized when, in reality, it was not. The SEC also claims that the companies made false statements about the value of the assets in the program.</p>
<p>The commission is seeking permanent injunctive relief, disgorgement of ill-gotten gains, plus front-end interest and civil penalties. The regulator also seeks to bar Genesis and Gemini from committing future securities violations —which might not be too far away for Genesis if rumors are true that it is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-lender-genesis-slashes-staff-and-mulls-bankruptcy-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">considering bankruptcy</a>.</p>
<p>The SEC said this case is a reminder that all crypto lending platforms and intermediaries need to comply with US securities laws to protect investors and ensure a fair and transparent market. As SEC Chairman Gensler stated, &#8220;It&#8217;s not optional. It&#8217;s the law.&#8221;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-files-complaint-against-gemini-and-genesis-for-allegedly-selling-unregistered-securities/" rel="nofollow">SEC Files Complaint Against Gemini and Genesis for Allegedly Selling Unregistered Securities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chair Gensler Advises US Troops to Stay Away From Crypto</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-gensler-advises-us-troops-to-stay-away-from-crypto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 23:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232865</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gary_Gensler.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Gary_Gensler.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Gensler thinks US soldiers should not deal with cryptocurrencies, expecting most tokens to eventually "fall."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Chairman of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8211; Gary Gensler &#8211; told members of the US Army to refrain from investing in cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes the sector lacks proper regulation and most digital assets will collapse in the future.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Wave of Scepticism</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of crypto&#8217;s keenest critics &#8211; Gary Gensler &#8211; launched another bashing manifest against the industry. In a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/i/spaces/1jMKgLywzYgGL" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter Space</a>, he pointed out that an increasing number of US soldiers have shown interest in the digital asset sector. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, he claimed that the niche looks like the &#8220;Wild West&#8221; due to its unregulated nature, meaning that people should not interact with it. The SEC Chairman also thinks most of the existing cryptocurrencies will crash at some point, triggering painful losses for investors:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Most of these 10 or 15,000 tokens will fail. That&#8217;s because venture capital fails, new startups fail &#8211; but also because history tells us that there&#8217;s not much room for micro currencies, meaning, you know, we have the US dollar and Europe has the euro and the like.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_189321" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-189321" style="width: 667px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-189321" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler.jpg" alt="Gary_Gensler" width="667" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 667px) 100vw, 667px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-189321" class="wp-caption-text">Gary Gensler, Source: Reuters</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gensler advised soldiers not to &#8220;get caught up in the FOMO — the fear of missing out,&#8221; maintaining that bitcoin and the alternative coins are &#8220;non-compliant&#8221; and &#8220;highly speculative.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SEC Commissioner Caroline Crenshaw also joined the discussion, stating that cryptocurrencies are well-known for being involved in fraudulent schemes.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;They claim to be transparent, what&#8217;s on the blockchain is transparent, but the rest of what&#8217;s there is not transparent, and I think there have been some examples of that recently,&#8221; she concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tough Stance But With a Few Friendly Winks</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite criticizing the cryptocurrency industry, the SEC has also displayed some kind of positive view of it over the past years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Commission </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gary-gensler-the-sec-has-no-plans-to-follow-china-and-ban-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> not to follow China&#8217;s example and ban everything related to digital assets in October 2021. Instead, Gensler said the agency will collaborate with bank regulators to impose enhanced supervision on the sector.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The SEC doubled down a few days later, approving the launch of ProShares Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) &#8211; the first BTC Futures ETF in the US. Back then, Gensler </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gensler-on-futures-etf-approval-were-technology-neutral-not-policy-neutral/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">commented</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I think that we in the official sector should be technology neutral, but not policy neutral.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Chairman </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-will-focus-on-regulating-crypto-exchanges-in-2022-says-gary-gensler/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the beginning of last year that the watchdog will focus on applying stricter rules on cryptocurrency exchanges. Despite those efforts, several platforms collapsed in 2022, with </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> being the most notable example.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-gensler-advises-us-troops-to-stay-away-from-crypto/" rel="nofollow">SEC Chair Gensler Advises US Troops to Stay Away From Crypto</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fraudsters Drain $2.5M in Crypto Exit Scam: CertiK Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fraudsters-drain-2-5m-in-crypto-exit-scam-certik-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 21:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232945</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto industry proved to be a breeding ground for scams, exploits, and hacks in 2022.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Less than two weeks into the new year, malicious entities have already started doing what they do best.</p>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/CertiKAlert/status/1613497811965804544" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a> by the blockchain security company CertiK, two recently created contracts &#8211; CirculateBUSD and CirculateWBNB &#8211; have been pumped away by the creators.</p>
<ul>
<li>The funds have been bridged to Ethereum and deposited into the OFAC-sanctioned coin mixer, Tornado Cash.</li>
<li>By doing so, the creators of the two contracts managed to pull off what looks like an exit scam by draining $2.5 million. CertiK <a href="https://twitter.com/CertiKAlert/status/1613497811965804544" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">explained</a>,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This incident is made possible due to a backdoor in the `Start Trading` function. Function calls a malicious unverified contract SwapHelper(0x112f8) with signature 0x6343756. CirculateBUSD deployer is set into SwapHelper who receives the funds.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In a recent report, CertiK <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/december-lowest-month-of-2022-for-crypto-thefts-certik/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">noted</a> observing a large number of incidents last year despite the crypto bear market and added that there will be no respite in exploits, flash loans, or exit scams this year as well.</li>
<li>In fact, the illicit transaction volume of crypto-assets hit a record level of $20 billion, according to Chainalysis &#8216;Crypto Crime Report.&#8217;</li>
<li>The firm also found that transactions related to sanctioned entities amplified by over 100,000-fold in 2022, accounting for 44% of the previous year&#8217;s illicit activity.</li>
<li>Chainalysis recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-tornado-cashs-activity-didnt-cease-completely-post-ofac-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">pointed</a> out that pulling the plug on a decentralized protocol such as Tornado Cash isn&#8217;t very easy, which explains why the coin mixer&#8217;s activity hasn&#8217;t completely stopped post-OFAC sanctions.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fraudsters-drain-2-5m-in-crypto-exit-scam-certik-report/" rel="nofollow">Fraudsters Drain $2.5M in Crypto Exit Scam: CertiK Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Soars to $19,000 Amid $380 Million in Liquidations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-to-19000-amid-380-million-in-liquidations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 20:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232994</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoing_green_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/bitcoing_green_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[
Bitcoin has returned to a trading price last seen before FTX’s implosion. 
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin has returned to $19,000 for the first time since October, soaring beyond its low trading range established after FTX’s collapse.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The move has many on crypto twitter calling for a new bull market – though some believe it&#8217;s a bull trap. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin traded for $17,911 early on Thursday, experiencing some volatility after December’s CPI inflation </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/enhanced-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-cpi-numbers-clock-in-at-6-5/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">clocked in</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> at 6.5%. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The asset pumped by roughly $1000 at about 17:35 UTC, and has maintained its elevated price level since then. By 19:47 UTC, Bitcoin had reached $19,036, before pulling back to $18,864 at writing time.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Data from </span><a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinglass</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows that the crypto market has experienced $382 million worth of liquidations within the past 24 hours, affecting over 59,000 traders, stemming from recent volatility. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Most of these liquidations took place on ETH trades, which alone accounted for $165 million in wiped trades. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The biggest liquidations took place on OKX, on a BTC-USDT swap with a value of $3.52 million.</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="qme" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://t.co/8uh1DBgyec" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/8uh1DBgyec</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PlanB (@100trillionUSD) <a href="https://twitter.com/100trillionUSD/status/1613621552368734208?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index has </span><a href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">risen</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from a score of 26 on Wednesday to 30 today, indicating less fear in the market. The index uses multiple signals to gauge market sentiment at all times, including price direction and social media. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-to-19000-amid-380-million-in-liquidations/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Soars to $19,000 Amid $380 Million in Liquidations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DCG Looking to Sell Off Some Assets as Genesis Owes Creditors Over $3B: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-looking-to-sell-off-some-assets-as-genesis-owes-creditors-over-3b-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232972</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Digital_Currency_Group.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Digital_Currency_Group.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DCG could be heading for a desperate move in order to repay some of its debts. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Digital Currency Group (DCG), the parent company of wholly-owned subsidiary, crypto brokerage firm Genesis, is reportedly looking to offload some of its venture capital portfolios to raise funds to cover part of the latter&#8217;s debt crisis.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Genesis halted withdrawals in November, becoming the latest crypto lender to face a financial crisis.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the Financial Times on Tuesday (January 12, 2023), anonymous sources <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/eb22bfab-ef05-48ce-83de-ebb904a35dca" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that Genesis is currently swimming in a debt worth over $3 billion.</li>
<li>The crypto lender earlier hired Moelis, a New-York headquartered global investment bank, to explore options, but there seems to be no interest in injecting capital into Genesis.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, parent company DCG is trying to raise funds to offset the debt, as revealed by people familiar with the matter. The conglomerate is looking to sell off some of its venture capital portfolios.</li>
<li dir="ltr">According to sources, these include 200 crypto exchanges, custodians, and banks, valued at $500 million. Some of DCG&#8217;s major venture portfolios include Coinbase, Blockchain.com, Kraken, and bankrupt FTX.</li>
<li dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Genesis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/troubled-crypto-firm-genesis-owes-geminis-customers-900-million-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">owes Gemini Earn users</a> around $900 million, while Dutch crypto exchange Bitvavo is owed €280 million. Bitvavo <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dutch-crypto-exchange-refuses-dcgs-offer-to-pay-70-of-its-debt/" data-wpel-link="internal">refused</a> DCG&#8217;s offer to repay 70% of its debt, stating that the conglomerate has the means to make full repayment.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Genesis, which is battling a financial crisis, halted withdrawals in November 2022 after being affected by FTX&#8217;s collapse. Recently, Gemini co-founder Cameron Winklevoss called on the Board of DCG to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-for-the-removal-of-dcg-ceo-barry-silbert/" data-wpel-link="internal">remove</a> its CEO, Barry Silbert, stating that Silbert is incapable of finding a solution that is reasonable for creditors.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-looking-to-sell-off-some-assets-as-genesis-owes-creditors-over-3b-report/" rel="nofollow">DCG Looking to Sell Off Some Assets as Genesis Owes Creditors Over $3B: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Breaks Silence During Home Arrest; Gives Details on FTX (In)solvency</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-breaks-silence-during-home-arrest-gives-details-on-ftx-insolvency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232976</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/sbf_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried breaks down how Alameda’s balance sheet crumbled across 2022, eventually rendering the trading firm insolvent.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) has released a written statement detailing his account of FTX and Alameda Research’s collapse, including approximations of each firm’s financials before it took place. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The former CEO maintains that FTX could have made customers “substantially whole” within a few weeks, had he not been pressured to file for bankruptcy. </span></p>
<h2>The Pre-Mortem</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The <a href="https://sambf.substack.com/p/ftx-pre-mortem-overview" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a>, titled “FTX Pre-Mortem Overview,” began by pinning Alameda’s collapse on three causes. These included a large and mostly illiquid asset pile, a failure to hedge its exposure during the bear market, and Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ)’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-blames-cz-for-the-ftx-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in early November. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Specifically, in early 2022, Bankman-Fried believes Alameda held roughly $100 billion in net asset value – only 7% of which was considered “liquid.” By November 10th, however, the firm had just $11 billion in assets left – only $3 billion of which were “liquid” – and a NAV of $0. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This triggered a wave of contagion comparable to the collapse of Three Arrows Capital in June – much of which as felt by FTX due to Alameda’s large margin position on the platform. Nevertheless, Bankman-Fried claimed that FTX still held $8 billion in assets of “varying liquidity” before he stepped down as its CEO. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Furthermore, another $4 billion in potential support had reportedly been tabled by other groups in the form of signed letters of intent (LOIs) – though he believes these pathways have been abandoned by FTX’s new leadership.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Even now, I believe that if FTX International were to reboot, there would be a real possibility of customers being made substantially whole,” he said. </span></p>
<h2>Accusations of Fraud</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankman-Fried has been widely accused of committing fraud and theft together with Alameda Research by comingling user assets at FTX with Alameda’s trading funds. FTX’s new CEO, John Ray, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-used-client-assets-for-margin-trading-at-alameda-confirms-bankruptcy-lawyer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">testified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> as much to Congress in December, while MicroStrategy’s executive chairman Michael Saylor has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-the-most-diabolical-thing-about-ftx-and-sbf-according-to-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">claimed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the same on multiple podcasts. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bankman-Fried </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">denies</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> any such claims, however. “I didn’t steal funds, and I certainly didn’t stash billions away,” he said.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By 2022, Alameda counted for about 2% of trading volume on FTX, which was far lower than in previous years. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Bankman-Fried, Alameda would have survived passed November if not for CZ and Binance’s “extremely effective months-long PR campaign against FTX.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Alameda CEO Caroline Ellison and FTX co-founder Gary Wang have each </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-alameda-crisis-caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pled guilty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to defrauding FTX’s investors in collaboration with Bankman-Fried. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-breaks-silence-during-home-arrest-gives-details-on-ftx-insolvency/" rel="nofollow">SBF Breaks Silence During Home Arrest; Gives Details on FTX (In)solvency</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Bitcoin Future Active ETF to Hit Hong Kong Stock Market on Jan 13</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/samsung-bitcoin-future-active-etf-to-hit-hong-kong-stock-market-on-jan-13/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Samsung]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232924</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Samsung_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Samsung_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Samsung's new Bitcoin ETF listing targets both retail and institutional investors. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Samsung investment arm&#8217;s subsidiary &#8211; Samsung Asset Management Hong Kong (SAMHK) &#8211; outlined plans to list Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF on the Hong Kong stock market starting January 13.</p>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.samsungetfhk.com/product/3135/#Overview" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announcement</a>, the fund in question is a sub-fund of Samsung ETFs Trust III, an umbrella unit trust established under Hong Kong law.</p>
<h2>Samsung&#8217;s Bitcoin Futures Active ETF</h2>
<p>The Samsung Bitcoin Futures Active ETF seeks to provide economic exposure to BTC&#8217;s value by investing in Bitcoin futures products listed on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME). Both retail and institutional investors will be able to gain exposure to Bitcoin. The fund, however, does not invest in the crypto asset directly.</p>
<p>Detailing the fund&#8217;s investment strategy, Samsung&#8217;s site noted,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In seeking to achieve the Sub-Fund’s investment objective, the Manager adopts an active investment strategy whereby it will enter into and have exposure of up to 100% of the Sub-Fund’s net asset value (“NAV”) in Bitcoin Futures on CME.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Following the development, Park Seong-jin, head of Samsung Asset Management Hong Kong, said in a statement,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Hong Kong is the only market in Asia where bitcoin futures ETFs are listed and traded in the institutional market. It will be a new option for investors who are interested in Bitcoin as a competitive product that reflects their experience in risk management.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The latest offering comes on the heels of Samsung Asset Management listing the Samsung Blockchain Technologies ETF and Samsung Asia Pacific Metaverse ETF in the region, catering to the growing demand for Web3-related exposure.</p>
<h2>Hong Kong&#8217;s Crypto Ecosystem</h2>
<p>Currently, Hong Kong is the only Asian venue for trading Bitcoin future ETFs. CSOP Asset Management, which submitted its applications to the Securities and Futures Commission (SFC), <a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/currencies/csop-bitcoin-futures-etf-closes-higher-hong-kong-debut-2022-12-16/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">became</a> the first company to list its Bitcoin Futures ETF for trading in Hong Kong&#8217;s stock market. Mirae Asset Global Investments is also in the process of bringing futures-based crypto asset ETFs to investors in the region.</p>
<p>Hong Kong government has been eyeing to reclaim its position as a global hub of crypto companies and even <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-intends-to-become-a-crypto-hub-could-that-trigger-next-bull-run/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">hinted</a> at launching a mandatory licensing program for platforms that will enable retail crypto trading.</p>
<p>More recently, the legislative council <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-includes-licensing-regime-for-crypto-exchanges-in-new-legislation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">added</a> a new amendment to the Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorist Financing (Amendment) Bill 2022 to fit the crypto industry, introducing a licensing regime for virtual asset service providers (VASPs). As part of the new legislation, misleading crypto advertisements will face severe clampdowns, while fraudulent transactions will attract hefty penalties as well as imprisonment.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/samsung-bitcoin-future-active-etf-to-hit-hong-kong-stock-market-on-jan-13/" rel="nofollow">Samsung Bitcoin Future Active ETF to Hit Hong Kong Stock Market on Jan 13</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enhanced Bitcoin Volatility as US CPI Numbers Clock in at 6.5%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/enhanced-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-cpi-numbers-clock-in-at-6-5/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232934</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin reacted with a sudden move that took it south by a few hundred dollars.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Labor Department just announced the inflation numbers (CPI) for the last month of 2022, and they stand at 6.5% YoY.</p>
<p>At the same time, most experts also nailed the core CPI increase at 5.7%.</p>
<ul>
<li><em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cpi-numbers-coming-on-thursday-what-to-expect/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier this week that all eyes will be on the US Labor Department come Thursday, with most estimations suggesting that the inflation numbers will be around 6%.</li>
<li>The actual figures announced by the US government are precisely the same &#8211; a YoY increase of 6.5% for the general CPI and a 5.7% rise in the core CPI (excluding food and energy). Nevertheless, both are still the highest December jumps in over 40 years.</li>
<li>As with previous US CPI announcements, this one had an immediate effect on bitcoin&#8217;s price.</li>
<li>The asset has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-records-longest-rally-since-july-volatility-comes-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">on a roll since the start of the year</a>, gaining almost $2,000 in less than two weeks.</li>
<li>This resulted in a price jump to a monthly high of $18,400 earlier today. However, the US CPI numbers took BTC from over $18,300 to just under $18,000 in a matter of minutes. As of now, though, the asset has recovered some ground and is back above $18,000.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/enhanced-bitcoin-volatility-as-us-cpi-numbers-clock-in-at-6-5/" rel="nofollow">Enhanced Bitcoin Volatility as US CPI Numbers Clock in at 6.5%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador&#8217;s Bitcoin-Backed Bonds Inch Closer After Greenlighting Digital Asset Bill</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-backed-bonds-inch-closer-after-greenlighting-digital-asset-bill/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232856</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/El_Salvador_Volcano_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/El_Salvador_Volcano_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The passing of its "Digital Asset Issuance" will bring a much-anticipated regulatory framework for tokenized securities, altcoins, and businesses.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>El Salvador faced a tough year after making Bitcoin legal tender in the country. But the country&#8217;s Legislative Assembly voted to pass a historic &#8211; Digital Asset Issuance legislation &#8211; that is expected to set the stage for the issuing of President Nayib Bukele&#8217;s bitcoin bonds, aka, the Volcano Bonds.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/bitcoinofficesv/status/1613242046944530440" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">new law</a> will focus on setting up a legal framework around the issuance of digital assets and the wider crypto classification, which includes every other type of digital asset in the market besides Bitcoin. This means that there is now a definitive regulatory framework for tokenized securities, altcoins, and businesses that wish to transact or offer services focused on digital assets other than Bitcoin.</p>
<h2>El Salvador&#8217;s Bitcoin Bonds</h2>
<p>President Bukele first introduced the plan to issue $1 billion in bonds on Blockstream&#8217;s Liquid Network, a federated Bitcoin sidechain, in November 2021. The bond issuance was delayed on numerous occasions partly due to the relentless bear market and the subsequent turmoil that significantly dragged Bitcoin&#8217;s price down.</p>
<p>The digital assets bill finally hit the Legislative Assembly in November 2022 and was passed on January 11th this year with Bukele&#8217;s Nuevas Ideas &#8211; 62 legislator voting in favor and 16 against.</p>
<p>With the bond issuance, half of the money would be invested in Bitcoin while the remaining would be deployed into building the necessary infrastructure for the BTC industry. Moreover, the bonds will pay a 6.5% yield and allow fast-tracked citizenship for investors.</p>
<p>According to El Salvador&#8217;s ONBTC, the legislation also marks the creation of the National Digital Assets Commission. This regulating agency will be tasked with implementing the securities law and protecting the rights of digital asset buyers as well as issuers in the nation as well as preventing fraudulent entities from operating.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The law plants another flag in history for El Salvador. Under President Bukele, El Salvador has become not only the safest country in Latin America but now also the country with the strongest protection of a person&#8217;s rights to economic freedom, sovereignty &amp; prosperity.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Tether&#8217;s Paolo Ardoino <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1613317428812959745" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">called</a> the event &#8211; a &#8220;great victory&#8221; and added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;El Salvador is on an amazing trajectory, providing to its citizens their best tools for freedom.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Launch of National Bitcoin Office (ONBTC)</h2>
<p>The law comes on the heels of the formation of the newly created &#8220;specialized administrative unit&#8221; National Bitcoin Office (ONBTC), formed in November of 2022. As reported earlier, ONBTC will be tasked with &#8220;designing, diagnosing, planning, programming, coordinating, following up, measuring, analyzing and evaluating projects related to Bitcoin for the economic development of the country.&#8221;</p>
<p>Furthermore, cryptocurrency exchange Bitfinex, in a <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/announcements/el-salvadors-historic-digital-asset-securities-law-passes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, revealed that it will be a technology provider for El Salvador&#8217;s Volcano Token.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are watching this development with excitement, along with the rest of the Bitcoin community.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-backed-bonds-inch-closer-after-greenlighting-digital-asset-bill/" rel="nofollow">El Salvador&#8217;s Bitcoin-Backed Bonds Inch Closer After Greenlighting Digital Asset Bill</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Molecular Group Established its New Investment Company XMG Capital in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/molecular-group-established-its-new-investment-company-xmg-capital-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=232904</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Molecular_Group.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Molecular_Group.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, 12th January 2023] Molecular Group, a leading investment firm based in Hong Kong, is pleased to announce the establishment of its new investment company, XMG Capital. Located in Singapore, a hub for the rapidly growing blockchain industry, XMG Capital will focus on investing in high-quality blockchain projects, equity, tokens, and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, 12th January 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.xmg.com/?tag=0" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Molecular Group</a>, a leading investment firm based in Hong Kong, is pleased to announce the establishment of its new investment company, XMG Capital. Located in Singapore, a hub for the rapidly growing blockchain industry, XMG Capital will focus on investing in high-quality blockchain projects, equity, tokens, and Web 3.0 technologies in the payment sector. The company will also explore opportunities in the wider fintech space.</p>
<p>With its favorable policies towards the blockchain industry and a strong track record of supporting innovation, Singapore is the perfect location for XMG Capital. The company&#8217;s team has a wealth of experience in finance and technology and is committed to identifying and supporting the most promising blockchain-based projects and companies.</p>
<p>XMG Capital is excited to be at the forefront of the transformation that the blockchain is bringing to various industries and is dedicated to helping drive the growth and development of the ecosystem. The company looks forward to creating value for its clients and stakeholders through its investments in the blockchain space.</p>
<p>As the blockchain industry continues to mature and evolve, XMG Capital is well-positioned to take advantage of the many opportunities it presents. The company will focus on identifying projects with strong potential for growth and success and will work closely with its portfolio companies to help them realize their full potential.</p>
<p>In addition to equity and token investments, XMG Capital will also consider strategic partnerships and other types of collaborations that can help its portfolio companies succeed. The company is committed to building long-term relationships with its portfolio companies and supporting their growth over the long term.</p>
<p>XMG Capital is excited to be a part of the vibrant and innovative community of blockchain companies and investors in Singapore and looks forward to contributing to the industry&#8217;s growth and success. The company is confident that its team&#8217;s expertise and experience, combined with the strong ecosystem in Singapore, will allow it to make a meaningful impact in the industry.</p>
<h2>About Molecular Group</h2>
<p>Molecular Group focuses on blockchain investments, the group also has a high-profile digital asset quantification and protection team, as well as a service platform for digital asset investment called Molecular Future. Additionally, the company has a research institute for the digital economy called Molecular Hub, as well as a blockchain media and exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/molecular-group-established-its-new-investment-company-xmg-capital-in-singapore/" rel="nofollow">Molecular Group Established its New Investment Company XMG Capital in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
