<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:08:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.4</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Wallet Strike Expands Support to 3 Billion People, Targets Global South</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wallet-strike-expands-support-to-3-billion-people-targets-global-south/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lightning Network]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251521</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_192078914_s-2019-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_192078914_s-2019-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Strike now supports India, New Zealand, Guatemala, Honduras, and over 40 more countries. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Strike – a Bitcoin payments company and remittance app – announced Friday that it is now available for download to over 3 billion people worldwide, including dozens of new countries.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The international expansion will allow wallet users in India, South Korea, Sri Lanka, and other countries to remit payments to one another in both USD and BTC. </span></p>
<h2>Targeting the Global South</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Speaking at Bitcoin 2023 in Miami, Strike CEO Jack Mallers </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7qRWurFaUD0&amp;ab_channel=BitcoinMagazine" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">explained</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the company’s expansion efforts were primarily targeted toward those that needed better payment tools and technology the most. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“It’s a lot of the global south,” said Mallers. “The global south has a lot to do with Bitcoin – they have a lot to say for where the world is going.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">An inexhaustive list of 47 supported countries presented during Mallers’ presentation included Bhutan, Brazil, Ecuador, Guatemala, Honduras, Kenya, New Zealand, Paraguay, and Uganda, alongside formerly announced expansions like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-brings-the-bitcoin-lightning-network-to-argentina/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Argentina</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Nigeria, Kenya, and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-brings-lightning-based-remittance-payments-to-africa/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ghana</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Within those countries, Strike leverages the Bitcoin lightning network to enable fast and immediate Bitcoin and dollar-based remittances worldwide. Lightning is a layer 2 network that bypasses the fees of Bitcoin’s base chain, which can </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">rise</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to levels that make small transactions infeasible when placed under stress. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Global outreach for Strike was a two-and-a-half-year effort, which partly involved working with regulators in El Salvador’s Bitcoin Office to create a licensing structure for Bitcoin companies to legally operate. The nation was the first besides the United States to support Strike, and is now home to the headquarters of Mallers’ company E4. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Maller stressed the importance of giving the global south access to a “money app,” rather than an existing “exchange” like Binance, FTX, or Coinbase, which encourages “speculative gambling.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We wanna compete with Binance,” said Mallers. “We know that the 3 billion people we’re serving – they got their first experience and their first Bitcoin from FTX, from Binance, from a lot of these exchanges that haven’t been totally proven to be trustworthy.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Strike also now supports Lightning Address, which lets users set up an email-like identifier for sending them Bitcoin over lightning, rather than using a QR code.</span></p>
<h2>Strike’s Previous Announcements</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Announcements at the Bitcoin conference have become something of a tradition for Mallers: In June 2021, he announced that El Salvador would make Bitcoin legal tender, which was an international first at the time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In 2022, Mallers revealed at the same conference that his company was partnering with Shopify, as well as NCR – the largest point-of-sale payment provider in the United States. This would ideally let users of Bitcoin’s lightning network pay with Bitcoin at popular stores like Walmart, McDonalds, Home Depot, and others. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though unexpected obstacles have severely delayed the full rollout of those plans, the company </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/strike-integrates-lightning-with-point-of-sale-giant-clover/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">integrated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with POS giant Clover in January.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-wallet-strike-expands-support-to-3-billion-people-targets-global-south/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Wallet Strike Expands Support to 3 Billion People, Targets Global South</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Investment Fund HashKey in Talks to Raise $200M at $1B Valuation (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-investment-fund-hashkey-in-talks-to-raise-200m-at-1b-valuation-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251424</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Hashkey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Hashkey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Besides Hong Kong, HashKey Group has a presence in Singapore and Japan.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Hong Kong takes center stage in the regional crypto business, local firms are trying to expand their customer base.</p>
<p>One such firm, HashKey Group, is reportedly raising up to $200 million in funding to tap new opportunities.</p>
<h2>HashKey Eyes $200 Million in Funding</h2>
<p>Targeting a more significant share of the Asian crypto market, Hong Kong-based crypto financial service provider HashKey Group plans to expand its operations. The crypto investment fund is reportedly in early-stage talks with venture capitalists to raise $200 million at over $1 billion Valuation.</p>
<p>A Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-05-19/crypto-firm-seeks-funds-at-1-billion-plus-value-as-hk-opens-up?sref=3REHEaVI#xj4y7vzkg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> said the details of the deal being discussed are not available as the talks are being held privately.</p>
<p>HashKey Group is in the entire crypto ecosystem – Exchange, Brokerage, Venture Capital, Custody Solutions, and Web3 Infrastructure. In addition, HashKey Pro holds a permit to operate virtual asset exchange in Hong Kong. Besides HashKey Pro, only OSL Exchange has this <a href="https://www.sfc.hk/en/Welcome-to-the-Fintech-Contact-Point/List-of-licensed-virtual-asset-trading-platforms" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">permit</a>.</p>
<h2>HashKey Capital to Launch Two Liquid Funds</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, HashKey Capital <a href="https://www.dealstreetasia.com/stories/hashkey-capital-funds-343567" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">plans</a> to launch at least two liquid funds to tap the opportunities in the secondary market, CEO of HashKey Capital and HashKey Singapore Deng Chao said in a recent interview.</p>
<p>In September last year, Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-regulator-allows-hashkey-capital-to-manage-a-100-crypto-portfolio/" data-wpel-link="internal">granted</a> HashKey Capital, the investment arm of HashKey Group, a license to manage a portfolio of 100% digital assets.</p>
<h2>Regional Crypto Hub</h2>
<p>Hong Kong has moved steadily in recent months with plans to provide a transparent regulatory environment for crypto firms. In addition, it announced a timeline to allow retail trading in digital assets.</p>
<p>From June 1, Hong Kong will issue licenses to virtual digital asset service providers, paving the way for retail investors to trade in leading cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ether.</p>
<p>Several big-ticket conferences on digital assets have occurred in the city-state in the last few months, generating global interest in Hong Kong’s potential to emerge as a regional crypto business hub.</p>
<p>In a landmark decision recently, the Hong Kong High Court ruled that crypto is property and can be held in trust. The court ruling goes a long way in instilling confidence among crypto investors. The asset class is now <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-court-declares-crypto-to-be-property-in-new-ruling/" data-wpel-link="internal">at par</a> with other intangible assets such as stocks and bonds.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-investment-fund-hashkey-in-talks-to-raise-200m-at-1b-valuation-report/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Investment Fund HashKey in Talks to Raise $200M at $1B Valuation (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cynthia Lummis Says Biden&#8217;s 30% Miner Tax “Isn’t Going to Happen”</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cynthia-lummis-says-bidens-30-miner-tax-isnt-going-to-happen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 22:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251505</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/CynthiaLummis.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/CynthiaLummis.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s most supportive senator is opposed to the Biden Administration’s Bitcoin mining tax, but thinks renewable mining still has a future across the globe. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin-friendly Republican Senator Cynthia Lummis doesn’t think the Biden Administration’s proposed 30% excise tax on Bitcoin miners isn’t likely to make it through the House. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On stage at Bitcoin Miami 2023, the politician remained supportive of miners, and believes the industry’s proliferation throughout the United States is a matter of national security. </span></p>
<h2>Mining: Dirty or Clean?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">During the </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=484pyxKnxIQ&amp;ab_channel=BitcoinMagazine" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Lummis spoke about the excise tax with Perianne Boring, a member of the crypto advocacy group Chamber of Digital Commerce. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Boring explained that companies within their membership, which represent 50% of Bitcoin’s hashrate, were “incredibly concerned” that they wouldn’t be able to operate in the United States if the tax were passed. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Lummis responded with reassurance for Bitcoiners. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“That isn’t going to happen,” she said. “It’s absolutely important that the development of this technology, as well as Bitcoin mining itself, to occur in the United States.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Biden’s excise tax was quietly </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/president-bidens-2024-tax-plan-to-target-crypto-wash-trading-and-capital-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">introduced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in his 2024 budget plan, which also included new rules targeting crypto wash trading and capital gains. Earlier this month, the President’s Council of Economic Advisors released </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">guidance</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for Congress to approve the tax, to face consequences for causing “local environmental pollution,” and “higher energy prices.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Contrary to their claims, Lummis believes Bitcoin mining is a net boon for the environment and energy grids, rather than a harm. In her home state of Wyoming, she explained that miners are already being used as an economic alternative for venting waste methane from oil and gas wells, preventing the methane gas from being flared into the atmosphere. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Bitcoin can actually be advantageous to stabilizing a grid,” she added, “because there can be efforts to mine Bitcoin when [energy] use is low, and then to scale back the mining when energy use is high.”</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Miner Can Mine Anywhere</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin miners engaged in similar stabilization efforts with the Texas grid in July 2022 in which miners paused their operations when </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-in-texas-halt-operations-due-to-a-severe-heat-wave/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">requested</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by regulators to conserve energy for homes. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, the Texas House of Representatives is currently weighing a proposal to cap the number of miners that can join the demand response program – which financially compensates miners for the time they spend offline.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As of Q4 2022, the global Bitcoin mining Industry had a green energy mix of 58.9%, per survey results from the Bitcoin Mining Council. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Should federal and state-level efforts ultimately succeed in discouraging mining in America, Lummis still isn’t worried about the global survival of the industry. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Miners can mine anywhere,” she said, referencing the inexpensive Norway-based </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/norway-is-producing-1-of-btc-hash-rate-using-renewable-energy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">hydroelectric mining operations</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. “There are opportunities all over the world for Bitcoin mining to occur in jurisdictions that are friends… and foes.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cynthia-lummis-says-bidens-30-miner-tax-isnt-going-to-happen/" rel="nofollow">Cynthia Lummis Says Biden&#8217;s 30% Miner Tax “Isn’t Going to Happen”</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Frogs Best Selling NFT for 24-Hrs as BTC Catches Pepe Mania</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-frogs-1-selling-nft-for-24-hrs-as-btc-catches-pepe-mania/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 21:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251258</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pepe_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Pepe_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It seems the Pepe hype has spread to other places as well. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ordinals are coming in dank this week. Bitcoin Frogs was the #1 selling NFT collection for the 24-hour period on Wednesday. Frogs sales outpaced Bored Apes Yacht Club, CryptoPunks, and other popular collections for the day.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" data-wpel-link="internal">BRC-20 memecoin</a> project describes itself as &#8220;10,000 unique frog collectibles minted directly on the Bitcoin Blockchain.&#8221; As of publication time, 3,700 frogs had owners. Meanwhile, hundreds were listed for sale on NFT marketplaces.</p>
<p>That gecko that sells insurance might be worrying these days about losing his job to Pepe the Frog. Cryptocurrency NFTs <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/pepe-coin-crypto-price-explained-fe6cf942" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">inspired by</a> PEPE Coin on Ethereum are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-but-on-solana-and-other-web-3-0-frogs-got-a-bump-on-pepe-coin-mania/" data-wpel-link="internal">all the rage</a> in the ecosystem this year.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Frogs Hops to #1 in NFT Trading Volume</h2>
<p>According to data from CryptoSlam, a leading aggregator of on-chain NFT analytics, Bitcoin Frogs sales reached a trading volume above $2.2 million for the day. Frogs outsold Bored Apes NFTs for Wednesday, May 17th.</p>
<p>Some of the BAYC sellers may have even been cashing out to buy PEPE Coin in the meanwhile. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/diversification-doesnt-work-nft-influencers-that-made-or-lost-money-with-memecoins/" data-wpel-link="internal">There&#8217;s been</a> a lot of that going on during this season of Pepe fever.</p>
<p>CryptoSlam data shows Bitcoin Frogs selling for an average price of 0.12 BTC (around $3,200 USD) on Wednesday. The PEPE-inspired boom in sales overtook Bored Apes Yacht Club despite the higher average sale price of around $83,000 for the blue-chip NFT.</p>
<h2>BRC-20 Brings PEPE Mania to Bitcoin</h2>
<p>BAYC NFT trading volume clocked in at 11 transactions for the day. Meanwhile, the voracious demand for frog meme crypto and Bitcoin ordinal NFTs pushed Bitcoin Frogs transactions up to 627 on Wednesday. Buyers are picking up the cute frog meme ordinals from NFT marketplaces like Magic Eden and Ordinals Wallet.</p>
<p>The inclusion of cool NFT features like generative AI to produce unique properties in each mint brings the artistry of smart contract minting to the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<p>But the mint was calibrated to maintain some fungibility among the frog. The project notes: &#8220;Rarities of all traits within each layer are equal, allowing subjective appreciation of aesthetics and satoshi-based rarities to emerge.&#8221;</p>
<p>Two separate meme coin manias have converged to drive the high demand for Bitcoin Frogs. One is the frog craze instigated by PEPE coin&#8217;s meteoric rise at the beginning of the month.</p>
<p>The other is the Bitcoin ordinals trend that started in January. Bitcoin ordinals inscriptions hit the 5 million milestone earlier this month. The number of BRC-20 tokens issued <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">doubled in</a> a week&#8217;s time to set the new record.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-frogs-1-selling-nft-for-24-hrs-as-btc-catches-pepe-mania/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Frogs Best Selling NFT for 24-Hrs as BTC Catches Pepe Mania</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Visa Deploys &#8216;Paymaster&#8217; Contracts on Ethereum Testnest for Gasless Transactions</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/visa-deploys-paymaster-contracts-on-ethereum-testnest-for-gasless-transactions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 20:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251363</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/visa_eth_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/visa_eth_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Visa has begun blockchain experiments to enable the use of ERC-20 tokens for gas fees or remove the need for transaction fees altogether.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Global payments giant Visa has deployed experimental smart contracts on Ethereum’s Goerli testnet to pilot gasless transactions through account abstraction.</p>
<p>The two sets of smart contracts, dubbed <a href="https://goerli.etherscan.io/address/0x5419D0cCc5B8f648ec47fF35E25A10886d612435#code" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Paymaster</a>, will simplify user interaction with the Ethereum network by performing complex tasks and managing transaction costs on behalf of other accounts.</p>
<h2>Visa Tests Paymaster for Frictionless Transactions</h2>
<p>Account abstraction is a proposal to increase flexibility in the management and behavior of Ethereum accounts by separating the control of an account from its associated private key, allowing it to be controlled by a smart contract. The mechanism is enabled by ERC-4337, a new Ethereum standard launched in March.</p>
<p>Visa <a href="https://usa.visa.com/solutions/crypto/rethink-digital-transactions-with-account-abstraction.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">seeks</a> to leverage the ERC-4337 standard to implement an intermediary currency conversion service. The first version of the Paymaster contract explores whether users can pay transaction fees with alternative tokens like dollar-pegged <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-ceo-says-theres-a-meaningful-future-for-stablecoins-and-cbdcs/" data-wpel-link="internal">stablecoins</a> or central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</p>
<p>The contract can collect any ERC-20 token from users and convert them into ether (ETH) based on the current exchange rate to pay for gas fees on the users’ behalf, thus removing the need to acquire ETH only for transaction fees.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This sample contract contains the governing logic for both the Paymaster and its custom ERC-20 token. To this contract, we introduced an allowlist and a function to update the token-to-ETH conversion rate. This allowed us to better simulate real-life conditions where the exchange rate between ETH and a token is dynamic,” Visa said in a report.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Enabling Gasless Transactions</h2>
<p>The payments giant believes the Paymaster concept can incentivize adoption by allowing users to only fund the gas cost at the time of the transaction without any pre-funding requirements to optimize their cash-flow management.</p>
<p>The second Paymaster contract seeks to eliminate the need for users to cover gas fees by themselves, just like in web2 peer-to-peer (P2P) transactions, by using a solution proffered by account abstraction, which allows third parties, such as fintech wallet providers, to handle the costs.</p>
<p>In this case, the third parties can act as Paymasters, completely sponsoring transaction fees for users. The experiments are based on the starter code provided by the Ethereum Foundation and ERC-4337 core team.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We tested two core user operations: 1) paying with ERC-20 tokens using ERC-4337 Paymaster; 2) Sponsoring transaction fees for users (aka gasless txs) with ERC-4337 Paymaster</p>
<p>— Catherine Gu (@catgu_) <a href="https://twitter.com/catgu_/status/1658695253447315456?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-deploys-paymaster-contracts-on-ethereum-testnest-for-gasless-transactions/" rel="nofollow">Visa Deploys &#8216;Paymaster&#8217; Contracts on Ethereum Testnest for Gasless Transactions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>1 Month After Shapella Staked Ether (ETH) Exceeds 20M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/1-month-after-shapella-staked-ether-eth-exceeds-20m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake (PoS)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251378</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ethereum_shanghai_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ethereum_shanghai_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shapella upgrade enabled withdrawals for the first time from the proof-of-stake blockchain.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ether holders are rushing to stake their tokens with network validators. This has pushed the deposit activity to the highest level since the Shapella upgrade last month.</p>
<p>In fact, the total volume of crypto-asset staked has exceeded 20 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>The latest <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1659453920295411714" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">milestone</a> comes a month after the much-anticipated Ethereum Shanghai upgrade that brought a record-breaking weekly inflow of Ether deposits for staking.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It has only been a month since Ethereum&#8217;s Shapella Upgrade. Since then, the total volume of $ETH staked has surpassed 20 million.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Shanghai enabled the withdrawal of tokens previously locked up in staking contracts for the first time &#8211; a crucial step after last year&#8217;s Merge to complete the network&#8217;s transition to validating transactions through staking from an &#8220;energy extensive&#8221; mining-based system.</li>
<li>Such an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/thats-a-first-after-shanghai-ether-staked-volume-exceeds-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">influx</a> appears to have been fueled by institutional staking service providers and investors reinvesting rewards after withdrawal.</li>
<li>An Ethereum whale, identified as an early participant in the blockchain ICO, <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1659038348571471873" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">emerged</a> after being dormant for over two years and staked a whopping 4,032 ETH (worth nearly $7.4 million), according to Lookonchain.</li>
<li>Lido Finance is one of the major staking platforms that has taken center stage after the success of Shapella. It lets anyone stake any amount instead of going the traditional way of depositing directly to the mainnet, which requires a minimum deposit of 32 ETH.</li>
<li>The service deployed its v2 iteration on May 15th after passing an on-chain vote.</li>
<li>Despite being one of the largest liquid staking protocols on Ethereum, Lido had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-finance-withdrawal-activation-only-0-42-processed-so-far/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">processed</a> only 0.42% of the withdrawals so far.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/1-month-after-shapella-staked-ether-eth-exceeds-20m/" rel="nofollow">1 Month After Shapella Staked Ether (ETH) Exceeds 20M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Swaprum DEX Drained in $3M Crypto Rugpull</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/swaprum-dex-drained-in-3m-crypto-rugpull/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251425</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/rugpull_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/rugpull_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The platform's native token, expectely, dumped by over 99% in hours.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Developers of decentralized exchange (DEX) Swaprum have drained $3 million in ether (ETH) tokens from the protocol in an apparent rugpull, otherwise known as an exit scam.</p>
<p>The exchange, launched on the Ethereum <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/layer-2-scaling-solution-arbitrum-flips-ethereum-in-daily-transactions/" data-wpel-link="internal">layer-2 network Arbitrum</a>, offers high farming rewards, low swapping fees, and potential earnings of up to 100% annual percentage yield (APY).</p>
<h2>Swaprum Rugpulls Users for $3M</h2>
<p>Blockchain security firm Peckshield <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1659404608685604864" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">flagged</a> the incident on Friday, disclosing that approximately 1,628 ETH, worth roughly $3 million, was drained from Swaprum’s liquidity pools. Onchain <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xaaf8b44376f4ef3ed477eeeb3553b7623fef5e1c#tokentxns" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> shows that the exit scam was executed in the late hours of Thursday.</p>
<p>The team first <a href="https://arbiscan.io/tx/0x36fef881f7e9560db466a343e541072a31a07391bcd0b9bcdb6cfe8ae4616fc0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">removed</a> the liquidity provided for SAPR, the platform’s native token, on the exchange and sold the assets for ETH. The funds were subsequently transferred from Arbitrum to Ethereum and then moved to cryptocurrency mixer Tornado Cash.</p>
<p>A deeper analysis by blockchain security platform Beosin <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1659482295211016194" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that the deployer of the Swaprum smart contract added a backdoor function to enable the theft of liquidity pool tokens staked by users. The deployer used the add() function to drain the pool for their profit.</p>
<p>Beosin further explained that the Swaprum team had upgraded the normal liquidity collateral reward contract to another containing backdoor functions.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The backdoor function add() will transfer LP tokens from the contract to the _devadd address. By querying the _devadd address, it will return the ‘Swaprum:Deployer’ address. The Swaprum: Deployer uses the stolen LP tokens in the previous step to remove liquidity,” the security platform stated.</p></blockquote>
<h2>SAPR Token Plunges 99%</h2>
<p>As a result of the rugpull, SAPR lost almost all of its value. At writing time, the token was trading at $0.000022 with a 24-hour trading volume of $83, signifying a 99% decline from its previous price of $0.147 before the rugpull, according to data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<p>In addition, the social media accounts of Swaprum on Twitter, GitHub, and Telegram have been deleted. Only the platform’s website was active at press time.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Swaprum’s rugpull is one of the largest exit scams on the Arbitrum network. The incident has overthrown that of DeFi protocol <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/largest-exit-scam-on-arbitrum-hope-finance-drained-for-2m/" data-wpel-link="internal">Hope Finance</a>, which suffered a $2 million exploit in February after a Nigerian hacker allegedly deployed a fake router on the platform.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swaprum-dex-drained-in-3m-crypto-rugpull/" rel="nofollow">Swaprum DEX Drained in $3M Crypto Rugpull</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP and PEPE Lead Markets, Bitcoin and Ethereum Flat but in Green: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-and-pepe-lead-markets-bitcoin-and-ethereum-flat-but-in-green-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251336</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple's XRP and PEPE are stealing the center stage this week, both in their respective categories. Meanwhile, BTC, ETH, and other majors are trading almost flat.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well, the past week had some exciting developments to offer, at least in certain segments of the market. The broader capitalization barely increased by around $5 billion, currently standing shy of $1.2 trillion. This came on the back of a relatively flat performance of major cryptocurrencies, but some altcoins managed to surprise. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s been a back-and-forth with Bitcoin this week. The cryptocurrency was trading at around $26,500 this time last week and managed to increase to around $27,500 a few days later. It plunged back below $27K, only to test $27,500 again on Thursday. The bears weren&#8217;t having it, though, and made another decisive swing down, putting BTC&#8217;s price where it&#8217;s currently trading at around $26,800, booking a slight increase of 1.3%.</p>
<p>Ethereum is also trading for a 2% increase on the weekly, followed by Cardano (ADA), MATIC, DOT, and TRX &#8211; all of which managed to book similar gains.</p>
<p>But that&#8217;s where things get more exciting.</p>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s XRP increased by around 8% in the past seven days, positioning it as the clear leader within the top 10 cryptocurrencies by means of total market cap. The reasons are probably two-fold. The judge presiding over the case against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) ruled against the agency&#8217;s motion to seal a certain record of former director Bill Hinman. Investors perceived this as bullish for XRP as it might have a positive impact on the outcome of the case. Ripple also entered a deal to acquire Metaco &#8211; a Swiss-based crypto custodian, for $250 million.</p>
<p>And then there&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a>. The memecoin that&#8217;s taken center stage in the cryptocurrency industry is up some 17% in the past week, leading the memecoin sector by a considerable margin. There&#8217;s no telling why PEPE is up but as with anything meme-related, it could be any number of reasons. It&#8217;s very interesting to see if it will maintain its position, though.</p>
<p>In any case, it remains very interesting to see how the market will shape in the following days and if XRP will continue on its positive trajectory.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,169B | 24H Vol: $34B | BTC Dominance: 44.4%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $26,829 (+1.3%) | ETH: $1,810 (+2%) | BNB: $309 (+1.1%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251473" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover.jpg" alt="xrp_pepe_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/xrp_pepe_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>We Asked ChatGPT Which 5 Cryptos Will Survive in 10 Years: The Answer Might Surprise You. </strong>We <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-which-5-cryptos-will-survive-in-10-years-the-answer-might-surprise-you/" data-wpel-link="internal">asked</a> the most popular AI language model on which five cryptocurrencies will survive in the next 10 years. The answer might surprise you.</p>
<p><strong>Tether Will Buy Bitcoin: Allocating 15% of Net Realized Operating Profits Regularly in BTC. </strong>The company behind the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin USDT &#8211; Tether &#8211; will be buying BTC. It <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-will-buy-bitcoin-allocating-15-of-net-realized-operating-profits-regularly-in-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that it will allocate as much as 15% of its net realized operating profits regularly.</p>
<p><strong>Coinbase Launches Zero-Fee Trading, But There Are Catches. </strong>The leading US-based cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Coinbase &#8211; is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launches-zero-fee-trading-but-there-are-catches/" data-wpel-link="internal">launching</a> zero-fee trading. However, there is a catch. Users will have to pay $30 per month to be able to take advantage of this feature, making it not exactly &#8220;zero-fee.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Ripple (XRP) Enters a $250 Million Deal to Acquire Metaco. </strong>Ripple, the company behind XRP, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-xrp-enters-a-250-million-deal-to-acquire-metaco/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the acquisition of the Swiss-based cryptocurrency custody provider &#8211; Metaco. The goal is to expand the firm&#8217;s services and grow within the institutional crypto custody market.</p>
<p><strong>SEC Says FIL Is A Security, Asks Grayscale to Retract Filecoin Trust’s Form 10 Application. </strong>The US Securities and Exchange Commission shows no mercy. It <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-says-fil-is-a-security-asks-grayscale-to-retract-filecoin-trusts-form-10-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that Filecoin (FIL) is a security and urged Grayscale to stop offering it to their clients.</p>
<p><strong>ChatGPT Predicts 8 Things That Will Happen to Crypto By 2033. </strong>ChatGPT <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-8-things-that-will-happen-to-crypto-by-2033/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> eight different things that will happen to the cryptocurrency industry in the next decade. From mainstream adoption to increased regulatory scrutiny, here&#8217;s what the AI thinks about the future of crypto.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, OP, and PEPE – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-19-eth-xrp-ada-op-and-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-and-pepe-lead-markets-bitcoin-and-ethereum-flat-but-in-green-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">XRP and PEPE Lead Markets, Bitcoin and Ethereum Flat but in Green: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Asked ChatGPT If Ethereum&#8217;s Price Can Flip Bitcoin in the Next 5 Years, Here&#8217;s the Answer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-if-ethereums-price-can-flip-bitcoin-in-the-next-5-years-heres-the-answer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251087</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Can ETH's price flip BTC? Will Ethereum overtake Bitcoin in the next 5 years? Let's find out what ChatGPT has to say. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A topic as old as time, if time was a few years old &#8211; will Ethereum flip Bitcoin in terms of total market cap? Will ETH overtake BTC?</p>
<p>This has been the &#8220;to be or not to be&#8221; in the cryptocurrency industry, and it pins communities against each other like no other. It&#8217;s true that BTC has been the predominant market leader ever since it has been created, but a few years ago, who would have thought that another cryptocurrency would have a market cap worth over 40% of Bitcoin&#8217;s? Well, that&#8217;s the case for Ethereum today.</p>
<p>So, we decided to do what any sane person in 2023 would do &#8211; ask an AI language model what it (?) thinks. ChatGPT is all the rage in 2023, so who better to ask?</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251248" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover.jpg" alt="ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ethereum_v_bitcoin_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Can Ethereum Flip Bitcoin?</h2>
<p>First things first, we prompted ChatGPT with this exact question: &#8220;Do you think Ethereum&#8217;s price can flip Bitcoin&#8217;s price in the next 5 years?&#8221;</p>
<p>The AI came back to us, explaining that this is an outcome that&#8217;s &#8220;uncertain and depends on various factors.&#8221;</p>
<p>These include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Adoption Rates</li>
</ul>
<p>According to ChatGPT, Ethereum&#8217;s robust ecosystem and use cases, such as DeFi, NFTs, and whatnot, could help it flip Bitcoin.</p>
<blockquote><p>Ethereum&#8217;s broader use cases, such as DeFi (Decentralized Finance), <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">NFTs (Non-Fungible Tokens)</a>, and smart contracts, could potentially drive wider adoption and thus increase its value relative to Bitcoin.</p></blockquote>
<p>Here&#8217;s where it got kind of interesting. You see, ChatGPT&#8217;s most recent knowledge cut-off on this topic was in September 2021. This means that it was before Ethereum transitioned to Proof-of-Stake.</p>
<p>That said, the second factor, according to the AI, is:</p>
<ul>
<li>Network Upgrades</li>
</ul>
<p>ChatGPT argues that &#8220;the successful completion of Ethereum&#8217;s planned upgrades, such as Ethereum 2.0, could significantly affect its price. This upgrade plans to improve the scalability, security, and sustainability of Ethereum, which could increase its attractiveness to investors and users.&#8221;</p>
<p>Well, Ethereum&#8217;s transition to proof-of-stake, otherwise known as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-merge-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-transition-to-ethereum-2-0/" data-wpel-link="internal">&#8220;The Merge,&#8221;</a> is already a fact in our timeline, and so far, it hasn&#8217;t really helped it get there.</p>
<h2>What Else Could Help ETH Flip BTC?</h2>
<p>The flippening can also take place under a few more conditions, according to ChatGPT. Regulation, for once, is among the factors.</p>
<blockquote><p>Changes in cryptocurrency regulation could impact prices. More restrictive regulations could lower prices, while more accommodating ones could raise them.</p></blockquote>
<p>While it does sound like an answer from Captain Obvious, it is true. Favorable regulation could push ETH&#8217;s price, but so far, the US government has taken a predatory approach, calling many of the projects built on Ethereum securities.</p>
<p>Going forward, the AI believes that market sentiment is also important. If enough investors believe Ethereum to be the better form of investment, it would inevitably lead to the flippening.</p>
<p>Last but not least, the broader economic factors, including inflation, economic growth, and overall changes in the financial sector, could also have an impact.</p>
<p>In conclusion, ChatGPT took a more cautious position and didn&#8217;t provide a straightforward yes or no answer. This was somewhat expected, but it what arguments would an AI use to structure a response to a question of this kind.</p>
<p>Of course, none of the above should be construed as financial advice. The content is solely for educational and entertaining purposes, and we do hope you had fun with it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-asked-chatgpt-if-ethereums-price-can-flip-bitcoin-in-the-next-5-years-heres-the-answer/" rel="nofollow">We Asked ChatGPT If Ethereum&#8217;s Price Can Flip Bitcoin in the Next 5 Years, Here&#8217;s the Answer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finblox Token (FBX) Listed on Major Exchanges After a Sold out Launchpad</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/finblox-token-fbx-listed-on-major-exchanges-after-a-sold-out-launchpad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251451</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Finblox, a leading crypto superapp backed and supported by behemoths like Dragonfly and Sequoia, is delighted to announce the remarkable success of its recent token launch, defying current market conditions and generating a trading volume exceeding 2 million USD in the first 12 trading hours. Preparation for the ICO [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>Finblox, a leading crypto superapp backed and supported by behemoths like Dragonfly and Sequoia, is delighted to announce the remarkable success of its recent token launch, defying current market conditions and generating a trading volume exceeding 2 million USD in the first 12 trading hours.</p>
<h2>Preparation for the ICO</h2>
<p>Leading up to the listing, Finblox witnessed impressive participation from the crypto community across various partner launchpads, with more than 3,000 unique addresses who purchased FBX during the pre-sale period from PoolZ, Decubate, Spores, and from Finblox’s own launchpad: FinLaunch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251455" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg" alt="finblox3" width="624" height="416" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/finblox3-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>As part of its comprehensive community strategy, Finblox conducted a series of compelling online and offline activities, including social media campaigns, learn-and-earn activities, and interactive ask-me-anything sessions.</p>
<p>The culmination of these efforts took shape in the form of highly successful offline meetups called Finblox Summit held in Manila, Philippines, and Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam last May 8 and 16, respectively, which brought together power users, partners, and media from the local communities.</p>
<p>FBX has further achieved a significant milestone by being listed on major exchanges, including Gate.io, MEXC Global, BTSE, starting May 18, 2023. The token&#8217;s all-time high during the ICO peaked at an astounding 500% above the listing price, demonstrating the market&#8217;s strong support for Finblox despite the volatility.</p>
<h2>Building a Sustainable Roadmap</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-251456" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg" alt="Finblox2" width="624" height="351" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Finblox2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>To further fortify the utility of Finblox Tokens, the superapp has <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7912800-party-to-30-30-apy-for-your-finblox-tokens?utm_source=hs_email&amp;&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz--MNmsh5keOgC-gZbc-IbWU2ZAdbXdxLujQ8zhXo_oyPfwXQbAK4pVZghFGQjzpbcKmP-7A" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">announced</a> a promotion of 30% APY for users who deposit their fresh FBX tokens into their Finblox Wallets between May 18 and July 18, 2023. This limited-time offer allows token holders to actively engage in the Finblox ecosystem while earning substantial rewards.</p>
<p>Finblox invites all token holders to take advantage of this exclusive offer by transferring their Finblox Tokens to their Finblox Wallets and embarking on a journey of earning rewards. By participating in this initiative, users become a part of the Finblox community while maximizing their potential within the platform.</p>
<p>Finblox has initiated a token burn in a strategic move to ensure fair value of the remaining tokens in circulation. As of May 19, 2023, 437 million tokens, valued at $3.07 million, representing 4.37% of the total supply, have been burnt.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our users can now be a part of the growth and development of the Finblox ecosystem. With the roadmap ahead, we invite the community to join us in the journey of democratising finance with Web3”, said Peter Hoang, CEO and Founder of Finblox.</p></blockquote>
<p>Users are encouraged to check out Finblox’s <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7919428-introducing-the-1st-fbx-burn-event" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">blog</a> to learn more about the token-burning activity. For more information on how you can accumulate more FBX tokens through the promotion, check out Finblox’s article <a href="https://help.finblox.com/en/articles/7912800-party-to-30-30-apy-for-your-finblox-tokens" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<h2>About Finblox</h2>
<p>Finblox is a crypto superapp backed by top-tier VCs like Sequoia Capital, Dragonfly, and Saison Capital. Users can earn up to 100x rewards by participating in the ecosystem of products, including trading, staking, and AI games.</p>
<p>Finblox Token (FBX) is the utility token native to the Finblox ecosystem. With FBX, users can enjoy perks that can be used across our entire suite of products &#8211; and shape the future direction of the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/finblox-token-fbx-listed-on-major-exchanges-after-a-sold-out-launchpad/" rel="nofollow">Finblox Token (FBX) Listed on Major Exchanges After a Sold out Launchpad</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
