<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Option Markets Keep Sending Bullish Signals – Here’s the Implications for BTC Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>Bitcoin options markets continue to signal that investors are anticipating further upside in the BTC price. According to a chart on The Block, the widely followed Bitcoin 25% delta skew has remained above zero since the middle of January and recently hit its highest since Q4 2021 at close to 6.0....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Option Markets Keep Sending Bullish Signals – Here’s the Implications for BTC Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Options</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Bull market</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102917/253660/bitcoin-3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6331437"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Mining Network Hits New Record Hash Rate Above 300 EH/s</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm</link><description>According to Bitcoin mining data tracking website MiningPoolStats, Bitcoin’s hash rate hit a new record high earlier this week. According to the website, the network reached the milestone of computing three hundred quintillion (300,000,000,000,000,000,000) hashes per second (300 EH/s)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Mining Network Hits New Record Hash Rate Above 300 EH/s&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102916/253651/bitcoin-miner.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2105861"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 27 January – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, CCHG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrencies are becoming increasingly popular as a way for investors to diversify their portfolios. With so many different coins and tokens available, it can be difficult to know which ones to buy.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this article, we will look at five of the best cryptos to buy today – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, and CCHG. We will discuss each coin's features and use cases in detail so that you can make an informed decision about which one is the right fit for your portfolio....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 27 January – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, CCHG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102902/253601/best-crypto-27-jan.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="331639"/></item><item><title>Formula 1 Racing Team Secures $100 Million Sponsorship from Crypto Casino – Is The Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>The crypto gambling platform based in Australia, Stake.com, has entered a partnership worth $100 million with the Alfa Romeo Racing team, indicating a comeback in crypto-related sponsorships. &lt;br /&gt;
This event marks one of the first and biggest sponsorship programs following the catastrophic collapse of FTX exchange which became known for its high-level and wide-reaching sponsorships....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Formula 1 Racing Team Secures $100 Million Sponsorship from Crypto Casino – Is The Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102907/253600/adobestock-110861591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1816993"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Moody’s to Develop a Scoring System for Stablecoins, Hive Ransomware Group Dismantled, Animoca Brands Subsidiary Hiring a Head of Degen Relationships</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-moodys-develop-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-hive-ransomware-group-dismantled-animoca-brands-subsidiary-hiring-head-of-degen-relationships.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-moodys-develop-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-hive-ransomware-group-dismantled-animoca-brands-subsidiary-hiring-head-of-degen-relationships.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Moody’s to Develop a Scoring System for Stablecoins, Hive Ransomware Group Dismantled, Animoca Brands Subsidiary Hiring a Head of Degen Relationships&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Moody's</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Legal</category><category>USA</category><category>FBI</category><category>Security</category><category>Argo</category><category>Animoca Brands</category><category>Gaming</category><category>SEC</category><category>Investment</category><category>Bitpay</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Career</category><category>Tax</category><category>Payments</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-moodys-develop-scoring-system-for-stablecoins-hive-ransomware-group-dismantled-animoca-brands-subsidiary-hiring-head-of-degen-relationships.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102846/253493/adobestock-tomertu-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="77786"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Jumps Up 10% in 7 Days – New Bull Market Starting?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-jumps-up-10-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has surged 10% in the past seven days, which has spurred speculation that a new bull market is beginning. While predicting the price of Bitcoin can be difficult, there are several factors to consider regarding its future prospects.  &lt;br /&gt;
With increased adoption around the world and a commitment to innovation, Bitcoin could be on track for another bull run in the near future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-jumps-up-10-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Jumps Up 10% in 7 Days – New Bull Market Starting?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-jumps-up-10-7-days-new-bull-market-starting.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102819/253545/market-roundup-night-27-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="516906"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as $300 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying SHIB?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-300-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib.htm</link><description>The Shiba Inu price has risen by 50% from its low point in December and its daily trading volume has seen an increase to $300 million.  &lt;br /&gt;
SHIB’s growth in volume and price has been reflected in its market cap, which stands at $6.8 billion. The meme coin is now the 13th largest crypto after toppling Litecoin (LTC). Shiba Inu has 549 trillion tokens in circulation, but a total supply of 589 billion. Other SHIB tokens have been locked in smart contracts for staking purposes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-300-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as $300 Million Trading Volume Comes In – Are Whales Buying SHIB?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Shiba Inu Price Prediction</category><category>Shiba Inu Price</category><category>SHIB</category><category>SHIB/USD</category><category>Shib Price</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-300-million-trading-volume-comes-are-whales-buying-shib.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102879/253539/screenshot-116.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="265809"/></item><item><title>Amazon to Enter the Crypto NFT Market with Gaming Initiative – Here’s What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/amazon-enter-crypto-nft-market-with-gaming-initiative-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Amazon reportedly aims to dabble into NFTs and Web3 gaming with an upcoming initiative related to digital assets.  &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s largest retailer is planning to launch a “digital assets enterprise” focused on non-fungible tokens and Web3 gaming this spring, Blockworks reported Thursday, citing four anonymous sources familiar with Amazon's intentions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/amazon-enter-crypto-nft-market-with-gaming-initiative-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Amazon to Enter the Crypto NFT Market with Gaming Initiative – Here’s What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Amazon</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Web3</category><category>Web3 Gaming</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/amazon-enter-crypto-nft-market-with-gaming-initiative-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102881/253542/christian-wiediger-rymh7ezpqrs-unsplash-1-646x360.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="16251"/></item><item><title>From Homeless to Quadrupled Monthly Income: Just One of Many Advantages of Blockchain and Web3</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/from-homeless-to-quadrupled-monthly-income-just-one-of-many-advantages-of-blockchain-and-web3.htm</link><description>Among the greatest values of blockchain and Web3 is that they enable different communities across the world to use the novel technology's building blocks to solve issues specific to each of them, said Xochitl Cazador, Head of Ecosystem Growth at the open-source, mobile-first Celo platform. The many opportunities created this way include universal basic income (UBI), undercollateralized loans, and micro-work. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/from-homeless-to-quadrupled-monthly-income-just-one-of-many-advantages-of-blockchain-and-web3.htm"&gt;Read More: From Homeless to Quadrupled Monthly Income: Just One of Many Advantages of Blockchain and Web3&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Celo</category><category>Web3</category><category>Loan</category><category>Africa</category><category>Latin America</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/from-homeless-to-quadrupled-monthly-income-just-one-of-many-advantages-of-blockchain-and-web3.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101680/251159/adobestock-erllre-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="171645"/></item><item><title>Tatsuya Kohrogi, CSO of Digital Entertainment Asset, on Web3 in Japan &amp; Decentralizing Game Development  | Ep. 199</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tatsuya-kohrogi-sco-of-digital-entertainment-asset-web3-japan-decentralizing-game-development-ep-199.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Tatsuya (Tats) Kohrogi, CSO of Digital Entertainment Asset, talks about fundraising challenges during the crypto winter, P2E/P&amp;E regulatory insights in Japan, and wow the growing Web3 gaming industry will help bring Web3 into the mainstream....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tatsuya-kohrogi-sco-of-digital-entertainment-asset-web3-japan-decentralizing-game-development-ep-199.htm"&gt;Read More: Tatsuya Kohrogi, CSO of Digital Entertainment Asset, on Web3 in Japan &amp; Decentralizing Game Development  | Ep. 199&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/tatsuya-kohrogi-sco-of-digital-entertainment-asset-web3-japan-decentralizing-game-development-ep-199.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102823/253463/tatsuya-kohrogi-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96402"/></item><item><title>Binance Stablecoin BUSD Loses $2 Billion in Market Cap in a Month – What’s Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-stablecoin-busd-loses-2-billion-market-cap-month-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The Binance USD (BUSD) stablecoin continues to lose ground versus other stablecoins, and has over the past month lost as much as $2bn in market capitalization. &lt;br /&gt;
At its low on Wednesday this week, BUSD’s market cap touched $15.3bn, down more than $2bn compared to the $17.5bn market cap it had on the same date in December....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-stablecoin-busd-loses-2-billion-market-cap-month-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Stablecoin BUSD Loses $2 Billion in Market Cap in a Month – What’s Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>BUSD</category><category>Binance</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-stablecoin-busd-loses-2-billion-market-cap-month-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102866/253524/binance.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="40405"/></item><item><title>North Korean Hackers ‘Trying to Bait Crypto Users With Bogus Job Offers’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-hackers-trying-bait-crypto-users-by-sending-bogus-job-offers.htm</link><description>North Korean hackers are trying to break into crypto accounts by sending bogus job offers, a security provider has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
The claims were made in a post by Proofpoint, a California-based security provider, and reported by the South Korean media outlets KBS and TVChosun....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-hackers-trying-bait-crypto-users-by-sending-bogus-job-offers.htm"&gt;Read More: North Korean Hackers ‘Trying to Bait Crypto Users With Bogus Job Offers’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hackers</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-korean-hackers-trying-bait-crypto-users-by-sending-bogus-job-offers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102827/253469/adobestock-78620964.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3225174"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Fantom? Crypto Experts Give Their Fantom Price Predictions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-fantom-crypto-experts-give-their-fantom-price-predictions.htm</link><description>FTM, the token that powers the high-performance Fantom blockchain, has been pumping in the last few days. FTM/USD recently came within a whisker of touching the $0.50 level, its highest since last May, before easing back to the $0.46s, where it trades higher by about 130% on the month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-fantom-crypto-experts-give-their-fantom-price-predictions.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Fantom? Crypto Experts Give Their Fantom Price Predictions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Fantom</category><category>FTM</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-fantom-crypto-experts-give-their-fantom-price-predictions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102856/253499/ftm.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="456893"/></item><item><title>US Congressman Hill Aims to Make America the Go-To Place for Blockchain Innovation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-congressman-hill-aims-to-make-america-the-go-to-place-for-blockchain-innovation.htm</link><description>US Congressman French Hill aims to promote digital assets and blockchain technology in America by creating a favorable regulatory framework. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking on CNBC’s Squawk Box on January 26, the chairman of the newly formed congressional subcommittee on digital assets said he plans to advocate a fair regulatory regime in order to make sure “America is the place for innovation in fintech and blockchain.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-congressman-hill-aims-to-make-america-the-go-to-place-for-blockchain-innovation.htm"&gt;Read More: US Congressman Hill Aims to Make America the Go-To Place for Blockchain Innovation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>French Hill</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Digital asset</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-congressman-hill-aims-to-make-america-the-go-to-place-for-blockchain-innovation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102842/253485/hill.JPG" type="image/jpeg" length="130106"/></item><item><title>As Polygon Price Explodes, These 3 New Altcoins Can 10x This Year</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-polygon-price-explodes-these-3-new-altcoins-can-10x-year.htm</link><description>The token that powers Ethereum scaling solution Polygon’s sidechain MATIC has been exploding higher. After having been stuck in a $0.92-$1.05 range for the last few weeks, MATIC surged as high as the $1.12s on Thursday, gaining over 13% on the day, though the rally has since eased off a little on Friday, with the cryptocurrency now trading back just to the south of the $1.10 level once again....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/as-polygon-price-explodes-these-3-new-altcoins-can-10x-year.htm"&gt;Read More: As Polygon Price Explodes, These 3 New Altcoins Can 10x This Year&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Polygon</category><category>MATIC</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-polygon-price-explodes-these-3-new-altcoins-can-10x-year.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102841/253486/polygon.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="456627"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Forecast as ADA Pumps Up 50% From Bottom – ADA to $10 Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-ada-pumps-up-50-from-bottom-ada-10-soon.htm</link><description>The value of the Cardano token, the eighth-largest cryptocurrency with a market capitalization of $13.2 billion, has grown by 45.5% in the past 30 days. However, this growth has slowed recently, with the token currently experiencing only a 0.9% increase in the past 24 hours. Here's where ADA is headed next....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-ada-pumps-up-50-from-bottom-ada-10-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Forecast as ADA Pumps Up 50% From Bottom – ADA to $10 Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>Cardano Price Prediction</category><category>Cardano Price Forecast</category><category>ADA</category><category>ADA/USD</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-ada-pumps-up-50-from-bottom-ada-10-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102826/253472/screenshot-115.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="284694"/></item></channel></rss>
