<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Taiwan Notes Rise in Bitcoin, Ethereum Use in Bribery Cases</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/taiwan-notes-rise-bitcoin-ethereum-use-bribery-cases.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH)-powered “bribery” cases are on the rise in Taiwan, the nation’s justice ministry has claimed. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the China Times, the ministry warned that cash is no longer the only currency used in corruption cases. &lt;br /&gt;
The ministry said that BTC, ETH, and other coins were also “emerging” as tools of corruption....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/taiwan-notes-rise-bitcoin-ethereum-use-bribery-cases.htm"&gt;Read More: Taiwan Notes Rise in Bitcoin, Ethereum Use in Bribery Cases&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Taiwan</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/taiwan-notes-rise-bitcoin-ethereum-use-bribery-cases.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118710/316230/adobestock-467429192-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="488870"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Lawmakers Want to Hear from Binance, Bitso &amp; OKX as MPs Target Crypto Scams</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-lawmakers-want-hear-from-binance-bitso-okx-as-mps-target-crypto-scams.htm</link><description>Brazilian lawmakers have summoned the heads of major crypto exchanges to parliament, with representatives of the trading platforms Binance, Bitso, and OKX all set to attend. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Brazilian media outlet Livecoins, a special parliamentary commission for “cryptocurrency-based financial pyramid schemes” (known as the CPI) has approved a list of 38 people who will be summoned to parliament to face questioning from MPs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-lawmakers-want-hear-from-binance-bitso-okx-as-mps-target-crypto-scams.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Lawmakers Want to Hear from Binance, Bitso &amp; OKX as MPs Target Crypto Scams&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-lawmakers-want-hear-from-binance-bitso-okx-as-mps-target-crypto-scams.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118638/316082/brazil-0407.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="563537"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tests $31,000 Psychological Level – Is it a Good Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tests-31000-psychological-level-it-good-time-buy.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin's (BTC) price tests the key psychological level of $31,000, investors are closely watching to assess whether this presents a favorable opportunity to enter the market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin's price has been hovering near this crucial level, with the market eagerly anticipating its next move.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this Bitcoin price prediction, we will analyze the current market conditions, focusing specifically on the technical aspects of BTC. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tests-31000-psychological-level-it-good-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tests $31,000 Psychological Level – Is it a Good Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tests-31000-psychological-level-it-good-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118715/316244/4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480399"/></item><item><title>Thailand Joins Singapore in Banning Crypto Lending Services</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/thailand-joins-singapore-banning-crypto-lending-services.htm</link><description>Amid increased global scrutiny on crypto exchanges, Thailand joins Singapore among Southeast Asian countries to ban retail lending and staking services.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Thai Securities and Exchanges Commission announced a ban stopping crypto exchanges from offering lending and staking services to retail customers on July 3. &lt;br /&gt;
The news came hours after the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) disclosed new measures to protect investors. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/thailand-joins-singapore-banning-crypto-lending-services.htm"&gt;Read More: Thailand Joins Singapore in Banning Crypto Lending Services&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/thailand-joins-singapore-banning-crypto-lending-services.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118711/316239/securities-and-exchange-g.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="187992"/></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency in China: Central Bank Shake-Up Dims Hopes for Policy Reversal</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-in-china-central-bank-shake-up-dims-hopes-for-policy-reversal.htm</link><description>Hopes that China’s anti-crypto stance could soon change have been crushed by the appointment of a known crypto-critic as the Communist Party’s top official at the People’s Bank of China (PBoC). &lt;br /&gt;
According to a recent Wall Street Journal report, the Party’s new appointee to the Chinese central bank is Pan Gongsheng, the bank’s current deputy governor....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-in-china-central-bank-shake-up-dims-hopes-for-policy-reversal.htm"&gt;Read More: Cryptocurrency in China: Central Bank Shake-Up Dims Hopes for Policy Reversal&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptocurrency-in-china-central-bank-shake-up-dims-hopes-for-policy-reversal.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118686/316189/china.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="185904"/></item><item><title>Bernstein: The U.S. Likely to Approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-us-likely-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf.htm</link><description>Brokerage firm Bernstein believes that there is a strong possibility that the US Securities and Exchange Commission will approve a spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded-funds (ETF).  &lt;br /&gt;
In a research report released on Monday, Bernstein said the SEC is under increasing pressure to greenlight such a product, specifically since the commission has already granted approval for futures-based bitcoin ETFs and leverage-based futures ETFs. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-us-likely-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf.htm"&gt;Read More: Bernstein: The U.S. Likely to Approve a Spot Bitcoin ETF&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bernstein</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-us-likely-approve-spot-bitcoin-etf.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118694/316209/24k-production-1-media-li.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="118863"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Reaches $500 Million Market Capitalization – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-reaches-500-million-market-capitalization-time-buy.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) coin has recently garnered attention in the cryptocurrency market as it reached a market capitalization of $500 million. &lt;br /&gt;
This achievement has sparked speculation among investors about the coin's price prediction and potential investment opportunities.  &lt;br /&gt;
As the crypto market evolves, investors are eager to determine whether now is the right time to buy LUNC tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-reaches-500-million-market-capitalization-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Reaches $500 Million Market Capitalization – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-reaches-500-million-market-capitalization-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118671/316216/terra.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="338555"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – PEPE2.0, KSI, RAIN</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-pepe20-ksi-rain.htm</link><description>Amid traditional financial market closures due to Independence Day holiday celebrations in the US, major cryptocurrencies aren’t seeing much by way of exciting price action on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH) are both holding close to recent highs above $31,000 and in the mid-$1,900s respectively....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-pepe20-ksi-rain.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – PEPE2.0, KSI, RAIN&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe 2.0</category><category>Pepe2.0</category><category>KSI</category><category>RAIN</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Shit Coin</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-pepe20-ksi-rain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118702/316217/pepe2-0.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="392676"/></item><item><title>Data Reveals Persistent 'Fake Followers' Problem on Crypto Twitter</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/data-reveals-persistent-fake-followers-problem-crypto-twitter.htm</link><description>Digital assets accounts and crypto celebrities on Twitter have gained an “influx of fake followers,” a new report reveals. &lt;br /&gt;
One of Elon Musk’s top priorities for Twitter, following his $44 billion deal to buy the social media giant, is cracking down on fake accounts dubbed “spam bots.” Fake accounts are the “single most annoying problem” on Twitter, Musk tweeted in April 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/data-reveals-persistent-fake-followers-problem-crypto-twitter.htm"&gt;Read More: Data Reveals Persistent 'Fake Followers' Problem on Crypto Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/data-reveals-persistent-fake-followers-problem-crypto-twitter.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118696/316213/twitter-1795652-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="112522"/></item><item><title>Justin Bieber Is Down $1.2 Million On His Bored Ape NFT – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/justin-bieber-down-12-million-his-bored-ape-nft-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Worldwide singer-superstar Justin Bieber is deep in the red ever since joining the NFT world’s infamous Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) last year.  &lt;br /&gt;
In January 2022, the celebrity notoriously purchased Ape #3001 for 500 ETH, worth $1.3 million at the time. Today, that same collectible is worth just 29.95 WETH ($58,610) according to OpenSea. That’s a 95% drawdown. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/justin-bieber-down-12-million-his-bored-ape-nft-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Justin Bieber Is Down $1.2 Million On His Bored Ape NFT – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/justin-bieber-down-12-million-his-bored-ape-nft-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118697/316214/adobestock-493483142-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="60085"/></item><item><title>Aptos Price Prediction: $300 Million Trading Volume Sends APT Soaring – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/aptos-price-prediction-300-million-trading-volume-sends-apt-soaring-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>Aptos (APTO), the cryptocurrency that powers the newly launched Aptos layer-1 blockchain protocol, is enjoying a pop higher on Tuesday amid a surge in trading volumes. &lt;br /&gt;
As per CoinGecko, APTO trading volumes were around $300 million in the last 24 hours, impressive for a cryptocurrency with a market cap of only around $1.67 billion....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/aptos-price-prediction-300-million-trading-volume-sends-apt-soaring-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Aptos Price Prediction: $300 Million Trading Volume Sends APT Soaring – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Aptos</category><category>APTO</category><category>Thug Life Token</category><category>THUG</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/aptos-price-prediction-300-million-trading-volume-sends-apt-soaring-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118695/316210/apto-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="591807"/></item><item><title>ApeCoin is Going to Zero After Azuki Drama Sends NFT Prices Crashing But Chimpzee Might Be The Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-after-azuki-drama-sends-nft-prices-crashing-but-chimpzee-might-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</link><description>ApeCoin (APE), the utility and governance token of the APE ecosystem which was built by Yuga Labs to expand the utility of its Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) non-fungible token collection, has been struggling recently. &lt;br /&gt;
APE/USD has been unable in recent weeks to muster a sustained pushback to the north of its 21-Day Moving Average (DMA), which has been acting as resistance going all the way back to April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-after-azuki-drama-sends-nft-prices-crashing-but-chimpzee-might-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: ApeCoin is Going to Zero After Azuki Drama Sends NFT Prices Crashing But Chimpzee Might Be The Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ApeCoin</category><category>APE</category><category>Bored Ape Yacht Club</category><category>BAYC</category><category>Azuki</category><category>NFT</category><category>Chimpzee</category><category>Charity Crypto</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-after-azuki-drama-sends-nft-prices-crashing-but-chimpzee-might-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118688/316205/apecoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3872726"/></item><item><title>New Proposal: Hong Kong Should Issue Stablecoin to Rival USDT and USDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-proposal-hong-kong-should-issue-stablecoin-rival-usdt-usdc.htm</link><description>In a revolutionary move, Hong Kong is exploring the idea of launching its Stablecoin, HKDG, to rival established Stablecoins like USDT and USDC.  &lt;br /&gt;
As reported by Wu Blockchain, the proposal, co-authored by prominent figures in academia and industry, including Vice Chancellor Wang Yang and angel investor Cai Wensheng, aims to enhance Hong Kong's position in the digital currency landscape. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-proposal-hong-kong-should-issue-stablecoin-rival-usdt-usdc.htm"&gt;Read More: New Proposal: Hong Kong Should Issue Stablecoin to Rival USDT and USDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>USDT</category><category>USDC</category><category>Hong Kong</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-proposal-hong-kong-should-issue-stablecoin-rival-usdt-usdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118681/316193/screenshot-2023-07-04-164330.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="915467"/></item><item><title>Shane Mac, Co-Founder of XMTP, on The Future of Messaging, and Decentralized Communication | Ep. 244</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shane-mac-co-founder-of-xmtp-on-the-future-of-messaging-and-decentralized-communication-ep-244.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Shane Mac, Co-Founder of XMTP, talks about the true importance of decentralized communication, building messaging-based business, and the future of messaging. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shane-mac-co-founder-of-xmtp-on-the-future-of-messaging-and-decentralized-communication-ep-244.htm"&gt;Read More: Shane Mac, Co-Founder of XMTP, on The Future of Messaging, and Decentralized Communication | Ep. 244&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shane-mac-co-founder-of-xmtp-on-the-future-of-messaging-and-decentralized-communication-ep-244.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118682/316182/shane-mac-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="113407"/></item><item><title>CoinShares Report: Bitcoin Receives Major Investor Attention Amidst New Highs for 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinshares-report-bitcoin-receives-major-investor-attention-amidst-new-highs-for-2023.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) remains the top target for institutional investors in the past two weeks as the market continues its uphill form this year.  &lt;br /&gt;
A new report from CoinShares shows Bitcoin’s investment products have attracted $310 million in inflows over 14 days amid skepticism over the approval of the spot BTC ETF by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). &lt;br /&gt;
According to the report, BTC leads the pack as it recovers from the previous nine weeks of consecutive outflows. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinshares-report-bitcoin-receives-major-investor-attention-amidst-new-highs-for-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: CoinShares Report: Bitcoin Receives Major Investor Attention Amidst New Highs for 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>CoinShares</category><category>ETF</category><category>Btc Price</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinshares-report-bitcoin-receives-major-investor-attention-amidst-new-highs-for-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118656/316122/bitcoin-gd222dceae-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="267928"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Bitget Launches Crypto Loans Product, Ethereum Community Proposes New Standard to Strengthen DeFi Protocols' Security, China Tightens Exports of Two Key Materials Used in Computer Chips</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bitget-launches-crypto-loans-product-ethereum-community-proposes-new-standard-to-strengthen-defi-protocols-security-china-tightens-exports-of-two-key-materials-used-in-computer-chips.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bitget-launches-crypto-loans-product-ethereum-community-proposes-new-standard-to-strengthen-defi-protocols-security-china-tightens-exports-of-two-key-materials-used-in-computer-chips.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Bitget Launches Crypto Loans Product, Ethereum Community Proposes New Standard to Strengthen DeFi Protocols' Security, China Tightens Exports of Two Key Materials Used in Computer Chips&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Lending</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Smart Contract</category><category>Security</category><category>China</category><category>Legal</category><category>Voyager Digital</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Credit Suisse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Sport</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>CleanSpark</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bitget-launches-crypto-loans-product-ethereum-community-proposes-new-standard-to-strengthen-defi-protocols-security-china-tightens-exports-of-two-key-materials-used-in-computer-chips.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118637/316108/adobestock-dan74-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="293440"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin and Cryptos Rally, Unfazed by BlackRock ETF Worries</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cryptos-rally-unfazed-by-blackrock-etf-worries.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) and the broader crypto market held on to their recent gains on Tuesday, with Bitcoin appearing to hold support above the $31,000 level. &lt;br /&gt;
As of Tuesday at press time, BTC traded just north of $31,000, up 1.2% for the past 24 hours, while Ethereum’s native ETH token was more or less unchanged over the same period, trading at $1,960. &lt;br /&gt;
Most other major coins were also little changed for the past 24 hours, holding on to their gains from late June....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cryptos-rally-unfazed-by-blackrock-etf-worries.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin and Cryptos Rally, Unfazed by BlackRock ETF Worries&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-cryptos-rally-unfazed-by-blackrock-etf-worries.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118659/316129/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="153373"/></item><item><title>Voyager Creditors Charged $5.1 Million for Legal Services Between March-May</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-creditors-charged-51-million-for-legal-services-between-march-may.htm</link><description>A crypto platform Voyager filed for bankruptcy a year ago, in July 2022, due to substantial losses caused by the bear market and the collapse of the Terra blockchain.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the aftermath, the company’s creditors requested the return of their assets. However, the legal fees kept stacking, leading them to a total amount of $16.4 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-creditors-charged-51-million-for-legal-services-between-march-may.htm"&gt;Read More: Voyager Creditors Charged $5.1 Million for Legal Services Between March-May&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/voyager-creditors-charged-51-million-for-legal-services-between-march-may.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118635/316126/voyager-creditors-charged.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="87974"/></item><item><title>Fintech Giant Revolut to Cease Offering Solana, Cardano, Polygon Tokens in the U.S.</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fintech-giant-revolut-cease-offering-solana-cardano-polygon-tokens-us.htm</link><description>Revolut, a prominent UK-based fintech app, has announced that it will halt the offering of Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC) tokens for customers in the United States.  &lt;br /&gt;
This decision comes after Revolut's provider, digital asset platform Bakkt, decided to delist these cryptocurrencies amid the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) categorizing these tokens as unregistered securities....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fintech-giant-revolut-cease-offering-solana-cardano-polygon-tokens-us.htm"&gt;Read More: Fintech Giant Revolut to Cease Offering Solana, Cardano, Polygon Tokens in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Revolut</category><category>Solana</category><category>Cardano</category><category>Polygon</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fintech-giant-revolut-cease-offering-solana-cardano-polygon-tokens-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118649/316100/adobestock-ascannio-1-med.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="91823"/></item><item><title>Crypto Will Benefit from Bank-Issued Stablecoins, aka Deposit Tokens, Says DAAA’s Bernard Blaha</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-will-benefit-from-bank-issued-stablecoins-aka-deposit-tokens-says-daaas-bernard-blaha.htm</link><description>In an interview with Cryptonews, Bernhard Blaha, co-founder of the Austrian Digital Asset Association (DAAA) and CEO of decentrally governed organization (DGO) The People's SCE, discussed the new type of digital coin: deposit tokens.  &lt;br /&gt;
He explained the key differences between deposit tokens and stablecoins, why he calls the former 'hybrids', and why they can't be compared to CBDCs - even if both are issued by banks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-will-benefit-from-bank-issued-stablecoins-aka-deposit-tokens-says-daaas-bernard-blaha.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Will Benefit from Bank-Issued Stablecoins, aka Deposit Tokens, Says DAAA’s Bernard Blaha&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>stablecoins</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Banking</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>EU</category><category>Europe</category><category>European Union</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-will-benefit-from-bank-issued-stablecoins-aka-deposit-tokens-says-daaas-bernard-blaha.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/116389/312344/bernard-blaha-source-ecre.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="79099"/></item></channel></rss>
