<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Legendary ‘The Big Short’ Investor Michael Burry Believes Binance Crypto Exchange Audit Is Meaningless – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/legendary-the-big-short-investor-michael-burry-believes-binance-crypto-exchange-audit-meaningless-heres-why.htm</link><description>Audits of Binance and other crypto exchanges are “essentially meaningless” since auditors don’t know how to deal with crypto, according to Michael Burry, the legendary investor who inspired the movie ‘The Big Short’. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Burry, this is the same problem as he was facing himself in 2005 when he started using “a new kind of credit default swap.” He said that auditors at the time were “learning on the job,” which is "not a good thing."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/legendary-the-big-short-investor-michael-burry-believes-binance-crypto-exchange-audit-meaningless-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Legendary ‘The Big Short’ Investor Michael Burry Believes Binance Crypto Exchange Audit Is Meaningless – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Michael Burry</category><category>Binance</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/legendary-the-big-short-investor-michael-burry-believes-binance-crypto-exchange-audit-meaningless-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98529/244850/michael-burry.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="263678"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Elon Musk Suggests He Might Step Down as Twitter CEO – Here are DOGE Levels to Look Out For</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-suggests-he-might-step-down-as-twitter-ceo-here-are-doge-levels-look-out-for.htm</link><description>Elon Musk might soon be stepping down as the CEO of Twitter and, judging by Dogecoin’s price action on Monday, the news isn’t going down well. DOGE, the token that powers the decentralized dog meme-inspired Dogecoin blockchain payments network, was last down just shy of 2.0% on Monday near $0.077 and eyeing a retest of last Friday’s lows in the $0.074 area. Price predictions for the cryptocurrency remain downbeat, with DOGE currently down close to 30% on the month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-suggests-he-might-step-down-as-twitter-ceo-here-are-doge-levels-look-out-for.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as Elon Musk Suggests He Might Step Down as Twitter CEO – Here are DOGE Levels to Look Out For&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DOGE</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Twitter</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-suggests-he-might-step-down-as-twitter-ceo-here-are-doge-levels-look-out-for.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98510/244824/dogeusd-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="397788"/></item><item><title>Experience the Power of Automated Trading with This New Crypto Platform – Presale Ending Soon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/experience-power-of-automated-trading-with-new-crypto-platform-presale-ending-soon.htm</link><description>Unlike traditional financial markets, the crypto markets trade 24/7 without any rest, making it virtually impossible to keep up to date with the latest developments, all the time. &lt;br /&gt;
The global nature of the crypto industry means that anything can happen at any time, anywhere in the world.  &lt;br /&gt;
This, amongst many other reasons, means that the crypto markets can be notoriously difficult to trade. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/experience-power-of-automated-trading-with-new-crypto-platform-presale-ending-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Experience the Power of Automated Trading with This New Crypto Platform – Presale Ending Soon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/experience-power-of-automated-trading-with-new-crypto-platform-presale-ending-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98500/244820/trading-income-allowance-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="320158"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Israel to Seize All Crypto in 150 Wallets, Nigeria to Recognize Crypto Usage, OneCoin Co-founder Pleads Guilty</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-israel-to-seize-all-crypto-in-150-wallets-nigeria-to-recognize-crypto-usage-onecoin-co-founder-pleads-guilty.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-israel-to-seize-all-crypto-in-150-wallets-nigeria-to-recognize-crypto-usage-onecoin-co-founder-pleads-guilty.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Israel to Seize All Crypto in 150 Wallets, Nigeria to Recognize Crypto Usage, OneCoin Co-founder Pleads Guilty&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>OneCoin</category><category>Legal</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Ripple</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Israel</category><category>USA</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>ETF</category><category>Ren</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-israel-to-seize-all-crypto-in-150-wallets-nigeria-to-recognize-crypto-usage-onecoin-co-founder-pleads-guilty.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98466/244782/adobestock-strixcode-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="105489"/></item><item><title>Argentina Fan Token Price Prediction as ARG Token Falls 50% Almost Instantly – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-fan-token-price-prediction-as-arg-token-falls-50-almost-instantly-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>In a reaction that perplexed many cryptocurrency traders, the price of the Argentina Football Association Fan Token (ARG) has been battered in wake of Argentina’s historic triumph in the FIFA World Cup final on Sunday. At one point, it had dropped over 50% in a matter of hours. Iconic Argentinian footballer Lionel Messi, widely regarded as one of, if not the best footballer of all time, led his side to victory in a thrilling final that was ultimately decided on penalties....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-fan-token-price-prediction-as-arg-token-falls-50-almost-instantly-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Fan Token Price Prediction as ARG Token Falls 50% Almost Instantly – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ARG</category><category>Argentina Football Association Fan Token</category><category>World Cup</category><category>Messi</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-fan-token-price-prediction-as-arg-token-falls-50-almost-instantly-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98497/244803/arg-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="507758"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Reach $1 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-reach-1-2023.htm</link><description>After posting a big 15% drop last Friday that saw the cryptocurrency fall from the $0.00016 area to as low as $0.00012, LUNC, the native token of the now largely defunct Terra Classic blockchain, was last trading in the $0.00014 area. LUNC/USD price action has stabilized over the weekend and amid a quiet start to the week for broader cryptocurrency markets, but price predictions remain pessimistic. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-reach-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Reach $1 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Luna Classic</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-reach-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98485/244771/lunc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="640192"/></item><item><title>Crypto Whales Just Snapped Up These Altcoins – Find Out Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-just-snapped-up-these-altcoins-find-out-why.htm</link><description>Crypto whales are people or groups who hold a large amount of a given cryptocurrency--and they're always on the hunt for ways to increase the ROI of their crypto portfolios. One way they do this is to buy promising cryptos early in their development and during presales, which allows them to get more altcoins before demand increases and prices go up. But what is it about certain cryptos that make these whales take notice?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-just-snapped-up-these-altcoins-find-out-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Whales Just Snapped Up These Altcoins – Find Out Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>Calvaria</category><category>RIA</category><category>FGHT</category><category>FightOut</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Taro</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-just-snapped-up-these-altcoins-find-out-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98480/244769/adobestock-446050042-editorial-use-only.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="627628"/></item><item><title>China Adds More Cities to its Digital Yuan Pilot</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-adds-more-cities-its-digital-yuan-pilot.htm</link><description>More Chinese cities will be added to the nation’s digital yuan pilot – with a rollout edging closer to reality. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the newspaper the Workers’ Daily, the city of Jinan, Shandong Province, will be added to the pilot area. Also joining the pilot will be Nanning and Fangchenggang in the Guangxi Zhuang Autonomous Region, as well as Yunnan Province’s Kunming. The Xishuangbanna Dai Autonomous Prefecture will also be added....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-adds-more-cities-its-digital-yuan-pilot.htm"&gt;Read More: China Adds More Cities to its Digital Yuan Pilot&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-adds-more-cities-its-digital-yuan-pilot.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98461/244725/adobestock-515607553.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="690861"/></item><item><title>On-Chain Data Suggests Bitcoin Whales are Unloading BTC at a Record-Breaking Rate – What’s Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chain-data-suggests-bitcoin-whales-are-unloading-btc-at-a-record-breaking-rate-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) whales are now unloading coins at a pace never before seen as measured on a 30-day basis. &lt;br /&gt;
In total, whales have offloaded some 280,000 BTC in the past 30 days, data from the on-chain analysis firm Glassnode showed as of Sunday. That is the highest number in any 30-day period, according to the firm....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chain-data-suggests-bitcoin-whales-are-unloading-btc-at-a-record-breaking-rate-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: On-Chain Data Suggests Bitcoin Whales are Unloading BTC at a Record-Breaking Rate – What’s Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 13:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chain-data-suggests-bitcoin-whales-are-unloading-btc-at-a-record-breaking-rate-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98478/244761/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131728"/></item><item><title>Leading Crypto Exchange Reports Outage for Several Hours with Deposits and Withdrawals Affected – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-crypto-exchange-reports-outage-for-several-hours-with-deposits-withdrawals-affected-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>OKX has released an update regarding its recent outage that lasted for more than seven hours, saying that it was due to hardware issues with its cloud service provider. &lt;br /&gt;
On December 18, the cryptocurrency exchange was hit with an outage that hindered customers from opening or closing a trade and processing withdrawals for several hours. The platform said on Twitter at the time:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-crypto-exchange-reports-outage-for-several-hours-with-deposits-withdrawals-affected-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Leading Crypto Exchange Reports Outage for Several Hours with Deposits and Withdrawals Affected – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>OKX</category><category>OKX Exchange</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 12:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/leading-crypto-exchange-reports-outage-for-several-hours-with-deposits-withdrawals-affected-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98460/244716/okx-interview-with-ceo-jay-hao-on-the-future-of-crypto-and-metaverse-applications.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="49401"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Spikes Up 4% – Here’s Where It’s Heading Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-spikes-up-4-heres-where-its-heading-next.htm</link><description>The Shiba Inu price is up 1.5% in 24 hours and is among the few top 100 cryptocurrencies in the green. Investors have recently been shifting attention back to the global meme market while Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) struggle to sustain key support areas....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-spikes-up-4-heres-where-its-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Spikes Up 4% – Here’s Where It’s Heading Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Shiba</category><category>Shiba Inu Price Prediction</category><category>SHIBA/USD</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-spikes-up-4-heres-where-its-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98437/244703/shibusd-2022-12-19-12-17-17.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="498496"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Cardano? Crypto Experts Give Their ADA Predictions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-crypto-experts-give-their-ada-predictions.htm</link><description>The price of Cardano (ADA) has fallen by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, reaching $0.264293 following a bad weekend for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. Its current price marks a 14% drop in a week and a 19% decline in the last 30 days, with ongoing market negativity serving to depress financial markets worldwide....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-crypto-experts-give-their-ada-predictions.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Cardano? Crypto Experts Give Their ADA Predictions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-cardano-crypto-experts-give-their-ada-predictions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98431/244707/is-it-too-late-to-buy-cardano-crypto-experts-give-their-ada-predictions.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1458810"/></item><item><title>Ex-President Donald Trump’s NFT Collection Receives Backlash After Users Spot Photoshop Errors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-president-donald-trumps-nft-collection-receives-backlash-after-users-spot-photoshop-errors.htm</link><description>The recently-released non-fungible token (NFT) collection by former US President Donald Trump, is being heavily criticized over its poor quality and editing, and use of stock images among other things.  &lt;br /&gt;
There are two major accusations leveled against Trump and the team behind the collection: &lt;br /&gt;
For example, there is an image of Trump as a duck hunter (or something akin to it), in an outfit very similar to a branded online clothing collection....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-president-donald-trumps-nft-collection-receives-backlash-after-users-spot-photoshop-errors.htm"&gt;Read More: Ex-President Donald Trump’s NFT Collection Receives Backlash After Users Spot Photoshop Errors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Donald Trump</category><category>Community</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Opensea</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-president-donald-trumps-nft-collection-receives-backlash-after-users-spot-photoshop-errors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98415/244695/fkntrrvwqayxjki.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="133156"/></item><item><title>Expert Says Crypto Selloffs Will Accelerate if This One Thing Happens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-says-crypto-selloffs-will-accelerate-if-one-thing-happens.htm</link><description>A top researcher in Japan has predicted that crypto selloffs could gather speed if Bitcoin (BTC) is unable to hold at the $17,000 mark for a significant period of time. &lt;br /&gt;
The claim was made by Yuya Hasegawa, a market analyst at the Japanese crypto exchange bitbank, and reported by the Japanese media outlet CoinPost. Hasegawa noted that “fortunately” for crypto holders, the market has not collapsed “significantly” – despite recent pressures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-says-crypto-selloffs-will-accelerate-if-one-thing-happens.htm"&gt;Read More: Expert Says Crypto Selloffs Will Accelerate if This One Thing Happens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/expert-says-crypto-selloffs-will-accelerate-if-one-thing-happens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98424/244685/adobestock-241617555.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2067621"/></item><item><title>Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson Calls XRP Army ‘Toxic’ and ‘Petty’ – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson-calls-xrp-army-toxic-petty-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson has called the XRP community "toxic and petty" while lashing out at the project and arguing that it "provides no partnership or technical value." &lt;br /&gt;
Hoskinson, who has been the target of hostile attacks from the XRP community, said in a recent video that he plans to no longer talk about Ripple and its native token XRP. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson-calls-xrp-army-toxic-petty-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson Calls XRP Army ‘Toxic’ and ‘Petty’ – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Charles Hoskinson</category><category>XRP</category><category>XRP Ripple</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-founder-charles-hoskinson-calls-xrp-army-toxic-petty-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98422/244683/18b6045102-media-library-original-900-601.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="81783"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction; Breakout Patterns Will Drive Price Action</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-breakout-patterns-will-drive-price-action.htm</link><description>During the Asian session on December 19, Bitcoin is trading at $16,700, as investors appear to be waiting for a solid fundamental reason to drive price action. Similarly, Ethereum is trading in a choppy range of $1,150 to $1,200. A break out of this range will help us determine future market price movements....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-breakout-patterns-will-drive-price-action.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price and Ethereum Prediction; Breakout Patterns Will Drive Price Action&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-prediction-breakout-patterns-will-drive-price-action.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/98392/244642/btc-image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="264216"/></item></channel></rss>
