<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Climbs To $27,000 – Will The News-Heavy Week Boost BTC?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-climbs-to-27000-will-the-news-heavy-week-boost-btc.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin (BTC) continues its upward trajectory, reaching a price of $27,000, the cryptocurrency market eagerly awaits the potential impact of a news-heavy week.  &lt;br /&gt;
With various developments, including regulatory updates, institutional adoption, and market sentiment shifts, the question arises: Will the accumulation of positive news propel BTC to new heights? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-climbs-to-27000-will-the-news-heavy-week-boost-btc.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Climbs To $27,000 – Will The News-Heavy Week Boost BTC?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-climbs-to-27000-will-the-news-heavy-week-boost-btc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114512/276510/21-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481191"/></item><item><title>RefundCoin Price Pumps 1000% - Meme Tokens Still The Best Cryptos to Buy Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/refundcoin-price-pumps-1000-percent-meme-tokens-still-the-best-cryptos-to-buy-now.htm</link><description>RefundCoin (RFD) is among the top trending cryptocurrency tokens on Uniswap's 'hot pairs' list with its performance since ICO and today's explosive pump. &lt;br /&gt;
Trending alongside $WAGMI, $BEN, $GEN and $PEPE, at points $RFD has been the #1 top trending crypto on DEXTools following its May 19th launch.  &lt;br /&gt;
Spiking well over 1000% today, RFD token is up by an even higher margin since its Uniswap listing.  &lt;br /&gt;
View the latest RFD price chart on DEXTools.io....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/refundcoin-price-pumps-1000-percent-meme-tokens-still-the-best-cryptos-to-buy-now.htm"&gt;Read More: RefundCoin Price Pumps 1000% - Meme Tokens Still The Best Cryptos to Buy Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/refundcoin-price-pumps-1000-percent-meme-tokens-still-the-best-cryptos-to-buy-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114509/276506/refundcoin-token.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="200783"/></item><item><title>Top Crypto Gainers &amp; Losers Today - Tornado Cash Crash, Pepe Price Bounces</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-losers-today-tornado-cash-crash-pepe-price-bounces.htm</link><description>In the dynamic world of cryptocurrencies, prices can fluctuate rapidly, presenting both opportunities and risks for investors.  &lt;br /&gt;
Today, we delve into the latest updates on the top gainers and losers in the crypto market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Two notable performers are Tornado Cash (TORN) and Pepe, with Pepe securing the second-highest gainer position on Binance USDT pairs. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-losers-today-tornado-cash-crash-pepe-price-bounces.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Crypto Gainers &amp; Losers Today - Tornado Cash Crash, Pepe Price Bounces&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-losers-today-tornado-cash-crash-pepe-price-bounces.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114503/276505/top.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="97419"/></item><item><title>Biden: I'm Not Willing to Strike a Deal With 'Crypto Traders'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biden-im-not-willing-strike-deal-with-crypto-traders.htm</link><description>US President Joe Biden has said he is not willing to ink a debt ceiling agreement that would benefit crypto traders. &lt;br /&gt;
During the final day of G7 talks in Japan, Biden addressed the budget negotiations, claiming that the proposed terms by Republican leaders are "unacceptable." &lt;br /&gt;
“I’m not going to agree to a deal that protects wealth tax cheats and crypto traders while putting food assistance at risk for nearly 1 million Americans.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biden-im-not-willing-strike-deal-with-crypto-traders.htm"&gt;Read More: Biden: I'm Not Willing to Strike a Deal With 'Crypto Traders'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Joe Biden</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biden-im-not-willing-strike-deal-with-crypto-traders.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114510/276500/54ce04ac7a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41932"/></item><item><title>New Uniswap Coins a Good Buy If Bitcoin Price Top In - Wall St Prediction as Traders Hunt Next Dogecoin, Shiba Inu or Pepe</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-uniswap-coins-on-a-good-buy-if-bitcoin-price-has-topped-wall-street-prediction.htm</link><description>Wall Street investment bank Morgan Stanley thinks the Bitcoin top could be in as investors are diversifying into newer cryptocurrencies on decentralized exchanges like Uniswap, particularly speculative meme coins. &lt;br /&gt;
Heading into June 2023, the Bitcoin price has risen approximately 100% from its November 2022 lows of just under $15,500. &lt;br /&gt;
The bearish price forecast appeared as an update this week on a Forbes article titled 'The Game May Be Over', referring to Bitcoin and Ethereum....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-uniswap-coins-on-a-good-buy-if-bitcoin-price-has-topped-wall-street-prediction.htm"&gt;Read More: New Uniswap Coins a Good Buy If Bitcoin Price Top In - Wall St Prediction as Traders Hunt Next Dogecoin, Shiba Inu or Pepe&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-uniswap-coins-on-a-good-buy-if-bitcoin-price-has-topped-wall-street-prediction.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114499/276490/pepe-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="151672"/></item><item><title>Crypto is Losing the Sense of Rarity: Does It Matter?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-losing-the-sense-of-rarity-does-it-matter.htm</link><description>Robert Quartly-Janeiro is the Chief Strategy Officer of the Singapore-based Tier-1 cryptocurrency exchange Bitrue.__________  &lt;br /&gt;
As I was flicking through the weekend supplement of a well-known financial newspaper, the number of luxury watch advertisements I had to bypass got me thinking: with so many high-end watchmakers out there, what makes their production rare — and, therefore, valuable?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-losing-the-sense-of-rarity-does-it-matter.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto is Losing the Sense of Rarity: Does It Matter?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Opinions</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Tokenomics</category><category>Web3</category><category>ICO</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Solana</category><category>Cardano</category><category>XRP</category><category>USDT</category><category>Altcoin</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Banking</category><category>Inflation</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Economics</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-losing-the-sense-of-rarity-does-it-matter.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114054/275878/adobestock-pixel-shot-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="81664"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Examining the Symmetrical Triangle Pattern and Resistance at $27,000</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-examining-symmetrical-triangle-pattern-resistance-at-27000.htm</link><description>In the volatile world of cryptocurrency, Bitcoin continues to be a focal point for investors and traders alike.  &lt;br /&gt;
As Bitcoin's price hovers around the crucial resistance level of $27,000, market analysts are closely examining the symmetrical triangle pattern that has formed on the charts.  &lt;br /&gt;
This pattern, characterized by converging trend lines, suggests a potential breakout in the near future. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-examining-symmetrical-triangle-pattern-resistance-at-27000.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Examining the Symmetrical Triangle Pattern and Resistance at $27,000&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-examining-symmetrical-triangle-pattern-resistance-at-27000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114484/276469/21-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="527831"/></item><item><title>What is PISS Coin And Why Is It Ranked in The Most Trending Cryptocurrency Tokens on DEXTools</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm</link><description>PISS coin, a unique cryptocurrency token, has captured attention as one of the most trending tokens on DEXTools.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this update, we delve into the intriguing world of PISS Coin, exploring its features, purpose, and the factors that have contributed to its rising popularity.  &lt;br /&gt;
Discover why PISS Coin has emerged as a notable player in the cryptocurrency market and the potential impact it may have on the evolving landscape of digital currencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm"&gt;Read More: What is PISS Coin And Why Is It Ranked in The Most Trending Cryptocurrency Tokens on DEXTools&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-piss-coin-why-it-ranked-most-trending-cryptocurrency-tokens-dextools.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114475/276465/fwd8wjcxsaa-dzb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="66836"/></item><item><title>$SLUTS, $WAGMI, $LFG Join the Shitcoin List After Andrew Tate Tweet – 5 Best Meme Cryptos to Buy Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm</link><description>The crypto space has been inundated with many new meme coin projects launched in a short period.  &lt;br /&gt;
Some of these meme tokens went on to record huge gains, while others dumped after fifteen minutes of fame. &lt;br /&gt;
One such project that has enjoyed brief stardom is $SLUTS. The digital asset was launched on the back of a viral tweet by social media influencer Andrew Tate. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm"&gt;Read More: $SLUTS, $WAGMI, $LFG Join the Shitcoin List After Andrew Tate Tweet – 5 Best Meme Cryptos to Buy Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sluts-wagmi-lfg-join-shitcoin-list-after-andrew-tate-tweet-5-best-meme-cryptos-buy-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114474/276462/meme-coins.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="907000"/></item><item><title>SEC, Ripple Seeking One-Week Extension on Unsealing Hinman Documents</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission and Ripple have requested a one-week extension on unsealing the internal deliberations following a speech by former director William Hinman. &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, both the SEC and Ripple reportedly filed a request seeking to extend the deadline for the filing of multiple exhibits including the Hinman documents....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC, Ripple Seeking One-Week Extension on Unsealing Hinman Documents&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>SEC</category><category>Ripple</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-ripple-seeking-one-week-extension-on-unsealing-hinman-documents.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114455/276425/9d2156dd21.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="120035"/></item><item><title>AI Meme Crypto Presale AiDoge Hits $10 Million Raised - Now 70% Sold Out</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm</link><description>New AI powered meme generation tool AiDoge.com has now passed the $10 million mark in its ongoing presale, now over 70% complete. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin project, which introduces crypto’s first meme-to-earn model, has been generating a buzz in the crypto space. It is raking in funds at a brisk pace, having raised $10,136,059 at the time of writing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Meme Crypto Presale AiDoge Hits $10 Million Raised - Now 70% Sold Out&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-meme-crypto-aidoge-hits-10-million-raised-70-sold-out.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114469/276451/aidoge-presale-progress.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="610051"/></item><item><title>The Political Memes Creating Generational Wealth - Wojak, Pepe, Copium, Chad Meme Coins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm</link><description>Meme coins have historically been seen as a way to generate interest in the crypto space and as a form of light-hearted humor as well as an investment vehicle, if a volatile one. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a number of them in 2023 are also delving into the political landscape, and helping many early buyers get rich in the process....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm"&gt;Read More: The Political Memes Creating Generational Wealth - Wojak, Pepe, Copium, Chad Meme Coins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/the-political-memes-creating-generational-wealth-wojak-pepe-copium-chad-meme-coins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114468/276450/meme-coins.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="875663"/></item><item><title>PSYOP Token Price Explodes 1,000% But Is It A Crypto Scam? - Best Meme Coins to Invest In Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm</link><description>The hot news in the cryptocurrency market today is the explosive rise of PSYOP token, with its price soaring by over 1,000%, and the coin ranked in the top trending assets on DEXTools. &lt;br /&gt;
However, despite its positive price action there have been questions posed about the legitimacy of the new crypto project....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm"&gt;Read More: PSYOP Token Price Explodes 1,000% But Is It A Crypto Scam? - Best Meme Coins to Invest In Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/psyop-token-price-explodes-1000-but-is-it-a-crypto-scam-best-meme-coins-to-invest-in-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114451/276426/listing.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="38532"/></item><item><title>Controversial Recoveries, Promising Partnerships, Regulation Gambling and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Controversial Recoveries, Promising Partnerships, Regulation Gambling and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/controversial-recoveries-promising-partnerships-regulation-gambling-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114340/276255/fwqatnhakautuc7.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="70363"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Holds At $26,800 – Is $30,000 the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin price continues to captivate investors as it holds steady at $26,800.  &lt;br /&gt;
With this stability, market analysts and enthusiasts are now wondering if $30,000 will be the next target for BTC.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this Bitcoin price prediction, we will explore the factors and predictions surrounding the Bitcoin price and delve into the possibilities of reaching this significant milestone....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Holds At $26,800 – Is $30,000 the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-holds-at-26800-30000-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114445/276419/20-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="529326"/></item><item><title>Mantle: BitDAO token will be Mantle after BIP-21 Vote</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm</link><description>BitDAO's native token BIT is set to rebrand to Mantle after the community voted in favor of a proposal seeking to optimize the token ahead of the launch of a new layer-2 mainnet. &lt;br /&gt;
The measure was approved by a majority vote as part of the BIP-21 proposal, which sought to unify the BitDAO ecosystem under a “One brand, One token” principle....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm"&gt;Read More: Mantle: BitDAO token will be Mantle after BIP-21 Vote&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>BitDAO</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Token</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mantle-bitdao-token-will-be-mantle-after-bip-21-vote.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114444/276412/bitdao-meta-image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="331341"/></item><item><title>Ripple Adds Nielsen CFO to Its Board of Directors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm</link><description>Ripple is bringing on the chief financial officer of market researcher Nielsen to its board of directors, the crypto firm announced on Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
Warren Jenson was added to the board and was also appointed as Ripple’s chair of the audit committee, overseeing the auditing process of Ripple’s operations, according to a press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple Adds Nielsen CFO to Its Board of Directors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Career</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-adds-nielsen-cfo-its-board-of-directors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114439/276406/screen-shot-2023-05-19-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="761798"/></item><item><title>South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</link><description>South Korea’s Justice Ministry has hit out at claims that Minister Han Dong-hoon “refused to disclose information” about whether or not he owns crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Newsis, the ministry claimed that “the cryptoasset holding status of public officials who work with cryptoasset [regulation]” is “checked regularly.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Politics</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114373/276294/adobestock-555291710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="304195"/></item><item><title>Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</link><description>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. made campaign promises on Friday advocating for bitcoin users, adding that he plans to accept campaign donations in bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable,” Kennedy said at the Bitcoin 2023 Conference in Miami. &lt;br /&gt;
Kennedy, who is the nephew of former President John F. Kennedy and the son of Robert F. Kennedy, announced his run for US president last month. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Presidential campaign</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114436/276402/screen-shot-2023-05-03-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="570501"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</link><description>The battle between Bitcoin and the $27,000 mark continues, with the cryptocurrency struggling to make headway in the face of mounting economic challenges. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a ray of hope is beginning to break through the macroeconomic clouds as Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell suggests a possible abatement in rate increases.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the face of mounting cryptocurrency market uncertainty, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>BGB</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>RNDR</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>INJ</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Render Token</category><category>Injective</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114440/276407/19-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="338633"/></item></channel></rss>
