<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>UK Adviser Calls for Regulation as AI Could Threaten Humanity in 2 Years</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-adviser-calls-for-regulation-as-ai-could-threaten-humanity-in-2-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 23:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254076</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/artificial_intelligence_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/artificial_intelligence_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Will AI take control of humans? Matt Clifford highlights the need for AI regulation in two years.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Artificial Intelligence (AI) continues to attain breakthroughs in what’s possible, there is a growing concern about whether these innovations may become more powerful than their creators.</p>
<p>Matt Clifford, chairman of the UK’s Advanced Research and Invention Agency (ARIA), stressed this in a recent <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wn4z1WnR6K0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with a local news outlet.</p>
<h2>AI Needs Regulation Within 2 Years</h2>
<p>Clifford emphasized that AI needs to be regulated soon to curb the risk of becoming “very powerful” within the next two years, as humans do not currently have control over them.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We’ve got two years to get in place a framework that makes both controlling and regulating these very large models much more possible than it is today,” he said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Commenting on the near-term and long-term risks that can sprout from using AI tools, Clifford said people could use AI-generated information to create bioweapons or conduct cyber attacks.</p>
<p>Clifford is not the only tech expert concerned about the risks tied to AI growth. In an open letter by the Center for AI Safety, 350 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ai-crypto-guide/" data-wpel-link="internal">artificial intelligence</a> experts endorsed the idea of AI being treated as an existential threat, just like nuclear weapons and pandemics threaten human existence.</p>
<h2>Can AI Pose More Threats to Humanity?</h2>
<p>Computer scientist and former Google employee Geoffrey Hinton also entertains the idea of AI overtaking power from humans. Earlier this month, he <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fears-for-humanity-and-the-dangers-of-artificial-intelligence-according-to-geoffrey-hinton/" data-wpel-link="internal">mentioned</a> in an interview that humans are building intelligence that could outthink humanity and pose threats to our existence.</p>
<p>Hinton, considered one of the godfathers of AI, highlighted the efficiency and knowledge-sharing capabilities of digital intelligence compared to the limitations of biological intelligence. While admitting that AI comes with potential benefits, Hinton emphasized the need to mitigate and prevent any negative consequences tied to it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-adviser-calls-for-regulation-as-ai-could-threaten-humanity-in-2-years/" rel="nofollow">UK Adviser Calls for Regulation as AI Could Threaten Humanity in 2 Years</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance CEO Summoned By U.S. District Court</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-summoned-by-u-s-district-court/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 22:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254315</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/cz_binance-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/cz_binance-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CZ must respond to a summons within 21 days regarding the SEC’s lawsuit against his firm.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) has been issued a summons by the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia following a lawsuit against himself and his exchange on Monday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The CEO must respond to the summons within 21 days, but is not required to appear in person. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Other entities named in the lawsuit, including Binance and Binance US, must also answer the </span><a href="https://www.docdroid.net/MHUeKyh/show-temp-2-pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">summons</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“If you fail to respond, judgment by default will be entered against you for the relief demanded in the complaint,” read the filing. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Per the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC)s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">136-page filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against Binance on Monday, the commission wants the exchange to “disgorge their ill-gotten gains with prejudgment interest,” and to permanently enjoin the firm from engaging in the crypto and securities trading business.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The lawsuit charged Binance with selling unregistered securities in the forms of BNB and BUSD, as well as operating as an unregistered securities exchange and broker-dealer within the United States.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">It also accused the firm of not retaining independence from Binance US, commingling billions of dollars in funds from both firms within Merit Peak – an entity controlled by CZ. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The CEO was not phased by the summons on Wednesday, viewing it as a procedural aspect of the lawsuit. </span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I was told this is just part of the SEC compliant process. Nothing new. </p>
<p>Also told I won&#39;t have to appear in person. No need to FUD. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f64f.png" alt="🙏" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/NYUlBCIirG" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/NYUlBCIirG</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1666513302304727059?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance US was issued a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-delists-101-trading-pairs-following-sec-freezing-order/" data-wpel-link="internal">restraining order</a> to have its assets frozen by the SEC on Tuesday, pending court approval. The order does not affect the international exchange. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-summoned-by-u-s-district-court/" rel="nofollow">Binance CEO Summoned By U.S. District Court</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized App Sweat Economy Unveils Governance Vote to Decide the Fate of 2B SWEAT Tokens</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-app-sweat-economy-unveils-governance-vote-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-sweat-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254197</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Sweat_Economy-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Sweat_Economy-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The 2 billion SWEAT tokens, which accounted for nearly 13% of the total supply, are currently locked up in a 24-month contract in inactive user accounts.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sweat Economy &#8211; a fitness-focused decentralized application &#8211;  announced the launch of a new governance vote on June 7th in the Sweat Wallet application.</p>
<p>The move would enable the community to decide the fate of 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens in inactive user accounts.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, users will be given two options.</li>
<li>They can either vote in favor of having the 2 billion idle SWEAT tokens recovered and transferred back to the ecosystem treasury for potential future distribution (or other uses as decided by upcoming votes), or they can vote in favor of leaving these tokens in inactive user accounts.</li>
<li>For the proposal to be approved or denied, a minimum of 75,000 votes is required. This criterion is requisite to ensure everyone has a fair opportunity to make their vote count.</li>
<li>Besides, the proposal will run for at least seven days. A three-day extension may be granted in the event of an ongoing influx of votes.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The new governance vote aims to resolve the lingering question: what should be done with these idle tokens? Sweat Economy now allows token holders to participate directly in the decision-making process, exercising the principle of one person, one vote, thereby democratizing the token&#8217;s future.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The team behind the network believes the new governance vote is &#8220;notable&#8221; due to the vast volume of SWEAT tokens at stake as well as the &#8220;deepening commitment&#8221; of the ecosystem to community-centric decision-making.</li>
<li>Sweat Economy said that the previous vote reportedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/100-million-sweat-tokens-burn-new-governance-proposal-seeks-community-input/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">garnered</a> 153,783 participants and expects to witness higher engagement numbers this time around.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-app-sweat-economy-unveils-governance-vote-to-decide-the-fate-of-2b-sweat-tokens/" rel="nofollow">Decentralized App Sweat Economy Unveils Governance Vote to Decide the Fate of 2B SWEAT Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance US Delists 101 Trading Pairs Following SEC Freezing Order</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-delists-101-trading-pairs-following-sec-freezing-order/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 21:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254305</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exchange confirmed no plans to resume trading for those pairs and is pausing its OTC trading portal for potentially months. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance’s U.S. subsidiary announced the removal of over 100 advanced trading pairs on Wednesday and paused its OTC trading portal following legal pressure from the SEC to freeze its assets earlier this week.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Some of the targeted pairs include </span><span style="font-weight: 400">AAVE/USDT, COMP/USDT, EOS/USDT, and BCH/BTC. </span></p>
<h2>Binance US Legal Trouble</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance US did not specify why the sudden pair removals were necessary, but assured users that their assets “remain safe” on the platform. The action will take effect at 12 pm EDT on June 8, and deposits and withdrawals will continue to process normally.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<figure id="attachment_254306" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254306" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254306 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61-1024x627.png" alt="" width="1024" height="627" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61-1024x627.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61-300x184.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61-768x471.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61-50x31.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Screenshot-61.png 1379w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254306" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance US</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The change brings the platform’s supported “convert” trading pairs down to 226. Buy, sell, and convert options remain available for most top cryptocurrencies by market capitalization, including BTC, ETH, USDT, USDC, DOGE, and others.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The exchange made no indication that it plans to bring such trading pairs back. While its OTC desk is currently “paused,” the firm said it will notify users when it’s available again “In the upcoming weeks and months.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Securities and Exchange Commission launched a </span><a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060/gov.uscourts.dcd.256060.4.1.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">restraining order</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against Binance US on Tuesday to freeze its assets, just one day after the agency launched its 136-page lawsuit against the exchange and its international parent company.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The exchange was also ordered to repatriate customers for all fiat currency and digital assets held on the Binance US platform within 10 days of receiving the restraining order. That included assets related to its staking-as-a-service program, for the SEC, which targeted </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase’s</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> equivalent program the same day. </span></p>
<h2>Commingling of Funds?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing placed particular emphasis on placing all customer assets back under the control of Binance US that are otherwise being controlled by either Binance or its CEO Changpeng Zhao. While Binance and Binance US are supposed to be independent entities, the SEC’s lawsuit on Monday alleged that billions of dollars from both platforms had been “commingled” within a Zhao-owned entity called Merit Peak Limited. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Within 5 days of this Restraining Order, Defendants will… remove Defendant Binance, Defendant Zhao, and any of the Binance Entities as a signatory or authorized person to transfer or withdraw assets from all accounts and/or wallets containing Customer Assets,” read the filing. Within 30 days, all customer funds must be held in wallets controlled by new private keys and administrative keys. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-delists-101-trading-pairs-following-sec-freezing-order/" rel="nofollow">Binance US Delists 101 Trading Pairs Following SEC Freezing Order</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Complains of Late Evidence Discovery That Supposedly Harms His Defense</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-complains-of-late-evidence-discovery-that-supposedly-harms-his-defense/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254221</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to a letter submitted by his lawyers, the prosecution has repeatedly delayed filing key evidence.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other FTX executives, who pleaded guilty to misdeeds while running FTX and have likely provided a treasure trove of information to the authorities in exchange for a lighter sentence, Sam Bankman-Fried has continued to maintain his innocence.</p>
<p>However, as the date that his case gets sent to trial grows ever nearer, his legal team continues to look for ways to lighten their load once October rolls around.</p>
<h2>Arguing Over Technicalities</h2>
<p>Last month, SBF’s legal team attempted to get a bevy of charges dismissed, claiming that they had not been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-files-to-dismiss-almost-all-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> at the time he agreed to be voluntarily extradited to the United States.</p>
<p>However, the court responded that most of the charges had been filed before the extradition and that the remaining ones needed only the (cursory) approval from Bahamian authorities to be filed as well.</p>
<p>With that particular avenue of mitigating possible jail time closed, SBF’s lawyers seem to have switched to a different approach: arguing over what evidence is admissible in court.</p>
<h2>Discovery Process Taking Too Long</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66631291/153/united-states-v-bankman-fried/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">letter</a> submitted by SBF’s legal team on behalf of the defendant, the discovery process – a legal term referring to the period in which legal evidence is submitted and the defense is made aware of said evidence – is taking far too long, prompting fears that this could hamper the efforts of the defense.</p>
<p>Although SBF allegedly does not want to postpone the trial date, his legal team has stated that this is a possibility if other measures are not taken.</p>
<blockquote><p>“As the trial date is now less than four months away, the defense is concerned that the late production of such voluminous and important discovery will impact the preparation of the defense. Mr. Bankman-Fried does not wish to adjourn the trial date. We raise these issues to alert the Court that Mr. Bankman-Fried may seek to leave to file additional motions […], including moving the Court to preclude the Government from using evidence produced too close to the trial date.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The evidence currently available reportedly adds up to a whopping 3.6 million documents and upwards of 10 million pages.</p>
<p>The prosecution is currently working through the contents of Gary Wang’s laptop and the information spread across 30 separate Google accounts tied to FTX management.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-complains-of-late-evidence-discovery-that-supposedly-harms-his-defense/" rel="nofollow">SBF Complains of Late Evidence Discovery That Supposedly Harms His Defense</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Market Recovers with Pepe Among Biggest Gainers and Wall Street Memes Presale Nearing $5M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-recovers-with-pepe-among-biggest-gainers-and-wall-street-memes-presale-nearing-5m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 20:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254247</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sponsored_wsm_cover.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sponsored_wsm_cover.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto market is back with a bang, spearheaded by popular projects like Pepe and Wall Street Memes, which are both seeing a significant uptick in investor interest. Pepe is now up over 10% in 24 hours, with Bitcoin, XRP, and Lido DAO also seeing significant gains, while the Wall Street Memes presale nears $5m. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market is back with a bang, spearheaded by popular projects like Pepe and Wall Street Memes, which are both seeing a significant uptick in investor interest.</p>
<p>Pepe is now up over 10% in 24 hours, with Bitcoin, XRP, and Lido DAO also seeing significant gains, while the Wall Street Memes presale nears $5m. Prices are rallying across the board as investors recuperate following the SEC&#8217;s crackdown on Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<p>With PEPE and <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">WSM</a> setting the pace, a wave of speculation is now building around which other coins could experience a similar resurgence soon.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Demonstrates Resilience Amidst SEC-Driven Storm</h2>
<p>It’s been a crazy few days for crypto investors, with significant news events prompting wild price swings that surprised everyone.</p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/us-sec-sues-binance-founder-zhao-alleging-securities-law-violations-2023-06-05/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by Reuters, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance and its CEO Changpeng Zhao on June 5, alleging that they operated a “web of deception” within the crypto market.</p>
<p>Binance denied the allegations, stating that they had cooperated with the SEC throughout their investigation – and even offered to settle so that it wouldn’t have to go to court.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254264" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-6.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="348" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-6-300x173.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-6-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>However, the SEC opted to proceed with litigation – and regulators didn’t stop there.</p>
<p>The Financial Times <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/8b107fe5-e993-4259-8b6c-67e6f35f199f" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">reported</a> on Tuesday that the SEC had also sued Coinbase, alleging it violated US securities law.</p>
<p>These two lawsuit announcements created massive volatility within the crypto market, leading to a rapid drop in Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), and other altcoins.</p>
<p>Investors were fearful that this drop would mark the beginning of a prolonged downturn. However, this hasn’t been the case, with the market showcasing remarkable resilience in the face of adversity – meaning most coins have almost erased the losses posted following the lawsuit reveal.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254263" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-8.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="269" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-8.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-8-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-8-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Pepe coin (PEPE) was one of the frontrunners of this resurgence, rising 29% in just eight hours. Although price has pulled back slightly, many PEPE bulls believe this could set the groundwork for another push.</p>
<p>Bitcoin was also up by 6%, while Ethereum rose by 5% as investors piled back into the market – causing a sea of green on the <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/crypto-heatmap/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap heatmap</a>.</p>
<p>All in all, this bounce-back showcases the enduring appeal of the crypto market – even in the face of regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Defies Bear Market &amp; Breaches $4.8 Million Mark in Highly-Successful Presale</h2>
<p>Another crypto that’s been making headway despite the market volatility is the brand-new<a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> project.</p>
<p>Although there has been an overwhelming sense of uncertainty in the past few days, Wall Street Memes’ presale continues to go from strength to strength – and has just passed the $4.8 million mark.</p>
<p>This fundraise highlights the growing buzz around Wall Street Memes, which combines the viral appeal of social media-based images with a colossal online community.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254262" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-5.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-5-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-5-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The Wall Street Memes community, made up of over 1.1 million people, is spread across several social media platforms – with the official <a href="https://www.instagram.com/wallstbets/?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Instagram page</a> having an audience of 524,000 alone.</p>
<p>The size of this online community has led to interactions with some big names. Tech tycoon Elon Musk, beloved in the crypto subculture, has <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1649784663924244482" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">interacted</a> with the community twice.</p>
<p>Ultimately, this innovative project aims to empower the people who made the Wall Street Memes community what it is by creating the WSM token – now available to purchase during the presale.</p>
<p>WSM can be bought through the ongoing presale for $0.0277. However, this presale has a staged structure, meaning the token price will increase between stages &#8211; incentivizing would-be investors to get involved.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>AiDoge Stirs Investor Excitement by Offering Last Chance to Buy Before Listing</h2>
<p>Alongside Wall Street Memes, trailblazing meme coin AiDoge (AI) is also piquing the interest of investors after selling out its presale phase.</p>
<p>AiDoge&#8217;s presale was a huge success, hitting its $14.9 million fundraising goal in just over one month – showcasing the tremendous demand from retail investors.</p>
<p>This demand has been driven by AiDoge’s groundbreaking use cases, which involve using artificial intelligence (AI) technology to help social media users create hilarious memes.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254261" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-4.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-4-300x122.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-4-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a>This setup has prompted colossal interest in the AiDoge project, with over 35,000 people following the official Twitter account to receive regular updates.</p>
<p>Although the presale has sold out, AiDoge’s team is offering one final window for investors to purchase $AI tokens for just $0.0000336 ahead of their debut on exchanges later this month.</p>
<p>Given that token exchange listings often cause substantial price increases, some investors believe this represents an opportunity to get involved at a low price point.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_c4d54499.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit AiDoge Website</strong></a></p>
<h2>Decentralized Crypto Analytics Platform yPredict Continues to Gain Momentum with Over $2m Raised</h2>
<p>Another project making waves in the crypto realm is yPredict (YPRED) – an innovative crypto analytics platform built on the Polygon blockchain.</p>
<p>yPredict’s goal is to provide accurate and objective insights into the performance of various coins and tokens – thereby giving traders an “edge” in the market.</p>
<p>As one of the most promising projects in the crypto analytics scene, yPredict aims to appeal to beginners and experienced investors by offering a suite of tools anyone can use.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254260" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-2.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="407" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-2-300x203.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-2-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Some of yPredict&#8217;s most exciting features include automated pattern recognition, AI-powered trading signals, market sentiment analysis, and a custom-built predictive model marketplace.</p>
<p>Users can even buy and stake YPRED, yPredict’s native ERC-20 token, to earn a recurring yield and access additional premium features.</p>
<p>Although yPredict is still in development, early investors can purchase YPRED tokens ahead of the platforms’ launch for $0.09 – 33% lower than the planned CEX listing price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Ripple Bounces Back &amp; Soars Past the $0.50 Level</h2>
<p>Ripple (XRP) is another crypto that has benefitted from the positive sentiment throughout the crypto market over the past day.</p>
<p>Although XRP had been rising for a few weeks prior, the token was still hit hard by the SEC’s market crackdown – yet it has recovered exceptionally well.</p>
<p>The XRP price has risen by just over 6% during the past 24 hours, soaring above the $0.50 level.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254259" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="602" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-300x165.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>At the time of writing, XRP is hovering around $0.52 – just below the high posted on June 4.</p>
<p>Whether XRP can sustain its recent gains remains to be seen, but for now, the outlook is overwhelmingly positive.</p>
<h2>Lido DAO Continues Bull Run Despite Market Volatility</h2>
<p>Finally, Lido DAO (LDO) has also been making a splash, with the token surging by 15% over the past day.</p>
<p>Per CoinMarketCap, there has been a 28% rise in LDO trading volume as investors clamor to buy tokens before the next leg to the upside.</p>
<p>Much like XRP, LDO was hurt by the ongoing market volatility yet has resumed its bull run, which commenced back in early May.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254258" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture8.jpg" alt="Picture8" width="602" height="335" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture8.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture8-300x167.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture8-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>LDO is up over 50% since this bull run began – and the price doesn’t look like stopping any time soon.</p>
<p>With solid fundamentals and a rapidly growing community, $LDO continues to show great promise for further gains.</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party. It is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-recovers-with-pepe-among-biggest-gainers-and-wall-street-memes-presale-nearing-5m/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Market Recovers with Pepe Among Biggest Gainers and Wall Street Memes Presale Nearing $5M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Explains Why SEC Legal Battle &#8220;Isn&#8217;t Good For America&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-explains-why-sec-legal-battle-isnt-good-for-america/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 18:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254284</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong disagrees with the SEC’s position that all crypto assets besides Bitcoin classify as securities. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong spoke at length on Wednesday about his initial reaction to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s lawsuit against his exchange.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The executive responded to SEC Chairman Gary Gensler’s claims about the market not needing more “digital currency,” and debated whether the SEC is acting in good faith. </span></p>
<h2>An Avalanche of Currencies</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/06/07/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-on-sec-lawsuit-weve-had-a-long-history-of-being-transparent-with-them.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with CNBC’s Squawk Box, Armstrong argued that Gensler was in no position to be “picking and choosing” the technology winners in the crypto space. “Let’s let the market decide that,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Gensler spoke with CNBC  about the lawsuit on Tuesday, asserting that “digital currency” was already a thing before crypto. “It’s called the U.S. dollar, It’s called the euro or it’s called the yen, they’re all digital right now,” he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, he questioned the use cases of the 16,000+ coins available for trading through Coinbase’s self-custodial wallet, arguing that disclosures were necessary to make those clear. As Armstrong explained, however, the vast majority of those cryptos are only tradeable on decentralized exchanges – not Coinbase’s platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We’ve reviewed over 1000 assets in crypto – we reject over 90% of them because we felt they weren’t appropriate for our exchange,” he said. Nevertheless, he stressed that cryptocurrencies besides fiat currencies can be used for payments, remittances, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-pledges-inviolable-right-to-hold-and-use-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">political donations</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and more. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The SEC’s Tuesday </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> named </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">13 assets</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> trading on Coinbase’s platform that it considers to be unregistered securities, some of which include Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC). Armstrong and Coinbase have long disagreed with Gensler about what constitutes a “security,” however, and argued that conflicting statements from the SEC and CFTC have created a lack of clarity around what the actual rules are. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This isn’t good for America, it’s not good for the industry,” he said, explaining that it would now be necessary to fetch clarity from </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">the courts</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<h2>Did The SEC “Change Its Mind” On Coinbase?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase and Armstrong have previously argued that the SEC was told what Coinbase’s business practices would be in its S1 registration form. That includes its plans to offer a staking-as-a-service product, which the SEC claimed in its lawsuit ought to have been registered with the agency before launching. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, CNBC panelists noted that the regulator made clear in its registration form that its S1 approval wasn’t tantamount to an “endorsement of the legality of the issuer’s underlying business.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">To the folks posting that it’s unfair that the SEC is filing an action when they approved the coinbase IPO, please stop. <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@coinbase</a> was warned that approval of the registration statement didn’t mean approval of the underlying business activity. It’s in the complaint. <a href="https://t.co/vvRYwD4pkd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/vvRYwD4pkd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Joe Carlasare (@JoeCarlasare) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeCarlasare/status/1666069135388815361?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While Armstrong conceded that a regulator has the right to “come back and edit their thinking,” his company does not share the agency’s legal interpretation that all crypto assets </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">aside from Bitcoin</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> are securities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This industry is just not going to exist in the United States if you take that position,” he said. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-explains-why-sec-legal-battle-isnt-good-for-america/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO Explains Why SEC Legal Battle &#8220;Isn&#8217;t Good For America&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buying the Dip: Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest Buys $21.6M Worth of Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Amid SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/buying-the-dip-cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-21-6m-worth-of-coinbases-coin-amid-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254192</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ArkInvest_Coinbase.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ArkInvest_Coinbase.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The latest purchase brings ARK's Coinbase stock portfolio to 11.44 million COIN valued at roughly $590 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Investment Management has doubled down on its bullish stance on Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in America. The investment management firm has purchased another pile of Coinbase (COIN) stock following a price dip caused by the recent SEC lawsuit against the exchange.</p>
<p>Recall that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> Coinbase on Tuesday, alleging that the firm failed to register as a national securities exchange, clearing agency, and broker despite performing all the functions. The commission also accused the company of failing to register its staking-as-a-service product and violating federal securities laws.</p>
<p>The SEC&#8217;s case against Coinbase came within 24 hours after the agency began enforcement action <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">against</a> Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange. Among the thirteen charges unveiled against the firm were allegations of self-dealing, market manipulation, and securities law violations.</p>
<h2>Ark Invest Buys $21.6M Worth of COIN</h2>
<p>Following the Coinbase lawsuit, COIN&#8217;s price came tumbling down. At the end of U.S. trading hours on Tuesday, the stock had plummeted by more than 13%, closing the trading day at $51.61.</p>
<p>According to Ark Invest&#8217;s trading activity on Tuesday, the company purchased 419,324 shares of Coinbase worth $21.6 million. The investment firm split the purchase across the ARK Innovation ETF, ARK Next Generation ETF, and ARK Fintech Innovation ETF.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Cathie Wood and Ark Invest&#8217;s trade activity from today 6/6 <a href="https://t.co/5np2GcZkWi" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/5np2GcZkWi</a></p>
<p>— Ark Invest Daily (@ArkkDaily) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkkDaily/status/1666234026569396224?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The latest acquisition brings ARK&#8217;s total COIN holdings to 11.44 million shares valued at roughly $590 million.</p>
<h2>Ark&#8217;s Previous COIN Purchases</h2>
<p>Ark Invest has a record of buying COIN&#8217;s dips emerging from market conditions and regulatory issues. In early May, the investment firm purchased 168,869 Coinbase stock worth about $8.5 million after the shares dropped 6.8% amid news of a class-action lawsuit that accused the exchange of violating privacy laws.</p>
<p>ARK acquired 304,300 COIN worth $17.5 million in April after purchasing 2.4 million shares for $117 million in the previous month. The company also made several rounds of COIN purchases in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-9-2m-worth-of-coinbases-coin-amid-price-drops/" data-wpel-link="internal">February</a> and January.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ark Invest sold thousands of Coinbase shares in March after a steady buying streak. On March 21, the firm dumped 160,887 COIN stock worth $13.5 million. ARK&#8217;s frequent COIN purchases show Wood is unrelenting in her bullish support for the exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/buying-the-dip-cathie-woods-ark-invest-buys-21-6m-worth-of-coinbases-coin-amid-sec-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">Buying the Dip: Cathie Wood&#8217;s Ark Invest Buys $21.6M Worth of Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Amid SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey Triggers Fresh Spat Between BTC Maximalists and ETH-Led Altcoin Tribe </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-triggers-fresh-spat-between-btc-maximalists-and-eth-led-altcoin-tribe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:22:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254222</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jack_Dorsey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Jack_Dorsey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[His assertion that Ether is a security splits the crypto community in two opposite camps.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the heat of SEC&#8217;s enforcement actions against Binance and Coinbase, a simple &#8220;Yes&#8221; by Jack Dorsey on Twitter elicited a flurry of comments.</p>
<p>It all started when a Twitter user asked Dorsey if he thinks Ether is a security, to which he answered in the affirmative.</p>
<h2>Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Ether Rant</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A known Bitcoin supporter, Dorsey has pointed out <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/billybambrough/2022/04/21/many-single-points-of-failure-twitter-founder-jack-dorsey-issues-stark-ethereum-warning-amid-price-volatility/?sh=187c6b3d5d4b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">dissatisfaction</a> with Ether in the past as well. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In the latest episode, the former Twitter CEO tweeted a screenshot of a 2015 post by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong, where he termed altcoins &#8220;distractions&#8221; and argued that they should be focused on Bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Then he went to retweet a video of Jack Mallers, CEO of Bitcoin Lighting app Strike, which calls out Coinbase CEO for prioritizing altcoins over bitcoin and the Lightning Network.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In fact, Dorsey&#8217;s take that Coinbase should focus on Bitcoin is not entirely his own. In the aftermath of the SEC lawsuit against Coinbase, various experts have put forth their suggestions. One from </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Pierre Rochard, vice president of research at Riot Platforms, suggested that Coinbase should <a href="https://u.today/elon-musk-gives-epic-dogecoin-reply-to-twitter-founder-who-says-ethereum-is-security" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">refocus</a> on Bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Twitter founder Dorsey stepped down as its CEO in November 2021 to focus on his digital payments company — Block Inc. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For his bravado, Dorsey earned some nasty <a href="https://twitter.com/udiWertheimer/status/1666080703648284672?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">trolls</a>, such as being called &#8220;Clowns&#8221; by Udi Wertheimer of Taproot Wizards. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Jack is the kind of MAXIs that keep this technology behind even after 200 years from now. So the less &#8220;Jack&#8217;s&#8221; we have, the better for the whole industry,&#8221; a Twitter user <a href="https://twitter.com/Ansi09Crypto/status/1666336414919716865" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">commented</a>.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>What&#8217;s Behind the Scene?</h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) sued Binance and Coinbase on June 5 and June 6, respectively. It charged the two biggest crypto trading platforms with operating as exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies without proper licenses. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At the root of the SEC action is the classification of cryptocurrencies. In its chargesheet against Coinbase, SEC has alleged that the latter facilitates trade in large-cap securities such as SOL, ADA, MATIC, and so on. Interestingly, both the SEC and the CFTC treat Bitcoin as a commodity but don&#8217;t offer a final decision on Ethereum, the second-largest cryptocurrency. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite a lack of regulation for the crypto industry, the SEC tends to treat the rest of the cryptocurrencies as securities, while the CFTC asks for jurisdiction and greater regulatory oversight on the asset class.       </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-triggers-fresh-spat-between-btc-maximalists-and-eth-led-altcoin-tribe/" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey Triggers Fresh Spat Between BTC Maximalists and ETH-Led Altcoin Tribe </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Will The SEC Fiasco Impact Bitcoin and What&#8217;s Next? (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-will-the-sec-fiasco-impact-bitcoin-and-whats-next-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254043</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-6-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-6-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin is currently on a downward trajectory since it faced resistance at $30K in April. However, there are notable support levels that may prevent further decline. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the Bitcoin price has consistently formed lower highs and lows in the past couple of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of Bitcoin is currently on a downward trajectory since it faced resistance at $30K in April. However, there are notable support levels that may prevent further decline.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<h3><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></h3>
<h3><strong>The Daily Chart:</strong></h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the Bitcoin price has consistently formed lower highs and lows in the past couple of months. The 50-day moving average acted as a strong resistance, causing a downward rejection near the $28K level.</p>
<p>Following yesterday&#8217;s rebound, the price is testing the 50-day moving average again. A bullish breakout would result in a rally towards the $30K level, while another rejection would lead to a drop-down to the $25K support level and the key 200-day moving average located around the $24K mark.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254251" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254251" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254251 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0706231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-Daily-Jun-7-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254251" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour timeframe, it is clear that the Bitcoin price faced a significant barrier at the $27,500 resistance level and experienced a sharp decline thereafter. The short-term support level at $26K has also been breached, indicating a continued downward movement with strong momentum.</p>
<p>However, the BTC price has now reversed following the RSI&#8217;s overbought signal and is currently retesting the $27,500 resistance area. If it breaks above this point, the descending channel is likely to be broken as well, paving the way for the market to rise toward the $30K level once again.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254252" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254252" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254252 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0706232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSDT-4H-Jun-7-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254252" class="wp-caption-text">Source: tradingVIew</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>While many were optimistic about the beginning of a bull market, a wave of fear and uncertainty spread through the industry because of what happened lately. On Monday, the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a lawsuit against Binance, leading to a 5% drop in the price of Bitcoin. The next day, it field a lawsuit against Coinbase as well.</p>
<p>A graph representing the Active Addresses metric, which indicates the number of participants actively engaging with Bitcoin&#8217;s network alongside the price, provides valuable insights. The chart demonstrates an upward trend, signaling a positive outlook for network activity and the demand for Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this trend has recently reversed, and the metric is now experiencing a significant decline, primarily attributed to the recent FUD.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254044" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254044" style="width: 2530px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254044 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023.jpg" alt="btc_active_addresses_chart_0706231" width="2530" height="1598" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023.jpg 2530w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-1024x647.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-768x485.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-1536x970.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-2048x1294.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-Active-Adresses-Jun-6-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2530px) 100vw, 2530px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254044" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-will-the-sec-fiasco-impact-bitcoin-and-whats-next-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">How Will The SEC Fiasco Impact Bitcoin and What&#8217;s Next? (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
