<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 15:57:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>26% of Family Offices Invest in Crypto: Goldman Sachs Survey</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/26-of-family-offices-invest-in-crypto-goldman-sachs-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249764</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/GoldmanSachs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/GoldmanSachs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["The proportion that is invested has risen from 16% in 2021 to 26%," the leading financial institution claimed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The banking giant Goldman Sachs determined in a recent study that 32% of family offices across the globe have exposure to digital assets, NFTs, or DeFi, while 26% have explicitly invested in cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The results from the 2021 research showed that only 16% of the wealth management firms were HODLers. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Two Years Difference </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Goldman Sachs contacted 166 family offices in the Americas, Europe, the Middle East and Africa (EMEA), and Asia-Pacific (APAC) to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.gsam.com/content/dam/pwm/direct-links/us/en/PDF/onegs_familyoffice_eyesonthehorizon.pdf?sa=n&amp;rd=n" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">determine</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> how their investment strategy has altered in the past few years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study from 2021 estimated that 16% of the respondents have invested in digital currencies, while the current figures have risen to 26%. Nonetheless, interest in the sector has dropped significantly:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Within the digital-asset ecosystem, family offices have become more decisive about cryptocurrencies: the proportion that is invested has risen from 16% in 2021 to 26%. However, the proportion that is not invested and not interested in the future has risen from 39% to 62%, and those that are potentially interested in the future has fallen from 45% to 12%.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Goldman Sachs further revealed that 32% of the participants currently have some exposure to digital assets (including cryptocurrencies, stablecoins, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), decentralized finance (DeFi), and blockchain-related funds).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The primary motivation for those who have entered the ecosystem is the belief in the power of blockchain technology (19%). 9% have joined the industry to diversify their portfolios, whereas 8% view digital currencies as a store of value. In addition, 8% have purchased bitcoin or altcoins, hoping to profit in the future or simply speculating.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249789" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249789" style="width: 1289px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249789" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2.png" alt="Reasons for Investing" width="1289" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2.png 909w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2-300x93.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2-768x238.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Goldman2-50x16.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1289px) 100vw, 1289px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249789" class="wp-caption-text">Reasons for Investing, Source: Goldman Sachs</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><br />
Most HODLers (30%) are from the APAC region. In addition, 27% of the family offices without crypto exposure from that area remain interested in the future.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The EMEA is on the opposite corner, with only 15% cryptocurrency investors and 79% who say they are not intrigued to join the pack. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hong Kong and Singapore Emerge as Leaders</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another recent study conducted by KPMG China and Aspen Digital </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-half-of-surveyed-family-offices-from-these-2-countries-have-invested-in-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">concluded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that nearly 60% of family offices and high-net-worth individuals (HNWIs) from Hong Kong and Singapore have invested some of their wealth in digital assets. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;For HNWIs and family offices, there is a real possibility of a big upside, so they may think, why not stick 2 or 3 percent of my portfolio in that and see what happens,&#8221; Paul McSheaffrey – Senior Banking Partner at KPMG China &#8211; explained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The research revealed that the two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalization &#8211; bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH) &#8211; are the most popular digital assets in both regions. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/26-of-family-offices-invest-in-crypto-goldman-sachs-survey/" rel="nofollow">26% of Family Offices Invest in Crypto: Goldman Sachs Survey</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tron&#8217;s Revenue in Q1, 2023 Surpassed $90M: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/trons-revenue-in-q1-2023-surpassed-90m-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250328</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/tron-nedir.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/tron-nedir.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tron is seeing substantial expansion across DeFi and stablecoin landscapes.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Tron blockchain witnessed an increase in usage in the first quarter of 2023, according to a new report from market intelligence firm Messari. The market cap of its native token, TRX, was up by almost 20% QoQ.</p>
<p>Despite the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announcing several lawsuits against Tron ecosystem tokens, the network activity remained mostly unfazed. Its total quarterly revenue climbed $90.04 million in Q1 2023, experiencing a 88% jump from its Q4 2022 revenue of $47.96 million.</p>
<h2>State of Tron: Q1 2023</h2>
<p>The average daily transactions during the three months under review grew by 7.7% to approximately 7 million. Messari stated that the increase can be partially attributed to staking activity on the network. The total transaction count originating from the staking activity was up by 197% QoQ, despite only accounting for nearly 3% of all transactions on the TRX network.</p>
<p>The State of Tron <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-tron-q1-2023?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, commissioned by Tron, stated that the transaction activity on the network was mostly dominated by smart contracts triggered and TRX transfers, representing 88% of all. Despite the activity across both transaction types being relatively flat throughout Q1, the USDT smart contract remained the main catalyst of contract execution on TRON.</p>
<p>Transaction fees also witnessed a surge in the first quarter. The stats revealed that the average transaction fee in TRX and USD was up 59.2% and 80.2%, respectively. Committee proposal No. 79, which passed in the previous quarter, played a crucial role in prompting an increase in the transaction fees. The proposal in question essentially altered network parameters and ramped up the amount of energy required to execute smart contracts.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the dynamic energy model was enabled earlier this year as part of TIP-474. The mechanism essentially focuses on increasing the transaction cost and disincentivizing the low-value smart contract transactions that are without affecting other applications.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Dynamic Energy Model and increased requirements for Energy resulted in greater revenue generation in TRX (total transaction fees paid in TRX), which increased by 65.5% QoQ (+87.7% in USD). Simultaneously, the circulating market cap of TRX increased by 18.1% QoQ.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Tron DeFi, Stablecoin Space</h2>
<p>The Total Value Locked (TVL) denominated in USD increased by 18.8% in the first quarter of the year. But TVL denominated in TRX noted a minor slump of 0.5%. Such a trend signaled that &#8220;an asset price increase in USD drove TVL rather than new capital inflow.&#8221;</p>
<p>The top protocols by TVL on top of the Tron network &#8211; JustLend and JustStables &#8211; also benefited from the broader market recovery throughout Q1. As a result, both protocols increased by 26% and 21%, respectively.</p>
<p>Tron&#8217;s position in the stablecoin landscape remains substantial as it trails behind Ethereum. The Justin Sun-spearheaded platform is also ahead of other rival chains with regard to the market cap of hosted stablecoins. At the end of Q1, it held more than $43 billion, up from nearly $33 billion QoQ. Moreover, Tron&#8217;s USDT market cap also increased by 30% to $10 billion QoQ, owing to Tether swapping $400 million USDT from ERC-20 to Tron.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/trons-revenue-in-q1-2023-surpassed-90m-report/" rel="nofollow">Tron&#8217;s Revenue in Q1, 2023 Surpassed $90M: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pros and Cons for Bitcoin Related to BRC-20 Token Standard: Bitfinex Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pros-and-cons-for-bitcoin-related-to-brc-20-token-standard-bitfinex-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 16:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250514</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitcoin_Network.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Bitcoin_Network.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While the new token standard underscores the potential of Ordinals, it still shows that more use cases are needed to accelerate its adoption.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest buzz in the crypto world revolves around the newly introduced Bitcoin token standard (BRC-20), which has garnered considerable attention and favor owing to the recent memecoin craze. Despite the ongoing hype, the token standard is still subject to certain constraints concerning the broader crypto landscape.</p>
<p>A recent <a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitfinex-Alpha-53-Special-Edition..pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> by leading crypto exchange Bitfinex has emphasized the token standard&#8217;s potential and the significance of identifying more use cases to expedite its widespread adoption.</p>
<h2>The BRC-20 Token Standard</h2>
<p>In March, the BRC-20 token standard, known as &#8220;Bitcoin Request for Comment,&#8221; was established utilizing the Ordinals protocol. Originally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-nfts-whats-the-impact-of-ordinals-on-the-btc-network-research/" data-wpel-link="internal">designed</a> to facilitate the creation of Bitcoin non-fungible tokens (NFTs) by inscribing data such as images, videos, codes, and text into the witness portion of BTC transactions, the protocol has evolved to allow for the distinctive transfer of fungible tokens on the blockchain.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://brc-20.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from brc-20.io, the market capitalization of BRC-20 tokens had exceeded $900 million at one point, with more than 14,400 tokens issued. However, the market has declined to approximately $542 million at the time of writing.</p>
<p>Since the introduction of Bitcoin-based fungible assets, transactions on the network have surged, with BRC-20 Ordinals transactions surpassing non-BRC-20 transactions by over four million, according to <a href="https://dune.com/cryptokoryo/brc20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from Dune Analytics.</p>
<p>Some of the most in-demand BRC-20 tokens include ORDI, NALS, PIZA, PEPE, and MEME.</p>
<h2>Limitations of the Network</h2>
<p>Despite showcasing the potential of the Ordinals protocol, the new token standard faces limitations that could impede its growth and advancement.</p>
<p>One significant drawback is the lack of use cases, which could hinder development. Additionally, the BRC-20 network doesn&#8217;t support smart contracts, and assets&#8217; prices depend mainly on market speculation. This, coupled with their 24-hour trading volume being less than 30% of their market cap, as evident in the case of ORDI, makes predicting their future challenging.</p>
<p>Another limitation is the absence of Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatibility, restricting developers&#8217; access to network resources and building capabilities. This could limit adoption and result in a narrow ecosystem.</p>
<p>Furthermore, BRC-20 tokens consume significant block space, which could lead to network congestion and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" data-wpel-link="internal">higher</a> transaction fees.</p>
<p>Despite these limitations, Bitcoin&#8217;s proof-of-work (PoW) consensus mechanism makes it difficult for hackers to breach the network, making the blockchain&#8217;s security robust.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pros-and-cons-for-bitcoin-related-to-brc-20-token-standard-bitfinex-report/" rel="nofollow">Pros and Cons for Bitcoin Related to BRC-20 Token Standard: Bitfinex Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Shaky at $27K as Another Drop Seemingly Underway (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-shaky-at-27k-as-another-drop-seemingly-underway-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250596</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been dropping continuously over the last week, and there may still be more. However, the bearish momentum is much lower than expected, and multiple support levels are available for the market to rely on. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart Looking at the daily timeframe, the price has been declining since [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been dropping continuously over the last week, and there may still be more. However, the bearish momentum is much lower than expected, and multiple support levels are available for the market to rely on.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the daily timeframe, the price has been declining since getting rejected from the $30K resistance level in April, and it has also broken below the 50-day moving average, located around the $29K mark.</p>
<p>Judging by the recent candlestick shapes, a bullish pullback to the broken moving average could be likely. Yet, the price could still push lower toward the $25K static support level before returning higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250599" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250599" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250599 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1405231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-14-2023-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250599" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The 4-hour chart shows that BTC has broken below the $27,500 minor support level and is likely to test the $25K zone in the coming days. However, with the RSI rising back above the oversold area and a clear bullish divergence being displayed between the two recent lows, a retest of the $27,500 level, which now acts as a resistance, could be expected in the short term.</p>
<p>Yet, all things considered, the market structure in this timeframe is clearly bearish until the price rallies above the $30K resistance level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250600" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250600" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250600 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1405232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-4H-May-14-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250600" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h1>Onchain Analysis</h1>
<h2>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></h2>
<p>The Bitcoin network has reached an all-time high in activity, with a new record of 682,000 daily transactions. This marks a significant increase from the 250,000 daily transactions seen at the beginning of 2023. The primary reason for this surge is the rising popularity of ordinal inscriptions, mainly used to create digital assets.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the surge in Bitcoin activity and the growing popularity of BRC-20 tokens have had a negative impact on the market. The Bitcoin network has become crowded, resulting in users having to pay higher transaction fees. This situation is affecting all Bitcoin participants, including everyday users and miners. As a result, trading in the BTC markets requires additional caution, as the market may experience high volatility.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250601" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250601" style="width: 2544px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250601 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023.jpg" alt="btc_transaction_count_1405231" width="2544" height="1602" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023.jpg 2544w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Transaction-Count-Total-May-14-2023-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2544px) 100vw, 2544px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250601" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-shaky-at-27k-as-another-drop-seemingly-underway-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Shaky at $27K as Another Drop Seemingly Underway (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyzing Ethereum Post-Shapella Upgrade: Nansen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/analyzing-ethereum-post-shapella-upgrade-nansen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 13:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250466</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Data suggest that the withdrawals have been minimal and have thus far been matched with inflows. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the lead-up to the last month&#8217;s Shapella upgrades, many crypto pundits speculated that activating staked Ether withdrawals could drag the price of the native asset down.</p>
<p>But the latest data suggest that the selling pressure on ETH post-withdrawal &#8220;has been somewhat of a non-event.&#8221; This is backed by the fact that deposits have almost matched the amount of ETH coming into circulation.</p>
<h2>State of Ethereum: Post Shapella</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-ethereum-shanghai-shapella-upgrade-everything-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Shapella</a> implementation was crucial as it enabled the withdrawals of staked ETH from the Beacon Chain for the very first time. However, the event also ignited <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-didnt-eth-dump-after-shanghai-interview-with-nansen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">concerns</a> about the unstaked ETH entering circulation potentially leading to sustained selling pressure. The bullish outlook, on the other hand, argued the risk of being unable to withdraw is eliminated, resulting in more deposits.</p>
<p>According to Nansen&#8217;s recent <a href="https://research.nansen.ai/article/815/state-of-ethereum-a-post-shapella-update" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> that analyzed the state of Ethereum post-Shapella, it was observed that the elimination of unstaking risks has thus far offset selling pressure from withdrawals. To top that, a significant proportion of the ETH withdrawn is likely not intended for selling.</p>
<p>The report stated that the upgrade had a net zero impact on ETH staked.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There are 19.3M ETH, including rewards, on the Beacon Chain today, equivalent to the amount of ETH on the Beacon Chain during the time of the Shapella upgrade, meaning that it has had a net zero impact on the network so far.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The withdrawal requests were dominated by centralized crypto exchanges. Kraken, for one, is leading with its withdrawal volume accounting for more than 26% of all ETH withdrawals since the upgrade. This is likely related to the recent regulatory crackdown on the US-based exchange&#8217;s staking service, which has forced it to return the staked ETH to depositors of its platform.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Other notable Principal ETH withdrawers include Binance, Coinbase, and Private Transactions Miner: 0xffd, with 13.3%, 12.5%, and 5.44% of the share of Principal ETH withdrawn, respectively.&#8221; &#8211; the report reads.</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_250572" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250572" style="width: 2070px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250572" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH.png" alt="Withdrawn ETH Since Shapella. Source: Nansen" width="2070" height="1162" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH.png 2070w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-300x168.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-1024x575.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-768x431.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-1536x862.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-2048x1150.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Withdrawn-ETH-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2070px) 100vw, 2070px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250572" class="wp-caption-text">Withdrawn ETH Since Shapella. Source: Nansen</figcaption></figure>
<p>A month after the upgrade, withdrawals have greatly slowed down, and Nansen&#8217;s data suggest that the majority of entities are currently holding onto their remaining balance for now. Entities such as Lido, Binance, Coinbase, Kiln, and Stakefish account for deposits of more than a million Ether over the past month.</p>
<h2>Withdrawers Behaviour</h2>
<p>Nansen reported that nearly 73% of the withdrawn ETH from the Beacon Chain thus far has been sent to centralized exchanges. But, the majority of this is CEXs withdrawing ETH to themselves, which indicates that the majority of the token being sent to these entities is not intended for selling. Instead, these tokens are for the exchange&#8217;s internal operations.</p>
<p>Contrastingly, the amount of ETH sent to decentralized exchanges from withdrawers only represents 1.23% of the total proportion. Around 20% of the withdrawn ETH were found to have been sent to all miscellaneous addresses which are not labeled as CEX, DEX, Staking, or DeFi, according to Nansen, and approximately 6% of all withdrawn ETH was sent to re-stake.</p>
<p>Nansen believes this cohort is less likely to take profits as they are still running validator nodes, and staking rewards are processed automatically. Therefore, some ETH from partial withdrawers would return to the Beacon Chain to rake in more yield.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/analyzing-ethereum-post-shapella-upgrade-nansen/" rel="nofollow">Analyzing Ethereum Post-Shapella Upgrade: Nansen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Generated $1.5B in Profits in Q1, 2023, Holds 2% Bitcoin in Total Reserves</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-generated-1-5b-in-profits-in-q1-2023-holds-2-bitcoin-in-total-reserves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250057</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TetherUSD.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TetherUSD.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[USDT's market cap has increased by nearly 25% since the beginning of the year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amid the banking turmoil in the United States, Tether (USDT) emerged as the preferred stablecoin.</p>
<p>The resurgence was evident in its latest attestation report, which revealed that the stablecoin issuer recorded a net profit of nearly $1.5 billion in the first quarter of 2023.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the official <a href="https://tether.to/en/tethers-latest-q1-2023-assurance-report-shows-reserves-surplus-at-all-time-high-of-244b-up-148b-in-net-profit-new-categories-for-additional-transparency-reveals-bitcoin-and-gold-allocations" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, Tether&#8217;s excess reserves reached an all-time high of $2.44 billion in Q1, as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-generated-over-700-million-in-profits-in-q4-2022/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">compared</a> to $960 million at the end of Q4 2022.</li>
<li>The stablecoin ended the first quarter of the year with $81.8 billion in consolidated total assets, while its consolidated total liabilities stood near $79.4 billion.</li>
<li>Tether&#8217;s reserves included additional categories such as bitcoin, physical gold, overnight repo, and corporate bond allocations. Its Bitcoin holdings were recorded to be $1.5 billion, while that of precious metals accounted for $3.3 billion.</li>
<li>85% of the stablecoin issuer&#8217;s investments are being held in cash, cash equivalents, and other short-term deposits. Gold and bitcoin represent approximately 4% and 2% of the total reserves, respectively,</li>
<li>Tether said it is doubling down its focus on limiting its reliance on pure bank deposits as a source of liquidity and &#8220;instead leverages the Repo market as an additional measure to ensure higher standards of protection for its users by maintaining the required liquidity.&#8221;</li>
<li>Commenting on the quarterly profit, Paolo Ardoino, CTO of Tether, stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled with the tremendous success Tether has achieved in Q1 2023. Looking ahead to Q2, we have an extremely positive outlook and remain committed to transparency, which is why we have introduced new categories in the reserves’ breakdown in our quarterly report to provide even greater transparency to our users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-generated-1-5b-in-profits-in-q1-2023-holds-2-bitcoin-in-total-reserves/" rel="nofollow">Tether Generated $1.5B in Profits in Q1, 2023, Holds 2% Bitcoin in Total Reserves</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Shoots Up 20% Daily, Bitcoin Flat at $27K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-shoots-up-20-daily-bitcoin-flat-at-27k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 07:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250575</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After several consecutive days of price drops, PEPE has bounced off rather impressively.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin tried its hand at taking down $27,000 yesterday but failed amid low weekend trading volumes and has remained relatively still.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also lacking any substantial price moves, with ETH reclaiming $1,800 and BNB pumping above $310.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stays Flat</h2>
<p>The past several days didn&#8217;t go well for the primary cryptocurrency. It all started on Wednesday when the asset jumped from $27,500 to $28,400 in minutes after the US CPI numbers came out for April.</p>
<p>Although BTC went on the offensive first, it reversed its trajectory almost immediately and dumped hard by almost $2,000 to a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/150m-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-dumped-to-2-month-low-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">multi-week low</a> of $26,600 (on Bitstamp).</p>
<p>The bulls tried to intercept the price slump and pushed the cryptocurrency back up to $28,000. However, another rejection followed that drove it back down to $27,000. As the weekend approached, BTC nosedived once again to under $26,000 for the first time in two months.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it managed to bounce off and even <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ldo-explodes-13-btc-eyes-27k-after-new-2-month-low-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">challenge</a> $27,000 in the past 24 hours but to no avail so far. As of now, the asset trades inches away from that level, but its market cap has gone back up to $520 billion. Its dominance over the alts is also flat on a daily scale at 46.3%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250576" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250576" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250576" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-13-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250576" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>PEPE Back on the Offensive</h2>
<p>The word in the crypto town for the past month or so has been on the recently launched memecoin &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a>. It became arguably the best performer as its market cap skyrocketed from $1 million to almost $2 trillion within this timeframe, making numerous investors rich overnight.</p>
<p>As the hype was at its highest, though, came listings on multiple exchanges, such as BitMEX and Binance. This turned out to be a sell-the-news moment as PEPE <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-pump-and-dump-from-1-8b-market-cap-to-800m-in-4-days-hype-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">lost</a> over half of its value in the following days.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours have been a lot more positive for the memecoin, which is up by 20%. On a weekly scale, though, PEPE is still down by over 30%.</p>
<p>In contrast, the larger-cap alts sit a lot quieter today, with little-to-no movements from the likes of ETH, NB, XRP, ADA, DOGE, SOL, and many others.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250577" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250577" style="width: 1881px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250577" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1881" height="850" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9.jpg 1881w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9-1024x463.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9-768x347.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9-1536x694.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-9-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1881px) 100vw, 1881px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250577" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-shoots-up-20-daily-bitcoin-flat-at-27k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Shoots Up 20% Daily, Bitcoin Flat at $27K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Korean Politician Agrees to Sell his Crypto Assets Following Public Scrutiny (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/korean-politician-agrees-to-sell-his-crypto-assets-following-public-scrutiny-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250008</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/South_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["I will faithfully implement the recommendation," Nam-kuk affirmed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kim Nam-kuk &#8211; a South Korean lawyer and politician &#8211; will reportedly sell his cryptocurrency holdings amid a conflict of interest that surrounds his stash. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Democratic party (DP), which he is part of, will also launch an investigation to determine whether he complied with local requirements when acquiring the tokens. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Inspection Could Reach Other Members of the Party</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a local media outlet, the DP </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20230510007551315" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">urged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Nam-kuk to sell his approximately 800,000 Wemix coins following allegations that he might have used insider information to acquire them. Some have also suggested the lawmaker has not abided by domestic rules when dealing with the tokens a few years back. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The party further announced it will thoroughly investigate the matter to discover any possible irregularities with Nam-kuk&#8217;s actions. While the examination will be focused initially on him, it could later affect other members of the DP. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Outside experts with specialist knowledge could join the investigation if necessary because coins involve things hard for ordinary people to understand,&#8221; spokesperson Kwon Chil-seung stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nam-kuk said he will fully cooperate and sell the stash, which is equivalent to approximately $700,000 at the moment of writing these lines. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I received the recommendation from the party to sell my crypto assets. I will faithfully implement the recommendation. I will transparently disclose data to the investigation team and undergo the inquiry faithfully.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_250037" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250037" style="width: 627px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a style="font-weight: bold; background-color: transparent;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kim-Nam-kuk.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250037" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kim-Nam-kuk.jpg" alt="Kim Nam-kuk " width="627" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kim-Nam-kuk.jpg 740w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kim-Nam-kuk-300x191.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Kim-Nam-kuk-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 627px) 100vw, 627px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250037" class="wp-caption-text">Kim Nam-kuk, Source: The Korea Times</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nam-kuk supposedly withdrew the coins before March 2022, ahead of legislation that requires crypto entities to report personal data when transferring above 1 million won ($758).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawmaker was also involved in a bill that proposed a delay of income taxation on digital assets. Interestingly, this happened several months before he withdrew his Wemix tokens. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Taxation Coming in 2025</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of South Korea displayed intentions to apply a 20% levy on gains made from cryptocurrency trading from the start of 2022. While the legislation sparked debates among lawmakers, it was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/survey-most-south-koreans-approve-the-upcoming-20-tax-on-crypto-gains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">well-received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by most locals.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The People Power Party </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/opposing-political-party-suggests-one-year-delay-on-south-koreas-crypto-tax-law-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">proposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in October 2021 that the rule should come into force with one year delay (from January 1, 2023). The political group also argued that people with profits of less than $42,000 per annum should be excluded from taxation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Democratic Party also tried to postpone the bill. Woong-rae – a Member of the DP &#8211; maintained that the Asian country has not designed an appropriate plan focused on the taxation procedure:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;In a situation where the relevant taxation infrastructure is not sufficiently prepared, the deferral of taxation on virtual assets is no longer an option but an inevitable situation.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Eventually, the Korean government </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.forbesindia.com/article/crypto-made-easy/south-korea-postpones-20-tax-on-crypto-gains-to-2025/78341/1" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">delayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the rule until 2025. It will apply to every local whose crypto profits exceed $1,900 per year. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/korean-politician-agrees-to-sell-his-crypto-assets-following-public-scrutiny-report/" rel="nofollow">Korean Politician Agrees to Sell his Crypto Assets Following Public Scrutiny (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animoca Brands Reports $3.4B in Cash and Token Reserves</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-reports-3-4b-in-cash-and-token-reserves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 22:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Sandbox (SAND)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250218</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Animoca.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Animoca.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Animoca plans to publish the audited financial statements for 2020 and the subsequent financial and business highlights soon. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain gaming giant &#8211; Animoca Brands &#8211; revealed around $3.4 billion in assets in an interim financial update that outlined its key unaudited financial positions as of April 30, 2023.</p>
<p>The Hong Kong-based company announced that it remains financially strong with a cash and stablecoin balance of $194 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>The financial <a href="https://www.animocabrands.com/animoca-brands-update-on-financial-position" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> also reported liquid digital assets of $566 million, including reserves of SAND, the utility token used in The Sandbox platform.</li>
<li>Additionally, the off-balance sheet token reserves for all other Animoca Brands&#8217; majority-owned Web3 subsidiaries stood at $2.7 billion.</li>
<li>Animoca is set to publish additional financial updates starting with the audited financial statements for 2020. Subsequently, the company also plans to roll out key financial and business highlights for the full year 2022 and Q1 2023.</li>
<li>It was earlier <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-slashes-target-of-metaverse-fund-by-20-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that the venture capital firm slashed its metaverse fund target to $800 million, with its valuation dropping from $6 billion to $2 billion amid volatility in the crypto market and instability in the banking sector.</li>
<li>Animoca Brands later refuted claims of scaling back its metaverse fund target.</li>
<li>After positioning itself as a prominent player in the Web3 industry, Animoca Brand was <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/what-metaverse-venture-investment-in-2022-can-tell-us-about-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">named</a> the most funded metaverse developer by Nasdaq.</li>
<li>It even bagged the majority of metaverse deals in 2022, closing 15 deals and receiving more than $564 million in funding.</li>
<li>The company was last valued at around $6 billion when it raised $110 million in a round announced last September. The funding round was led by Temasek, Boyu Capital, and GGV Capital. Two months later, Animoca raised an additional $75 million in a Liberty City Ventures-led round at the same valuation</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-reports-3-4b-in-cash-and-token-reserves/" rel="nofollow">Animoca Brands Reports $3.4B in Cash and Token Reserves</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Half of North Korea&#8217;s Missile Programs Funded via Stolen Crypto: White House</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-north-koreas-missile-programs-funded-via-stolen-crypto-white-house/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 19:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250207</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/North_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/North_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Anne Neuberger said the US government is committed to identify North Korean crypto hackers and trace the stolen digital assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to an undisclosed White House official, North Korea has funded approximately half of its missile tests through crypto theft and cyberattacks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent Chainalysis report suggested that North Korean hackers embezzled $1.7 billion of digital assets in 2022. Arguably the most notorious local hacking collective &#8211; the Lazarus Group &#8211; stood behind numerous exploits last year, with the $625 million breach on Ronin Network being the most famous one. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">North Korean Hackers Remain a Threat </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Democratic People&#8217;s Republic of Korea is on its way to becoming a military giant over the past years and is one of the few countries globally with nuclear weapons. Its government, led by Kim Jong Un, also takes every opportunity to upgrade its weapons by carrying out missile programs and various tests.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A White House official recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://edition.cnn.com/2023/05/10/politics/north-korean-missile-program-cyberattacks/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">disclosed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that stolen cryptocurrencies or cyberattacks fund half of those war efforts. Anne Neuberger &#8211; Deputy National Security Adviser for cyber and emerging technology &#8211; said Biden&#8217;s cabinet is &#8220;putting a lot of time and thought&#8221; and is trying to understand how &#8220;a country like [North Korea] is so darn creative in this space.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She also asserted that US intelligence agencies are trying to identify the bad actors and trace the drained assets. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United Nations (UN) also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/north-korea-funds-missile-programs-with-stolen-crypto-un-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the totalitarian nation financed its missile programs and nuclear experiments with crypto theft. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite all the accusations and threats from the Western world, North Korea remains focused on war-related efforts. The country&#8217;s authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-65271835" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a month ago that they tested the &#8220;most powerful&#8221; missile to date. Experts warned that the new weapon will be able to strike other nations, including the US, quicker and with a more devastating impact. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kim Jong Un, who supervised the test, said the experiment would make rivals &#8220;suffer from extreme fear and anxiety.&#8221; </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Leaving a Mark Last Year</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stealing cryptocurrencies via sophisticated hacks is a signature move adopted by North Korean cybercriminals. The blockchain data platform &#8211; Chainalisys &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/north-korean-hackers-stole-1-7b-worth-crypto-in-2022-chainalysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">estimated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that such wrongdoers drained $1.7 billion worth of digital assets via several attacks in 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Lazarus Group &#8211; a notorious hacking group supposedly tied to the local government &#8211; was responsible for some of the biggest exploits last year. For example, the FBI claimed the organization stood behind the massive $625 million </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-biggest-ever-crypto-hack-what-happened-in-the-ronin-bridge-attack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ronin Network attack</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The compliance platform MistTrack </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-suspected-as-culprits-for-100-million-harmony-bridge-hack/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">maintained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this year that the Lazarus Group stole $100 million from the cryptocurrency protocol Harmony. Prior to that, Elliptic Enterprise suggested the same.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-north-koreas-missile-programs-funded-via-stolen-crypto-white-house/" rel="nofollow">Half of North Korea&#8217;s Missile Programs Funded via Stolen Crypto: White House</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
