<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:47:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>BlackRock Files Bitcoin Spot ETF Application, Taps Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255540</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/blackrock_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/blackrock_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Could the world’s largest asset manager be the first firm to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The $10 trillion asset management giant BlackRock filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch a Bitcoin Spot ETF on Thursday – a product yet to see life within the United States. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">BlackRock plans to partner with Coinbase to provide custody for the Bitcoin backing the funds, as with its Bitcoin </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-taps-coinbase-for-institutional-crypto-trading-and-custody-services/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">trading service</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> announced last year. </span></p>
<h2>BlackRock’s ETF Bid</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/06/15/blackrock-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-coinbase-as-a-crypto-custodian.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by CNBC, the asset manager filed with the SEC to launch the iShares Bitcoin Trust, which would provide easy investor access to Bitcoin from a Wall Street Giant. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The Trust seeks to reflect generally the performance of the price of bitcoin,” reads the </span><a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1980994/000143774923017574/bit20230608_s1.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. “The assets of the Trust consist primarily of bitcoin held by the Bitcoin Custodian on behalf of the Trust.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing added that shares in the trust are meant to constitute a simple means of investing in Bitcoin rather than trading and holding it on a peer-to-peer basis. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other firms have spent years trying to launch a similar product, but have continuously been denied by the SEC. By contrast, the agency has approved multiple </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ill-timed-proshares-bitcoin-etf-plunges-over-70/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin Futures ETFs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, which are backed by Bitcoin futures contracts rather than real BTC. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The SEC prefers the futures product because the market for its underlying assets is surveilled by the Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME), which can help detect market manipulation. </span></p>
<h2>Can BlackRock Succeed?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale’s spot ETF proposal was rejected last year because it tried to form a surveillance-sharing agreement with the CME Bitcoin Futures market, which the SEC did not consider closely related enough to the spot Bitcoin market. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Grayscale has since sued the SEC, and judges overseeing the case have expressed </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judges-scrutinize-sec-during-oral-arguments-in-grayscale-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">skepticism</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> over the SEC’s argument. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Blackrock said it would determine the value of the Bitcoin in its trust each day with reference to the CF Benchmarks Index.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Index tracks the price of Bitcoin across Coinbase, Bitstamp, iBit, Kraken, Gemini, and LMAX Digital, and strives for “resistance to manipulation” while not including “any futures prices in its methodology.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" rel="nofollow">BlackRock Files Bitcoin Spot ETF Application, Taps Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Crypto Lender Suspends Withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-crypto-lender-suspends-withdrawals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 23:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255284</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/RedLightHalted-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/RedLightHalted-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Delio is suspending withdrawals on its platform following its exposure to Haru Invest, which previously halted its services. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Delio, a major South Korean cryptocurrency lending platform, has suspended withdrawals temporarily on its platform, claiming that the measure was taken in connection with another local crypto company, Haru Invest, which recently did the same.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto lender stated that the decision to suspend withdrawals was unavoidable.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Delio&#8217;s Exposure to Haru Invest</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a <a href="https://delio.io/m/notice/noticeDetail?id=376&amp;p=0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">notice</a> to customers, Delio announced that it will temporarily suspend withdrawals starting from June 14. According to the firm, the inevitable suspension happened following increased market volatility and investor confusion after Haru Invest stopped deposits and withdrawals.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Delio further said it had to take action to safeguard customer assets in its custody. While the company claimed the measure was unavoidable, it explained that withdrawals will remain suspended &#8220;until the above situation and its aftermath are resolved.&#8221; An excerpt from the announcement reads:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;Delio will do our best to protect the assets of our customers while quickly grasping the facts and aftermath related to this situation. We will continue to inform you through announcements regarding the facts to be identified later, protection of customers&#8217; assets, and measures for this.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Block Media <a href="https://www.blockmedia.co.kr/archives/324818" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> that Delio CEO Jung Sang-ho said the firm experienced an uptick in withdrawal requests after Haru Invest suspended services.</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">“Withdrawal requests are pouring in after the one-day incident, so we stopped withdrawing to calm the situation. There is a transactional relationship with Haru Invest, and the amount cannot be disclosed.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">South Korean crypto exchange giant Upbit reacted to Delio&#8217;s action by restricting digital asset withdrawals to the crypto lending platform as &#8220;part of investor protection measures.&#8221;</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Haru Invest Denies Rug Pull Rumors</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Crypto yield platform Haru Invest <a href="https://haruinvest.com/blog/important-update-june-13-2023/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">informed</a> investors that it would suspend deposits and withdrawals beginning from June 13 until further notice. According to the company, the decision came following internal investigations, which revealed that one of its consignment operators provided false information.</p>
<p dir="ltr">After Haru Invest&#8217;s initial announcement, rumors were making the rounds about the company experiencing a rug pull. The platform later <a href="https://twitter.com/haruinvest/status/1668542464825921540?t=AT4cgaB-9CYCBBk2H8vVIQ&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">debunked</a> the speculations, stating it is &#8220;fully committed to fact-finding and responding to the related tasks&#8221; while also working to ensure investor protection.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The company later provided <a href="https://haruinvest.com/blog/notice-to-investors-june-14-2023/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">another update</a> naming the consignment operator B&amp;S Holdings (formerly Aventus). While Haru Invest stated it is currently holding talks with B&amp;S Holdings over the matter, the crypto firm revealed that it already initiated a criminal complaint against the entity and was also planning to file a civil action.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-crypto-lender-suspends-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">South Korean Crypto Lender Suspends Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui Tanks 14% in 7 Days &#8211; Can it Get Worse? Meanwhile Wall Street Memes Presale Pumps Past $7M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sui-tanks-14-in-7-days-can-it-get-worse-meanwhile-wall-street-memes-presale-pumps-past-7m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:44:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255527</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-14.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-14.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC’s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase remains the overarching narrative of the crypto market. With extreme bearish forces at play, Sui prices are down over 14% over the past week and 44% in 30 days. Sui saw a huge rise of 2,000% when listing in May following its presale, but despite a major upcoming [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC’s lawsuit against Binance and Coinbase remains the overarching narrative of the crypto market. With extreme bearish forces at play, Sui prices are down over 14% over the past week and 44% in 30 days.</p>
<p>Sui saw a huge rise of 2,000% when listing in May following its presale, but despite a major upcoming network upgrade, the token is expected to continue to struggle throughout June.</p>
<p>On the other hand, two new crypto presale tokens &#8211; Wall Street Memes and Ecoterra &#8211; have emerged with bullish momentum in recent weeks as traders look to hedge against the bear market.</p>
<h2><strong>Sui Unable To Stave Off Crypto Bears, More Selling Pressure Expected In June</strong></h2>
<p>The Sui blockchain, which derives its name from the Japanese word for water, has gained strong traction for its flexible architecture and scalability. The proof-of-stake blockchain boasts faster transaction speeds and low costs. However, the SUI token is going through a tough stretch, with extreme bearishness driving down its price.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255530" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="902" height="454" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12.jpg 902w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12-768x387.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-12-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 902px) 100vw, 902px" /></a></p>
<p>Earlier in the week, Sui saw a strong surge as the network announced its latest SIP 6 proposal. The proposal enables liquid staking and allows developers to build features for the same. Liquid staking is one of the most attractive features of any token’s tokenomics.</p>
<p>However, the token finally buckled under the strong bearish pressure created by the SEC suing Binance and Coinbase. Despite the token not being explicitly named in the lawsuit, it plummeted 14% over the last week. The downward movement continues as the token corrected another 5% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>With SEC chair Gary Gensler stating multiple times that Bitcoin is the only token he is comfortable calling a commodity, a token like Sui will need to be on red alert. Crypto assets that are proven to be securities often have to deal with suffocating regulations which make them less attractive.</p>
<p>Sui may also face difficulties from the global economy. While the Federal Reserve announced that it will pause any further interest rate hike for now, it did mention that it can see two other hikes this year alone. Such a hawkish stance can result in extreme bearishness for the token.</p>
<p>The token’s analysis highlights that investors may have to face further bumps in June. TradingView gives a Strong Sell signal to Sui in the daily time frame, with the token underperforming with 7 out of 8 important moving average indicators.</p>
<h2>Could Wall Street Memes Be the Next Big Crypto Presale After Raising $7?</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes token</a> has emerged as one of the most attractive buys in the crypto market. With other meme tokens such as Dogecoin &amp; Shiba Inu struggling, investors are flocking to WSM.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-10.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255529" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-10.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="324" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-10.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-10-300x161.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-10-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>After being launched on the 26th of May this year, the token has raised over $7 million in less than three weeks. With the token adding $350k every day to its total, it won’t be long before it is hitting the $10 million milestone.</p>
<p>The token’s success is unsurprising considering the incredible track record of the Wall Street Memes group. It received global fame during the historic GameStop short squeeze in 2021 when a group of small internet traders took on the might of wealthy institutions and won.</p>
<p>The group has also built a strong following in the crypto space as well. It sold out its Wall St Bulls NFT collection in 32 minutes, making $2.5 million in profits. Inspired by the success, the group also launched its own Bitcoin Ordinal NFTs recently.</p>
<p>Investors are also getting drawn to the token’s community-driven tokenomics. The entire WSM supply is available for the community, with 50% available during the presale itself. Furthermore, 30% of the tokens are allocated for cool community rewards.</p>
<p>5 lucky degens will also win $10k worth of WSM tokens through an incredibly generous airdrop.</p>
<p>Investors can become a part of this revolutionary movement by <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">purchasing WSM tokens</a> through bank cards or by swapping ETH or USDT tokens. Numerous crypto traders have <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WIcVkD9W3Q0&amp;pp=ygURd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXM%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">speculated</a> that it could be the next big meme coin.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Meems Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2><strong>New Green Token Ecoterra Also Surging with Over $5m in Presale</strong></h2>
<p>With investors becoming increasingly environmentally conscious, there is an increasing demand for eco-friendly tokens. The newly launched <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra token</a> is dominating this demand as the token has raised over $5.1 million in a short span of a few weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255528" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-5.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-5-300x192.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-5-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The Recycle2Earn project incentivizes individuals and corporations to play their part against climate change. For example, corporations can earn an eco-friendly reputation by simply purchasing recycled products at a cheap cost from Ecoterra’s Recycled Products Marketplace. On the other hand, individuals receive an equitable amount of Ecoterra tokens for recycling waste products through Ecoterra’s Recycle2Earn application.</p>
<p>This supply and demand of recycled products create a sustainable circular economy. Ecoterra’s Carbon Offsets Marketplace enables individuals and companies to purchase verified carbon credits to reduce their emissions and carbon footprint.</p>
<p>Lawmakers all across the world are concerned over the energy consumption of tokens such as Bitcoin, with some lawmakers even calling for banning crypto altogether. Projects like Ecoterra can end up playing a crucial role in changing the mainstream perception of the industry.</p>
<p>ECOTERRA tokens are the default and discounted payment option for every platform service. While users can complete their payments using fiat currency, Bitcoin, or USDT as well, Ecoterra payments require smaller transaction fees.</p>
<p>Investors can <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">buy Ecoterra</a> through their bank cards or by swapping ETH or USDT tokens.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-tanks-14-in-7-days-can-it-get-worse-meanwhile-wall-street-memes-presale-pumps-past-7m/" rel="nofollow">Sui Tanks 14% in 7 Days &#8211; Can it Get Worse? Meanwhile Wall Street Memes Presale Pumps Past $7M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager to Enable Customer Withdrawals This Month</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-this-month/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 21:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255366</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Voyager_Loan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Voyager_Loan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Customers of the broker could start receiving their funds as soon as June 20. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a respite to Voyager Digital customers, the cryptocurrency brokerage is reportedly gearing up to reopen its app, which will enable the withdrawal of their funds. The development comes almost a year after it filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.</p>
<p>According to a court <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x193/11753/PLEADINGS/1175306142380000000027.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a> on June 14th, Voyager&#8217;s bankruptcy plan administrator, Paul Hage, stated that around June 15, the Voyager app would be updated to enable the viewing of the forms and amounts of their initial distribution. The estimated period of withdrawal will be between June 20 and July 5.</p>
<ol>
<li>As per the bankruptcy plan <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-approved-to-start-repaying-frozen-customers-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">approved</a> in court on May 17, Voyager customers will initially receive 35.72% of what they are owed.</li>
<li>Hage also pointed out the $445 million funds which the FTX&#8217;s failed trading arm, Alameda Research, tried to claw back from Voyager Digital.</li>
<li>This amount could be made available to creditors pending a final resolution of Alameda Research&#8217;s preference claim against the lender. However, a resolution is not likely to happen until at least mid-September 2023.</li>
<li>The bankruptcy plan administrator also noted that bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) still owes Voyager $650 million making the lender one of its biggest creditors.</li>
<li>The primary focus will shift to recovering additional assets that can be distributed to creditors through, among other things, litigation claims and asset sales as soon as the initial distribution is complete, Hage asserted in the court filing.</li>
<li>Since sliding into bankruptcy last July, Voyager witnessed two failed buyouts. First, Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s FTX, which itself collapsed, followed by Binance&#8217;s US affiliate, which <a href="https://www.google.com/amp/s/cryptopotato.com/binance-us-pulls-out-of-1-billion-asset-purchase-deal-with-voyager/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">pulled out</a> of the $1 billion deal as a result of increased regulatory scrutiny in the country.</li>
</ol>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-this-month/" rel="nofollow">Voyager to Enable Customer Withdrawals This Month</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miami Bitcoin-Loving Mayor Joins the US Presidential Race</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/miami-bitcoin-loving-mayor-joins-the-us-presidential-race/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 20:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miami]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255344</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Francis-Suarez.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Francis-Suarez.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Francis Suarez became the third person from Florida to run for a President of the USA as part of the Republican Party.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Francis Suarez &#8211; the mayor of Miami &#8211; filed documents to run for President of the United States. He will be a candidate of the Republican party, attempting to prevail over well-known names, such as Donald Trump and Ron DeSantis. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Suarez is an outspoken advocate of bitcoin, and his administration has introduced numerous initiatives focused on the asset. He also became the first US politician to receive his salary in BTC instead of fiat currency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Latest Candidate is a Bitcoin Fan</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">With the approach of the US Presidential elections in 2024, more and more individuals join the race to become the next political leader of the nation. A recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://docquery.fec.gov/cgi-bin/forms/P40013765/1707313" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> showed that the latest to do so is the 45-year-old Francis Suarez, who currently serves his second term as mayor of Miami. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Under his rule, Florida&#8217;s financial heart has undergone a somewhat digital revolution. For one, his cabinet digitized the process of obtaining a license to start a business, making the city much more attractive to entrepreneurs and investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Suarez is also a huge proponent of the cryptocurrency industry, specifically bitcoin. The politician, who invested some of his wealth in BTC and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-continues-to-receive-his-salary-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his salary in the primary digital asset, previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-open-to-explore-investing-1-of-citys-treasury-reserves-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the city could invest 1% of its treasure reserves in it.<br />
</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The mayor&#8217;s administration has also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miami-mayor-considering-salaries-taxes-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">contemplated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> accepting bitcoin as a payment method for taxes and public employee wages. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Suarez enjoys a solid level of support in Miami, winning nearly 80% of the votes at the latest mayoral elections. However, he joins the contest for a leader of the States as an underdog since he has to prevail over former President Donald Trump and the Governor of Florida &#8211; Ron DeSantis &#8211; to become the candidate of the Republican Party.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_255368" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255368" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Suarez.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-255368" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Suarez.webp" alt="Francis Suarez" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Suarez.webp 760w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Suarez-300x200.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Suarez-50x33.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255368" class="wp-caption-text">Francis Suarez, Source: NBC News</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Democrats Also Have a BTC Supporter</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similar to their rivals, the &#8220;Dems&#8221; also have a candidate who has shown his affection toward bitcoin, and his name is Robert F. Kennedy Jr (nephew of former President John F. Kennedy).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-proponent-robert-f-kennedy-announces-run-for-president-of-the-usa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">criticized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Federal Reserve for collaborating with several banks between 2008 and 2022 to print staggering amounts of US dollars, thus negatively affecting the financial system of the USA. Kennedy believes bitcoin could serve as a lifeboat amid the infused turbulence:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin give the public an escape route from the splatter zone when this bubble invariably bursts. So the White House is colluding with the banksters to keep us all trapped in the bubble of profiteering and control.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/miami-bitcoin-loving-mayor-joins-the-us-presidential-race/" rel="nofollow">Miami Bitcoin-Loving Mayor Joins the US Presidential Race</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Curve Founder Repays 1.3M USDT of Aave Loan to Reduce Liquidation Risk: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/curve-founder-repays-1-3m-usdt-of-aave-loan-to-reduce-liquidation-risk-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aave]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Curve Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255448</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Curve_Loan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Curve_Loan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Curve-Aave loan fiasco caused USDT to slip slightly from its 1:1 peg with the USD.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A wallet linked to Michael Egorov, the founder of decentralized exchange (DEX) and automated market maker protocol Curve, has reduced its on-chain debt by repaying 1.35 million USDT of a loan on the decentralized lending platform, Aave.</p>
<p>Egorov’s move comes as Curve’s native token (CRV), used as the loan’s collateral, significantly declined in the past week, reducing the loan’s health factor and increasing the liquidation risk.</p>
<h2>Egorov Returns 1.3M USDT to Aave</h2>
<p>Egorov started borrowing stablecoins on Aave in April. <a href="https://debank.com/profile/0x7a16ff8270133f063aab6c9977183d9e72835428" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Data</a> from blockchain analytics platform Debank shows that the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/1-billion-value-locked-curve-crv-founder-takes-71-of-voting-power/" data-wpel-link="internal">Curve founder</a> has deposited 288.7 million CRV tokens worth $173 million on Aave to borrow about 64 million USDT in an open position. The CRV tokens represent roughly 34% of the asset’s total supply.</p>
<p>Analysis from blockchain sleuth Lookonchain <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1668160807862157312?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that Egorov sent $37.7 million worth of USDT to crypto exchange Bitfinex, while $51 million in USDC was sent to market-making protocol Wintermute Trading.</p>
<p>Three days ago, the open position had a health rate of 1.68. However, at the time of writing, the health factor was at 1.58 due to the declining value of CRV, which has plummeted by more than 20% in the past seven days. Data from CoinMarketCap shows that the asset was trading at $0.60 as of press time.</p>
<p>The collateral will be automatically liquidated if the health rate drops below 1.00. Egorov was forced to return some USDT tokens to curb the liquidation risk.</p>
<h2>Community Reacts</h2>
<p>The high CRV stake involved in the loan has caught the attention of the decentralized finance (DeFi) community, as it may lead to major selling pressure on the asset, increasing the risk of platform liquidation.</p>
<p>Gauntlet, an entity that manages DeFi risk, has <a href="https://governance.aave.com/t/gauntlet-recommendation-to-freeze-crv-and-set-crv-ltv-0-on-aave-v2/13644" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">submitted</a> a proposal to the Aave community, suggesting that all CRV tokens used as collateral on the V2 platform be frozen, and the loan-to-value (LTV) ratio for CRV be set to 0. This is to prevent the account linked to Egorov from adding more CRV as collateral to increase concentration risk and minimize the possibility of accruing bad debt.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the Curve-Aave loan fiasco has caused USDT to slip slightly from its 1:1 peg with the USD. While whales and investors are taking arbitrage opportunities to swap the assets for USDC and DAI, Tether CTO Paul Ardoino has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-cto-paolo-ardoino-alleviates-usdt-de-peg-scares/" data-wpel-link="internal">assured</a> the community that the company is ready for any amount of redemptions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-founder-repays-1-3m-usdt-of-aave-loan-to-reduce-liquidation-risk-data/" rel="nofollow">Curve Founder Repays 1.3M USDT of Aave Loan to Reduce Liquidation Risk: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazil&#8217;s President Empowers the Central Bank as Crypto Regulator</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/brazils-president-empowers-the-central-bank-as-crypto-regulator/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255386</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Brazil.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Brazil.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The bank will set standards in the local crypto sector and partner with the SEC on the regulation of digital assets classified as securities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The President of Brazil &#8211; Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, simply known as Lula &#8211; assigned the country&#8217;s central bank to supervise the local cryptocurrency sector. The legislation that comes into force on June 20 will give the financial institution jurisdiction to determine which firms can operate in the local market. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The bank will also cooperate with Brazil&#8217;s Securities and Exchange Commission (the Comissão de Valores Mobiliários, or CVM) to oversee coins deemed as securities. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brazil&#8217;s Central Bank to Establish Crypto Rules</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">President Lula recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.scribd.com/document/652920517/Decreto-N%C2%BA-11-563-De-13-de-Junho-de-2023-Decreto-N%C2%BA-11-563-De-13-de-Junho-de-2023-Dou-Imprensa-Nacional#" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">signed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an official decree that empowers Banco Central do Brasil to regulate the domestic cryptocurrency industry. As stated in the order, companies willing to offer digital asset services will have to obtain the bank&#8217;s permission. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The institution will also introduce a licensing system for crypto providers, where all participants must register. Monitoring if entities abide by anti-money laundering procedures and whether they are linked to any criminal activities, such as financing terrorism, will also be under the central bank&#8217;s scope. The upcoming changes will go into effect on June 20. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brazil&#8217;s SEC will play a role in the regulatory process, too. The agency and Banco Central do Brasil will supervise cryptocurrencies labeled as securities. However, current law does not clarify which digital assets fit into that category and which are considered commodities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Setting clear standards for dealing with digital assets could make the country more attractive to crypto enthusiasts. Brazilians have already shown their sympathy towards the sector. A survey conducted by Gemini last year </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazil-and-indonesia-global-leaders-in-crypto-adoption-gemini-survey/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">determined</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that over 40% of the locals own digital currencies.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Expansion Efforts of Binance and Coinbase in Brazil</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Two of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges &#8211; Binance and Coinbase, which have recently been targeted by the US SEC, have launched different crypto initiatives in the largest country by landmass in South America.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-taps-mastercard-to-introduce-crypto-prepaid-card-in-brazil-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">partnered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the multinational financial services giant – Mastercard &#8211; in January this year to introduce a prepaid card in the region. The move came as a result of the company&#8217;s ambitions to &#8220;broaden the connection between traditional finance and crypto.&#8221; The card is accepted in every shop that uses Mastercard&#8217;s payment services.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-expands-to-brazil-supporting-the-central-banks-payment-system-pix/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">teamed up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with Brazil&#8217;s settlement system Pix to offer additional cryptocurrency services. The partnership enables the purchase of digital assets using Brazilian reals and allows withdrawals and deposits in the country&#8217;s national currency.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazils-president-empowers-the-central-bank-as-crypto-regulator/" rel="nofollow">Brazil&#8217;s President Empowers the Central Bank as Crypto Regulator</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Crashes 6% Daily, is $1500 The Next Target? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-crashes-6-daily-is-1500-the-next-target-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255426</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price has experienced a decline in recent days after being unable to surpass the $2,000 level. However, it is currently testing an important support level, and its response to it is expected to have a significant impact on performance in the coming months. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has experienced a decline in recent days after being unable to surpass the $2,000 level. However, it is currently testing an important support level, and its response to it is expected to have a significant impact on performance in the coming months.</p>
<h2><strong>Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, Ethereum&#8217;s price has faced rejection from the 50-day moving average at approximately $1,850 and has subsequently declined below $1,800. The price is currently experiencing downward momentum, but it is finding support near the 200-day moving average around $1,600.</p>
<p>The 200-day moving average is a strong indicator of the overall trend, and if ETH falls below it, it would indicate a continuation of the bearish market sentiment, potentially leading to a drop toward the $1,300 level.</p>
<p>However, if the price bounces back from the mentioned moving average and successfully breaks above both the $1,800 level and the 50-day moving average, there is a high likelihood of Ethereum rallying towards the resistance level at $2,300 and potentially even higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255435" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255435" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-255435 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_Chart_1506231" width="2560" height="1440" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-2048x1152.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jun-15-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255435" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, Ethereum&#8217;s price has experienced a rapid decline in recent days after being rejected from the $1,900 level and the upper boundary of the large falling wedge pattern.</p>
<p>It is currently testing the lower trend line of the pattern, which is situated around the $1,600 support level. A breakdown below it would have severe consequences for the price.</p>
<p>However, the RSI indicator is suggesting that the market is oversold, which suggests the possibility of a potential pullback, consolidation, or even a bullish reversal from the current area. Yet, the outcome will depend on whether the price is able to hold at the current level or if it breaks down further.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255436" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255436" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-255436 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1506232" width="2560" height="1440" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-2048x1152.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ETHUSDT-4H-Jun-15-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255436" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2><strong>Sentiment Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: Edris</strong></p>
<p><strong>Ethereum Taker Buy Sell Ratio</strong></p>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has experienced a bearish trend after failing to surpass the $2,000 level. To gain insights into the reasons behind this behavior, analyzing the sentiment in the futures market can be informative.</p>
<p>The taker buy-sell ratio metric, depicted in the chart with a 100-day moving average applied, examines whether buyers or sellers are executing their perpetual futures orders more aggressively, meaning entering at the market price instead of setting limit orders.</p>
<p>It is apparent that when the price approached $2,000, the metric dropped below 1, indicating that short sellers started dominating the market and actively shorting Ethereum. This contributed to the downward pressure on the price. Although the ratio has shown a slight recovery recently, as long as it remains below 1, there is still potential for further downward price movement.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255437" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255437" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-255437 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_taker_buy_sell_ratio_chart_1506231" width="2560" height="1616" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-768x485.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-1536x970.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-2048x1293.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jun-15-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255437" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-crashes-6-daily-is-1500-the-next-target-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Crashes 6% Daily, is $1500 The Next Target? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analysis of This Week&#8217;s Worst Performers: LDO, ADA, APT, SOL, and MATIC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/analysis-of-this-weeks-worst-performers-ldo-ada-apt-sol-and-matic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aptos Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido DAO (LDO)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255340</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/worst_performers_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/worst_performers_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at the worst performing altcoins with a market cap of over $1 billion: Lido, Cardano, Aptos, Solana, and Polygon. Lido (LDO) &#124; -24.8% LDO is the worst performer on our list this week after falling by almost 25%. Buyers failed to sustain the uptrend and with the support [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at the worst performing altcoins with a market cap of over $1 billion: Lido, Cardano, Aptos, Solana, and Polygon.</p>
<h2>Lido (LDO) | -24.8%</h2>
<p>LDO is the worst performer on our list this week after falling by almost 25%. Buyers failed to sustain the uptrend and with the support at $2 lost, the price was quick to crash.</p>
<p>At the time of this post, the most significant support level is found at $1.4 and the resistance is at $1.8. Considering the market sentiment, the price is unlikely to change its current momentum which is bearish.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Lido appears to continue its correction that started in February. With lower lows and lower highs, the bears have the upper hand and they may not stop their assault until the price reaches the key support indicated above.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255361" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255361" style="width: 1825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255361" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13.png" alt="LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13" width="1825" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13.png 1825w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/LDOUSDT_2023-06-15_10-12-13-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1825px) 100vw, 1825px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255361" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA) | &#8211; 20.9%</h2>
<p>ADA disappointed across the board in June and, in this week alone, has lost 20% of its valuation. Those who were hoping that the support at 30 cents would hold were let down as the price suddenly dropped all the way to 22 cents on June 9th. Since then, the price has recovered somewhat.</p>
<p>At this time, sellers have full control of the price action, and they are aiming to take this cryptocurrency to the key support at 24 cents. The current resistance is at 28 cents.</p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking ahead</span></span>, this major correction appears to be picking up speed, and this is confusing most ADA holders. The expectation is that buyers will return once the price hits the key support, similar to June 9th, but there are no guarantees.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255360" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255360" style="width: 1825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255360" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02" width="1825" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02.png 1825w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ADAUSDT_2023-06-15_10-17-02-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1825px) 100vw, 1825px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255360" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Aptos (APT) | -20.4%</span></p>
<p>APT failed to stop its downtrend and fell by 20% this week. In the process, it has formed a large descending triangle which was confirmed with the drop on June 9th. This is both concerning and bearish.</p>
<p>Should the support at $5.5, which forms the base of this large triangle, not hold, then buyers of APT may find themselves in a difficult position, as such a scenario would open the way for the price to fall towards $3 again. The current resistance is $6.8.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, APT is giving no clear signs that it can stop this correction. More so, Bitcoin and Ethereum have also made lower lows which re-confirms the bearish bias of the market at this time.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255359" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255359" style="width: 1824px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255359" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18.png" alt="APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18" width="1824" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18.png 1824w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/APTUSDT_2023-06-15_10-20-18-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1824px) 100vw, 1824px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255359" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Solana (SOL) | -20.2%</span></p>
<p>Solana has a similar price action to Cardano and also fell by 20% this past week. Buyers are currently struggling to keep the price above $14, and with the sentiment remaining bearish, it is unlikely they will succeed at this time.</p>
<p>The sudden drop in the price has also formed a parabola as shown on the chart below. The key support is found at $12, which has a good chance to hold sellers if reached. The current resistance is at $15.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Solana is trying its best to stop the bleeding, but buyers remain uninterested.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255358" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255358" style="width: 1825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255358" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41" width="1825" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41.png 1825w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SOLUSDT_2023-06-15_10-22-41-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1825px) 100vw, 1825px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255358" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Polygon (MATIC) | -19.4%</h2>
<p>Polygon formed a large wedge, and unfortunately, the price fell below it. This is bearish, and MATIC did not hesitate to show it as it lost 19% of its valuation this week.</p>
<p>The current support is found at 58 cents, and bulls may return at that level since the drop on June 9th saw buyers return as soon as the price went under 60 cents. The current resistance is at 75 cents.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, MATIC may test the key support soon, which could stop this bearish momentum. It is critical for this cryptocurrency to hold at that level as. Otherwise, sellers could be encouraged to take the price under 50 cents in the future.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255357" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255357" style="width: 1824px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255357" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53.png" alt="MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53" width="1824" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53.png 1824w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MATICUSDT_2023-06-15_10-26-53-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1824px) 100vw, 1824px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255357" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/analysis-of-this-weeks-worst-performers-ldo-ada-apt-sol-and-matic/" rel="nofollow">Analysis of This Week&#8217;s Worst Performers: LDO, ADA, APT, SOL, and MATIC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>EthCC6 Returns, Ethereum Community Rallies for a Pivotal Discussion on Post-Shanghai, Pre-MiCa Landscape</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethcc6-returns-ethereum-community-rallies-for-a-pivotal-discussion-on-post-shanghai-pre-mica-landscape/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 15:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255470</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ECC6.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ECC6.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] Paris gathers Ethereum’s thought leaders following the recent successful execution of the Shanghai Upgrade and the upcoming danksharding upgrade in the fall that will boost Ethereum’s scalability. PARIS, France &#8211; July 2023 &#8211; EthCC (Ethereum Community Conference), the largest annual European Ethereum conference created for the community, by the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>Paris gathers Ethereum’s thought leaders following the recent successful execution of the Shanghai Upgrade and the upcoming danksharding upgrade in the fall that will boost Ethereum’s scalability.</p>
<p>PARIS, France &#8211; July 2023 &#8211; <a href="https://www.ethcc.io/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">EthCC (Ethereum Community Conference)</a>, the largest annual European Ethereum conference created for the community, by the community, will return for EthCC[6] from 17-20 July 2023 in Paris, France, and bring together the top minds in Ethereum to share their vision for the future of the ecosystem.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;EthCC has been a watercooler for new ideas that help push the envelope of Ethereum’s growth. Observing the kind of products and technologies that come out of the space six months after is a strong indicator of this. As major shifts like The Merge and the Shapella Update have taken place since the last edition, we have calibrated our approach and introduced new elements to the conference that will continue to highlight ideas and projects with great potential.</p>
<p>We’ve seen a record amount of ETH deposited after the enablement of staked ETH withdrawals in April. This demonstrates that challenging market conditions have a minimal bearing on efforts to build and grow the Ethereum ecosystem. This year, we hope EthCC[6] will continue to be strong nurturing ground for talent and productivity, fostering meaningful connections and the community&#8217;s growth&#8221;, said Jerome de Tychey, Founder and President of <a href="https://www.ethereum-france.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ethereum France</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>Crypto has proven its resilience through the bear market. Developments in blockchain technology, progress in crypto&#8217;s regulatory landscape, and zero knowledge advancements that strengthen Ethereum&#8217;s security, continue to attract mainstream interest and investment with deal activity picking up in Q1 2023, with 439 deals raised vs. 366 in Q4 2022.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The web3 ecosystem finds itself at a momentous juncture, where it has persevered through a challenging year, demonstrating remarkable resilience and continuous innovation. Despite the obstacles faced, the ecosystem players continue to build. Ethereum, a trailblazer in these advancements, has witnessed remarkable growth – a progression that EthCC has had the honour of witnessing first hand. As EthCC enters its sixth year, the anticipation grows for a new wave of attendees that transcends crypto-native audiences. EthCC extends a warm invitation to both returning and new enthusiasts, welcoming them to participate in this next transformative phase of growth”, said Bettina Boon Falleur, Head of EthCC.</p></blockquote>
<p>For the Ethereum community, 2023 continues to be a big year with the recent successful execution of the Shanghai Upgrade and the upcoming <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/expect-ethereum-next-big-upgrade-111500784.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">danksharding upgrade</a> in the fall that will boost Ethereum’s scalability. As the ecosystem moves through these milestones, builders are looking towards the next wave of blockchain technology that will move beyond DeFi and into new areas, including scalability, social good, AI, privacy, and governance.</p>
<p>ETHCC[6] will gather more than 350 speakers from all around the world with various talks, workshops, and side events with the goal of sharing and transmitting knowledge to develop a positive and abundant Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p>Headline speakers include Tim Beiko, Protocol Support at the Ethereum Foundation; Xin Wan, Researcher at Uniswap Labs, a protocol for trading and automated liquidity provision on Ethereum; Sid Shekhar, Blockchain Researcher at Coinbase, one of the world’s top crypto exchanges; and Patrick Hansen, Director of EU Strategy &amp; Policy at Circle, a global internet finance company built on blockchain technology and powered by crypto assets.</p>
<p>EthCC[6] will also provide the opportunity for vetted startups to pitch in front of top VCs such as, HashKey, BPI France, and Accel through the EthVC program.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethcc6-returns-ethereum-community-rallies-for-a-pivotal-discussion-on-post-shanghai-pre-mica-landscape/" rel="nofollow">EthCC6 Returns, Ethereum Community Rallies for a Pivotal Discussion on Post-Shanghai, Pre-MiCa Landscape</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
