<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 07:50:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CashApp’s Bitcoin Sales Up 25% Since Last Quarter</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cashapps-bitcoin-sales-up-25-since-last-quarter/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:53:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249512</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/jackdorsey_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/jackdorsey_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although revenue from Bitcoin only accounts for a small part of CashApp’s success last quarter, the increase in such transactions is noteworthy.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Quarterly earnings reports are starting to pour in across the financial sector, and with them, updates on the state of crypto adoption across the industry.</p>
<p>Although some companies are, understandably, still feeling the chill of crypto winter, even those are doing <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal">better than expected</a> by analysts. In the case of firms with other priorities who have nonetheless adopted crypto in some measure, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-sees-first-quarterly-profit-in-2-years-due-to-bitcoin-bet/" data-wpel-link="internal">MicroStrategy</a>, the asset class has, so far, proven to be a part of their success.</p>
<h2>Beating Expectations and Short-Seller Predictions</h2>
<p>Block – better known by its former name Square, which is still used for its business platform – has reported a slight increase in revenues and earnings per share, in spite of doubts fueled in part by a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hindenburg-drops-astonishing-details-on-jack-dorseys-block-payment-firm-fires-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> published by short-sellers at Hindenburg Research. The firm is now reportedly considering legal actions against the company.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We intend to work with the SEC and explore legal action against Hindenburg Research for the factually inaccurate and misleading report they shared about our Cash App business today. We will not be distracted by typical short-seller tactics.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Although its quarterly results turned out just fine, Block’s stock took a nosedive shortly after the report was published. Fortunately for its investors, the firm has reported that its earnings per share are now 40 cents, as opposed to analysts’ predictions of 35 cents. At the time this article was written, the company stocks were worth just under $60, <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/sq" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to MarketWatch.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Role in Block’s Recovery</h2>
<p>Jack Dorsey, the co-founder and former CEO of Twitter who is currently Block’s CEO, has long been a Bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-and-jay-z-launch-bitcoin-education-course-in-brooklyn-new-york/" data-wpel-link="internal">believer</a>. This quarter, the cryptocurrency played an important <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/05/04/cash-app-quarterly-bitcoin-sales-near-2-2-billion-up-25-percent-year-over-year/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">part</a> in his company’s financial bottom line, with results that could indicate even greater success in the future.</p>
<p><a href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q1/Shareholder-Letter_Block_1Q23.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Block, Bitcoin sales on CashApp – one of Block’s most hyped products – benefited from a 25% increase since last year. This is in stark contrast to the prior quarterly report, in which Bitcoin sales decreased by 7% YoY.</p>
<p>Although revenue resulting from BTC sales only amounted to a total of $50 million out of the firms’ total gross profit of $1.71 billion, the results nevertheless prove that Bitcoin adoption rates are still increasing for the general public.</p>
<p>As institutional investors continue to accumulate BTC using more traditional financial products, it’s important to keep easy ways to access crypto open to the public – and doing so can result in profit, as Block’s financials show.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cashapps-bitcoin-sales-up-25-since-last-quarter/" rel="nofollow">CashApp’s Bitcoin Sales Up 25% Since Last Quarter</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba Cloud Builds Launchpad to Deploy Metaverse on Avalanche</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alibaba-cloud-builds-launchpad-to-deploy-metaverse-on-avalanche/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249268</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Alibaba.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Alibaba.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cloudverse is avaliable to millions of Alibaba Cloud clients and billions of users worldwide. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alibaba Cloud &#8211; a subset of Chinese e-commerce behemoth Alibaba &#8211; along with Avalanche has built a launchpad for businesses to deploy metaverses on the layer 1 blockchain.</p>
<p>Dubbed &#8220;Cloudverse,&#8221; the platform is designed to serve as a one-stop, end-to-end solution for businesses to easily customize, launch, and maintain their own metaverse space, thereby creating new dimensions for engaging customers.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Cloud&#8217;s Metaverse Launchpad</h2>
<p>According to the official blog post, all of the blockchain elements in the new offering, such as digital land, wearables, and other digital assets, are built on Avalanche.</p>
<p>Alibaba Cloud is tasked with providing scalable, highly efficient, and secure cloud infrastructure offerings, including computing, storage, database and networking, and intelligence operation platforms. On the other hand, Avalanche, along with a third partner called MUA DAO, will focus on providing solutions for building metaverse spaces.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.avax.network/blog/alibaba-cloud-and-its-partners-unlock-rapid-metaverse-deployment-on-avalanche-for-millions-of-cloud-clients" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, Raymond Xiao, Head of International Web3 Solutions, Alibaba Cloud Intelligence, spoke about the strong demand from businesses in the Asia-Pacific region planning to foray into the Web3 space as a result of the rising popularity of blockchain technology and the metaverse. Xiao further added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Through the launch of the metaverse launchpad on Avalanche for CloudVerse, we are excited to offer businesses a way to kickstart their metaverse journeys and drive innovations and new possibilities for their businesses while elevating customer experiences.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The partnership between Alibaba Cloud and Avalanche dates back to December 2022, when the two entities announced an integration to power the former&#8217;s Node-as-a-Service initiatives. During the same time, the cloud computing division of the Chinese conglomerate began offering infrastructure and tools to help Asia-based users launch validators on the network.</p>
<h2>Alibaba Cloud&#8217;s Web3 Strategy</h2>
<p>As it strengthens its footprint in the Web3 space, Alibaba Cloud recently unveiled plans to accelerate the growth of a more inclusive and secure modern internet powered by blockchain technology. As such, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alibaba-cloud-partners-with-elastos-to-spur-adoption-of-open-source-tech/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with a layer one blockchain protocol &#8211; Elastos &#8211; last month in order to build and deploy next-generation solutions.</p>
<p>Besides, Alibaba Cloud also signed a memorandum of understanding with Sui blockchain developer Mysten Labs in January to develop sustainable Web3 ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alibaba-cloud-builds-launchpad-to-deploy-metaverse-on-avalanche/" rel="nofollow">Alibaba Cloud Builds Launchpad to Deploy Metaverse on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BC Securities Regulator Accuses Defunct Crypto Platform of Committing Multimillion-Dollar Fraud</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bc-securities-regulator-accuses-defunct-crypto-platform-of-committing-multimillion-dollar-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249128</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A division of the Canadian police force investigated ezBtc in 2019 but did not find enough evidence to file criminal charges. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The British Columbia Securities Commission has accused ezBtc, a defunct Nanaimo-based cryptocurrency platform, and its founder David Smillie, of perpetrating a multimillion-dollar securities fraud scheme.</p>
<p>The commission alleged that Smillie and his crypto firm lied to customers about the platform and diverted their assets to online gambling sites.</p>
<h2>ezBtc Allegedly Diverted $13M in Customer Assets</h2>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/securities-commission-alleges-fraud-committed-by-b-c-crypto-firm-1.1915370" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, the accusations were outlined in a notice of hearing issued last month. The B.C. Securities Commission accused Smillie and ezBtc of moving $13 million worth of users&#8217; assets, including bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH), to virtual gambling sites without authorization from the owners.</p>
<p>While ezBtc ceased operations in October 2022, users moved 2,300 BTC and 600 ETH tokens into the platform&#8217;s wallets between 2016 and 2019. The company&#8217;s founder allegedly told investors their assets were often kept offline in cold storage. However, the firm never had enough assets to cover users&#8217; funds.</p>
<p>In addition, ezBtc was never registered with the B.C. commission, and the agency claims that the company&#8217;s agreements with users fell under futures contracts, which are within its jurisdiction.</p>
<h2>ezBtc&#8217;s Founder to Pay Fines</h2>
<p>Upon further investigation, the B.C. commission found that ezBtc and Smillie faced numerous lawsuits several years ago. Constable Gary O&#8217;Brien of the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP), which facilitated the suits before, said the force&#8217;s investigation into ezBtc in 2019 did not yield enough evidence to file criminal charges.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;All I can say is that the matter was investigated, and there was insufficient evidence gathered by the primary investigator to pursue criminal matters, so they decided it would probably be best to go from a civil angle. That&#8217;s the only information that I could provide at this point,&#8221; the constable said.</p></blockquote>
<p>On the other hand, the securities commission director of enforcement Doug Muir disclosed that there had been a lengthy probe into the ezBtc, hence the hearing notice.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In this case, like in all of our cases, we need time to investigate, so we need to be able to gather evidence that we are satisfied. So, that takes time to gather. Our investigations are often time consuming and complex and this one is an example of that,&#8221; Muir said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The regulator further revealed that the case is not criminal but administrative, adding that the involved parties may face monetary penalties or prohibitions from public markets instead of serving jail terms.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bc-securities-regulator-accuses-defunct-crypto-platform-of-committing-multimillion-dollar-fraud/" rel="nofollow">BC Securities Regulator Accuses Defunct Crypto Platform of Committing Multimillion-Dollar Fraud</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Increased its BTC Holdings for 11 Consecutive Quarters</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-increased-its-btc-holdings-for-11-consecutive-quarters/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 16:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249070</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has purchased bitcoin each quarter ever since embracing the BTC strategy.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MicroStrategy &#8211; the business intelligence company co-founded by Michael Saylor &#8211; has purchased bitcoin each quarter since August 2020.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company is the largest corporate holder of the primary cryptocurrency, owning 140,000 BTC. It accumulated its stash at an average price of $29,803, meaning it currently sits on a minor unrealized loss.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Adding More BTC During Every Quarter</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the volatile nature of bitcoin and the 2022 bear market that disrupted the cryptocurrency industry, MicroStrategy seems determined to only keep strengthening its BTC position.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20200811005331/en/MicroStrategy-Adopts-Bitcoin-as-Primary-Treasury-Reserve-Asset" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">jumped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on the bandwagon in August 2020 by purchasing over 21,000 BTC and embracing a strategy focused on the leading digital asset. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our investment in bitcoin is part of our new capital allocation strategy, which seeks to maximize long-term value for our shareholders.</span></p>
<p>This investment reflects our belief that Bitcoin, as the world&#8217;s most widely-adopted cryptocurrency, is a dependable store of value and an attractive investment asset with more long-term appreciation potential than holding cash,&#8221; MicroStrategy&#8217;s Executive Chairman &#8211; Michael Saylor &#8211; said at the time.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company stayed loyal to Saylor&#8217;s words and continued increasing its possessions in the following years. In fact, it purchased certain amounts of BTC during each quarter up until now. The firm&#8217;s most substantial purchases came at the start of its strategy when it accumulated over 38,000 BTC in Q3 2020 and then took that amount to more than 70,000 BTC by the end of the year. </span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249115" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249115" style="width: 748px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249115" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1.png" alt="MicroStrategy's BTC Purchases" width="748" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1.png 950w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1-300x160.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1-768x411.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/MicroStrategy1-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 748px) 100vw, 748px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249115" class="wp-caption-text">MicroStrategy&#8217;s BTC Purchases, Source: DropsTab</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization kept its pace throughout the entire 2021, spending notable sums each quarter. Due to bitcoin&#8217;s price records in that year, the firm&#8217;s investment turned highly successful, and at one point in November 2021, it was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-bought-another-7k-bitcoin-worth-415-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sitting</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on nearly $3.5 billion in unrealized profits. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While the crypto winter in 2022 halted the bitcoin forays of multiple entities, this was not the case with MicroStrategy. It bought over 8,200 BTC throughout last year, increasing its holdings even during the second quarter (which saw the LUNA/UST crash) and Q4 (when the collapse of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> took place). Due to bitcoin&#8217;s declined price, MicroStrategy was sitting on a whopping $1.8 billion of unrealized loss by the end of 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trends changed with the start of 2023 as the crypto market showed some signs of recovery. Last month, the company&#8217;s BTC bet </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategys-bitcoin-investment-in-the-green-as-btc-reclaims-30k/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">went</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in the green for the first time since June 2022 after the leading digital asset soared above $30K. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MicroStrategy acquired additional 7,500 BTC since the beginning of the year, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-took-its-bitcoin-holdings-to-140k-with-another-purchase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">rounding up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the total holdings to 140,000 BTC. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Positive Start of the Year</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The increase of bitcoin&#8217;s value over the past several months has financially benefited MicroStrategy, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-sees-first-quarterly-profit-in-2-years-due-to-bitcoin-bet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it to turn a profit during Q1. It registered a net income of $461 million, whereas the software business revenue exceeded the estimations. The development is partly due to tax benefits resulting from the firm&#8217;s BTC holdings. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company also used bitcoin&#8217;s price surge to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-repaid-205m-loan-to-silvargate-and-bought-6500-more-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">repay </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">its $205 million loan to the failed Silvergate Bank at a 22% discount.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">MicroStrategy, which is a publicly-listed firm &#8211; saw its shares rise during the first months of the year. MSTR stocks were worth approximately $145 on January 1, while currently, they hover around $318 (a 120% surge).</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-increased-its-btc-holdings-for-11-consecutive-quarters/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Increased its BTC Holdings for 11 Consecutive Quarters</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum (ETH) Could be Hit by New Wave of Volatity: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-eth-could-be-hit-by-new-wave-of-volatity-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 13:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249397</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ethereum_mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ethereum_mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ETH deposits on exchanges hitting a new high could be a harbinger of future volatility .]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum network&#8217;s active deposits have reached an eight-month high. This metric depicts the total number of all incoming and outcoming transactions involving deposit addresses and accounts for both user-to-exchange transactions &#8211; from a personal wallet to a deposit address, as well as from a deposit address to the main exchange wallet.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1654355262638288897" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> compiled by crypto-analytic Santiment, the deposits hitting an eight-month high could potentially foreshadow volatility in Ethereum&#8217;s price.</li>
<li>In such a case, the enhanced price movements are likely to have a similar effect on the asset to that of the blockchain&#8217;s highly anticipated transition from PoW to PoS during Merge, as well as the FTX&#8217;s collapse.</li>
<li>The volatility forecast comes as Ether&#8217;s price remained trapped in a tight range amid low trading volume, unfazed by the Fed&#8217;s widely expected 25 basis point interest rate hike.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-ethereum-shanghai-shapella-upgrade-everything-you-need-to-know/" data-wpel-link="internal">Shapella upgr</a><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-the-ethereum-shanghai-shapella-upgrade-everything-you-need-to-know/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ade</a> also failed to charm the bulls, as the asset is up by a mere 3% since the event on April 12th.</li>
<li>While it is unclear as to the direction Ether&#8217;s price will be swayed in the near term, data suggest increased selling pressure on the asset.</li>
<li>ETH suppression in the price comes as whales holding 1,000 to 10,000 ETH <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1653302180105842688?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">offloaded</a> a massive amount of tokens over the past two weeks.</li>
<li>Moreover, ETH also saw the <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1653149761300733953" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">transfer</a> of $505 million to crypto exchange Binance on May 2nd. This level of exchange inflow was last seen before the Merge. Investors depositing their ETH tokens on exchange is typically a bearish indication.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-eth-could-be-hit-by-new-wave-of-volatity-data/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum (ETH) Could be Hit by New Wave of Volatity: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Voyager Digital to Liquidate its Assets After 2 Failed Purchase Agreements</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-digital-to-liquidate-its-assets-after-2-failed-purchase-agreements/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 10:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249491</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/voyager_defaultnotice_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/voyager_defaultnotice_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance.US's long-running effort to acquire the bankrupt crypto lender's assets came to an end nearly ten days ago.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Voyager Digital is planning to self-liquidate its assets and shut down operations after failing to secure purchase deals with Binance as well as FTX.US.</p>
<p>The planned FTX-Voyager acquisition failed as a result of the exchange sliding into an abrupt bankruptcy and the subsequent arrest of its chief, Sam Bankman-Fried. However, the collapse of the deal with the American arm of crypto giant Binance was seen as a major blow to the digital asset industry&#8217;s efforts to establish itself in the US amid a massive crackdown by the regulators.</p>
<h2>Voyager Liquidation</h2>
<p>According to a court <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysb.312840/gov.uscourts.nysb.312840.1374.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> on May 4th, the estimated initial recovery of Voyager’s customers was found to be 35.72%. It also revealed that 38 &#8220;unsupported&#8221; tokens &#8211; such as Tron (TRX), Solana (SOL), Algorand (ALGO), Celo (CELO), and Avalanche (AVAX) &#8211; cannot be withdrawn and hence will be liquidated and returned to customers.</p>
<p>On the other hand, those with any of the 67 &#8220;supported&#8221; assets, such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), will be able to withdraw the allowable percent of their holdings directly. The initial distributions are expected to begin within the next few weeks.</p>
<p>The deadline for any objection to the liquidation process is May 15th at 4 PM EST, and the responses should be submitted to the US Bankruptcy Court of the Southern District of New York.</p>
<h2>Purchase Deal Failures</h2>
<p>Voyager filed for bankruptcy protection in July 2022 after crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) defaulted on a significant loan position extended by the platform. The company has since been working out how to return assets to investors who used its services.</p>
<p>FTX won the bid to buy its assets in October 2022, a month before its own eventual collapse. Voyager then received an offer from Binance.US, which it described as &#8220;the highest and best bid for its assets after a review of strategic options with the core objective of maximizing the value returned to customers and other creditors on an expedited timeframe.&#8221;</p>
<p>Binance.US spent months seeking to convince regulators to approve the acquisition but hit several roadblocks, including opposition from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) as well as the Committee on Foreign Investment in the country.</p>
<p>The $1 billion deal came to an end last month after the exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-pulls-out-of-1-billion-asset-purchase-deal-with-voyager/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">issued</a> a letter of termination highlighting the hostile regulatory climate. Voyager called the development &#8220;disappointing.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-digital-to-liquidate-its-assets-after-2-failed-purchase-agreements/" rel="nofollow">Voyager Digital to Liquidate its Assets After 2 Failed Purchase Agreements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Slides to $29K, PEPE to End The Week With 350% Gains (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-slides-to-29k-pepe-to-end-the-week-with-350-gains-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 07:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249519</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE's triple-digit weekly surge has found it a place within the top 50 largest cryptocurrencies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin failed to conquer the $30,000 level yesterday, and the subsequent rejection drove it south by over $1,500.</p>
<p>The altcoins are Laos slightly in the red on a daily scale, with ETH struggling to remain above $1,900 and SHIB dumping by over 4%.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Back at $29K</h2>
<p>After the unfavorable start of the week, which saw BTC slumping to under $27,800, the asset began its recovery almost immediately and spiked to $29,000 by Thursday. This came even after the US Fed&#8217;s latest interest rate <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-reclaims-29k-after-feds-latest-interest-rate-hike-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">hike</a> of 25 bps.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency went on a roll on Saturday morning, which drove it to $29,900. As the bulls were preparing to take down the coveted $30,000 line, the bears stepped up and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-floki-skyrocket-by-double-digits-bitcoin-stopped-ahead-of-30k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">pushed</a> BTC south hard.</p>
<p>As a result, bitcoin dropped by over $1,500 in hours and fell to a daily low of $28,400 (on Bitstamp). It has been able to recover some ground since then and currently stands at around $29,000.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, BTC is still 1.5% down on the day. Its market capitalization has slid to $560 billion, but its dominance over the altcoins has increased slightly to 47.2% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249520" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249520" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249520" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-5-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249520" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>It&#8217;s PEPE&#8217;s Show</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s safe to say that the past few weeks belong to the new craze in the crypto and memecoin space &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a>. It went on a tear shortly after its launch in mid-April. The past week alone saw a massive surge of 350%, which made it the 45th largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization as of now. The latest massive <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepes-market-cap-soars-above-1-billion-following-another-60-daily-surge/" data-wpel-link="internal">pump</a> came after it was listed on Binance alongside Floki Inu.</p>
<p>Most of the larger-cap alts are in a less favorable position, though. ETH is down by over 2.5% in the past 24 hours and is close to breaking below $1,900 once more. Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, MATIC, Solana, Polkadot, Tron, and Litecoin are also well in the red.</p>
<p>Shiba Inu has declined the most from the larger-cap alts, being down by 4.5%.</p>
<p>The total market cap has seen roughly $25 billion gone in the day, and the metric has dipped below $1.2 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249521" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249521" style="width: 1880px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249521" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1880" height="851" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4.jpg 1880w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-1024x464.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-768x348.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-1536x695.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-4-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1880px) 100vw, 1880px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249521" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-slides-to-29k-pepe-to-end-the-week-with-350-gains-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Slides to $29K, PEPE to End The Week With 350% Gains (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americans Lead the Memecoin Craze in 2023 (Study)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/americans-lead-the-memecoin-craze-in-2023-study/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 22:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[US residents generated more than 23% of the global interest in memecoins, with SHIB being their favorite one.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to CoinGecko research, the residents of the United States seem the most interested in memecoins such as Dogecoin (DOGE), Shiba Inu (SHIB), Floki Inu (FLOKI), and Pepe Coin (PEPE). India and the United Kingdom rank respectively second and third. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite being the first memecoin, DOGE has lost its leading position in numerous countries. Morocco is the only nation in the top 10 where Elon Musk&#8217;s favorite digital asset captured the most interest. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Trends This Year</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CoinGecko&#8217;s study </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/top-meme-coin-countries?utm_campaign=Data%2BVisualization&amp;utm_medium=social" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">estimated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that over 23% of the global interest towards memecoins comes from the USA. The most popular such asset for locals is Shiba Inu (60.7%), followed by Pepe Coin (11.8%), Bonk, and Volt Inu.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Indians are close to the top, accounting for 20.3% of the overall craze. Shiba Inu is once again the token that generates the most interest, whereas Baby Doge Coin comes in second place. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United Kingdom &#8211; the only representative from Europe on the top 10 list &#8211; ranks third, making up about 16% of the global interest in memecoins. However, CoinGecko did not outline which assets are most desirable for Britons.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Floki Inu (FLOKI), which has been up by over 300% YTD, is another coin that people find intriguing. In fact, it is the most interesting one in the Philippines and Nigeria. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a> &#8211; the recent sensation in the crypto sector &#8211; reaches the top in Canada, accounting for nearly 27% of the local interest. It saw the light of day in the middle of April and its market capitalization neared $1 trillion this week.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dogecoin &#8211; the cryptocurrency created as a joke in 2013 &#8211; seems to have lost steam this year. It receives 61.1% of the interest in Morocco, making the African nation the only one where Musk&#8217;s favorite token climbs up the leaderboard.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DOGE Rises Despite the Diminishing Interest</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While investors appear to have new favorite memecoins, DOGE remains a fundamental member of the pack. Its price has gone up by 11% YTD, and it still has a place among the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies by market cap.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Elon Musk has been a frequent player on the DOGE scene. The South African entrepreneur, who acquired Twitter for $44 billion last year, temporarily </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-explodes-25-after-elon-musk-changes-twitter-icon-to-doge-meme/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">changed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the logo of the social media platform into a picture of the infamous &#8220;Doge&#8221; meme last month. The digital asset soared 25% in the following hours. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It won&#8217;t be considered a surprise if Dogecoin surges in the future, considering Musk&#8217;s plans to eventually </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-teases-dogecoin-integration-for-twitter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">integrate</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> DOGE payments on Twitter.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/americans-lead-the-memecoin-craze-in-2023-study/" rel="nofollow">Americans Lead the Memecoin Craze in 2023 (Study)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polkadot&#8217;s KILT Identity Blockchain Integrates With Deloitte</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/polkadots-kilt-identity-blockchain-integrates-with-deloitte/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 19:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249264</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Polkadot_Deloitte.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Polkadot_Deloitte.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One of the world's biggest accounting firms is integrating into the Polkadot ecosystem.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Polkadot announced that Deloitte Switzerland is integrating the former&#8217;s parachain KILT blockchain technology for issuing reusable digital credentials to support KYC and KYB processes.</p>
<p>With this move, Deloitte has become the latest major enterprise partner to come to the Polkadot ecosystem. The digital credentials in question will have extensive use cases such as regulatory compliance for banking and decentralized finance (DeFi), age verification for e-commerce, private logins, and fundraising.</p>
<h2>Deloitte-KILT Integration</h2>
<p>The official <a href="https://medium.com/kilt-protocol/deloitte-integrates-kilt-identity-blockchain-7ea12c0e0806" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a> explained that reusable KYB and KYC credentials, generated on KILT’s identity infrastructure, address the challenges associated with offering control and flexibility to the customer. As such, clients remain in control since credentials are stored in the wallet on their own devices, thereby granting them the power to choose with whom they share their credentials and which data points of the credential they make available.</p>
<p>As part of the integration, Deloitte will provide a wallet to the customer for the purpose of managing and sharing their credential. This new feature will be in the form of a browser extension, setting up, which would not require any prior knowledge of blockchain.</p>
<p>Following the development, Micha Bitterli, Head of Deloitte Managed Services, stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By offering reusable digital credentials anchored on the KILT blockchain, Deloitte is transforming verification processes for individuals and entities. Deloitte has the technology knowledge, reach and trust to issue credentials that are globally accepted.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The exec further highlighted the convenience, cost-effectiveness, and security aspects of using digital credentials and its potential to set the stage for new digital marketplaces, from e-commerce and DeFi to gaming.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Deloitte will be tasked with digitally signing the credentials, and the accounting firm can revoke them using blockchain technology if the conditions of the customer have altered after the credential was issued.</p>
<h2>Polkadot&#8217;s KILT</h2>
<p>Polkadot KILT&#8217;s tech is a blockchain-based decentralized identity solution that seeks to eliminate existing inefficiencies around KYC/KYB processes that can put consumer data privacy at risk. The latest integration follows yet another <a href="https://medium.com/kilt-protocol/axel-springer-and-kilt-introduce-service-for-login-based-on-web3-technology-db41c2c0ad66" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">collaboration</a> with Axel Springer, which happens to be one of Europe’s largest digital publishers, to introduce a service for login based on Web3 tech.</p>
<p>Last year, it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kilt-launches-new-application-for-digital-identities/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the launch of an application called &#8211; web3name &#8211; for creating a custom name to represent users&#8217; digital identity. The goal was to ramp up the transparency of users&#8217; identities without sacrificing the privacy involved with personal data.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polkadots-kilt-identity-blockchain-integrates-with-deloitte/" rel="nofollow">Polkadot&#8217;s KILT Identity Blockchain Integrates With Deloitte</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase is 100% Committed to the US Despite Regulatory Uncertainty: Brian Armstrong</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-100-committed-to-the-us-despite-regulatory-uncertainty-brian-armstrong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 16:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249360</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinbase_America.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinbase_America.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Armstrong said Coinbase would continue its global expansion plans as the US works towards creating a new and clear rule book for crypto.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brian Armstrong, the co-founder and chief executive officer of major American cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, revealed that the company is still 100% committed to the US market, despite the lack of regulatory clarity in the country.</p>
<p>The CEO’s disclosure came as a response to a question from shareholders, who were curious about Coinbase’s plans to move operations out of the US and the implications of such for customers, during an <a href="https://s27.q4cdn.com/397450999/files/doc_downloads/2023/Coinbase-Q123-Earnings-Call-Transcript.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">earnings call</a> for Q1 2023 on Thursday.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Will Not Leave the US</h2>
<p>Armstrong said he founded Coinbase in the US because he observed the prevalence of the rule of law in the country. He expressed his optimism about America eventually getting it right, as he had already noticed strong bipartisan support for Congress to create <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launches-nationwide-pro-crypto-policy-campaign/" data-wpel-link="internal">clear legislation</a> for cryptocurrencies during his visits to Washington, DC.</p>
<blockquote><p>“So let me be clear, we’re 100% committed to the US. I founded this company in the United States because I saw that rule of law prevails here. That’s really important. And I’m actually really optimistic on the US getting this right,” the CEO said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Coinbase boss insisted that it was important for America to fix the regulatory issue because other countries, including financial hubs, were vying to take the top position in the crypto space. While supranational organizations like the European Union have passed comprehensive crypto regulation, regions like the United Kingdom, Hong Kong, and Singapore have become more optimistic than the US.</p>
<p>Armstrong believes the EU’s Markets in Cryptoassets (<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eu-lawmakers-give-final-approval-to-the-mica-crypto-legislation/" data-wpel-link="internal">MiCA</a>) regulation has placed the union and its member states in the lead.</p>
<h2>Coinbase to Go Global</h2>
<p>The Coinbase CEO further explained that as the US works towards getting its crypto regulation right, his company will continue its mandate of serving as many people as possible by exploring the global market. In line with its plans, the firm recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> Coinbase International Exchange, a Bermuda-based crypto derivatives platform for non-US institutional clients.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Obviously, we have to make choices about where we’re going to allocate our capital every year. And so we do look at where we could think that can have the greatest ROI. But yes, the leading financial centers, they’re all working to create responsible crypto rules and clarity right now and the US is going to follow suit, I believe,” Armstrong added.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-100-committed-to-the-us-despite-regulatory-uncertainty-brian-armstrong/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase is 100% Committed to the US Despite Regulatory Uncertainty: Brian Armstrong</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
