<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 26 May – AGIX, AXS, AI, ECOTERRA, OKB, YPRED, HT</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm</link><description>As May comes to an end, Bitcoin and Ether are struggling to gain momentum and are at risk of closing out the month lower. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin has plateaued this week and may post its first monthly loss of 2023. Ether has ticked slightly higher but could also end May down from its open. &lt;br /&gt;
Given the recent slow movements in the cryptocurrency market, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 26 May – AGIX, AXS, AI, ECOTERRA, OKB, YPRED, HT&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AGIX</category><category>AXS</category><category>AI</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>OKB</category><category>YPRED</category><category>HT</category><category>SingularityNET</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>Axie Shards</category><category>Huobi Token</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-26-may-agix-axs-ai-ecoterra-okb-ypred-ht.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115096/277650/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>US Sen. Lummis Says President Biden Is Picking ‘Winners and Losers’ With Proposed Crypto Mining Tax</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm</link><description>The Biden administration is picking “winners and losers” in a proposal to tax cryptocurrency miners, US Sen. Cynthia Lummis said in a tweet on Thursday.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Wyoming Republican called Biden’s proposed 30 percent tax a “blatant attempt by the administration to pick winners and losers.” &lt;br /&gt;
“I will not let President Biden tax the digital asset industry out of existence,” Lummis said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm"&gt;Read More: US Sen. Lummis Says President Biden Is Picking ‘Winners and Losers’ With Proposed Crypto Mining Tax&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-sen-lummis-says-president-biden-picking-winners-losers-with-proposed-crypto-mining-tax.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115090/277640/cl-official-portrait-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="720776"/></item><item><title>Nike's Swoosh Web3 Platform Surpasses $1 Million in Sales</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nikes-swoosh-web3-platform-surpasses-1-million-sales.htm</link><description>.SWOOSH, a web3 platform developed by the popular sports brand Nike, has already generated more than $1 million in sales from its first sneaker-themed non-fungible token (NFT) collection. &lt;br /&gt;
The strong sales number indicates that despite some early technical issues and delays, the demand for well-designed shoes in the metaverse is healthy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nikes-swoosh-web3-platform-surpasses-1-million-sales.htm"&gt;Read More: Nike's Swoosh Web3 Platform Surpasses $1 Million in Sales&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Nike</category><category>NFT</category><category>Web3</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nikes-swoosh-web3-platform-surpasses-1-million-sales.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115045/277487/nike-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="14607"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Gemini Selects Ireland for Its European Headquarters</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-selects-ireland-for-its-european-headquarters.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Gemini will have a second home in Ireland after co-founder Cameron Winklevoss announced it would make Ireland its European headquarters. &lt;br /&gt;
Gemini, which is run by both Cameron Winklevoss and his twin Tyler, is based in New York. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-selects-ireland-for-its-european-headquarters.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Gemini Selects Ireland for Its European Headquarters&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Ireland</category><category>Exchanges</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-selects-ireland-for-its-european-headquarters.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115084/277592/adobestock-4110803.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="190887"/></item><item><title>WEF White Paper on Crypto Asset Regulation Highlights Need for Regulation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wef-white-paper-crypto-asset-regulation-highlights-need-for-regulation.htm</link><description>The World Economic Forum, in collaboration with its Digital Currency Governance Consortium, has released a paper on regulating crypto assets. &lt;br /&gt;
The international organization published the paper, titled "Pathways to Crypto-Asset Regulation: A Global Approach," on Thursday, stressing the urgency of regulation and the importance of global collaboration to prevent inconsistent enforcement, regulatory arbitration, and ambiguity. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wef-white-paper-crypto-asset-regulation-highlights-need-for-regulation.htm"&gt;Read More: WEF White Paper on Crypto Asset Regulation Highlights Need for Regulation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wef-white-paper-crypto-asset-regulation-highlights-need-for-regulation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115062/277531/wef.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="271012"/></item><item><title>Binance Launches Non-fungible Token (NFT) Loan Feature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launches-non-fungible-token-nft-loan-feature.htm</link><description>Many crypto service providers have accelerated efforts to expand their offerings and revenue streams and increase their user base.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to an announcement, the largest crypto exchange by trading volume, Binance, has added a non-fungible token (NFT) loan feature to its services. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency exchange will allow borrowers to use their NFT as collateral to borrow cryptocurrency without needing to sell assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launches-non-fungible-token-nft-loan-feature.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Launches Non-fungible Token (NFT) Loan Feature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-launches-non-fungible-token-nft-loan-feature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115083/277591/non-fungible-token-g17237.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="47363"/></item><item><title>Florida Governor Ron Desantis: 'you Have Every Right to Do Bitcoin'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-governor-ron-desantis-you-every-right-do-bitcoin.htm</link><description>The current Governor of Florida, Ron DeSantis, of the U.S. Republican party, announced his intent to run for the U.S. presidency in 2024.  &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, his stance on crypto and Bitcoin gives him an advantage in the large United States crypto community.   &lt;br /&gt;
Presently under U.S. President Joe Biden, crypto regulations are rising in America, restricting users' access to many products and platforms....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-governor-ron-desantis-you-every-right-do-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Florida Governor Ron Desantis: 'you Have Every Right to Do Bitcoin'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-governor-ron-desantis-you-every-right-do-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115081/277590/ron-desantis.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="215497"/></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Urges the SEC To Include State-Regulated Custodians in New Rule</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-urges-the-sec-to-include-state-regulated-custodians-in-new-rule.htm</link><description>Lawmakers urged a US regulator to not further limit certain financial stakeholders in its proposed rule tightening cryptocurrency custody requirements.  &lt;br /&gt;
Republican Rep. Mike Flood of Nebraska and Democratic Rep. Ritchie Torres of New York sent a letter to the Securities and Exchange Commission last week, urging the regulator to “maintain a pathway to state-regulated custodians.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-urges-the-sec-to-include-state-regulated-custodians-in-new-rule.htm"&gt;Read More: US Lawmakers Urges the SEC To Include State-Regulated Custodians in New Rule&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Congress</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Custody</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-urges-the-sec-to-include-state-regulated-custodians-in-new-rule.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115075/277564/us-capitol-gea1ca8469-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="134167"/></item><item><title>yPredict Coin Sees Huge Surge - Next Explosive Coin After Success of Ordinal Pepe (OPEPE)</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-coin-sees-huge-surge-next-explosive-coin-after-success-of-ordinal-pepe-opepe.htm</link><description>yPredict is a crypto platform backed by AI technology, providing insights for traders and analysts in the crypto market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Recently, the platform's native token, YPRED, attained a $1.7 million presale milestone making it one of the fastest-selling crypto in 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
Its utility rooted in advanced technology is its stand-out feature that will hopefully sustain its relevance moving forward. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-coin-sees-huge-surge-next-explosive-coin-after-success-of-ordinal-pepe-opepe.htm"&gt;Read More: yPredict Coin Sees Huge Surge - Next Explosive Coin After Success of Ordinal Pepe (OPEPE)&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-coin-sees-huge-surge-next-explosive-coin-after-success-of-ordinal-pepe-opepe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115069/277548/ypredict-media-library-or.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="156159"/></item><item><title>EU Investment Firms Should ‘Clearly Disclose’ That Some Assets, Including Crypto Are Unregulated: ESMA</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-investment-firms-should-clearly-disclose-that-some-assets-including-crypto-are-unregulated-esma.htm</link><description>Investment firms should make sure clients are aware of the regulatory status of the products they offer, including cryptocurrency, according to the latest notice from the European Union’s financial markets regulator.  &lt;br /&gt;
The European Securities and Markets Authority, or ESMA, said it was concerned about investment firms that offer unregulated products and services, in an investor protection statement released on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-investment-firms-should-clearly-disclose-that-some-assets-including-crypto-are-unregulated-esma.htm"&gt;Read More: EU Investment Firms Should ‘Clearly Disclose’ That Some Assets, Including Crypto Are Unregulated: ESMA&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eu-investment-firms-should-clearly-disclose-that-some-assets-including-crypto-are-unregulated-esma.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115066/277540/wind-g85f024e25-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="74885"/></item><item><title>5 Best Trending Coins on Dextools Today – RefundCoin, GMFAM, Ben, Pepe, Papi Chulo</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today-refundcoin-gmfam-ben-pepe-papi-chulo.htm</link><description>Crypto meme coin markets remain in a state of frenzy, with new coins popping up every day and many surging as investors hunt out the next major meme coin success story. &lt;br /&gt;
Here are the top five trending Ethereum-based ERC-20 coins on the decentralized exchange (DEX) analysis website DEX Tools. &lt;br /&gt;
Claiming the number 1 spot on DEX Tools’ trending coins list is RefundCoin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today-refundcoin-gmfam-ben-pepe-papi-chulo.htm"&gt;Read More: 5 Best Trending Coins on Dextools Today – RefundCoin, GMFAM, Ben, Pepe, Papi Chulo&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Trending Coins</category><category>RFD</category><category>GMFAM</category><category>BEN</category><category>Pepe</category><category>PAPI</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Shitcoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today-refundcoin-gmfam-ben-pepe-papi-chulo.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115063/277539/crypto.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6827508"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Gemini Chooses Ireland for European Headquarters, Coinone Exec Admits to Bribe-for-Listing Charges, Chinese's City Reveals Metaverse Policy Draft to Attract Companies</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gemini-chooses-ireland-for-european-headquarters-coinone-exec-admits-to-bribe-for-listing-charges-chineses-city-reveals-metaverse-policy-draft-to-attract-companies.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gemini-chooses-ireland-for-european-headquarters-coinone-exec-admits-to-bribe-for-listing-charges-chineses-city-reveals-metaverse-policy-draft-to-attract-companies.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Gemini Chooses Ireland for European Headquarters, Coinone Exec Admits to Bribe-for-Listing Charges, Chinese's City Reveals Metaverse Policy Draft to Attract Companies&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Ireland</category><category>Europe</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Legal</category><category>Coinone</category><category>Mining</category><category>USA</category><category>China</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Dubai</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-gemini-chooses-ireland-for-european-headquarters-coinone-exec-admits-to-bribe-for-listing-charges-chineses-city-reveals-metaverse-policy-draft-to-attract-companies.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115025/277476/adobestock-andrey-popov-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="165537"/></item><item><title>Steve Cho, Partner at Mechanism Capital, on Web3 VC funding and the Current Crypto Market Landscape | Ep. 233</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-cho-partner-at-mechanism-capital-web3-vc-funding-current-crypto-market-landscape-ep-233.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Steve Cho, Head of Mechanism Play and Partner at Mechanism Capital, talks about the state of the Web3 gaming industry, the current crypto market landscape and its impact on VC funding for crypto projects....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-cho-partner-at-mechanism-capital-web3-vc-funding-current-crypto-market-landscape-ep-233.htm"&gt;Read More: Steve Cho, Partner at Mechanism Capital, on Web3 VC funding and the Current Crypto Market Landscape | Ep. 233&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/steve-cho-partner-at-mechanism-capital-web3-vc-funding-current-crypto-market-landscape-ep-233.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115053/277511/steve-cho-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="101250"/></item><item><title>Which Crypto Can Give 1000x Return on Investment in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/which-crypto-can-give-1000x-2023.htm</link><description>Are you looking for the next cryptocurrency that has the potential to skyrocket in value and potentially offers a 1000x return on investment in 2023?  &lt;br /&gt;
With the rapidly evolving crypto market, investors are always looking for the next big opportunity.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this update, we will explore two cryptocurrencies that have been generating significant buzz and speculation: WSM and $SPONGE. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/which-crypto-can-give-1000x-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Which Crypto Can Give 1000x Return on Investment in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/which-crypto-can-give-1000x-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115035/277501/ape.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="419406"/></item><item><title>BONGOCAT Coin Price Prediction as Coin Blasts Up 1500% in 24 Hours – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bongocat-coin-price-prediction-as-coin-blasts-up-1500-24-hours-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>A new cat meme coin has been going parabolic in the last 24 hours, blasting up over 1,500%. &lt;br /&gt;
BONGOCAT was last trading in the mid-$0.26s, up nearly 400x versus its initial listing price across decentralized exchanges on Thursday of around $0.00065. &lt;br /&gt;
The BSC Chain-based meme coin says on its website that it has one goal; “to create a strong community of diamond hands who will all prosper from the project’s success”....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bongocat-coin-price-prediction-as-coin-blasts-up-1500-24-hours-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: BONGOCAT Coin Price Prediction as Coin Blasts Up 1500% in 24 Hours – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>BONGOCAT</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>AI</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bongocat-coin-price-prediction-as-coin-blasts-up-1500-24-hours-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115048/277496/bongocat-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227158"/></item><item><title>Is Pepe Coin Price Doomed? Consider Launchpad and Deelance as Top Crypto Options</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-doomed-consider-launchpad-deelance-as-top-crypto-options.htm</link><description>Enthusiasm for Pepe coin (PEPE), a Pepe the frog meme coin that exploded onto the scene in mid-April and went on to claim a market capitalization of around $1.8 billion at its all-time high, continues to wane. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE was last changing hands in the mid-$0.0000014s, down around 70% form its all-time high price in the $0.000005 area that was hit earlier this month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-doomed-consider-launchpad-deelance-as-top-crypto-options.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Pepe Coin Price Doomed? Consider Launchpad and Deelance as Top Crypto Options&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>DLANCE</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-doomed-consider-launchpad-deelance-as-top-crypto-options.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115046/277488/pepe.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2201456"/></item><item><title>Wall Street Memes Crypto Presale Raises $100k Minutes After Launch, The Next Pepe Coin or Dogecoin?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-crypto-presale-raises-100k-minutes-after-launch-next-pepe-coin-or-dogecoin.htm</link><description>Today marks the launch of the Wall Street Memes token ($WSM) presale, courtesy of the the internet’s hottest investing community, that turns stock stonks into hard cash, and is now doing the same for meme coins. &lt;br /&gt;
If you are looking for the next meme coin to explode like Pepecoin, Dogecoin or Shiba Inu, then look no further. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-crypto-presale-raises-100k-minutes-after-launch-next-pepe-coin-or-dogecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Wall Street Memes Crypto Presale Raises $100k Minutes After Launch, The Next Pepe Coin or Dogecoin?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/wall-street-memes-crypto-presale-raises-100k-minutes-after-launch-next-pepe-coin-or-dogecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115033/277480/wall-street-memes-crypto-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1196540"/></item><item><title>Singapore Venture Capital Firm Foresight Ventures Launches Second Phase of Web3 Accelerator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-venture-capital-firm-foresight-ventures-launches-second-phase-of-web3-accelerator.htm</link><description>Foresight Ventures, a venture capital company based in Singapore, has opened up the application process for the second phase of its accelerator program.  &lt;br /&gt;
This round focuses on Web3 projects in various emerging ecosystems, with an additional $10 million pledged towards the program, the company said in a recent announcement.  &lt;br /&gt;
The first phase saw 30 companies selected and given investments ranging from $50,000 to $200,000 each. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-venture-capital-firm-foresight-ventures-launches-second-phase-of-web3-accelerator.htm"&gt;Read More: Singapore Venture Capital Firm Foresight Ventures Launches Second Phase of Web3 Accelerator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Web3</category><category>Singapore</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-venture-capital-firm-foresight-ventures-launches-second-phase-of-web3-accelerator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115036/277473/adobestock-richie-chan-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="175324"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Meme Coin Google Trends Data Shows Decline - Time to Sell DOGE?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-google-trends-data-shows-decline-time-to-sell-doge.htm</link><description>Memecoin season has enjoyed a sensational run over the past two months, but as interest appears to be dwindling many fear Dogecoin (DOGE) could be the next to tank? Find out in this Dogecoin price prediction. &lt;br /&gt;
The 2023 memecoin season was ignited in April as now #71 ranked cryptocurrency Pepe coin (PEPE) gained explosive traction that powered a 50,000% gain for the earliest investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-google-trends-data-shows-decline-time-to-sell-doge.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as Meme Coin Google Trends Data Shows Decline - Time to Sell DOGE?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 12:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coin-google-trends-data-shows-decline-time-to-sell-doge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115019/277462/dogecoin-gcf9c234c6-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="314663"/></item><item><title>Microsoft's Brad Smith Calls for More Regulation of Artificial Intelligence</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/microsofts-smith-calls-for-more-regulation-of-artificial-intelligence.htm</link><description>Artificial intelligence (AI) may the “the most consequential” technological change in our lifetime, and governments now need to learn how to control it, according to Microsoft President Brad Smith. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at a panel discussion in Washington, D.C. on Thursday, Smith said that “government needs to move faster” to stay on top of the developments that are happening in AI....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/microsofts-smith-calls-for-more-regulation-of-artificial-intelligence.htm"&gt;Read More: Microsoft's Brad Smith Calls for More Regulation of Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>OpenAI</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>Microsoft</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/microsofts-smith-calls-for-more-regulation-of-artificial-intelligence.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115030/277457/ai-chip.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1518047"/></item></channel></rss>
