<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>US Regulator Charges Five in a “Fraudulent Digital Assets Trading Scheme” After They Targeted Spanish-Speaking Communities</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-charges-five-in-a-fraudulent-digital-assets-trading-scheme-after-they-targeted-spanish-speaking-communities.htm</link><description>A US regulator charges five people on Wednesday for allegedly “fraudulently soliciting” money from more than 170 people for a company called Icomtech to trade bitcoin and other assets for them.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Commodity Futures Trading Commission filed a complaint in the US District Court for the Central District of California against David Carmona, Juan Arellano Parra, Moses Valdez, David Brend and Marco A. Ruiz Ochoa — who all did business as Icomtech, the regulator said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-charges-five-in-a-fraudulent-digital-assets-trading-scheme-after-they-targeted-spanish-speaking-communities.htm"&gt;Read More: US Regulator Charges Five in a “Fraudulent Digital Assets Trading Scheme” After They Targeted Spanish-Speaking Communities&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Charges</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ether</category><category>USDC</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-charges-five-in-a-fraudulent-digital-assets-trading-scheme-after-they-targeted-spanish-speaking-communities.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114876/277166/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="387163"/></item><item><title>Central Bank: Crypto May ‘Infect’ Russian Economy – Is a Crackdown Incoming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-crypto-may-infect-russian-economy-crackdown-incoming.htm</link><description>Cryptoassets have the power to “infect” the Russian economy, the nation’s crypto-skeptic Central Bank has warned. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the domestic news agency Interfax, the bank’s First Deputy Chairwoman Ksenia Yudaeva made the comments at a recent economic forum. &lt;br /&gt;
She claimed that the government and regulators needed to ensure that cryptoassets were restricted to the fringes of economic activity....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-crypto-may-infect-russian-economy-crackdown-incoming.htm"&gt;Read More: Central Bank: Crypto May ‘Infect’ Russian Economy – Is a Crackdown Incoming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Central Bank</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/central-bank-crypto-may-infect-russian-economy-crackdown-incoming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114859/277133/adobestock-376251271-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="844157"/></item><item><title>IRS Sends Experts Next Month Around the World To Combat Cybercrime With a Focus on Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-sends-experts-next-month-around-world-combat-cybercrime-focused-those-that-use-crypto.htm</link><description>The US Internal Revenue Service will deploy experts next month to four continents to combat cybercrime, with a particular focus on tax and financial crimes that use cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
That is part of a pilot program the IRS announced last week where “cyber attachés” will be sent to Sydney, Bogota, Frankfurt and Singapore from June to September. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-sends-experts-next-month-around-world-combat-cybercrime-focused-those-that-use-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: IRS Sends Experts Next Month Around the World To Combat Cybercrime With a Focus on Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>IRS</category><category>Crime</category><category>Cybercrime</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-sends-experts-next-month-around-world-combat-cybercrime-focused-those-that-use-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114862/277143/adobestock-222371839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="346561"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 24 May – Kava, AiDoge, Render, ecoterra, Toncoin, yPredict, DeeLance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-may-kava-aidoge-render-ecoterra-toncoin-ypredict-deelance.htm</link><description>The minutes from the Federal Reserve's early May meeting reveal a lack of consensus regarding future interest rate changes, bringing an air of uncertainty to markets today. &lt;br /&gt;
Officials expressed indecision about whether to continue raising rates or maintain the status quo. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this uncertain macroeconomic backdrop, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-may-kava-aidoge-render-ecoterra-toncoin-ypredict-deelance.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 24 May – Kava, AiDoge, Render, ecoterra, Toncoin, yPredict, DeeLance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>KAVA</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Render</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Toncoin</category><category>yPredict</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>AI</category><category>RNDR</category><category>TON</category><category>YPRED</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Web3</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>R2E</category><category>M2E</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 22:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-may-kava-aidoge-render-ecoterra-toncoin-ypredict-deelance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114874/277164/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>FOMC Minutes Signal Central Bank Divided on Need for More Tightening – Here is How Crypto Reacted</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fomc-minutes-signal-central-bank-divided-need-for-more-tightening-here-how-crypto-reacted.htm</link><description>The minutes from this month’s FOMC meeting of US Federal Reserve policymakers were just released, revealing the bank to be divided on the need for further interest rate hikes. &lt;br /&gt;
Cryptocurrency, forex, US equity and US bond markets didn’t see much of a reaction to the minutes, the tone of which were broadly as expected....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fomc-minutes-signal-central-bank-divided-need-for-more-tightening-here-how-crypto-reacted.htm"&gt;Read More: FOMC Minutes Signal Central Bank Divided on Need for More Tightening – Here is How Crypto Reacted&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Fed</category><category>FOMC</category><category>Minutes</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ether</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fomc-minutes-signal-central-bank-divided-need-for-more-tightening-here-how-crypto-reacted.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114872/277161/fed.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3080018"/></item><item><title>China Central Television’s Segment on Crypto Garners Attention Around the World</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-central-televisions-segment-crypto-garners-attention-around-world.htm</link><description>China Central Television aired a segment on Tuesday involving virtual assets, which garnered attention from around the world.  &lt;br /&gt;
The segment, which is just over a minute long, features bitcoin, nonfungible tokens and is titled “Hong Kong Securities Regulatory Commission: Implementing a mandatory licensing system for virtual asset trading platforms from June 1.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-central-televisions-segment-crypto-garners-attention-around-world.htm"&gt;Read More: China Central Television’s Segment on Crypto Garners Attention Around the World&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CZ binance</category><category>Binance</category><category>China</category><category>Hong Kong</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-central-televisions-segment-crypto-garners-attention-around-world.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114865/277148/adobestock-167378805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="598009"/></item><item><title>U.S. Charges Russian In Ransomware Scheme Worth Up To $200 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-charges-russian-ransomware-scheme-worth-up-200-million.htm</link><description>The U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has indicted a Russian man for his alleged participation in several ransomware schemes. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a press release from the Justice Department, the individual, identified as Russian national Mikhail Pavlovich Matveev, has carried out cyberattacks on victims across the United States, including on law enforcement agencies and companies in several important sectors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-charges-russian-ransomware-scheme-worth-up-200-million.htm"&gt;Read More: U.S. Charges Russian In Ransomware Scheme Worth Up To $200 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ransomware</category><category>Crime</category><category>hacking</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-charges-russian-ransomware-scheme-worth-up-200-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114866/277147/ransom.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="318493"/></item><item><title>What Is Azra Games' Approach To NFTs In Gaming</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-azra-games-approach-nfts-gaming.htm</link><description>Blockchain gaming company Azra Games is taking a different approach to NFTs in Web3 games, focusing on the gameplay itself rather than the crypto elements.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent interview, Azra Games founder and CEO Mark Otero said Web3 games need to be so good that people adopt it for the gameplay not for NFTs or its in-game tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/what-azra-games-approach-nfts-gaming.htm"&gt;Read More: What Is Azra Games' Approach To NFTs In Gaming&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Arza Games</category><category>Blockchain games</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/what-azra-games-approach-nfts-gaming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114829/277064/fwxtqekacaanvga.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="109295"/></item><item><title>LOVESNOOPY Burns 85% of Tokens While Crypto Experts Amass New Eco-Friendly Cryptocurrency In Anticipation of Exchange Listing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lovesnoopy-burns-85-of-tokens-while-crypto-experts-amass-new-eco-friendly-cryptocurrency-in-anticipation-of-exchange-listing.htm</link><description>Image by Fareed Mindalano / Playground AI &lt;br /&gt;
LOVESNOOPY recently announced a massive 85% reduction in its total token supply through a strategic token burn. &lt;br /&gt;
This dramatic move could increase the value of its remaining tokens over time, representing an ambitious maneuver in the volatile cryptocurrency market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lovesnoopy-burns-85-of-tokens-while-crypto-experts-amass-new-eco-friendly-cryptocurrency-in-anticipation-of-exchange-listing.htm"&gt;Read More: LOVESNOOPY Burns 85% of Tokens While Crypto Experts Amass New Eco-Friendly Cryptocurrency In Anticipation of Exchange Listing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Meme Coins</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Sustainability</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Carbon Credits</category><category>Recycled Materials Marketplace</category><category>Waste management</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lovesnoopy-burns-85-of-tokens-while-crypto-experts-amass-new-eco-friendly-cryptocurrency-in-anticipation-of-exchange-listing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114821/277056/cartoon-character-snoopy-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="3175500"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs’ Do Kwon’s Bail Revoked in Montenegro Court: Bloomberg</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-do-kwons-bail-revoked-montenegro-court-bloomberg.htm</link><description>A court in Montenegro has repealed a lower court’s decision under which to release Terraform Labs co-founder Do Kwon on bail, according to Bloomberg News.  &lt;br /&gt;
A court spokesperson said a high court in Montenegro’s capital overturned the earlier decision and Kwon remains in jail, Bloomberg reported.  &lt;br /&gt;
This also applies to Terraform Labs’ former Chief Financial Officer Han Chong-joon, according to Bloomberg....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-do-kwons-bail-revoked-montenegro-court-bloomberg.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs’ Do Kwon’s Bail Revoked in Montenegro Court: Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>Terra</category><category>TerraUSD</category><category>Montenegro</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-do-kwons-bail-revoked-montenegro-court-bloomberg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114854/277104/screen-shot-2023-05-11-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="637793"/></item><item><title>Binance Accused of Mixing Company Revenue with Customer Money In U.S</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-accused-of-mixing-company-revenue-with-customer-money-us.htm</link><description>The world’s largest crypto exchange, Binance, has mixed company revenues with customer funds in the US, according to a Reuters report. &lt;br /&gt;
The comingling of customer funds and company revenues happened “almost daily” in bank accounts the exchange had at the now-bankrupt crypto-friendly bank Silvergate, the report said, citing “a person with direct knowledge of Binance’s group finances.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-accused-of-mixing-company-revenue-with-customer-money-us.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Accused of Mixing Company Revenue with Customer Money In U.S&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-accused-of-mixing-company-revenue-with-customer-money-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114851/277103/binance-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="144781"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Elon Musk Isn’t Exactly Telling People To Invest in Dogecoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-elon-musk-isnt-exactly-telling-people-invest-dogecoin.htm</link><description>Though Billionaire Elon Musk has shown his love for meme coin Dogecoin over the years, that doesn’t mean he is telling investors to put their life savings into it.  &lt;br /&gt;
Musk told the Wall Street Journal this week that at its CEO Council Summit to not “bet the farm on dogecoin.” &lt;br /&gt;
"I'm not advising anyone to buy crypto or bet the farm on dogecoin," Musk said.  &lt;br /&gt;
Musk added that dogecoin is his favorite because it has "the best humor" and "it has dogs."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-elon-musk-isnt-exactly-telling-people-invest-dogecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Elon Musk Isn’t Exactly Telling People To Invest in Dogecoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-elon-musk-isnt-exactly-telling-people-invest-dogecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114838/277080/adobestock-484838882-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="344548"/></item><item><title>NFT and Token Airdrop Fuel Enthusiasm for New Trending Meme Coin $COPIUM</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/exciting-nft-and-token-airdrop-fuel-enthusiasm-for-upcoming-launch-of-copium-a-promising-new-meme-coin-early-buying-guide.htm</link><description>There's a new player shaking up the meme coin vertical, $COPIUM, poised to disrupt the market, packing the punch with an exciting NFT and token airdrop event on the horizon. &lt;br /&gt;
This captivating event is drawing the gaze of crypto enthusiasts, particularly with the unique utility and lucrative prospects it presents. &lt;br /&gt;
$COPIUM is an audacious meme coin that doesn't shy away from the spotlight....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/exciting-nft-and-token-airdrop-fuel-enthusiasm-for-upcoming-launch-of-copium-a-promising-new-meme-coin-early-buying-guide.htm"&gt;Read More: NFT and Token Airdrop Fuel Enthusiasm for New Trending Meme Coin $COPIUM&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/exciting-nft-and-token-airdrop-fuel-enthusiasm-for-upcoming-launch-of-copium-a-promising-new-meme-coin-early-buying-guide.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114831/277076/copium-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="665786"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Crypto Hacks Drop 70% in Q1 2023, Binance CSO Said Reuters' 'Weak' Article is Filled with Conspiracy Theories, Solana Integrates AI with a ChatGPT Plugin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-crypto-hacks-drop-70-in-q1-2023-binance-cso-said-reuters-weak-article-is-filled-with-conspiracy-theories-solana-integrates-ai-with-a-chatgpt-plugin.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-crypto-hacks-drop-70-in-q1-2023-binance-cso-said-reuters-weak-article-is-filled-with-conspiracy-theories-solana-integrates-ai-with-a-chatgpt-plugin.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Crypto Hacks Drop 70% in Q1 2023, Binance CSO Said Reuters' 'Weak' Article is Filled with Conspiracy Theories, Solana Integrates AI with a ChatGPT Plugin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Security</category><category>Hack</category><category>TRM Labs</category><category>Binance</category><category>Legal</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>USA</category><category>China</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Pakistan</category><category>Ban</category><category>Solana</category><category>AI</category><category>chatGPT</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-crypto-hacks-drop-70-in-q1-2023-binance-cso-said-reuters-weak-article-is-filled-with-conspiracy-theories-solana-integrates-ai-with-a-chatgpt-plugin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114808/277036/adobestock-photo-gonzo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="41186"/></item><item><title>Should You Buy SOL? Solana Price Prediction Surges as SOL Blockchain Attracts a Wave of New Users Amidst High ETH Gas Fees</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/should-you-buy-sol-solana-price-prediction-surges-as-sol-blockchain-attracts-wave-of-new-users-amidst-high-eth-gas-fees.htm</link><description>Solana (SOL), a blockchain platform known for its scalability and low transaction fees, has recently gained significant attention as it attracts a wave of new users.  &lt;br /&gt;
The surge in interest comes as Ethereum (ETH) gas fees remain high, prompting many users to explore alternative options.  &lt;br /&gt;
The growing popularity of the Solana blockchain has led to speculation about the future price of its native cryptocurrency, SOL. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/should-you-buy-sol-solana-price-prediction-surges-as-sol-blockchain-attracts-wave-of-new-users-amidst-high-eth-gas-fees.htm"&gt;Read More: Should You Buy SOL? Solana Price Prediction Surges as SOL Blockchain Attracts a Wave of New Users Amidst High ETH Gas Fees&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/should-you-buy-sol-solana-price-prediction-surges-as-sol-blockchain-attracts-wave-of-new-users-amidst-high-eth-gas-fees.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114818/277067/solana.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="283995"/></item><item><title>Digital-Native City 'Cabin' Seeks To Reinvigorate The City</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-native-city-cabin-seeks-to-reinvigorate-the-city.htm</link><description>Digital-native coliving city project, Cabin wants to revolutionize its initiative by integrating crypto governance with a newly launched Network City. &lt;br /&gt;
Cabin announced the launch of the first-ever network city, a globally-distributed property for remote workers and creators who love nature. &lt;br /&gt;
The city is a global alliance of self-governing neighborhoods accessible to residents holding NFTs, dubbed citizenship passports. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-native-city-cabin-seeks-to-reinvigorate-the-city.htm"&gt;Read More: Digital-Native City 'Cabin' Seeks To Reinvigorate The City&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-native-city-cabin-seeks-to-reinvigorate-the-city.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114832/277066/fantasy-g71b66bb7e-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293265"/></item><item><title>Fungible Token Marketplace NFTrade Offers Easy Way To Pay For Items On Multiple Networks</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fungible-token-marketplace-nftrade-offers-easy-way-pay-for-items-multiple-networks.htm</link><description>Non-fungible token marketplace NFTrade has introduced a more flexible payment method on its platform.  &lt;br /&gt;
The marketplace now allows cross-chain purchases and payments on Ethereum, BNB Chain, Polygon, and Avalanche. &lt;br /&gt;
According to an announcement, NFTrade partnered with cross-chain interoperability protocol Rarimo to roll out the new features. &lt;br /&gt;
These new features allow NFT collectors to initiate a purchase on one network and pay on another in one click....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fungible-token-marketplace-nftrade-offers-easy-way-pay-for-items-multiple-networks.htm"&gt;Read More: Fungible Token Marketplace NFTrade Offers Easy Way To Pay For Items On Multiple Networks&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fungible-token-marketplace-nftrade-offers-easy-way-pay-for-items-multiple-networks.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114823/277059/pexels-markus-winkler-12188470.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="163549"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Forecast as Lawsuit Resolution Nears - Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-forecast-as-lawsuit-resolution-nears-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm</link><description>Amid a broader pullback in the cryptocurrency market on Wednesday as hotter-than-expected UK inflation data triggers jitters about sticky inflation across major global economies that might prevent central bank from being able to cut interest rates in the coming quarters, XRP has been falling....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-forecast-as-lawsuit-resolution-nears-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Forecast as Lawsuit Resolution Nears - Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-forecast-as-lawsuit-resolution-nears-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114820/277052/xrp.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="11332564"/></item><item><title>Santiment Measures Social Media Text Volumes of Bitcoin - Here's What They Find</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/santiment-measures-social-media-text-volumes-of-bitcoin-heres-what-they-find.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin (BTC) generally moves in the opposite direction of what traders anticipate, crypto sentiment analysis firm Santiment has found. &lt;br /&gt;
Writing on Twitter earlier this week, Santiment said that the fact that Bitcoin’s price moves contrary to what “the crowd” expects is something that has been seen many times, and most recently this past weekend....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/santiment-measures-social-media-text-volumes-of-bitcoin-heres-what-they-find.htm"&gt;Read More: Santiment Measures Social Media Text Volumes of Bitcoin - Here's What They Find&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/santiment-measures-social-media-text-volumes-of-bitcoin-heres-what-they-find.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114813/277043/bitcoin-bull-and-bear.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="164179"/></item><item><title>ICC Securities Watchdog To Help Regulate Cryptocurrency - Here's What It Says </title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/icc-securities-watchdog-to-help-regulate-cryptocurrency-heres-what-it-says.htm</link><description>With a number of securities regulators across the world developing new rules for the crypto industry, the International Organization of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) aims to contribute to the ongoing discussion by releasing its own batch of crypto-focused policy recommendations. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/icc-securities-watchdog-to-help-regulate-cryptocurrency-heres-what-it-says.htm"&gt;Read More: ICC Securities Watchdog To Help Regulate Cryptocurrency - Here's What It Says &lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>IOSCO</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/icc-securities-watchdog-to-help-regulate-cryptocurrency-heres-what-it-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114801/277009/earth-g78fc97b00-1920-med.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="308126"/></item></channel></rss>
