<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Novogratz Advises Investors to Buy Bitcoin As Federal Interest Payments Skyrocket</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/novogratz-advises-investors-to-buy-bitcoin-as-federal-interest-payments-skyrocket/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263148</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/MikeNovogratz-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/MikeNovogratz-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the US government continues turning over its debt at higher rates, can the Federal Reserve afford not to print?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto investor and Galaxy Digital CEO Mike Novogratz told followers on Wednesday to “Buy BTC” in response to the United States government’s rapidly growing interest expense on its sovereign debt.</p>
<p>To some analysts, the trend suggests that the Federal Reserve will be forced to lower its benchmark interest rate again if the Federal government can no longer keep up.</p>
<h2>The US Debt Problem</h2>
<p>According to market analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeConsorti/status/1684584512318058497" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Joe Consorti</a>, the U.S. government is now paying $970 billion per year in interest payments – up $41 billion from Q2. That’s the highest interest expense of all time by a wide margin, with annual payments only reaching $600 billion as recently as Q1 2022.</p>
<p>Consorti expects interest costs to reach $1 trillion soon. That’s over 20% of the government’s $4.7 trillion federal tax revenue, according to <a href="https://www.usdebtclock.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">US Debt Clock</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>“As tax receipts continue to lag sovereign debt growth, interest payments will increasingly be funded with revenue from&#8230; more debt issuance,” wrote Consorti to Twitter on Thursday. “Get it now?”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="und" dir="ltr">Buy <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$BTC</a>!!! <a href="https://t.co/UyGNaGXzyI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/UyGNaGXzyI</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Mike Novogratz (@novogratz) <a href="https://twitter.com/novogratz/status/1684694364679790592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Interest costs began to surge after the Federal Reserve began its monetary tightening cycle, during which it raised its benchmark rate from 0.25% to 5.25%. It’s also continued to sell Treasury debt and agency mortgage-backed securities, driving up rates for short-term T-bills.</p>
<p>Such rate hikes make it more difficult for the government to roll over its previously issued debt, as new loans force it to pay out buyers at a higher interest rate.</p>
<p>In June, the St. Louis Fed <a href="https://research.stlouisfed.org/publications/economic-synopses/2023/06/02/assessing-the-costs-of-rolling-over-government-debt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> an essay stating that while interest payments are large in absolute terms, they’re still “relatively small” against the size of the US economy.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;However, the longer interest rates stay high, more and more of the fixed-rate marketable portion of the U.S. debt will be rolled over at higher rates, continuing to cause interest payments by the government to become a larger and larger portion of the budget,” the bank’s analysts added.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Where Does Bitcoin Come In?</h2>
<p>Mounting interest expenses suggest that the central bank may need to inject money into the economy again to keep it upright. This would likely be bullish for risk assets, including Bitcoin – which is know for having an absolutely fixed supply irrespective of economic circumstances.</p>
<p>Bitcoin already rose from $19,000 to $30,000 in March when the Federal Reserve bailed out depositors to Silicon Valley Bank and Signature Bank, while also adding another $300 billion in assets back to its balance sheet.</p>
<p>Mike Novogratz correctly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/venture-capitalist-mike-novogratz-predicts-30k-bitcoin-this-quarter/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> the pump at the time. He also <a href="https://twitter.com/novogratz/status/1681387712220102672" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">called</a> Bitcoin a “report card on fiscal stewardship” earlier this month, in response to the fast-depreciating Turkish Lira reaching another all-time high in Bitcoin terms.</p>
<p>Coinbase CTO Balaji Srinivasan has repeatedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/balaji-forfeits-and-settles-1-million-bitcoin-bet-but-stands-by-hyperinflation-thesis/" data-wpel-link="internal">argued</a> this year that mounting debt across all sectors of the economy could cause the government to “print trillions”, which will ultimately boost Bitcoin’s price.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/novogratz-advises-investors-to-buy-bitcoin-as-federal-interest-payments-skyrocket/" rel="nofollow">Novogratz Advises Investors to Buy Bitcoin As Federal Interest Payments Skyrocket</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Loses $30K as US Federal Reserve Hikes Interest Rates by Another 25BPS: This Week’s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-loses-30k-as-us-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-another-25bps-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263108</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/federal_reserve_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/federal_reserve_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[From potential crypto bills in the US to Fed's interest rate hike and Twitter's rebranding - let's unpack the past seven days. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although most prices in the cryptocurrency market have shown high levels of stagnation in the past week, there were still several notable developments on different fronts.</p>
<p>Starting with US regulations, this week saw discussions for a few separate bills, including the Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act, which Democrats claimed still &#8220;<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/congressional-stablecoin-bill-still-reeks-of-sam-bankman-fried-democrats-say/" data-wpel-link="internal">reeks</a>&#8221; of Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; the disgraced former FTX exec who was among the chief supporters. On the other hand, Republicans were not too happy that the stablecoin legislative proposal also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/republicans-blast-white-house-for-failure-to-compromise-on-stablecoin-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">failed</a> to pass.</p>
<p>Another talked-about point coming from the States was the Wednesday FOMC meeting. The Federal Reserve was expected to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-raises-rates-again-by-0-25-bitcoin-trades-flat/" data-wpel-link="internal">increase</a> the key interest rates by 25 basis points after failing to do so during the previous such meeting.</p>
<p>Typically, such moves lead to enhanced volatility for bitcoin and the rest of the market, but this wasn&#8217;t the case on Wednesday. The primary cryptocurrency didn&#8217;t have the best week in terms of price action, as it failed to remain above $30,000 during the weekend and hasn&#8217;t been above that line since. Furthermore, it painted a monthly low beneath $29,000 on Monday.</p>
<p>Interesting news came out from Twitter as the owner &#8211; Elon Musk &#8211; announced a rebranding and a logo change to &#8220;X.&#8221; Additionally, he hinted at potential integration of Dogecoin, which sent the meme coin&#8217;s price flying to a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/doge-tapped-3-month-high-following-musk-engagement-btc-sustains-29k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">three-month peak</a> during the week.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, most crypto assets suffered in the past week, with GALA, Injective, Mantle, and PEPE leading the adverse trend with double-digit price drops. Ripple&#8217;s native token, as well as Bitcoin SV, also posted 7-day declines of around 8%.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,230B | 24H Vol: $32B | BTC Dominance: 46.3%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $29,281 (-1.6%) | ETH: $1,869 (-1%) | BNB: $241 (-1.1%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-140242" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm.jpg" alt="BitcoinCalm" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week’s Crypto Headlines You Can’t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>4 Problems With Sam Altman’s Worldcoin, According to Vitalik</strong>. This week saw the much-anticipated launch of Worldcoin, but the project faced enhanced criticism over centralization and a potential lack of privacy. Ethereum&#8217;s Vitalik Buterin also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-problems-with-sam-altmans-worldcoin-according-to-vitalik/" data-wpel-link="internal">weighed in</a> on the matter, outlining his four problems with it.</p>
<p><strong>KuCoin CEO Sheds Light on Allegations of Mass Layoffs</strong>. Reports <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kucoin-reportedly-slashes-30-of-its-workforce/" data-wpel-link="internal">emerged</a> earlier this week that the popular exchange was planning to cut 30% of its workforce. KuCoin&#8217;s CEO was quick to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kucoin-ceo-sheds-light-on-allegations-of-mass-layoffs/" data-wpel-link="internal">address</a> the rumors, saying the layoffs will be due to performance reviews, not internal problems.</p>
<p><strong>Binance Officially Files for Dismissal of CFTC’s Case</strong>. After a week of speculations, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, alongside its CEO, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-officially-files-for-dismissal-of-cftcs-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> to have the lawsuit by the US CFTC dismissed, claiming the regulator didn&#8217;t have jurisdiction over Binance and CZ.</p>
<p><strong>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong Calls for Voting in Favor of FIT21</strong>. In continuation of the aforementioned FIT21 bill, Coinbase&#8217;s CEO <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-calls-for-voting-in-favor-of-fit21/" data-wpel-link="internal">urged</a> US citizens to vote &#8220;yes&#8221; to it, even though it&#8217;s just the first out of many steps needed for regulatory clarity in the States.</p>
<p><strong>Federal Reserve Raises Rates Again By 0.25%, Bitcoin Trades Flat</strong>. As mentioned above, the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-raises-rates-again-by-0-25-bitcoin-trades-flat/" data-wpel-link="internal">resumed</a> its monetary policy of increasing the interest rates. The latest 25 bps hike, though, didn&#8217;t result in immediate price volatility for BTC.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Correlation With US Equities at 2-Year Low, Potential Bullish Signal? </strong>On-chain data provided by Kaiko <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-correlation-with-us-equities-at-2-year-low-potential-bullish-signal/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the positive correlation between some of the most prominent US stock market indexes and BTC has dropped to a 2-year-low, which some speculated could be a potential bullish signal for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-loses-30k-as-us-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-another-25bps-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Loses $30K as US Federal Reserve Hikes Interest Rates by Another 25BPS: This Week’s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creta Prepares to Launch Hyper-Realistic Multiverse ‘Dayroot’</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/creta-prepares-to-launch-hyper-realistic-multiverse-dayroot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 13:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263113</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6_1690544774rj0OjGbAae.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/6_1690544774rj0OjGbAae.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 28th, 2023] Creeta has announced the creation of Dayroot, a hyper-realistic multiverse platform that extends the capabilities of the metaverse. It will enable players to enter a digital realm where anything is possible and where countless parallel universes exist. Dayroot is the first world to be created by Creta&#8217;s [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Dubai, UAE, July 28th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Creeta has announced the creation of Dayroot, a hyper-realistic multiverse platform that extends the capabilities of the metaverse. It will enable players to enter a digital realm where anything is possible and where countless parallel universes exist. Dayroot is the first world to be created by Creta&#8217;s multiverse service.</p>
<p>Creta breaks the barriers of existing metaverse content by offering a high-performance public blockchain and web3-based multiverse platform. Headquartered in Dubai, Creta boasts a team of renowned developers, publishers, and blockchain experts with decades of experience in the gaming industry. Its team includes Ray Nakazato, a respected producer in the gaming industry, and Alexander Harutyunyan, the former CEO of Innova. Their vision is to create a next-generation, global-oriented web3 multiverse platform ecosystem that caters to both gamers and game creators alike.</p>
<p>Creta&#8217;s concept of a mega multiverse unites interconnected metaverses with stunning photorealistic visual quality. Initially, the platform will introduce three basic metaverse worlds, with plans to continually add diverse metaverses through partnerships. This design ensures that users can seamlessly explore and enjoy a multiverse world that transcends the boundaries of any single metaverse.</p>
<p>The technological backbone behind Creta’s ambitious concept is the Locus GameChain, capable of reducing server costs dramatically, and the high-performance public blockchain known as Locus Chain, which addresses scalability challenges.</p>
<p>The Creta multiverse aims to be an all-in-one hub for a wide range of content services, seamlessly integrating games, performances, shopping, and user-generated content spaces. This consolidation of experiences caters to the preferences of each user, ensuring a harmonious blend of light goal-achievement games, immersive high-quality content, and more.</p>
<p>Creta is also preparing to launch a web3-based community known as Creta SuperClub. This community-driven platform will empower users to share information, engage in discussions through clubs and forums, and make use of blockchain’s many advantages. Notably, users, not developers, will have ownership of the clubs and be able to trade various NFTs, such as game items, within the platform.</p>
<p>Creta Japan CEO Ray Nakazato said: “The Creta platform&#8217;s high-performance, blockchain-based photorealistic graphics hold infinite potential for expansion, promising an entirely new world of experiences that has never been seen before.”</p>
<p>The hyper-realistic multiverse platform offered by Creta has the potential to reshape the entertainment industry, offering a limitless range of experiences and uniting the worlds of gaming, blockchain, and web3 into a single, cohesive genre.</p>
<h2>About Creta</h2>
<p>Creta is building the ultimate web3 gaming platform, featuring the metaverse, blockchain games, and a suite of solutions for web3 gaming. The company is run by the development team of acclaimed video game franchise Kingdom Under Fire and is supported by veterans from both blockchain and video game industries such as Yield Games Guild Japan and Yoshiki Okamoto, an award-winning game designer behind Monster Strike. Creta has offices in South Korea, Japan, Dubai, and Armenia and is advised by a global network of blockchain partners and associations.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/3_16905449961ySS3oQikF.jpg" /></p>
<p>Please refer to the below for more information on CRETA</p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/CRETA_WORLD" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://twitter.com/CRETA_WORLD</a></p>
<p>Discord: <a href="https://discord.com/invite/FWCd28vv36%20" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://discord.com/invite/FWCd28vv36 </a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/creta-prepares-to-launch-hyper-realistic-multiverse-dayroot/" rel="nofollow">Creta Prepares to Launch Hyper-Realistic Multiverse ‘Dayroot’</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI DAOs Could Boost Ethereum Transactions Exponentially: Arthur Hayes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ai-daos-could-boost-ethereum-transactions-exponentially-arthur-hayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 12:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DAO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263068</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of AI-powered DAOs could transform global economy.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Artificial Intelligence (AI) could potentially organize itself using a Decentralised Autonomous Organisation (DAO) structure, according to BitMEX founder Arthur Hayes.</p>
<p>Traditional companies cannot operate without certain state-sanctioned entities such as auditors, accountants, lawyers, and bankers that serve as the &#8220;cartel of trust.&#8221; But with AI slowly taking over, it&#8217;s hard to imagine how an economic organization under the technology will ensure compliance.</p>
<p>Hayes&#8217;s latest <a href="https://entrepreneurshandbook.co/moai-da798c72a83b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a>, titled &#8216;Moai,&#8217; delves into the role of AI in an organizational structure. The former exec highlighted that DAOs are reliant on public blockchains to operate and not the state.</p>
<h2>Emergence of AI DAOs</h2>
<p>A DAO framework would facilitate collaboration between AI and humans, serving as the organizational backbone that fosters growth within the AI and human economy.</p>
<p>According to Hayes, the state will not be able to exert control over AIs because it cannot technically kill or meaningfully punish such systems.</p>
<p>Such a scenario leaves no reason for an AI economic unit, i.e., an AI DAO, to follow any state-based legal norms.</p>
<p>For compliance purposes, the network substrate that underlines the DAOs will need to use smart contracts deployed and executed on public blockchains.</p>
<p>And since the state can’t exert control over DAOs, these entities will resort to fundraising and trade debt, equity, utility, etc., tokens on DEXs that are not hosted on traditional centralized exchanges (CEX).</p>
<p>This will ultimately position DEXs as what Hayes deems to be &#8220;natural monopolies,&#8221; proving as global trading venues where any being with an internet connection can interact and transact.</p>
<h2>AI DAO Hypothesis into Reality</h2>
<p>If the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ai-crypto-guide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Artificial Intelligence</a> DAOs hypothesis turns into reality, the former BitMEX boss said Ethereum transactions will grow exponentially as a result of their proliferation. This, in turn, will catalyze ETH&#8217;s value to skyrocket.</p>
<p>He also believes a few DEXs will end up having &#8220;natural monopolies&#8221; over the trading of specific types of tokens. Investors will be able to cash in on profits upon identifying such decentralized entities and purchasing their governance tokens.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, well-functioning AI DAOs are expected to gain significant traction since they play a crucial role in helping visualize the accounts of AI DAOs.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ai-daos-could-boost-ethereum-transactions-exponentially-arthur-hayes/" rel="nofollow">AI DAOs Could Boost Ethereum Transactions Exponentially: Arthur Hayes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sequoia Reduces Crypto Fund by Almost $400 Million: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sequoia-reduces-crypto-fund-by-almost-400-million-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263078</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Sequoia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Sequoia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The decision was accompanied by an equally large cut to the venture capital sector overall.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sequoia Capital, an investment firm long revered for its direct involvement with Silicon Valley’s intricate web of venture capitalists and tech sector visionaries, has decided to reduce its exposure to cryptocurrencies, according to a confidential source.</p>
<h2>A Reflection of The Market</h2>
<p>In a message to investors, Sequoia Capital announced its decision to reduce its cryptocurrency fund from $585 million to about $200 million, as <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sequoia-capital-slashes-crypto-fund-as-it-downsizes-amid-startup-crunch-f396bb0b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by the Wall Street Journal.</p>
<p>According to Sequoia, the pivot to more traditional sectors is a reflection of current market conditions, in which low-interest loans have gutted through much of the tech industries’ wild spending.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Sequoia Capital curbed crypto investments by a hefty 65% <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f43b.png" alt="🐻" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, opting for a nurturing stance on startups. Not a volatile market apathy, but strategic cognition, folks! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f331.png" alt="🌱" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4a1.png" alt="💡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CryptoInvestments?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#CryptoInvestments</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$BTC</a><a href="https://t.co/hfsAAd8jeV" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/hfsAAd8jeV</a> <a href="https://t.co/8JvtyShg0n" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/8JvtyShg0n</a></p>
<p>— Chain Review (@Chain_Review) <a href="https://twitter.com/Chain_Review/status/1684681464862892032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Seeking to avoid the fate of SVB, Sequoia has also downsized its so-called ecosystem fund, which invested in other tech sector startups, to $450 million. Previously, this fund was worth $900 million.</p>
<h2>Lower Expectations, Smaller Returns</h2>
<p>The two downsized funds were originally announced in February 2022. At the time, they were already part of a restructuring plan imposed by Sequoia’s leadership in response to crypto winter and to the first signs of a global recession.</p>
<p>However, Sequoia’s crypto (mis)adventures were merely beginning. Later that year, the company lost about $150 million when FTX collapsed, prompting the later <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/2-crypto-investors-leave-sequoia-capital-following-botched-ftx-investment-bloomberg/" data-wpel-link="internal">departure</a> of five key partners.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried, who famously decided to play League of Legends during a call with Sequoia regarding a potential investment, unsurprisingly turned out to be a letdown to the investors who “loved this founder.” They allegedly leveraged their own reputation promoting FTX, which in turn led to a vote of confidence that otherwise could have prevented the ill-fated investment.</p>
<blockquote><p>“As a result of defendants’ significant investments in the FTX entities, each was incentivized to leverage their professional reputations and media outreach capabilities to portray FTX as a trustworthy and legitimate crypto exchange.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Commenting on Sequoia’s decision, Conor Moore, a KPMG VC partner, <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/4cfd2711-315e-40bd-8ea6-1b818f65e5d8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">clarified</a> that the move was representative of the investment sector’s increasing apathy towards the tech sector – and more specifically, towards funding wild ideas, or moonshots in r/wallstreetbets parlance.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Venture investors are just a little more cautious in general,” said Conor Moore, a partner in KPMG’s venture capital practice. &#8220;There’s still money there to be invested, but the pace has slowed down because exits have all but stopped.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Fortunately for Sequoia Capital, the firm was<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sequoia-capital-paradigm-thoma-bravo-accused-of-promoting-the-legitimacy-of-ftx-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"> big enough</a> to simply take the loss from FTX and move on, going so far as to issue a rare apology to investors for the poor judgment.</p>
<p>However, the debacle seems to have understandably soured Sequoia’s view of crypto, at least for now.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sequoia-reduces-crypto-fund-by-almost-400-million-report/" rel="nofollow">Sequoia Reduces Crypto Fund by Almost $400 Million: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Crypto Millionaire&#8217;s Body Parts Found in a Suitcase: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/missing-crypto-millionaires-body-parts-found-in-a-suitcase-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 09:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263058</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Argentinian police suspect that the crypto millionaire's gory death was connected to his huge debt.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The remains of Fernando Pérez Algaba, a crypto millionaire who also ran a luxury car rental outfit, were reportedly found dismembered in a suitcase while the deceased was staying in Argentina.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Authorities suspect that the amputation was done by professionals, with an autopsy showing that he was shot before his body was cut to pieces.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Another Crypto Millionaire Found Dead</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Argentinian police have launched an investigation into the <a href="https://nypost.com/2023/07/27/millionaire-crypto-influencer-found-dismembered-in-suitcase/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">mysterious death </a>of Fernando Pérez Algaba, whose body parts were found in a suitcase over the weekend in Ingeniero Budge, a town in the province of Buenos Aires.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Algaba was reported missing on July 19 after the millionaire influencer did not return the keys to an apartment he rented for a week while in Argentina or answer his phone.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to reports, Algaba&#8217;s dismembered remains were discovered by some children whose parents took the matter to the Buenos Aires police. On getting to the scene, authorities discovered Algaba&#8217;s legs and forearm in the suitcase, another arm in the stream, and later discovered the victim&#8217;s head and torso on Wednesday, July 26.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the police are yet to uncover the motive behind Algaba&#8217;s murder, they suspect that the amputation was the work of an expert, judging from the clean cuts. An autopsy carried out also showed that the deceased was shot thrice before being chopped to pieces.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Before his death, Algaba, who was 41 years old, ran a luxury car and jet ski rental firm in Miami, the United States, before moving to Barcelona, Spain, earlier in 2023. The victim claimed to have started working since he was 14 years old selling sandwiches and later got involved with acquiring vehicles for repair and resale.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Algaba&#8217;s efforts seemed to have paid off, with the entrepreneur owning a large warehouse full of expensive cars, jet skis, and motorcycles 10 years later at the age of 24. His <a href="https://instagram.com/fernandoperezalgaba?igshid=MzRlODBiNWFlZA==" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Instagram page</a>, which has over 900,000 followers, mostly contains pictures of him in luxurious cars.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The entrepreneur was also said to be a crypto trader who operated an office in Buenos Aires with 25 employees. Algaba said he made millions through his luxury vehicle rental business and cryptocurrency trading.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Murder Suspiciously Connected to Huge Debt Pile</h2>
<p dir="ltr">However, Algaba seemed to be neck deep in debts, with his company &#8220;Motors Lettuce SRL&#8221; bouncing checks less than one year after its establishment in January 2018. This caused the businessman to accumulate what was described as an &#8220;irrevocable&#8221; debt with the Argentinian tax agency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The entrepreneur was also said to run into trouble with the Barra Bravas gang, which demanded a $40,000 loan from Algaba. A message from the victim read, &#8220;If something happens to me, everyone is already warned.&#8221; Algaba further revealed that he lost a lot of money to crypto investments.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While investigations into the murder are ongoing, police have arrested a suspect in connection with the case.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Algaba&#8217;s mysterious murder follows a wave of crypto-related deaths that happened in 2022. As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-recent-wave-of-mysterious-deaths-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, Amber Group&#8217;s co-founder, Tiantian Kullander, passed away in his sleep. Another was the billionaire crypto businessman Vyacheslav Taran, who died in a helicopter crash, and MakerDAO developer Nikolai Mushegian, who allegedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/makerdao-co-founder-nikolai-mushegian-found-dead-in-puerto-rico/" data-wpel-link="internal">drowned</a> in Puerto Rico.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/missing-crypto-millionaires-body-parts-found-in-a-suitcase-report/" rel="nofollow">Missing Crypto Millionaire&#8217;s Body Parts Found in a Suitcase: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Struggles to Maintain $29K, PEPE Down 13% Weekly (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-struggles-to-maintain-29k-pepe-down-13-weekly-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263055</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/btc_pepe_mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[GALA, INJ, and MNT have also dropped by double digits within the past seven days.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin remained relatively calm after the US Fed&#8217;s latest interest rate hike, but the past 24 hours brought a minor retracement that pushed the asset back down to just over $29,000.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have also lost some steam today, with DOGE and MATIC losing the most value from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>BTC Struggles at $29K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s week started on a negative tone as the asset failed during its Sunday conquest at $30,300. The subsequent rejection pushed it south hard, and BTC found itself dumping to a monthly low at under $29,000 on Monday.</p>
<p>The bulls managed to intervene at this point and didn&#8217;t allow any further declines. They pushed the cryptocurrency to just over $29,000 as the community prepared for the next US FOMC meeting <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-raises-rates-again-by-0-25-bitcoin-trades-flat/" data-wpel-link="internal">scheduled</a> for Wednesday.</p>
<p>As many anticipated, the US Federal Reserve increased the key interest rates by 25 bps. Unlike previous such developments, this one had<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-remains-flat-after-feds-rate-hike-xlm-soars-14-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal"> little-to-no effect</a> on BTC right off the bat. It was hours later when the asset added a few hundred dollars but was stopped from challenging $30,000.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours brought some more pain for the bulls as the cryptocurrency fell back down to just over $29,000, where it currently stands. Its market cap has fallen to $565 billion while its dominance over the alts stands still at 48.2% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263057" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263057" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263057" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-24-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263057" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>PEPE Down Hard Weekly</h2>
<p>Most altcoins are also slightly in the red on a daily scale. Ethereum, Ripple, and Binance Coin have also declined by up to 1% to $1,860, $0.7, and $240, respectively. Cardano and Litecoin have seen similar drops.</p>
<p>Dogecoin and Polygon have retraced the most from the larger-cap alts, as both assets are down by around 3%. SOL, DOT, BCH, and SHIB are also in the red now.</p>
<p>ICP is among the few exceptions on a daily scale, posting a 3% increase that has pushed it to $4.25.</p>
<p>The landscape is quite painful on a weekly scale as well. PEPE, GALA, INJ, and MNT have all dumped by somewhere between 10-15%.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has also lost some steam and struggles at $1.180 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263059" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263059" style="width: 1877px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263059" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1877" height="827" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5.png 1877w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-300x132.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-1024x451.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-768x338.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-1536x677.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-5-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1877px) 100vw, 1877px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263059" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-struggles-to-maintain-29k-pepe-down-13-weekly-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Struggles to Maintain $29K, PEPE Down 13% Weekly (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Staynex&#x2122; Partners with Huawei to Enhance Web3 Initiatives for the Travel and Hospitality Industry</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/staynex-partners-with-huawei-to-enhance-web3-initiatives-for-the-travel-and-hospitality-industry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 07:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263035</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xxx_1690462211jwVWgjAG6l.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/xxx_1690462211jwVWgjAG6l.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, July 28th, 2023] Global vacation club platform, Staynex&#x2122;, has announced a partnership with the tech giant, Huawei, to leverage Web3 technologies and enhance the travel and hospitality industry. This partnership will potentially offer users a more comprehensive travel experience with increased convenience and variety using advanced AI tools. The firm [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, July 28th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Global vacation club platform, <a href="https://staynex.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Staynex</a><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, has announced a partnership with the tech giant, <a href="https://www.huawei.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Huawei</a>, to leverage Web3 technologies and enhance the travel and hospitality industry.</p>
<p>This partnership will potentially offer users a more comprehensive travel experience with increased convenience and variety using advanced AI tools. The firm will provide travelers with a wider range of hotels and itinerary options to suit their preferences, lifestyles, and budgets. This significant development reinforces Staynex&#8217;s<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> dedication to creating superior travel solutions for a wide-ranging audience.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We anticipate that our partnership with Huawei will facilitate the creation of more solutions for the travel and hospitality industry,&#8221; states Bernard Lau, Founder and CEO of Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />. &#8220;We are keen to explore the numerous opportunities and aim to empower global travellers.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are delighted to partner with Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> to augment its platform with our cutting-edge technological tools, while also allowing us to improve our range of corporate services,” shares Rex Lei, Managing Director of Huawei Cloud Singapore. &#8221; With our expertise in cloud technology, we currently support companies across numerous industries. We are confident that this partnership will enable us to develop more efficient and advanced information and communication technology (ICT) solutions for the travel and hospitality industry.“</p></blockquote>
<p>Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, an integral component of the <a href="https://labsgroup.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">LABS Group</a> ecosystem, will offer its AI-powered Travel Solutions, supported by Huawei&#8217;s innovative technology. Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is set to introduce solutions for everyday travelers and in addition, it will offer corporate solutions designed to streamline the process of booking travel tickets for employees attending events such as conferences.</p>
<p>The partnership also includes Staynex&#8217;s<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> integration into the Huawei Marketplace, providing millions of Huawei device users with easy access to Staynex&#8217;s<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> comprehensive travel platform.</p>
<p>Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> plans to use this partnership to accelerate its expansion into the Chinese market and beyond.</p>
<h2>About Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></h2>
<p>Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, operating as part of the Labs Group Ecosystem, is a global vacation club platform aiming to reshape the travel and hospitality industry. It utilizes advanced technologies like artificial intelligence and Web3 to improve individual travel experiences and streamline corporate travel bookings. Staynex<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is committed to continuous service enhancement and global expansion, fostering a vision of making travel more accessible, efficient, and enjoyable for everyone.</p>
<p>For Partnerships &amp; Investing: <a href="mailto:partnerships@staynex.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">partnerships@staynex.com</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/staynex-partners-with-huawei-to-enhance-web3-initiatives-for-the-travel-and-hospitality-industry/" rel="nofollow">Staynex&#x2122; Partners with Huawei to Enhance Web3 Initiatives for the Travel and Hospitality Industry</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Officially Files for Dismissal of CFTC&#8217;s Case</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-officially-files-for-dismissal-of-cftcs-case/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CFTC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263027</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The 49-page document addresses the CFTC’s complaints and claims that they are unfounded.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several days ago, Binance’s legal team announced they will be pursuing the dismissal of the CFTC’s court case against them, mirroring similar actions by Coinbase and Bittrex.</p>
<p>Binance’s hefty <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767/gov.uscourts.ilnd.431767.59.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">plea</a> has now been filed and is largely based on refutations of the CFTC’s jurisdiction since neither the exchange nor its CEO reside or are headquartered in the United States.</p>
<p>The document, which is 49 pages long once annexes and other norms are applied, is far longer than the 15 pages usually allowed by such a plea. However, given the broad scope of the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-28/binance-asks-court-to-dismiss-us-derivatives-regulator-s-lawsuit" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">CFTC’s accusations</a>, Binance’s legal team found it necessary to exceed the customary limit.</p>
<h2>CFTC Has No Jurisdiction Over Either Defendant</h2>
<p>Mirroring CZ’s personal opinion expressed on Binance’s <a href="https://archive.is/qUVHt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog</a>, the document accuses the CFTC of attempting to regulate foreign entities and individuals.</p>
<p>Since Binance is not headquartered in the States, and CZ is a Canadian national with no permanent residence within the country, the company argued that it is outside of the jurisdiction of any U.S. regulatory entity.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The CFTC seeks to regulate foreign individuals and corporations that reside and operate outside the United States &#8211; outstripping the limits of its statutory authority and treading on deep-rooted principles of comity with foreign sovereigns.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Another complaint of Binance’s in the same vein is that the CFTC accused the firm of knowingly accepting orders of cryptocurrency, fiat, and other financial products on behalf of U.S. corporations or citizens – all while admitting that the end customer in these transactions is often unknown.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The complaint rarely identifies whether the supposed “U.S. customer” is a natural or corporate person, though that fact matters in determining whether a customer is a “U.S. person” under both the agency’s guidance and its regulation.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Among other rebuttals of the CFTC’s case, another salient point made by Binance’s legal team is the one against client solicitation.</p>
<h2>Binance Is an Intermediary, Not a Vendor</h2>
<p>According to lawyers for Binance, the platform is primarily a marketplace where third parties can buy and sell cryptocurrencies. Although the exchange naturally holds reserves that it can choose to sell to customers, the primary sources of cryptocurrencies sold to Binance customers are the wallets of other company users, who entered into a voluntary agreement with the third party.</p>
<p>Therefore, the defense argued that Binance cannot be accused of client solicitation. This refutation is followed up by an argument that there is no legal precedent for such an accusation against a crypto platform “for good reason.”</p>
<p>For now, no response has been provided by the court. Should Binance and CZ manage to shake the accusations brought against them by the CFTC, they will still have to contend with other <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-and-cz-will-pursue-cftc-case-dismissal/" data-wpel-link="internal">court cases</a> and investigations filed by other regulatory entities.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-officially-files-for-dismissal-of-cftcs-case/" rel="nofollow">Binance Officially Files for Dismissal of CFTC&#8217;s Case</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sui Foundation Ends Partnership With MoveEX Following Contract Violation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sui-foundation-ends-partnership-with-moveex-following-contract-violation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262881</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Sui_Network.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The foundation asked MovEX to move the entire 2.5 million SUI to a qualified custodian who will release them according to the token emission schedule.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sui Foundation, the non-profit organization behind the Sui Network, has terminated its partnership with MovEX, a decentralized exchange (DEX) and liquidity management platform, following the violation of a lockup agreement.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://blog.sui.io/understanding-sui-token-supply/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> by the Sui Foundation, MovEX moved some Sui tokens (SUI) that were subject to a contractual lockup without informing or seeking consent from the organization, sparking accusations of misrepresented emissions from the crypto community.</p>
<h2>Sui Foundation Cuts Ties With MovEX</h2>
<p>MovEx was an early contributor to Sui during its mainnet <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-faced-massive-volatility-minutes-after-mainnet-launch/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> in May, serving as a core builder for the network’s DeepBook, a shared decentralized central limit order book created for the ecosystem.</p>
<p>At the time, 5.15% of the total SUI supply was in circulation, with the rest released on a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-sui-networks-tokens-will-be-unlocked/" data-wpel-link="internal">preset schedule</a> to early contributors to maintain network stability. The tokens were subject to a lockup period in line with the release schedule.</p>
<p>In June, however, the pseudonymous Twitter user DefiSquared <a href="https://twitter.com/DefiSquared/status/1673572324145078273?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">accused</a> Sui of intentionally misrepresenting token emissions and dumping rewards from locked, non-circulating staked SUI on crypto exchange Binance.</p>
<p>Through several investigations, the Sui Foundation discovered that MovEX executed the transactions that stirred the accusations. Out of the 2.5 million SUI received as payment for contributing to DeepBook, the decentralized exchange had initiated three transactions of 625,000 SUI to three different wallets, leaving the rest in the original wallet.</p>
<p>Sui Foundation has ended its relationship with MovEX as the DEX breached the contractual lockup and failed to seek consent before initiating those transactions. Earlier this month, the foundation asked MovEX to move the 2.5 million SUI to a qualified custodian who will release them according to the token emission schedule.</p>
<h2>MovEX Reponds</h2>
<p>In response to the announcement by Sui Foundation, MovEX took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/joinMovEX/status/1684496073967140864?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">explain</a> that it had only distributed the tokens to custodian and non-custodian wallets.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We would like to express our understanding regarding the conclusion of our partnership with Sui. We deeply value the journey filled with dedication, hard work, and honors, and we are truly appreciative of the support we received from the community,” MovEX said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The Sui Foundation has assured the crypto community that “all other tokens subject to contractual lockups are held in qualified custodian accounts that have agreed to enforce the terms of such lockups.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-foundation-ends-partnership-with-moveex-following-contract-violation/" rel="nofollow">Sui Foundation Ends Partnership With MoveEX Following Contract Violation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
