<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:31:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How Low Can BTC Go Following the 11% Weekly Crash? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-low-can-btc-go-following-the-11-weekly-crash-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267524</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After a prolonged period of silence near the critical $30K threshold, the price has encountered significant rejection, resulting in a swift and rapid decline. However, the current scenario shows the price consolidating close to the crucial support range of $25K, where it could potentially find a bottom and halt further downtrends. Technical Analysis By Shayan [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a prolonged period of silence near the critical $30K threshold, the price has encountered significant rejection, resulting in a swift and rapid decline.</p>
<p>However, the current scenario shows the price consolidating close to the crucial support range of $25K, where it could potentially find a bottom and halt further downtrends.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Following a minor corrective phase, where a bearish divergence occurred between the price and the RSI indicator, Bitcoin experienced a forceful rejection and underwent a rapid drop. This recent decline caused the price to breach a significant and pivotal support area encompassing the 100-day and 200-day moving averages, indicative of an overall bearish sentiment in the market. Subsequently, the cryptocurrency dipped and arrived at the pivotal support zone of $25K.</p>
<p>However, the price action within this critical support zone carries substantial significance, as the $25K level has long served as crucial psychological support. Therefore, if it receives support and witnesses an upsurge in buying activity, market participants could potentially anticipate a reversal.</p>
<p>Conversely, without such support, the price might breach this mentioned support level, potentially triggering a cascading effect that drives it toward the notable support area at $20K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267529" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267529" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-267529 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1908231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267529" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Shifting attention to the 4-hour chart, it becomes evident that the price is confined within a static range, oscillating between the notable resistance at $30K and the significant support at $25K. Following a swift descent from the $30K resistance zone, BTC has now approached the lower threshold of the range, resting near the $25K support area.</p>
<p>Despite this decline, the $25K support level holds the potential to stave off further short-term declines due to the existing demand around this crucial range. Consequently, a positive response within this defined range could potentially pave the way for a fresh upward trajectory, propelling the price toward the substantial resistance level at $30K.</p>
<p>Conversely, if the price dips below the $25K mark once again, the market might embark on an extended bearish phase, leading to a further decline toward lower support regions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267528" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267528" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-267528 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_1908232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267528" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>The &#8220;Exchange Whale Ratio&#8221; gauges the ratio between the top 10 significant inflows and the total inflow volume on cryptocurrency exchanges. Elevated values of this metric indicate substantial funds from prominent players, commonly known as &#8220;whales,&#8221; being transferred into exchanges.</p>
<p>Presently, the Exchange Whale Ratio has surged after marking its lowest point since February 2018, simultaneously with the price experiencing a rapid decline. While a low ratio might not have an immediate impact, historical trends reveal that its rebound often exerts a negative influence on the price of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Accordingly, back in February 2018, as the ratio rebounded from an all-time low, the price of BTC hit its peak and subsequently embarked on a decline. This emphasizes that a sudden surge in the ratio could potentially indicate a downward trajectory for BTC&#8217;s price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267527" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267527" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-267527 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_whale_ratio_chart_1908231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267527" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-low-can-btc-go-following-the-11-weekly-crash-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">How Low Can BTC Go Following the 11% Weekly Crash? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase&#8217;s Incubated Base Blockchain Attracts Over 500 Scam Tokens: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-incubated-base-blockchain-attracts-over-500-scam-tokens-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:10:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267492</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/ScamAlert-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Scam tokens generated nearly $3.7 million in trading volume on decentralized exchanges on the Base network.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase recently introduced &#8220;Base&#8221; to foster a community of developers dedicated to constructing decentralized features for its users. While Base is geared toward enhancing the exchange&#8217;s utility and encouraging greater customer engagement, this new blockchain attracted more than 500 fraudulent tokens in a relatively brief period.</p>
<p>Scam token creators thrive on &#8220;hype, promise, and price and volume manipulation.&#8221; The fervor surrounding the Base network is no different in this regard. According to the New York-based crypto market integrity platform Solidus Labs, scammers have churned approximately $2 million in profits with these efforts.</p>
<h2>Scams on Coinbase-Incubated Base</h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://www.soliduslabs.com/post/scam-token-developers-create-more-than-500-scam-tokens-before-base-layer-2-launch" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> by Solidus revealed that scam tokens attracted approximately $3.7 million worth of trading volume on Base-based decentralized exchanges. In the process, the scammers managed to execute $2.7 million worth of buys, $700,000 worth of sales, and $300,000 worth of wash sales.</p>
<p>Scammers use either of the two methods to profit from their schemes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Swiftly withdrawing all liquidity from their DEX pairs once a substantial number of users had invested &#8211; totaling $1.7 million, or</li>
<li>generating an excessively large number of new coins through &#8220;minting&#8221; and subsequently selling them, causing the DEX pair to lose its Ether reserves, amounting to $300,000.</li>
</ul>
<h2>BALD Rug Pull</h2>
<p>Besides the existence of hundreds of scam coins, the researchers at Solidus observed &#8220;deceptively touted and traded&#8221; cryptocurrencies that made it to Base between mid-July and its public debut in August.</p>
<p>Base&#8217;s traction was scant when it was first opened to builders. But the likes of BALD triggered abrupt capital and user influx. This initial frenzy around the memecoin pushed prices 4,000,000% from issuance and attracted more than $68 million from traders.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-bald-truth-or-conspiracy-memecoins-suspected-links-to-alameda-and-sam-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">BALD</a> creator appeared to have raked in over $5.2 million after hyping the token on X (formerly known as Twitter) and pumping up its price on a Base-based decentralized exchange called LeetSwap.</p>
<p>Solidus representative <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-16/coinbase-coin-blockchain-base-is-flooded-with-hundreds-of-scam-crypto-tokens#xj4y7vzkg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">told</a> Bloomberg,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We encourage consumers to do their research diligently before participating in any dapp [decentralized application], on Base or any other chain, just as they would on the open internet.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Base is accessible to all users, but it is this aspect that also exposes vulnerabilities that scammers exploit. Solidus Labs analysts cautioned users against meme coins and decentralized exchanges on the layer-2 solution since funds lost to rug pulls or tokens exclusive to these DEXes offer no means for recovery or withdrawal should an exploit occur.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-incubated-base-blockchain-attracts-over-500-scam-tokens-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase&#8217;s Incubated Base Blockchain Attracts Over 500 Scam Tokens: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Mining Stocks Are Up 200% YTD, but One Has Soared Almost 400%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-up-200-ytd-but-one-has-soared-almost-400/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 16:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267493</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinWallStreet2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinWallStreet2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While several BTC mining stocks have soared significantly, one stands above all. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is down for the week, but it&#8217;s still up about 50% YTD. Meanwhile, Bitcoin mining stocks have jumped by over 200% year-to-date. One miner stock, Cipher Mining (CIFR), is up by a whopping 389% for the year so far.</p>
<p>Bitcoin price fell 10% against USD Thursday amid speculations that SpaceX might have sold its remaining holdings. That brings the most work-based cryptocurrency down to what may be a bargain price at this time in its halving cycle, at under $26,000.</p>
<p>While markets are watching crypto prices after this week&#8217;s turbulence, crypto stocks are another class of blockchain assets in the bargain bin this week, especially with their soaring YTD trendline.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miners Are Popping on Wall Street</h2>
<p>Crypto stocks are up by quite a bit more this far into 2023 than the broad stock market benchmarks. The S&amp;P 500 Index of the top 500 U.S. companies has increased by a very healthy 14% thus far in 2023.</p>
<p>The tech-focused NASDAQ Composite is up a whopping 28% for the year. The Dow Jones Industrial Average is up a paltry 4% in comparison to the other benchmarks. Meanwhile, top performers include stocks like Nvidia (219%), Meta (164%), and Tesla (117%).</p>
<p>But even those three top-performing stocks aren&#8217;t flying as high as some Bitcoin miners are, with the blockchain surging in activity this year. Two Bitcoin mining stocks, Riot Platforms Inc. (RIOT) and Marathon Digital Holdings Inc. (MARA), are trading well above 200% since January.</p>
<p>Riot is up 228%. The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-much-btc-riot-platforms-mined-in-q2/" data-wpel-link="internal">mined 1,775 BTC</a> in Q2. Marathon&#8217;s gains are also at 228%, exactly like its competitor. But since January, Cipher Mining is up by even more this week: 389%.</p>
<h2>Why BTC Mining Stocks Have Soared So Much</h2>
<p>Although it has unraveled some in 2023, the correlation between Bitcoin and stock prices has meant investors could ride market swings in the same direction, up or down, but with more leverage in long BTC positions on-chain.</p>
<p>Interestingly, long positions in Bitcoin mining stocks are like owning BTC on-chain but with even more leverage than they have over traditional stocks. Part of the reason why may be, as Nasdaq <a href="https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/better-buy%3A-bitcoin-or-bitcoin-mining-stocks" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">notes</a>:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For institutional investors that are unable to buy Bitcoin directly, getting exposure to Bitcoin mining stocks is a useful proxy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>While their enormous returns on investment this year have made Bitcoin miners attractive to stock traders, there are additional Bitcoin-specific risks to mining stocks. Nasdaq advises:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the price of Bitcoin down significantly, these miners become big money-losing operations. So, before you start buying Bitcoin mining stocks, be sure you understand the cyclical nature of these stocks.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The incredible outlier returns of mining stocks could be a leading indicator of sea change price moves ahead in Bitcoin&#8217;s future when institutional investors begin to adopt the SHA-256 hash currency in earnest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-stocks-are-up-200-ytd-but-one-has-soared-almost-400/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Mining Stocks Are Up 200% YTD, but One Has Soared Almost 400%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Figure Proves US is Lightyears Ahead of Europe on Crypto Adoption</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-figure-proves-us-is-lightyears-ahead-of-europe-on-crypto-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 13:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European Union]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266363</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A Bloomberg analyst pointed out what puts the US ahead of Europe in terms of adoption. Hint, it has something to do with BTC ETFs.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has basically been on pause since mid-June, as the asset trades range-bound since then. The exchange rate of BTC to USD remained above $29,000, with resistance at $30,000. It&#8217;s as if markets are waiting on the SEC&#8217;s spot Bitcoin ETF approvals.</p>
<p>In fact, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weird-signal-bitcoin-5-day-volatility-inversion-with-wall-st-what-does-it-mean-for-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">one metric of</a> bitcoin&#8217;s price stability touched five-year historic lows at the beginning of August. Weirdly, BTC was even less volatile than U.S. stocks briefly this month.</p>
<p>But with each new application for a spot Bitcoin ETF, there&#8217;s more bullish pressure on BTC&#8217;s chart. Institutional investors are wetting their whistle for blockchain exposure via an ETF product they can understand, with a Tradfi partner they can trust.</p>
<p>The list of spot <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-vaneck-invesco-amend-bitcoin-spot-etf-filings-following-secs-warning-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">ETF applications for Bitcoin</a> is long and growing. When the first approval comes, market watchers are expecting a big upswing in exchange prices.</p>
<h2>US Dominates World Crypto ETF Volumes</h2>
<p>Bloomberg senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas recently pointed out in a (Twitter) X post that &#8220;Every single one of the Top 15 best-performing equity ETFs this year is crypto-related.&#8221; Furthermore, Balchunas added that a spot Bitcoin ETF would send North American crypto ETF volumes to 99.5% of the global market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Every single one of the Top 15 best performing equity ETFs this year is crypto-related. <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24WGMI&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$WGMI</a> leading way w +227%. Finally attracting flows too, altho pretty modest considering these perf numbers. This is part of our monthly Crypto ETF Report via <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@JSeyff</a> &amp; <a href="https://twitter.com/SirYappityyapp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SirYappityyapp</a> <a href="https://t.co/iPIHhH82Jr" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/iPIHhH82Jr</a></p>
<p>— Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1689655154470232064?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The real stunner is that, in the first place, that figure is already 97.67%.</p>
<p>ETFs are a preferred way to get blockchain exposure for institutional and Tradfi players. This shows how far ahead of European Tradfi companies and baby boomers US investors are at taking the disruptions of the cryptocurrency industry seriously.</p>
<h2>US Tradfi Players Far More Open to Blockchain</h2>
<p>The differences in US versus European openness to blockchain and cryptocurrencies are shocking by this metric. Sophisticated European investors are nearly entirely passing on crypto ETFs despite some of the face-melting ROIs.</p>
<p>One contributing factor to this sizeable delta is that Americans have a <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbesbusinesscouncil/2022/04/13/cultural-differences-explain-the-business-chasm-between-the-us-and-europe/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">greater appetite</a> for risk in business ventures and financial investments. That&#8217;s backed by research that has found:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;People living in Germany, Austria, and the Netherlands are the most risk-averse, while those in the US, Turkey, Australia, and the UK are more accepting of risk.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Another factor may be how well the traditional American values of individual liberty and private property line up with blockchain&#8217;s free market.</p>
<p>It may be that cryptocurrency businesses and advocates in the Eurozone can find more success promoting the industry&#8217;s products by emphasizing how they align with the values of fairness, social justice, and progress.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-figure-proves-us-is-lightyears-ahead-of-europe-on-crypto-adoption/" rel="nofollow">This Figure Proves US is Lightyears Ahead of Europe on Crypto Adoption</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Michael Saylor, MicroStrategy, and Bitcoin 3 Years After</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-microstrategy-and-bitcoin-3-years-after/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 10:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Michael Saylor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266361</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[3 years after making its first historical bitcoin purchase, Michael Saylor's MicroStrategy now holds nearly 153,000 BTC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">MicroStrategy&#8217;s co-founder and executive chairman, Michael Saylor, who served as the company&#8217;s former CEO for over 30 years, continues to remain bullish on bitcoin three years after his publicly-traded business intelligence company decided to make its first BTC purchase.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Saylor has also made big price predictions for the asset, believing its value could exceed $1 million per coin.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">MicroStrategy Holds Nearly 153,000 BTC 3 Years Later</h2>
<p dir="ltr">MicroStrategy <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-of-many-nasdaq-listed-company-buys-250-million-in-bitcoin-as-inflation-hedge/" data-wpel-link="internal">made history</a> and headlines on August 11, 2020, after becoming the first publicly-traded company to purchase bitcoin. The firm initially hinted in July 2020 about its plans to invest in assets such as bitcoin or gold rather than holding cash, as a way to escape inflation, with the company later deciding to buy BTC worth $250 million and adopting it as its primary treasury reserve asset.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to Saylor at the time, who was MicroStrategy&#8217;s CEO, the decision to go for bitcoin was made because the cryptocurrency served as a better hedge against inflation and had a higher return on investment compared to other assets.</p>
<p dir="ltr">That first purchase marked the beginning of several investments amid the crypto&#8217;s volatile price movements, causing the company to hold a large BTC stash. In June 2023, Saylor announced that the business intelligence giant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-12333-btc-for-350-million-at-28k-per-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bought 12,333 BTC</a> for $347 million, making it one of the company&#8217;s largest purchases in a single quarter since Q2 2021.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As of July 31, 2023, MicroStrategy <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-another-420-btc-for-14-4-million/" data-wpel-link="internal">holds 152,800 BTC</a>, which the company said was purchased for $4.53 billion at an average purchase price of $29,672 per bitcoin. The business intelligence software firm is the largest corporate holder of bitcoin.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, in a December 2022 SEC filing, MicroStrategy revealed that it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-microstrategy-sold-704-bitcoins-on-december-22/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold</a> 704 BTC to generate tax benefits. The sale was a first for the company, with the action contrary to a previous statement by Saylor, who said MicroStrategy would never sell any of its stash.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Saylor Continues to Solidify Bitcoin Support</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Saylor is known as one of bitcoin&#8217;s biggest supporters and has continued to promote the asset as far superior to gold, calling it the &#8220;digital gold.&#8221; However, he was not always pro-bitcoin, as he predicted the asset&#8217;s imminent demise in a 2013 tweet, stating that it would suffer the same fate as online gambling.</p>
<p dir="ltr">But Saylor&#8217;s view on bitcoin has since changed, and not only has the billionaire spearheaded several BTC purchases at MicroStrategy while also making personal acquisitions, he has also made big price predictions for the number one cryptocurrency.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The MicroStrategy executive chairman in May 2022 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-go-into-the-millions-predicts-microstrategys-michael-saylor/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> BTC&#8217;s price could &#8220;go into the millions&#8221; while stating that it is the future of money. The following month, Saylor predicted that bitcoin&#8217;s price will skyrocket to $1 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Later in September 2022, the exec said the cryptocurrency could be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-sees-bitcoin-trading-at-69000-in-the-next-four-years/" data-wpel-link="internal">valued at $500,000</a> in the next 10 years if it matches the market capitalization of gold. For context, BTC&#8217;s market cap is $572.3 billion, while gold&#8217;s is currently estimated at $12.8 trillion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, Saylor seems to be unfazed by the ongoing enforcement crackdown on the crypto sector by the US SEC, stating that the regulator&#8217;s action could <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-thinks-the-sec-crackdown-could-boost-bitcoins-dominance-to-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">benefit</a> bitcoin by boosting the asset&#8217;s price and increasing its market share dominance to 80%.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Saylor, who served as MicroStrategy&#8217;s CEO for over 30 years, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-is-no-longer-the-ceo-of-microstrategy/" data-wpel-link="internal">left</a> his position in August 2022 to become the company&#8217;s executive officer, with MicroStrategy president Phong Le serving as the new CEO. The American business executive explained that his new role will help him to better focus on the firm&#8217;s &#8220;bitcoin acquisition strategy and related bitcoin advocacy initiatives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-microstrategy-and-bitcoin-3-years-after/" rel="nofollow">Michael Saylor, MicroStrategy, and Bitcoin 3 Years After</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Slips Below $26K Again, LTC, SHIB, XRP Down 20% Weekly (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-slips-below-26k-again-ltc-shib-xrp-down-20-weekly-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 08:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267514</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In contrast, KAS and HBAR have soared by double-digits in the past 24 hours. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s troubles continue as the asset has returned below $26,000 after exceeding that level yesterday following the price flash crash.</p>
<p>Most altcoins have also seen daily declines, with ETH and BNB dropping by 1.5% once more.</p>
<h2>BTC Still Below $26K</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency was stuck in a tight range between $29,200 and $29,500 for a week until a few days ago. It tried to break out toward $30,000 on Monday but was stopped in its tracks, and the subsequent rejection pushed it back south to around $29,000.</p>
<p>By Thursday, BTC had lost half a grand more, but the worst was yet to come. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-flash-crash-to-25-3k-triggers-speculation-spacex-write-down-in-focus/" data-wpel-link="internal">Speculations</a> arose that SpaceX had disposed of its remaining bitcoin stash, and the asset reacted with an immediate <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-crashed-to-25-3-but-these-altcoins-have-it-worse-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">price drop</a> that drove it all the way down to $25,300 on several exchanges.</p>
<p>This became its lowest price tag in just over two months. BTC bounced off initially and reclaimed $26,000, but another 1-2% decline in the past 24 hours has pushed it to just under that level.</p>
<p>Its market cap is close to breaking below $500 billion, while its dominance over the alts is at 48.1%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267515" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267515" style="width: 1793px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267515" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1793" height="765" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8.png 1793w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8-300x128.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8-1024x437.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8-768x328.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8-1536x655.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-8-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1793px) 100vw, 1793px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267515" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Alts Tumble Weekly</h2>
<p>Most alternative coins tumbled just as badly in the past few days, wiping more than $110 billion from the total market cap.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours have been less volatile, but still some of the largest are in the red today, including ETH and BNB. Both have declined by about 1.5% and sit at $1,660 and $215, respectively.</p>
<p>The situation is a lot worse on a weekly scale. XRP, SHIB, and LTC are among the poorest performers, declining by more than 20% since last Saturday.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, there are two impressive gainers from the top 100 alts &#8211; HBAR and KAS. Both have soared by 13-16% and HBAR has reclaimed $0.06, while KAS is above $0.04.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267516" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267516" style="width: 1864px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267516" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1864" height="729" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8.jpg 1864w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8-300x117.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8-1024x400.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8-768x300.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8-1536x601.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-8-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1864px) 100vw, 1864px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267516" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-slips-below-26k-again-ltc-shib-xrp-down-20-weekly-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">BTC Slips Below $26K Again, LTC, SHIB, XRP Down 20% Weekly (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CAIZcoin Announces Exciting Launch on Major Worldwide Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/caizcoin-announces-exciting-launch-on-major-worldwide-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 07:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267503</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/321.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/321.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] CAIZcoin, a blockchain and cryptocurrency pioneer, is excited to announce its official debut on major cryptocurrency exchanges across the world. This widely anticipated move represents a huge step forward in CAIZcoin&#8217;s mission to revolutionize how people access and interact with digital assets. CAIZcoin is a leader in innovation with [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>CAIZcoin, a blockchain and cryptocurrency pioneer, is excited to announce its official debut on major cryptocurrency exchanges across the world. This widely anticipated move represents a huge step forward in CAIZcoin&#8217;s mission to revolutionize how people access and interact with digital assets.</p>
<p>CAIZcoin is a leader in innovation with an agenda of developing a fair and ethical financial environment that could accommodate users from all walks of life. The choice to list on trustworthy exchanges demonstrates CAIZcoin&#8217;s commitment to making top-notch digital assets easily available and available to a wider audience.</p>
<p>The presence of CAIZcoin on these exchanges has several advantages for current as well as potential token holders. Investors and enthusiasts alike may now engage in the dynamic world of cryptocurrencies with ease by trading on platforms that follow the highest security standards in the industry.</p>
<p>Philippe Theunissen, CEO of the CAIZgroup, stated, &#8220;We&#8217;re proud to see CAIZcoin establishing itself on the world stage. As we work to get rid of barriers and open up opportunities to a more multicultural and ethical financial environment, this listing marks a significant turning point in our path. A wide variety of newcomers are being warmly welcomed into the CAIZcoin community.”</p>
<p>CAIZcoin continues to be dedicated to innovation, security, and transparency as the cryptocurrency industry changes. CAIZcoin has invested a great deal of attention to make sure that every aspect adheres to the highest standards of quality, working with a team of professionals and consultants in the blockchain and financial industries.</p>
<p>For traders and early participants, CAIZcoin has planned a variety of promo’s and incentives to mark this significant occasion. CAIZcoin provides an original perspective on digital assets, supported by their reputation for innovation and honesty, whether you&#8217;re an experienced crypto enthusiast or a beginner to the field.</p>
<h2>About us:</h2>
<p><a href="https://caizcoin.com/index.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Caizcoin</a> is the World&#8217;s First Islam Compliant Blockchain Ecosystem, based in the EU. Envisioned to be the bridge between the centralized and decentralized financial world.<br />
Social Links:</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/caizcoin/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/caizcoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/caizcoin_official" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/caizcoin-announces-exciting-launch-on-major-worldwide-exchanges/" rel="nofollow">CAIZcoin Announces Exciting Launch on Major Worldwide Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Australian Regulator Sentences Crypto Lender Helio for False License Claims</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/australian-regulator-sentences-crypto-lender-helio-for-false-license-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267303</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Australia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Australia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto lending platform pleaded guilty to ASIC’s charges, and the regulator considered the plea during sentencing.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) has sentenced Melbourne-based cryptocurrency lending firm Helio for falsely claiming it held an Australian credit license (ACL) in August 2019.</p>
<p>According to an official release from the ASIC, Helio was <a href="https://asic.gov.au/about-asic/news-centre/find-a-media-release/2023-releases/23-223mr-cryptocurrency-lender-sentenced-for-false-licence-claims/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">sentenced</a> to a non-conviction bond and entered into a recognizance of A$15,000 ($9,600) for 12 months on the condition of good behavior.</p>
<h2>ASIC Sentences Helio</h2>
<p>The Australian securities regulator <a href="https://asic.gov.au/about-asic/news-centre/find-a-media-release/2022-releases/22-085mr-cryptocurrency-lender-charged-for-false-australian-credit-licence-claims/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">charged</a> Helio in April 2022, accusing the firm of falsely representing in a news article on its website that it held an ACL, whereas it did not. The lender also <a href="https://www.fundingstrategies.com.au/assets/resources/Helio_Lending_secures_Cash_Flow_Investments__Final_16nov18.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">mentioned</a> in an investor update that it obtained the license through the acquisition of CashFlow Investments.</p>
<p>However, on both occasions, Helio, which offered crypto-backed loans, was neither an ACL holder nor a representative of an ACL holder, according to the ASIC. The firm’s conduct violated section 30 of the National Consumer Credit Protection Act 2009.</p>
<p>The crypto lender pleaded guilty to ASIC’s charges, and the regulator considered the plea during the sentencing. The Commission withdrew a second charge relating to alleged content on Helio’s website in February 2019 and sentenced the firm under section 19B(1)(d) of the Crimes Act 1914(Cth).</p>
<blockquote>
<p style="text-align: left;">ASIC Deputy Chair Sarah Court said: “We expect entities and individuals to provide accurate information to their customers and potential customers. Helio falsely claimed that it held an Australian Credit license, misleading their customers to believe that they had the protections afforded by such a license.”</p>
</blockquote>
<h2>ASIC’s Crackdown on Crypto Firms</h2>
<p>The ASIC has recently initiated a crackdown on several crypto firms. Helio’s sentencing comes just two weeks after the regulator sued crypto-related trading platform eToro over claims that its contract for difference (CFD) product could harm investors.</p>
<p>A CFD is a leveraged derivative product that enables users to speculate on the prices of digital assets. eToro was among the first firms to allow bitcoin trading via CFDs and later added support for other cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/australias-financial-regulator-sues-etoro-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that the Aussie regulator argued eToro’s CFD products might not have been tested properly before they were introduced to users due to their high risk and volatility.</p>
<p>The agency also estimated that roughly 20,000 eToro customers lost money between October 2021 and June 2023 while trading CFDs.The crypto lending platform pleaded guilty to ASIC’s charges, and the regulator considered the plea during sentencing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/australian-regulator-sentences-crypto-lender-helio-for-false-license-claims/" rel="nofollow">Australian Regulator Sentences Crypto Lender Helio for False License Claims</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Requests Permission To Appeal Ripple Ruling</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-requests-permission-to-appeal-ripple-ruling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267482</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC claims an appeal is justified given the grounds for "difference of opinion" on crypto's relationship with securities law between different courts. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a motion requesting permission to appeal a federal court ruling last month claiming that secondary sales of Ripple’s XRP token are not securities.</p>
<p>The agency argued that there are still “substantial grounds for difference of opinion” regarding how securities laws apply to crypto, making frequent reference to a similar case involving Terraform Labs where the judge ruled differently.</p>
<h2>Ripple Case Not Over?</h2>
<p>The motion, <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.893.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filed</a> on Friday, contested two of Judge Analisa Torres‘s rulings last month: one that “Programmatic Sales” of XRP (ex. secondary market sales) did not satisfy Howey, and another that “Other Distributions” (ex. Payments for services) also failed to do so.</p>
<blockquote><p>“There are significant grounds for difference of opinion on the correctness of both rulings,” wrote the agency. “Since this Court’s decision, another court in this district explicitly disagreed with the Order’s ruling on the Programmatic Sales.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Shortly after the Ripple ruling, Terraform Labs attempted to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-rejects-terraforms-attempt-to-capitalize-on-ripple-precedent-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">capitalize</a> with a motion to dismiss a similar SEC case against the firm, alleging securities fraud for failing to register its now failed TerraUSD (UST) stablecoin.</p>
<p>District Judge Jed Rakoff rejected the group’s reasoning, however, refusing to distinguish “institutional” and “secondary” market sales in regards to being a security. “Howey makes no such distinction,” he wrote at the time.</p>
<p>The agency referenced numerous prior cases – including its charges against Telegram and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/can-ripple-xrp-lose-against-the-sec-lawyers-debate-following-lbry-lawsuit-judgment/" data-wpel-link="internal">LBRY</a> – as proof that courts have already identified securities act violations when transactions occurred through intermediaries, including through exchanges.</p>
<blockquote><p>“In the opinion of the Terraform court, for example, the inquiry turns on what the issuer objectively invites investors to understand, and not on the method of carrying out the transaction,” argued the SEC.</p></blockquote>
<p>The agency added that the source of purchase for XRP should not affect whether Ripple had established a reasonable expectation of profit for investors – one of the core pillars defining an investment contract.</p>
<h2>Lawyers Give Their Take</h2>
<p>Bitcoin-supportive litigator Joe Carlesare expressed support for the SEC’s appeal on Friday, agreeing that a crypto issuer’s promotions equally impact both direct purchasers and secondary market buyers.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This is the economic reality of the crypto market — where most participants are relying on the team/devs to promote/develop the token,” he <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeCarlasare/status/1692614892790919367" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>On the other hand, XRP supportive lawyer Sandy Seth called the SEC’s position “utterly ridiculous,” given that the agency didn’t appeal Torres’s ruling that XRP itself is a security.</p>
<blockquote><p>“So if XRP is not a security how can sales of XRP be a sales of a security?” he <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoDukeji/status/1692651462264750313" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">asked</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-requests-permission-to-appeal-ripple-ruling/" rel="nofollow">SEC Requests Permission To Appeal Ripple Ruling</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Judge Grants SEC&#8217;s Motion to Interrogate Terra Labs Co-founder Daniel Shin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-judge-grants-secs-motion-to-interrogate-terra-labs-co-founder-daniel-shin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267340</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Terra_Lawsuit.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Terra_Lawsuit.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kwon was arrested in Montenegro while attempting to travel to Dubai using forged documents in March this year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A United States judge has ruled that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can seek assistance from the South Korean government in interviewing Daniel Shin, co-founder of Terraform Labs, along with Do Kwon.</p>
<p>US District Judge Jed Rakoff ruled on Thursday that the SEC is permitted to utilize a procedure outlined in a 1970 treaty that regulates international evidence-gathering requests. Despite denying any misconduct, Kwon did not contest SEC&#8217;s request.</p>
<ul>
<li>As part of the <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66820843/45/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-terraform-labs-pte-ltd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">motion</a> granted by Judge Rakoff, the SEC also intends to obtain evidence from Chai Corp., the Seoul-based payments company founded by Kwon.</li>
<li>The move is part of the SEC&#8217;s strategy to validate the accusations made in the lawsuit against Terraform and its former CEO.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66820843/45/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-terraform-labs-pte-ltd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">lawsuit</a>, filed in February by the SEC, accuses TFL and Kwon of orchestrating a multi-billion dollar crypto asset securities fraud involving the now-defunct algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD and other alleged crypto securities.</li>
<li>The relationship between Chai and Terra has been a bone of contention. Several reports have hinted that Kwon may have overstated the extent and duration of the relationship between Terra and the e-commerce system.</li>
<li>The SEC made a startling allegation that Chai Payments did not use the Terraform blockchain to process and settle payments as per the partnership deal of 2019.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Rather, Defendants deceptively replicated Chai payments onto the Terraform blockchain, in order to make it appear that they were occurring on the Terraform blockchain, when, in fact, Chai payments were made through traditional means.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In addition to the SEC lawsuit, Kwon is facing criminal charges in the US as well as in South Korea.</li>
<li>The disgraced exec had previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-sorry-for-cocky-tweets-takes-full-responsibility-for-terras-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">stated</a> that the charges leveled against him by the prosecutors of his home country are &#8220;politically motivated.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-judge-grants-secs-motion-to-interrogate-terra-labs-co-founder-daniel-shin/" rel="nofollow">US Judge Grants SEC&#8217;s Motion to Interrogate Terra Labs Co-founder Daniel Shin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
