<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 04:11:01 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ex-Ethereum Miner CoreWeave Raises $221M in Series B]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/ex-ethereum-miner-coreweave-raises-221m-in-series-b-update</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coreweave-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coreweave-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coreweave-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/ex-ethereum-miner-coreweave-raises-221m-in-series-b-update</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">CoreWeave, a specialized cloud provider, recently announced the successful completion of a $221 million Series B funding round. This comes after the company previously raised $50 million from lead investor Magnetar Capital in November 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The latest round saw contributions from major silicon design firm NVIDIA, Nat Friedman, and Daniel Gross, with Magnetar Capital taking lead. The funds raised are set for allocation for the purpose of expanding CoreWeave's cloud infrastructure for massive computational workloads such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, visual effects, rendering, batch processing, and pixel streaming. According to CEO and co-founder Michael Intrato, NVIDIA's support will prove instrumental in helping the company continue to scale its operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Established in 2017, CoreWeave utilizes clourd technology to scale graphics processing unit (GPU) computational resources, offering solutions it claims are "35 times faster and 80% less expensive" than competitor offerings. Initially, the firm began as an Ethereum miner, using GPUs to verify transactions on the previously proof-of-work blockchain.</p>
Why the transition?
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The transition of companies like CoreWeave from focusing on crypto and blockchain to artificial intelligence (AI) and related technologies can be attributed to various factors, including market trends, technological developments, and the growth potential in AI-driven industries.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This shift is also indicative of the increasing competition in the crypto and blockchain landscape. As more businesses and startups emerge in this space, companies that initially built their foundation in crypto and blockchain technology may find it chall;enging to maintain their edge. By diversifying into AI and other emerging technologies, they can explore new opportunities and tap into different market segments, thereby mitigating the risks associated with relying solely on the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Technological developments also play a significant role in this shift. As the capabilities of AI and machine learning (ML) continue to advance, their applications in various industries are growing exponentially. Companies like CoreWeave can leverage their existing expertise in computational resources and infrastructure, which are essential for both blockchain and AI, to cater to the growing demand for high-performance computing in AI-driven industries.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"AI has reached an inflection point, and we&rsquo;re seeing accelerated interest in AI computing infrastructure from startups to major enterprises,&rdquo; shares Manuvir Das, Vice President of Enterprise Computing at NVIDIA. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">NVIDIA itself has made some harsh statements, comparing crypto to AI.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another reason for this shift is the changing landscape of blockchain technology itself. For instance, Ethereum, one of the most popular blockchain platforms, has transitioned from a proof-of-work (PoW) consensus mechanism to a proof-of-stake (PoS) model. This change has rendered Ethereum mining unattractively less profitable, and alongside it, the use mining GPUs became unfit, affecting companies like CoreWeave which initially focused on crypto mining.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">CoreWeave's latest funding will facilitate the expansion of its specialized cloud infrastructure for compute-intensive workloads, including AI and machine learning, visual effects, rendering, batch processing, and pixel streaming. This strategy enables CoreWeave to deliver purpose-built solutions capable of outperforming larger, more generalized cloud providers. The new capital will also support the opening of two new U.S.-based data centers this year, bringing CoreWeave's total North America-based data centers to five.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;CoreWeave&rsquo;s innovative, agile and customizable product offering is well-situated to service this demand and the company is consequently experiencing explosive growth to support it. We are proud to collaborate with NVIDIA in supporting CoreWeave&rsquo;s next phase of growth as it continues to bolster its already strong positioning in the marketplace," shares Ernie Rogers, COO at Magnetar.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the rise in demand for generative AI technology, CoreWeave is poised to capitalize on this burgeoning market. Its partnership with industry leaders such as NVIDIA and Magnetar Capital is key to bolstering its efforts at scaling and expansion, positioning the company to become a significant player in the rapidly evolving world of AI and cloud-native technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">CoreWeave, a specialized cloud provider, recently announced the successful completion of a $221 million Series B funding round. This comes after the company previously raised $50 million from lead investor Magnetar Capital in November 2021.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The latest round saw contributions from major silicon design firm NVIDIA, Nat Friedman, and Daniel Gross, with Magnetar Capital taking lead. The funds raised are set for allocation for the purpose of expanding CoreWeave's cloud infrastructure for massive computational workloads such as artificial intelligence, machine learning, visual effects, rendering, batch processing, and pixel streaming. According to CEO and co-founder Michael Intrato, NVIDIA's support will prove instrumental in helping the company continue to scale its operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Established in 2017, CoreWeave utilizes clourd technology to scale graphics processing unit (GPU) computational resources, offering solutions it claims are "35 times faster and 80% less expensive" than competitor offerings. Initially, the firm began as an Ethereum miner, using GPUs to verify transactions on the previously proof-of-work blockchain.</p>
Why the transition?
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The transition of companies like CoreWeave from focusing on crypto and blockchain to artificial intelligence (AI) and related technologies can be attributed to various factors, including market trends, technological developments, and the growth potential in AI-driven industries.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This shift is also indicative of the increasing competition in the crypto and blockchain landscape. As more businesses and startups emerge in this space, companies that initially built their foundation in crypto and blockchain technology may find it chall;enging to maintain their edge. By diversifying into AI and other emerging technologies, they can explore new opportunities and tap into different market segments, thereby mitigating the risks associated with relying solely on the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Technological developments also play a significant role in this shift. As the capabilities of AI and machine learning (ML) continue to advance, their applications in various industries are growing exponentially. Companies like CoreWeave can leverage their existing expertise in computational resources and infrastructure, which are essential for both blockchain and AI, to cater to the growing demand for high-performance computing in AI-driven industries.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"AI has reached an inflection point, and we&rsquo;re seeing accelerated interest in AI computing infrastructure from startups to major enterprises,&rdquo; shares Manuvir Das, Vice President of Enterprise Computing at NVIDIA. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">NVIDIA itself has made some harsh statements, comparing crypto to AI.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another reason for this shift is the changing landscape of blockchain technology itself. For instance, Ethereum, one of the most popular blockchain platforms, has transitioned from a proof-of-work (PoW) consensus mechanism to a proof-of-stake (PoS) model. This change has rendered Ethereum mining unattractively less profitable, and alongside it, the use mining GPUs became unfit, affecting companies like CoreWeave which initially focused on crypto mining.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">CoreWeave's latest funding will facilitate the expansion of its specialized cloud infrastructure for compute-intensive workloads, including AI and machine learning, visual effects, rendering, batch processing, and pixel streaming. This strategy enables CoreWeave to deliver purpose-built solutions capable of outperforming larger, more generalized cloud providers. The new capital will also support the opening of two new U.S.-based data centers this year, bringing CoreWeave's total North America-based data centers to five.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;CoreWeave&rsquo;s innovative, agile and customizable product offering is well-situated to service this demand and the company is consequently experiencing explosive growth to support it. We are proud to collaborate with NVIDIA in supporting CoreWeave&rsquo;s next phase of growth as it continues to bolster its already strong positioning in the marketplace," shares Ernie Rogers, COO at Magnetar.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the rise in demand for generative AI technology, CoreWeave is poised to capitalize on this burgeoning market. Its partnership with industry leaders such as NVIDIA and Magnetar Capital is key to bolstering its efforts at scaling and expansion, positioning the company to become a significant player in the rapidly evolving world of AI and cloud-native technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Société Générale Introduces Euro-pegged Stablecoin On Ethereum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/societe-generale-introduces-euro-pegged-stablecoin-on-ethereum-update</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/societe-generale-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/societe-generale-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/societe-generale-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/societe-generale-introduces-euro-pegged-stablecoin-on-ethereum-update</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale Forge (SG Forge), the digital asset subsidiary of the prominent French banking firm Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale, has unveiled a new stablecoin, CoinVertible ($EURCV), pegged on the Euro. The stablecoin was launched on the Ethereum blockchain, and will be exclusively available for qualified institutional clients.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale has not disclosed the requirements for qualifying to access the $EURCV stablecoin, only stating that it has pre-qualified institutional clients who have passed for its KYC verification process. The launch can be seen as a response to the growing demand for an on-chain asset that can be used for cross-border settlements. In effect, this bridges a gap between traditional capital markets and the digital asset management, particularly those linked in decentralized finance and the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The stablecoin also aims to offer new solutions for corporate treasury management, cash flow and on-chain liquidity management, as well as cash pookling initiatives for funding and refinancing. However, the new stablecoin was met with a certain degree of criticism from blockchain developers, highlighting some concerning traits inside the contract code.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A software engineer known as Cygaar has recently discovered that the stablecoin could potentially allow the bank to seize and burn all its users' funds through certain functions in its smart contract. Cygaar criticized the bank's choice of system, stating that Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale would have been better off using JPMorgan's Onyx or an internal database for a centralized settlement layer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Origin Protocol developer Scott Mitchell expressed skepticism about the stablecoin's feasibility on Ethereum from an economic perspective. He argued that even with batch validation and low gas costs, the system would still be too expensive at scale.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another developer, 0xfoobar, pointed out that the code requires every ERC20 transfer to be approved by the centralized registrar in a separate Ethereum transaction before it can be processed.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Pseudonymous smart contract engineer alephv.eth also drew attention to this issue, noting that the bank coded the system in such a way that it necessitates the whitelisting of all users and the processing of all user transfers and ERC20 approvals before executing the "transferFrom" function. This could significantly slow down the transaction speed for the stablecoin and complicate the process.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As concerns mount over the EUR CoinVertible smart contract's design and functionality, it remains to be seen how Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale-Forge will address these issues and whether the stablecoin will gain traction among institutional clients given the issues highlighted by blockchain developers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The EURCV stablecoin will be traded under the ticker symbol EURCV, accessible only to investors who have been onboarded by Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale through its Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) procedures. In the coming weeks, SG-Forge CEO Jean-Marc Stenger will assess the interest of prospective clients and address their questiopns as part of the gradual adoption process.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The newly introduced stablecoin is designed to adhere to major market standards, including the open-source interoperability and securitization framework known as Compliant Architecture for Security Token (CAST). SG-Forge emphasizes that it will guarantee the "complete segregation" of the collateral assets backing the value of the stablecoins from the issuer. According to the bank, this will be coupled with daily transparency reports and collateral positions to ensure the utmost integrity.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The EUR CoinVertible smart contract has undergone auditing by professional services network PwC. Law firm White &amp; Case has advised SG-Forge on the issuance of the stablecoin, while the role of the fiduciary is entrusted to Equitis Gestion, a private equity firm regulated by the French financial regulator, the Autorit&eacute; des March&eacute;s Financiers (AMF).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Jean-Marc Stenger, SG-Forge's CEO, is optimistic about the potential of stablecoins built under a banking-grade structure in bolstering trust and confidence in the crypto ecosystem, sharing that:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;This issuance is a major step in SG-Forge&rsquo;s roadmap to deliver innovative solutions to its clients, either real-money institutions and corporates or entities of the crypto industry, and to facilitate the emergence of new market infrastructures based on blockchain.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale, which operates as one of France's largest banks by volume and assets held, has been increasingly involved in crypto and blockchain-related implementations over the past few years. In September 2022, the bank introduced custodial services for crypto fund managers through its Security Services subsidiary. The bank has also been experimenting with issuing security tokens on blockchains such as Tezos.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale Forge (SG Forge), the digital asset subsidiary of the prominent French banking firm Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale, has unveiled a new stablecoin, CoinVertible ($EURCV), pegged on the Euro. The stablecoin was launched on the Ethereum blockchain, and will be exclusively available for qualified institutional clients.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale has not disclosed the requirements for qualifying to access the $EURCV stablecoin, only stating that it has pre-qualified institutional clients who have passed for its KYC verification process. The launch can be seen as a response to the growing demand for an on-chain asset that can be used for cross-border settlements. In effect, this bridges a gap between traditional capital markets and the digital asset management, particularly those linked in decentralized finance and the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The stablecoin also aims to offer new solutions for corporate treasury management, cash flow and on-chain liquidity management, as well as cash pookling initiatives for funding and refinancing. However, the new stablecoin was met with a certain degree of criticism from blockchain developers, highlighting some concerning traits inside the contract code.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A software engineer known as Cygaar has recently discovered that the stablecoin could potentially allow the bank to seize and burn all its users' funds through certain functions in its smart contract. Cygaar criticized the bank's choice of system, stating that Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale would have been better off using JPMorgan's Onyx or an internal database for a centralized settlement layer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Origin Protocol developer Scott Mitchell expressed skepticism about the stablecoin's feasibility on Ethereum from an economic perspective. He argued that even with batch validation and low gas costs, the system would still be too expensive at scale.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Another developer, 0xfoobar, pointed out that the code requires every ERC20 transfer to be approved by the centralized registrar in a separate Ethereum transaction before it can be processed.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Pseudonymous smart contract engineer alephv.eth also drew attention to this issue, noting that the bank coded the system in such a way that it necessitates the whitelisting of all users and the processing of all user transfers and ERC20 approvals before executing the "transferFrom" function. This could significantly slow down the transaction speed for the stablecoin and complicate the process.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As concerns mount over the EUR CoinVertible smart contract's design and functionality, it remains to be seen how Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale-Forge will address these issues and whether the stablecoin will gain traction among institutional clients given the issues highlighted by blockchain developers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The EURCV stablecoin will be traded under the ticker symbol EURCV, accessible only to investors who have been onboarded by Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale through its Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) procedures. In the coming weeks, SG-Forge CEO Jean-Marc Stenger will assess the interest of prospective clients and address their questiopns as part of the gradual adoption process.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The newly introduced stablecoin is designed to adhere to major market standards, including the open-source interoperability and securitization framework known as Compliant Architecture for Security Token (CAST). SG-Forge emphasizes that it will guarantee the "complete segregation" of the collateral assets backing the value of the stablecoins from the issuer. According to the bank, this will be coupled with daily transparency reports and collateral positions to ensure the utmost integrity.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The EUR CoinVertible smart contract has undergone auditing by professional services network PwC. Law firm White &amp; Case has advised SG-Forge on the issuance of the stablecoin, while the role of the fiduciary is entrusted to Equitis Gestion, a private equity firm regulated by the French financial regulator, the Autorit&eacute; des March&eacute;s Financiers (AMF).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Jean-Marc Stenger, SG-Forge's CEO, is optimistic about the potential of stablecoins built under a banking-grade structure in bolstering trust and confidence in the crypto ecosystem, sharing that:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;This issuance is a major step in SG-Forge&rsquo;s roadmap to deliver innovative solutions to its clients, either real-money institutions and corporates or entities of the crypto industry, and to facilitate the emergence of new market infrastructures based on blockchain.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Soci&eacute;t&eacute; G&eacute;n&eacute;rale, which operates as one of France's largest banks by volume and assets held, has been increasingly involved in crypto and blockchain-related implementations over the past few years. In September 2022, the bank introduced custodial services for crypto fund managers through its Security Services subsidiary. The bank has also been experimenting with issuing security tokens on blockchains such as Tezos.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flow Secures $3M Seed Funding To Build A Rollup Centric NFT Ecosystem.]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/flow-secures-3m-seed-funding-to-build-a-rollup-centric-nft-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Screen_Shot_2023-04-13_at_114219_AM_1681404158wdPnkai1Kv.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Screen_Shot_2023-04-13_at_114219_AM_1681404158wdPnkai1Kv.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Screen_Shot_2023-04-13_at_114219_AM_1681404158wdPnkai1Kv.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:25:14 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/flow-secures-3m-seed-funding-to-build-a-rollup-centric-nft-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, United States, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Introducing Flow: The Game-Changing NFT Ecosystem Set to Revolutionize the NFT Market. Aggregator Beta Launches on Ethereum Mainnet. Groundbreaking AI and Rollup-Centric Roadmap Unveiled; Anticipated Token Launch on April 30.</p><p>Flow&rsquo;s aggregator makes NFT bidding a breeze with their groundbreaking "place bid once, buy from everywhere" technology.&nbsp;Flow's powerful order matching and execution engines provide users a great UX while protecting them from frontrunners and unnecessary gas fees by routing transactions via Flashbots. With a $3M seed funding round led by Nima Capital and participation from Shima Capital and other industry heavyweights, Flow is poised to take the NFT world by storm.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Flow is a great example of what people can build on top of Reservoir which aggregates liquidity from all marketplaces&rdquo; said Peter Watts, founder of Reservoir.<p>Developed by a team led by an ex-Googler and ex-Binance Labs incubee, Flow will soon integrate AI into its platform such as LLM-based NFT analytics solutions, cutting-edge agents to automate trading and tools for the community to create and deploy NFTs. The developers' smart contracts already support the seamless automation of NFT trading actions.</p><p>As the blockchain world moves towards a modular, plug-and-play approach, Flow is perfectly positioned to create a modular NFT ecosystem.</p>"We are entering a modular world where execution environments, data availability, consensus and transaction sequencing are moving towards a plug-and-play model. NFT platforms built on this modular stack can leverage shared security from an underlying L1 while building fast, low cost NFT trading infrastructure and creator tooling. Flow's matching and execution engines are well positioned for this future" said nneverlander, the project&rsquo;s founder.<p>Flow is currently available on the Goerli testnet and in beta on the Ethereum mainnet. Those interested in contributing to the success of Flow can consider joining the ambassador program, which provides rewards for participation. This could be an opportunity to be a part of the future.</p><p>Users can stay updated on the much-anticipated token launch of Flow by following Flow's journey on Twitter and joining the conversation on Discord. By following, users can get more information about the platform and its developments.</p><p>About Flow</p><p>Flow is a rollup-centric NFT ecosystem built for the modular future. Developed by a team with Google and Binance Labs backgrounds, Flow offers powerful order matching, execution engines, and LLM-based NFT analytics. As the blockchain world moves towards a modular, plug-and-play approach, Flow is well poised to create an NFT ecosystem by leveraging cutting edge tech capabilities offered by AI and the modular blockchain stack.</p>ContactFounderFlow teamFlowa@flow.so]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco, United States, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Introducing Flow: The Game-Changing NFT Ecosystem Set to Revolutionize the NFT Market. Aggregator Beta Launches on Ethereum Mainnet. Groundbreaking AI and Rollup-Centric Roadmap Unveiled; Anticipated Token Launch on April 30.</p><p>Flow&rsquo;s aggregator makes NFT bidding a breeze with their groundbreaking "place bid once, buy from everywhere" technology.&nbsp;Flow's powerful order matching and execution engines provide users a great UX while protecting them from frontrunners and unnecessary gas fees by routing transactions via Flashbots. With a $3M seed funding round led by Nima Capital and participation from Shima Capital and other industry heavyweights, Flow is poised to take the NFT world by storm.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Flow is a great example of what people can build on top of Reservoir which aggregates liquidity from all marketplaces&rdquo; said Peter Watts, founder of Reservoir.<p>Developed by a team led by an ex-Googler and ex-Binance Labs incubee, Flow will soon integrate AI into its platform such as LLM-based NFT analytics solutions, cutting-edge agents to automate trading and tools for the community to create and deploy NFTs. The developers' smart contracts already support the seamless automation of NFT trading actions.</p><p>As the blockchain world moves towards a modular, plug-and-play approach, Flow is perfectly positioned to create a modular NFT ecosystem.</p>"We are entering a modular world where execution environments, data availability, consensus and transaction sequencing are moving towards a plug-and-play model. NFT platforms built on this modular stack can leverage shared security from an underlying L1 while building fast, low cost NFT trading infrastructure and creator tooling. Flow's matching and execution engines are well positioned for this future" said nneverlander, the project&rsquo;s founder.<p>Flow is currently available on the Goerli testnet and in beta on the Ethereum mainnet. Those interested in contributing to the success of Flow can consider joining the ambassador program, which provides rewards for participation. This could be an opportunity to be a part of the future.</p><p>Users can stay updated on the much-anticipated token launch of Flow by following Flow's journey on Twitter and joining the conversation on Discord. By following, users can get more information about the platform and its developments.</p><p>About Flow</p><p>Flow is a rollup-centric NFT ecosystem built for the modular future. Developed by a team with Google and Binance Labs backgrounds, Flow offers powerful order matching, execution engines, and LLM-based NFT analytics. As the blockchain world moves towards a modular, plug-and-play approach, Flow is well poised to create an NFT ecosystem by leveraging cutting edge tech capabilities offered by AI and the modular blockchain stack.</p>ContactFounderFlow teamFlowa@flow.so]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Orbiting 28340 - 22 April 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-28340-22-april-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-april-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-april-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-april-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bitcoin-price-analysis-orbiting-28340-22-april-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 28340:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 22 April 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained under pressure early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 28340.37 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broad appreciating range from 19568.52 to 31050.&nbsp;&nbsp; The pair was unable to sustain a recent brief rebound to the 28371.88 area and extended the sell-off to the 27815 area.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 28479.91 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 30500 area.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 27758, 27283, 27119, 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical resistance include the 29159, 29383, 29408, 29657, 29701, 29965, 30012, 30413, and 30472 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical support include the 27370, 26664, 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, and 21415 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28407.77 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28692.51.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;27283.59/ 26533.04/ 25604.51 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Orbiting 28340:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 22 April 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained under pressure early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 28340.37 area, representing the 23.6% retracement of the broad appreciating range from 19568.52 to 31050.&nbsp;&nbsp; The pair was unable to sustain a recent brief rebound to the 28371.88 area and extended the sell-off to the 27815 area.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 28479.91 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 30500 area.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 27758, 27283, 27119, 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical resistance include the 29159, 29383, 29408, 29657, 29701, 29965, 30012, 30413, and 30472 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical support include the 27370, 26664, 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, and 21415 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 28407.77 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 28692.51.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;27283.59/ 26533.04/ 25604.51 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sparklo (SPRK) to the Forefront as Solana (SOL) and Binance Coin (BNB) Face Declines]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/sparklo-sprk-to-the-forefront-as-solana-sol-and-binance-coin-bnb-face-declines</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160540.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160540.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160540.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/sparklo-sprk-to-the-forefront-as-solana-sol-and-binance-coin-bnb-face-declines</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">As the cryptocurrency market continues to experience fluctuations, investors are increasingly seeking more stable and promising alternatives. Amid the downtrends observed in established coins such as Solana (SOL) and Binance Coin (BNB), Sparklo is a shining light for those seeking refuge from market volatility. </p>
<p class="s7">This innovative platform offers a unique approach to investment opportunities, capturing the attention of investors looking for the next big thing in the crypto space. </p>
<p class="s9">Solana (SOL) in Crisis: Investors Lose Trust in the &ldquo;Ethereum Killer&rdquo;</p>
<p class="s7">Solana (SOL), once heralded as the &ldquo;Ethereum Killer,&rdquo; is now facing a severe crisis as investors and users lose trust in the platform. Despite high anticipation, Solana (SOL) has suffered a steep decline in value, dropping from an all-time high of $250 in late November 2021 to under $10. Solana (SOL) dramatic downfall has been attributed to a combination of factors, including technical problems and security flaws that have severely impacted investor confidence in the project.</p>
<p class="s7">One of the primary causes of Solana (SOL) decline has been its security issues, which have manifested in a series of hacks and vulnerabilities over recent months. Solana (SOL) breaches have raised serious concerns about the reliability and safety of the blockchain platform, further eroding investor confidence.</p>
<p class="s9">Binance Coin (BNB) Struggles Amidst Controversies and Investor Skepticism </p>
<p class="s7">Binance Coin (BNB), once considered a dominant player in the world of digital asset marketplaces, has experienced a tumultuous few months. Following the collapse of rival exchange FTX, Binance Coin (BNB) seemed to be in an advantageous position, but the subsequent fallout brought unwelcome attention to the platform&rsquo;s finances, leading to a decline of over 50% in the value of Binance Coin (BNB) this year.</p>
<p class="s7">Despite Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao&rsquo;s attempts to alleviate concerns among users and investors by attributing the value decline to external factors and scare tactics, larger withdrawals and increasing apprehensions about the Binance Coin (BNB) financial stability have surfaced in recent weeks, alongside reports of money laundering charges. It is time to look beyind Binance Coin (BNB) and Solana (SOL).</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) Presale offers good value for money</p>
<p class="s7">Investing in cryptocurrency can be an excellent way to achieve financial growth, but finding the right opportunity can be challenging. With the sheer number of projects out there, it can be hard to differentiate between those with genuine potential and those that are just riding the hype train. However, Sparklo seems to be one of the former, a project with a unique proposition that is poised to offer investors significant value for their money.</p>
<p class="s7">With a presale priced at just $0.015 that offers attractive tokenomics, including a total maximum supply of 1,000,000,000 tokens, 60% of which is available in the presale, Sparklo (SPRK) is an investment opportunity that should not be overlooked. In addition, the team behind Sparklo (SPRK) has demonstrated its commitment to building a successful platform through its rigorous development process and partnerships with established players in the crypto space.</p>
<p class="s7">Investors can also rest assured that the Sparklo (SPRK) project has undergone an independent audit to ensure that it is both secure and reliable. This is a crucial factor in the world of cryptocurrency, where security breaches and hacks can have devastating consequences for investors.</p>
<p class="s7">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s7">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">As the cryptocurrency market continues to experience fluctuations, investors are increasingly seeking more stable and promising alternatives. Amid the downtrends observed in established coins such as Solana (SOL) and Binance Coin (BNB), Sparklo is a shining light for those seeking refuge from market volatility. </p>
<p class="s7">This innovative platform offers a unique approach to investment opportunities, capturing the attention of investors looking for the next big thing in the crypto space. </p>
<p class="s9">Solana (SOL) in Crisis: Investors Lose Trust in the &ldquo;Ethereum Killer&rdquo;</p>
<p class="s7">Solana (SOL), once heralded as the &ldquo;Ethereum Killer,&rdquo; is now facing a severe crisis as investors and users lose trust in the platform. Despite high anticipation, Solana (SOL) has suffered a steep decline in value, dropping from an all-time high of $250 in late November 2021 to under $10. Solana (SOL) dramatic downfall has been attributed to a combination of factors, including technical problems and security flaws that have severely impacted investor confidence in the project.</p>
<p class="s7">One of the primary causes of Solana (SOL) decline has been its security issues, which have manifested in a series of hacks and vulnerabilities over recent months. Solana (SOL) breaches have raised serious concerns about the reliability and safety of the blockchain platform, further eroding investor confidence.</p>
<p class="s9">Binance Coin (BNB) Struggles Amidst Controversies and Investor Skepticism </p>
<p class="s7">Binance Coin (BNB), once considered a dominant player in the world of digital asset marketplaces, has experienced a tumultuous few months. Following the collapse of rival exchange FTX, Binance Coin (BNB) seemed to be in an advantageous position, but the subsequent fallout brought unwelcome attention to the platform&rsquo;s finances, leading to a decline of over 50% in the value of Binance Coin (BNB) this year.</p>
<p class="s7">Despite Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao&rsquo;s attempts to alleviate concerns among users and investors by attributing the value decline to external factors and scare tactics, larger withdrawals and increasing apprehensions about the Binance Coin (BNB) financial stability have surfaced in recent weeks, alongside reports of money laundering charges. It is time to look beyind Binance Coin (BNB) and Solana (SOL).</p>
<p class="s9">Sparklo (SPRK) Presale offers good value for money</p>
<p class="s7">Investing in cryptocurrency can be an excellent way to achieve financial growth, but finding the right opportunity can be challenging. With the sheer number of projects out there, it can be hard to differentiate between those with genuine potential and those that are just riding the hype train. However, Sparklo seems to be one of the former, a project with a unique proposition that is poised to offer investors significant value for their money.</p>
<p class="s7">With a presale priced at just $0.015 that offers attractive tokenomics, including a total maximum supply of 1,000,000,000 tokens, 60% of which is available in the presale, Sparklo (SPRK) is an investment opportunity that should not be overlooked. In addition, the team behind Sparklo (SPRK) has demonstrated its commitment to building a successful platform through its rigorous development process and partnerships with established players in the crypto space.</p>
<p class="s7">Investors can also rest assured that the Sparklo (SPRK) project has undergone an independent audit to ensure that it is both secure and reliable. This is a crucial factor in the world of cryptocurrency, where security breaches and hacks can have devastating consequences for investors.</p>
<p class="s7">Find out more about the presale:</p>
<p class="s7">Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Tank Post Wormhole Hack, Analysts Predicts Top 100 Spot for Sparklo (SPRK)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/solana-sol-tank-post-wormhole-hack-analysts-predicts-top-100-spot-for-sparklo-sprk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160043.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160043.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-160043.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/solana-sol-tank-post-wormhole-hack-analysts-predicts-top-100-spot-for-sparklo-sprk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">One of the major flaws of decentralized finance (DeFi) has been the security of digital assets held in their vaults. The DeFi sector has been the constant target of cybercriminals, who are often successful, stealing millions in crypto.</p>
<p class="s7">Updates from Wormhole, one of the largest bridges between Solana and other blockchains, show that the loss from the hack makes it the second-largest DeFi hack on record. As a result, Solana (SOL) has continued to tank. </p>
<p class="s7">On the brighter side of DeFi, analysts have predicted possible use cases of Sparklo, combined with the momentum it is building could make the project a top 100 crypto within the first year of its launch.</p>
<p class="s9">Solana (SOL) Tanks 8% as Wormhole Hack Hit $320 Million</p>
<p class="s7">The price of Solana (SOL) has tanked 8% in the last 24 hours as reports show that the losses of the Wormhole hack surpassed $320 million &ndash; now making it the second-largest DeFi hack on record.</p>
<p class="s7">The attack on Wormhole started with the hacker&rsquo;s Solana account. After the attack, the hacker then swapped the SOL in his account for USDCet (Wormhole USDC), before bringing it across to Ethereum to move the funds.</p>
<p class="s7">The losses of Solana (SOL) are compounded by a market-wide sell-off, which has seen 3% of the global crypto market cap lost in just 24 hours. With today&rsquo;s loss, Solana (SOL) now trades at $23, despite trading at over $110 year-over-year.</p>
<p class="s7">If Solana (SOL) fails to hold the $23 level, the price of the asset could fall as low as $20. However, if it manages to find enough bullish momentum in the coming days, then Solana (SOL) could retest the $25 level.</p>
<p class="s9">Analysts Predict Top 100 Spot for Sparklo</p>
<p class="s7">Despite the broader crypto markets suffering from bearish sentiments at the moment, analysts predict that Sparklo &ndash; which has been gaining grounds as an alternative investment platform &ndash; could outperform the market and claim a top 100 spot within a year of its launch. </p>
<p class="s7">Analysts are bullish about the prospects of Sparklo because of its unique, problem-solving platform which will allow users to be able to purchase rare and precious metals, such as silver, gold, and platinum in form of fractional NFTs, meaning you can own gold without needing to buy an entire bar. </p>
<p class="s7">Users won&rsquo;t need to be worried about a possible Wormhole incident as the smart contracts and reserves of Sparklo have been audited by the InterFi Network. According to the Sparklowhitepaper, all the NFTs minted on the platform will be backed by physical assets, further raising trust in the project</p>
<p class="s7">In addition, the current liquidity and reserves of Sparklo will be locked in for 100 years. Sparklois currently in presale for $0.015. These are the reasons why analysts predict that when Sparklolaunches, it could outperform the entire crypto market.</p>
<p class="s7">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">One of the major flaws of decentralized finance (DeFi) has been the security of digital assets held in their vaults. The DeFi sector has been the constant target of cybercriminals, who are often successful, stealing millions in crypto.</p>
<p class="s7">Updates from Wormhole, one of the largest bridges between Solana and other blockchains, show that the loss from the hack makes it the second-largest DeFi hack on record. As a result, Solana (SOL) has continued to tank. </p>
<p class="s7">On the brighter side of DeFi, analysts have predicted possible use cases of Sparklo, combined with the momentum it is building could make the project a top 100 crypto within the first year of its launch.</p>
<p class="s9">Solana (SOL) Tanks 8% as Wormhole Hack Hit $320 Million</p>
<p class="s7">The price of Solana (SOL) has tanked 8% in the last 24 hours as reports show that the losses of the Wormhole hack surpassed $320 million &ndash; now making it the second-largest DeFi hack on record.</p>
<p class="s7">The attack on Wormhole started with the hacker&rsquo;s Solana account. After the attack, the hacker then swapped the SOL in his account for USDCet (Wormhole USDC), before bringing it across to Ethereum to move the funds.</p>
<p class="s7">The losses of Solana (SOL) are compounded by a market-wide sell-off, which has seen 3% of the global crypto market cap lost in just 24 hours. With today&rsquo;s loss, Solana (SOL) now trades at $23, despite trading at over $110 year-over-year.</p>
<p class="s7">If Solana (SOL) fails to hold the $23 level, the price of the asset could fall as low as $20. However, if it manages to find enough bullish momentum in the coming days, then Solana (SOL) could retest the $25 level.</p>
<p class="s9">Analysts Predict Top 100 Spot for Sparklo</p>
<p class="s7">Despite the broader crypto markets suffering from bearish sentiments at the moment, analysts predict that Sparklo &ndash; which has been gaining grounds as an alternative investment platform &ndash; could outperform the market and claim a top 100 spot within a year of its launch. </p>
<p class="s7">Analysts are bullish about the prospects of Sparklo because of its unique, problem-solving platform which will allow users to be able to purchase rare and precious metals, such as silver, gold, and platinum in form of fractional NFTs, meaning you can own gold without needing to buy an entire bar. </p>
<p class="s7">Users won&rsquo;t need to be worried about a possible Wormhole incident as the smart contracts and reserves of Sparklo have been audited by the InterFi Network. According to the Sparklowhitepaper, all the NFTs minted on the platform will be backed by physical assets, further raising trust in the project</p>
<p class="s7">In addition, the current liquidity and reserves of Sparklo will be locked in for 100 years. Sparklois currently in presale for $0.015. These are the reasons why analysts predict that when Sparklolaunches, it could outperform the entire crypto market.</p>
<p class="s7">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s7">Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p class="s7">Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p class="s7">Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Steven Bartlett’s Flight Story announces acquisition of Zebu Digital & Zebu Live to launch innovation marketing arm, Flight3.]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/steven-bartlett-flight-story-announces-acquisition-of-zebu-digital-and-zebu-live-to-launch-innovation-marketing-arm-flight3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/flight.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/flight.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/flight.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:47:46 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/steven-bartlett-flight-story-announces-acquisition-of-zebu-digital-and-zebu-live-to-launch-innovation-marketing-arm-flight3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Flight Story is today announcing the 100% acquisition of Zebu, a marketing company with a key focus on innovation, web3 and emerging technologies</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">As part of the acquisition, Zebu Digital will now form Flight3, adding an additional arm to Flight Story&rsquo;s 360-marketing offering&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Harry Horsfall, CEO and co-founder of Zebu, is a serial entrepreneur and web3 innovator with over a decade of experience in the space, having established, built and helped scale a number of web3 enterprises.</li>
</ul>
<p>London, 19th April 2023: Flight Story, the digital marketing and communications company, co-founded by Steven Bartlett (thirdweb Co-founder, BBC Dragon&rsquo;s Den &amp; Diary of a CEO podcast host) and Oliver Yonchev (former MD of Social Chain AG), today announces the acquisition of web3 marketing collective Zebu to launch Flight3 &ndash; a new innovation marketing arm.</p>
<p>Founded in 2021, Steven and Oliver set out to make Flight Story the most forward-thinking digital marketing company in the market, with the sole aim of keeping its clients at the forefront of the changing digital media landscape. The acquisition of Zebu strengthens Flight Story&rsquo;s services and capabilities in web3, ai and VR strategy, content, comms and media, with a specific focus on supporting brands in the innovation, web3 and emerging technology spaces.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Brothers Harry and Jolyon Layard Horsfall founded Zebu with their close friend Henry Hankin in 2021 as the digital world saw a colossal upheaval Web3 and blockchain boomed, and many companies didn&rsquo;t know how to keep up. To give brands a fighting chance in the evolving landscape, Harry, Jolyon and Henry built Zebu, forming a 30-strong best-in-class team that accelerates web3 and innovation projects (working with brands including Solana, Tezos, OKX and NEAR) set to change the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Steven Bartlett, co-founder of Flight Story shares:</p>

<p>&ldquo;&lsquo;Web 3.0&rsquo; includes AI, Machine Learning and blockchain technology. The total market valuation of the metaverse is forecasted to be $678bn by 2030, per Grand View Research and &lsquo;web 3.0&rsquo; is already on its way to becoming a multi-trillion dollar industry. Flight Story endeavours to be the most advanced marketing agency in the world, to do that, we need people who are native to the technology that the future will be built on. That&rsquo;s why Zebu is the perfect addition to the Flight Story team - they further our mission of keeping brands at the very forefront of what&rsquo;s possible.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The new Flight3 division of Flight Story will focus on providing web3-focused community growth, influencer marketing, social media, content marketing, brand design &amp; animation, PR and live events. Zebu Live, the brands&rsquo; web3 conference, will remain as a core part of the Flight3 offering.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Oliver Yonchev, CEO and co-founder of Flight Story adds: </p>

<p>&ldquo;During a time of fast growth within the Flight Story business, we are excited to be launching Flight3 as part of our Flight Story ecosystem. The company perfectly embodies our values and the new team will strengthen Flight Story&rsquo;s expertise in community building and new technologies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Harry Horsfall, CEO of Flight3 says: </p>

<p>&ldquo;Since we met Steven and Oliver, we instantly connected on our excitement for the changing digital landscape. We can&rsquo;t wait to become fully embedded and integrate into Flight Story&rsquo;s marketing and communication services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Flight3 joins the existing Flight Story ecosystem of Flight Studio (a creative studio), Flight Deck (a social listening tool) and R. Agency (a communications agency).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Please find a full media kit with further imagery HERE.For more information, please contact flightstory@ragency.com&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Flight Story is today announcing the 100% acquisition of Zebu, a marketing company with a key focus on innovation, web3 and emerging technologies</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">As part of the acquisition, Zebu Digital will now form Flight3, adding an additional arm to Flight Story&rsquo;s 360-marketing offering&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1">Harry Horsfall, CEO and co-founder of Zebu, is a serial entrepreneur and web3 innovator with over a decade of experience in the space, having established, built and helped scale a number of web3 enterprises.</li>
</ul>
<p>London, 19th April 2023: Flight Story, the digital marketing and communications company, co-founded by Steven Bartlett (thirdweb Co-founder, BBC Dragon&rsquo;s Den &amp; Diary of a CEO podcast host) and Oliver Yonchev (former MD of Social Chain AG), today announces the acquisition of web3 marketing collective Zebu to launch Flight3 &ndash; a new innovation marketing arm.</p>
<p>Founded in 2021, Steven and Oliver set out to make Flight Story the most forward-thinking digital marketing company in the market, with the sole aim of keeping its clients at the forefront of the changing digital media landscape. The acquisition of Zebu strengthens Flight Story&rsquo;s services and capabilities in web3, ai and VR strategy, content, comms and media, with a specific focus on supporting brands in the innovation, web3 and emerging technology spaces.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Brothers Harry and Jolyon Layard Horsfall founded Zebu with their close friend Henry Hankin in 2021 as the digital world saw a colossal upheaval Web3 and blockchain boomed, and many companies didn&rsquo;t know how to keep up. To give brands a fighting chance in the evolving landscape, Harry, Jolyon and Henry built Zebu, forming a 30-strong best-in-class team that accelerates web3 and innovation projects (working with brands including Solana, Tezos, OKX and NEAR) set to change the world.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Steven Bartlett, co-founder of Flight Story shares:</p>

<p>&ldquo;&lsquo;Web 3.0&rsquo; includes AI, Machine Learning and blockchain technology. The total market valuation of the metaverse is forecasted to be $678bn by 2030, per Grand View Research and &lsquo;web 3.0&rsquo; is already on its way to becoming a multi-trillion dollar industry. Flight Story endeavours to be the most advanced marketing agency in the world, to do that, we need people who are native to the technology that the future will be built on. That&rsquo;s why Zebu is the perfect addition to the Flight Story team - they further our mission of keeping brands at the very forefront of what&rsquo;s possible.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The new Flight3 division of Flight Story will focus on providing web3-focused community growth, influencer marketing, social media, content marketing, brand design &amp; animation, PR and live events. Zebu Live, the brands&rsquo; web3 conference, will remain as a core part of the Flight3 offering.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Oliver Yonchev, CEO and co-founder of Flight Story adds: </p>

<p>&ldquo;During a time of fast growth within the Flight Story business, we are excited to be launching Flight3 as part of our Flight Story ecosystem. The company perfectly embodies our values and the new team will strengthen Flight Story&rsquo;s expertise in community building and new technologies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Harry Horsfall, CEO of Flight3 says: </p>

<p>&ldquo;Since we met Steven and Oliver, we instantly connected on our excitement for the changing digital landscape. We can&rsquo;t wait to become fully embedded and integrate into Flight Story&rsquo;s marketing and communication services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Flight3 joins the existing Flight Story ecosystem of Flight Studio (a creative studio), Flight Deck (a social listening tool) and R. Agency (a communications agency).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Please find a full media kit with further imagery HERE.For more information, please contact flightstory@ragency.com&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Massive Pump Incoming For Uwerx (WERX), PancakeSwap (CAKE), and Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/massive-pump-incoming-for-uwerx-werx-pancakeswap-cake-and-shiba-inu-shib</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-150415.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-150415.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-150415.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/massive-pump-incoming-for-uwerx-werx-pancakeswap-cake-and-shiba-inu-shib</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market remains volatile. But analysts have seen signs that indicate a massive pump for Uwerx, PancakeSwap (CAKE), and Shiba Inu (SHIB). Increased DeFi activity and a more risk-on macroeconomic environment are the driving forces behind this predicted surge. Investors who want to capitalize on this incoming rally, need to act fast. </p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX)Analysts investigating Uwerx noted two key points: the 25-year liquidity lock following launch and the audits completed by InterFi Network and Solidproof. Two fundamental indicators of a project with a long-term vision. Uwerx leads a paradigm shift for the gig economy and will create an industry-first decentralized freelancing platform. Uwerx will employ blockchain technology to deliver a platform better suited to freelancers, one that is more secure and transparent and does not charge exorbitant platform fees. Upwork made more than $373 million in service fees in 2020, and this heavy bureaucratic attitude with escrow services has harmed the growth of freelancing, making it more difficult for newer players to enter the space. Uwerx will provide an alternative and, as a result, has the potential to become a blue-chip project used by millions worldwide. Some have already stated their expectations for the current presale price of $0.0065 to increase to $7 by the end of 2023. </p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE)</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is a decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC) that allows users to trade through the use of liquidity pools. PancakeSwap (CAKE) has displayed steady growth since its launch in 2020. PancakeSwap (CAKE) grew partly because of its speed, and PancakeSwap (CAKE) is one of the fastest DEXs due to its deep liquidity and the BSC network.</p>
<p>Increased DeFi activity on the BSC always leads to price appreciation for PancakeSwap (CAKE). The PancakeSwap (CAKE) token is an integral part of the PancakeSwap (CAKE) platform, and holders who lock their tokens receive yield boosts on the core farms. &nbsp;Shiba Inu (SHIB)</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has announced the launch of Shibarium, a layer two scaling solution built on Ethereum. Shiba Inu (SHIB) holders have understandably been excited by the news. Shiba Inu (SHIB) will pump on the release, and more importantly, it will add another use case for Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens.</p>
<p>The release of Shiba Inu (SHIB) layer two will further fuel the enormous Shiba Inu (SHIB) token burn. Analysts expect a solid performance in 2023 for Shiba Inu (SHIB) with this continued commitment to development from the team. Breakout Year For Uwerx (WERX)Uwerx will explode in 2023. It provides real-world utility, and coupled with growing DeFi activity and a more risk-on environment; investors should not be surprised when they see the WERX token start rocketing through the rankings. Exclusive to the presale period is a 25% bonus, this bonus will not be available after, so we would definitely say to act quickly getting in.Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s10">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s10">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/ </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market remains volatile. But analysts have seen signs that indicate a massive pump for Uwerx, PancakeSwap (CAKE), and Shiba Inu (SHIB). Increased DeFi activity and a more risk-on macroeconomic environment are the driving forces behind this predicted surge. Investors who want to capitalize on this incoming rally, need to act fast. </p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX)Analysts investigating Uwerx noted two key points: the 25-year liquidity lock following launch and the audits completed by InterFi Network and Solidproof. Two fundamental indicators of a project with a long-term vision. Uwerx leads a paradigm shift for the gig economy and will create an industry-first decentralized freelancing platform. Uwerx will employ blockchain technology to deliver a platform better suited to freelancers, one that is more secure and transparent and does not charge exorbitant platform fees. Upwork made more than $373 million in service fees in 2020, and this heavy bureaucratic attitude with escrow services has harmed the growth of freelancing, making it more difficult for newer players to enter the space. Uwerx will provide an alternative and, as a result, has the potential to become a blue-chip project used by millions worldwide. Some have already stated their expectations for the current presale price of $0.0065 to increase to $7 by the end of 2023. </p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE)</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is a decentralized exchange (DEX) built on the Binance Smart Chain (BSC) that allows users to trade through the use of liquidity pools. PancakeSwap (CAKE) has displayed steady growth since its launch in 2020. PancakeSwap (CAKE) grew partly because of its speed, and PancakeSwap (CAKE) is one of the fastest DEXs due to its deep liquidity and the BSC network.</p>
<p>Increased DeFi activity on the BSC always leads to price appreciation for PancakeSwap (CAKE). The PancakeSwap (CAKE) token is an integral part of the PancakeSwap (CAKE) platform, and holders who lock their tokens receive yield boosts on the core farms. &nbsp;Shiba Inu (SHIB)</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) has announced the launch of Shibarium, a layer two scaling solution built on Ethereum. Shiba Inu (SHIB) holders have understandably been excited by the news. Shiba Inu (SHIB) will pump on the release, and more importantly, it will add another use case for Shiba Inu (SHIB) tokens.</p>
<p>The release of Shiba Inu (SHIB) layer two will further fuel the enormous Shiba Inu (SHIB) token burn. Analysts expect a solid performance in 2023 for Shiba Inu (SHIB) with this continued commitment to development from the team. Breakout Year For Uwerx (WERX)Uwerx will explode in 2023. It provides real-world utility, and coupled with growing DeFi activity and a more risk-on environment; investors should not be surprised when they see the WERX token start rocketing through the rankings. Exclusive to the presale period is a 25% bonus, this bonus will not be available after, so we would definitely say to act quickly getting in.Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s10">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s10">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/ </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Can Now Start Operating In Bermuda]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/coinbase-can-now-start-operating-in-the-bermuda</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-1450-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/coinbase-can-now-start-operating-in-the-bermuda</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S.-based crypto exchange has recently acquired the license required to offer crypto trading services in the island territory of Bermuda.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Bermuda Receives License
<p>At a time when U.S. regulators, like the SEC, are making it harder and harder for crypto companies to survive, Coinbase has made the prudent decision to take matters offshore. The crypto exchange had recently applied for the operational license for the offshore haven of Bermuda. In a blog published on the company website on April 19, it was revealed that the application was approved, and the license was granted to Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Coinbase Bermuda Ltd. has obtained a Class F License under the Digital Asset Business Act from the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA).&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to reports, thanks to the license, Coinbase is all set to launch a crypto derivatives exchange in Bermuda as soon as next week.&nbsp;</p>
BMA Makes Bermuda A Crypto Haven
<p>The announcement also addressed the factors which drove the company to branch out its operations to the island, touching upon the comprehensive digital assets regulation guidelines that were passed in 2018. Furthermore, the announcement claimed that the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA) is a highly respected and experienced financial regulator with tremendous leadership and was also another contributing factor to the establishment of Coinbase Bermuda Ltd. The fact that BMA is also a member of several international organizations and has worked closely with other regulatory agencies around the world is an added advantage.</p>
<p>The team wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Working with global regulators is key to the Coinbase mission, as we continue to increase economic freedom in the world. As the most transparent and trustworthy centralized exchange, Coinbase will help bring the next billion users into the cryptoeconomy.&rdquo;</p>

Trouble With SEC
<p>The company&rsquo;s CEO, Brian Armstrong, has categorically stated that the crypto firm will be exploring all its offshore options, especially regulatory havens like Bermuda, unless there is more clarity from the UK and U.S. watchdogs. Coinbase has recently been in trouble with the SEC, which has served the company with a Wells notice. The high probability of a lengthy court battle with the regulatory watchdog could have been a key motivating factor to its increased offshore efforts lately. Other than Bermuda, the firm is also in talks with the financial regulators in Abu Dhabi about a potential operating license.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company hinted at its regulatory troubles,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Coinbase chose to become a public company in the US because we believe the US would best be served by embracing this fundamental innovation, but we&rsquo;re also focused on international markets, many of which are moving forward with strategies to become &ldquo;crypto hubs.&rdquo; We would like to see the US take a similar approach, but a regulation by enforcement approach in the US is instead leading to a disappointing trend for crypto development in the US.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S.-based crypto exchange has recently acquired the license required to offer crypto trading services in the island territory of Bermuda.&nbsp;</p>
Coinbase Bermuda Receives License
<p>At a time when U.S. regulators, like the SEC, are making it harder and harder for crypto companies to survive, Coinbase has made the prudent decision to take matters offshore. The crypto exchange had recently applied for the operational license for the offshore haven of Bermuda. In a blog published on the company website on April 19, it was revealed that the application was approved, and the license was granted to Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Coinbase Bermuda Ltd. has obtained a Class F License under the Digital Asset Business Act from the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA).&rdquo;</p>

<p>According to reports, thanks to the license, Coinbase is all set to launch a crypto derivatives exchange in Bermuda as soon as next week.&nbsp;</p>
BMA Makes Bermuda A Crypto Haven
<p>The announcement also addressed the factors which drove the company to branch out its operations to the island, touching upon the comprehensive digital assets regulation guidelines that were passed in 2018. Furthermore, the announcement claimed that the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA) is a highly respected and experienced financial regulator with tremendous leadership and was also another contributing factor to the establishment of Coinbase Bermuda Ltd. The fact that BMA is also a member of several international organizations and has worked closely with other regulatory agencies around the world is an added advantage.</p>
<p>The team wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Working with global regulators is key to the Coinbase mission, as we continue to increase economic freedom in the world. As the most transparent and trustworthy centralized exchange, Coinbase will help bring the next billion users into the cryptoeconomy.&rdquo;</p>

Trouble With SEC
<p>The company&rsquo;s CEO, Brian Armstrong, has categorically stated that the crypto firm will be exploring all its offshore options, especially regulatory havens like Bermuda, unless there is more clarity from the UK and U.S. watchdogs. Coinbase has recently been in trouble with the SEC, which has served the company with a Wells notice. The high probability of a lengthy court battle with the regulatory watchdog could have been a key motivating factor to its increased offshore efforts lately. Other than Bermuda, the firm is also in talks with the financial regulators in Abu Dhabi about a potential operating license.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The company hinted at its regulatory troubles,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Coinbase chose to become a public company in the US because we believe the US would best be served by embracing this fundamental innovation, but we&rsquo;re also focused on international markets, many of which are moving forward with strategies to become &ldquo;crypto hubs.&rdquo; We would like to see the US take a similar approach, but a regulation by enforcement approach in the US is instead leading to a disappointing trend for crypto development in the US.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uwerx (WERX) Will Come As An Excellent Substitute For Shiba Inu (SHIB) And Gala (GALA)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/uwerx-werx-will-come-as-an-excellent-substitute-for-shiba-inu-shib-and-gala-gala</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-145627.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-145627.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-04-21-at-145627.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/uwerx-werx-will-come-as-an-excellent-substitute-for-shiba-inu-shib-and-gala-gala</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Investing in the crypto industry has made many individuals millionaires, but what knowledge did they possess? They invested during a project's early stages, capitalizing on its growth opportunity and solid fundamentals while maximizing its profits. This strategy has always been very lucrative, and we would like to introduce a perfect chance for you to utilize it - Uwerx! It is a project currently in phase 1 of its presale with an opportunity to surpass both Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Gala (GALA) in 2023 as it becomes a top-tier crypto platform with millions of supporters. </p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) To Become The Most Profit-Yielding Coin</p>
<p>The freelance industry will soon have a new dominating platform with features that other traditional freelance platforms do not have, joining its ranks. This platform will be Uwerx - the first-ever blockchain-based freelance platform!</p>
<p>Uwerx aims to solve some of the freelance industry's problems- through blockchain technology! Both freelancers and companies will benefit from lower fees (1% vs. 20%) since Uwerx will cut out the intermediary escrow service and much more! Decentralized storage will bring greater trust and security and more significant record-keeping since every piece of information will be kept on the blockchain itself.</p>
<p>Now let's talk about security, another area that is very important when making your investment choice. The famous auditing firms InterFi Network and Solidproof have already finished two audits of the project, all while the minds behind Uwerx will place a lock on project liquidity for 25 years after its launch. These safety nets genuinely reflect the team's long-term faith and confidence in the project and are a good sign for any potential buyer. Since the token price is only $0.0065, now is the right time to buy into a possible top 10 coin at a low cost. With many crypto insiders predicting a $2.80 price point by July 2024, we believe that Uwerx may be one of the most profitable investment choices in 2023! </p>
<p class="s7">The Shiba Inu (SHIB) Value Goes Up</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), established in 2020, is a spoof of Dogecoin (DOGE), another joke coin. The currency was developed by the Shiba Inu (SHIB) team as a way of rewarding content providers.</p>
<p>Recently, Shiba Inu (SHIB) developers unveiled "Shibarium" proposals, describing intentions to introduce a layer-2 blockchain. This news helped the Shiba Inu (SHIB) value go up 25% in the past week, which is currently worth $0.00001116. Its trading volume has also shot up 350% in the past 24 hours, but some investors are still skeptical. For it to reach the $1 mark, the developers must make many changes, and even though Shiba Inu (SHIB) may see green charts in the future, those who wish for more significant profit should look for other projects with more utility cases. </p>
<p class="s7">Gala (GALA) Sinks By 11%</p>
<p>Gala (GALA) is a brand-new gaming environment built on Ethereum. The Gala (GALA) coin was launched in 2020 but has already become quite attractive among players to send and receive payments within the environment. </p>
<p>This popularity helped the Gala (GALA) coin reach its all-time high of $0.8367 in 2021. However, the token has been on a downward trend ever since then. Currently, the Gala (GALA) coin is heading down a negative trajectory again, dropping by 11% in a single day as it is currently trading at $0.04622. Another negative indicator is that its market cap has also been losing strength, going down 11.60% in the same period. Experts believe this bearish trend is bound to continue as Gala (GALA) fails to reach the $0.050 support level.</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investing in the crypto industry has made many individuals millionaires, but what knowledge did they possess? They invested during a project's early stages, capitalizing on its growth opportunity and solid fundamentals while maximizing its profits. This strategy has always been very lucrative, and we would like to introduce a perfect chance for you to utilize it - Uwerx! It is a project currently in phase 1 of its presale with an opportunity to surpass both Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Gala (GALA) in 2023 as it becomes a top-tier crypto platform with millions of supporters. </p>
<p class="s7">Uwerx (WERX) To Become The Most Profit-Yielding Coin</p>
<p>The freelance industry will soon have a new dominating platform with features that other traditional freelance platforms do not have, joining its ranks. This platform will be Uwerx - the first-ever blockchain-based freelance platform!</p>
<p>Uwerx aims to solve some of the freelance industry's problems- through blockchain technology! Both freelancers and companies will benefit from lower fees (1% vs. 20%) since Uwerx will cut out the intermediary escrow service and much more! Decentralized storage will bring greater trust and security and more significant record-keeping since every piece of information will be kept on the blockchain itself.</p>
<p>Now let's talk about security, another area that is very important when making your investment choice. The famous auditing firms InterFi Network and Solidproof have already finished two audits of the project, all while the minds behind Uwerx will place a lock on project liquidity for 25 years after its launch. These safety nets genuinely reflect the team's long-term faith and confidence in the project and are a good sign for any potential buyer. Since the token price is only $0.0065, now is the right time to buy into a possible top 10 coin at a low cost. With many crypto insiders predicting a $2.80 price point by July 2024, we believe that Uwerx may be one of the most profitable investment choices in 2023! </p>
<p class="s7">The Shiba Inu (SHIB) Value Goes Up</p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), established in 2020, is a spoof of Dogecoin (DOGE), another joke coin. The currency was developed by the Shiba Inu (SHIB) team as a way of rewarding content providers.</p>
<p>Recently, Shiba Inu (SHIB) developers unveiled "Shibarium" proposals, describing intentions to introduce a layer-2 blockchain. This news helped the Shiba Inu (SHIB) value go up 25% in the past week, which is currently worth $0.00001116. Its trading volume has also shot up 350% in the past 24 hours, but some investors are still skeptical. For it to reach the $1 mark, the developers must make many changes, and even though Shiba Inu (SHIB) may see green charts in the future, those who wish for more significant profit should look for other projects with more utility cases. </p>
<p class="s7">Gala (GALA) Sinks By 11%</p>
<p>Gala (GALA) is a brand-new gaming environment built on Ethereum. The Gala (GALA) coin was launched in 2020 but has already become quite attractive among players to send and receive payments within the environment. </p>
<p>This popularity helped the Gala (GALA) coin reach its all-time high of $0.8367 in 2021. However, the token has been on a downward trend ever since then. Currently, the Gala (GALA) coin is heading down a negative trajectory again, dropping by 11% in a single day as it is currently trading at $0.04622. Another negative indicator is that its market cap has also been losing strength, going down 11.60% in the same period. Experts believe this bearish trend is bound to continue as Gala (GALA) fails to reach the $0.050 support level.</p>
<p class="s11">Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p class="s11">Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p class="s11">Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[NFT Marketplaces Losing Users & Sales, Crypto Daily TV 21/4/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/nft-marketplaces-are-losing-users-sales-crypto-daily-tv-21-4-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-nft-plummet.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-nft-plummet.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-nft-plummet.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/nft-marketplaces-are-losing-users-sales-crypto-daily-tv-21-4-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Ensuring client's best interest</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is advising brokers and investment advisers they need to use heightened scrutiny when it comes to making crypto recommendations to ensure the risky products are in the best interests of their clients, the agency said in a new bulletin.</p>
<p>Deribit sets up crypto exchange battle with push into free trading</p>
<p>Crypto derivatives exchange Deribit is launching free trading of bitcoin and other tokens, setting up a fresh price war among digital asset exchanges as they seek to re-emerge after a bruising year for the industry.</p>
<p>NFT marketplaces sales, users drop</p>
<p>The number of daily users and sales has dipped across NFT marketplaces over the last week, according to data pulled from analytics platform Dune, reaching new lows not seen since July 2021.</p>
BTC/USD dove 2.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 2.0% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 27527.3333 and resistance at 31061.3333.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>Ethereum rose 0.3% against the Dollar in the last trading session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1808.8967 and resistance at 2167.8167.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD plummeted 3.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair fell 3.9% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.6% during the session. The RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.4309 and resistance at 0.5671.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 1.9% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair fell 1.9% in the last session after gaining as much as 2.3% during the session. According to the CCI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 80.8467 and resistance at 106.7067.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Baker Hughes US Oil Rig Count</p>
<p>The Baker Hughes Rig Count is an important business barometer for the drilling industry and its suppliers. Active drilling rigs consume products and services produced by the oil service industry. The US Baker Hughes US Oil Rig Count will be released at 17:00 GMT, Japan's Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI at 00:30 GMT, and Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI at 00:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI gives an early snapshot of the health of the Japanese manufacturing sector.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions. Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions will be released at 20:30 GMT, the UK's Retail Sales at 06:00 GMT, and the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Retail Sales</p>
<p>Retail Sales measure the total receipts of retail stores. Monthly percent changes reflect the rate of change of such sales.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Ensuring client's best interest</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is advising brokers and investment advisers they need to use heightened scrutiny when it comes to making crypto recommendations to ensure the risky products are in the best interests of their clients, the agency said in a new bulletin.</p>
<p>Deribit sets up crypto exchange battle with push into free trading</p>
<p>Crypto derivatives exchange Deribit is launching free trading of bitcoin and other tokens, setting up a fresh price war among digital asset exchanges as they seek to re-emerge after a bruising year for the industry.</p>
<p>NFT marketplaces sales, users drop</p>
<p>The number of daily users and sales has dipped across NFT marketplaces over the last week, according to data pulled from analytics platform Dune, reaching new lows not seen since July 2021.</p>
BTC/USD dove 2.0% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair plummeted 2.0% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an oversold market. Support is at 27527.3333 and resistance at 31061.3333.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is signalling an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>Ethereum rose 0.3% against the Dollar in the last trading session. The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1808.8967 and resistance at 2167.8167.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD plummeted 3.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair fell 3.9% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.6% during the session. The RSI is giving a negative signal. Support is at 0.4309 and resistance at 0.5671.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD dove 1.9% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair fell 1.9% in the last session after gaining as much as 2.3% during the session. According to the CCI, we are in an oversold market. Support is at 80.8467 and resistance at 106.7067.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an oversold market.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Baker Hughes US Oil Rig Count</p>
<p>The Baker Hughes Rig Count is an important business barometer for the drilling industry and its suppliers. Active drilling rigs consume products and services produced by the oil service industry. The US Baker Hughes US Oil Rig Count will be released at 17:00 GMT, Japan's Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI at 00:30 GMT, and Japan's Jibun Bank Services PMI at 00:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Manufacturing PMI gives an early snapshot of the health of the Japanese manufacturing sector.</p>
<p>JP Jibun Bank Services PMI</p>
<p>The Jibun Bank Services Purchasing Managers Index (PMI) captures the business conditions in the services sector. The services PMI is an important indicator of the overall economic conditions.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions. Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions will be released at 20:30 GMT, the UK's Retail Sales at 06:00 GMT, and the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>UK Retail Sales</p>
<p>Retail Sales measure the total receipts of retail stores. Monthly percent changes reflect the rate of change of such sales.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bisonai Partners with Polygon Supernet to Revolutionize Blockchain Infrastructure for Web3]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bisonai-partners-with-polygon-supernet-to-revolutionize-blockchain-infrastructure-for-web3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Bisonai_1682056568jfALDB5xD3.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Bisonai_1682056568jfALDB5xD3.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Bisonai_1682056568jfALDB5xD3.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:37:36 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bisonai-partners-with-polygon-supernet-to-revolutionize-blockchain-infrastructure-for-web3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Singapore-based blockchain startup to help businesses of all sizes overcome challenges to build cutting-edge infrastructure for Web3.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai, a Singapore-based company specializing in Web3 infrastructure, has joined forces with Polygon Supernet, a blockchain developer that provides a Layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum, to revolutionize enterprise blockchain solutions, offering scalable and customizable Web3 infrastructure to businesses worldwide.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As companies increasingly look to adopt blockchain technology, they often encounter significant challenges related to scalability and complex infrastructure requirements. Bisonai's partnership with Polygon represents a significant milestone in its mission to provide innovative and cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure for Web3 to businesses of all sizes.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Traditional blockchain networks, such as Ethereum, are limited in their capacity to handle large volumes of transactions, which can result in slow transaction times and high fees.&nbsp;Moreover, setting up and maintaining a blockchain infrastructure can be a daunting and costly task, requiring specialized technical knowledge and resources that many companies may not possess. Bisonai will leverage Polygon's Supernet program to deliver blockchain solutions that meet the unique needs of each client.</p>"We are thrilled to partner with Polygon and join their Supernet program as a technology implementation partner. The Supernet has already been adopted by major global enterprises such as Starbucks and Disney, offering customization services that allow companies to issue their own native tokens or adjust gas fees," said Tae-goo Kim, CEO of Bisonai.&nbsp;"Our expertise in blockchain development and Web3 infrastructure, combined with Polygon's scalable and customizable blockchain services, will offer businesses of all sizes the opportunity to benefit from the power of blockchain technology,&rdquo; Kim added.<p class="ql-align-justify">With collaborations with industry leaders such as Netmarble and Altava Group, Bisonai is rapidly expanding its business into various sectors after recently raising seed investment. As a technology implementation partner with Polygon, Bisonai is well-positioned to offer businesses of all sizes innovative and cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure for Web3.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Bisonai &amp; its services in Web3 infrastructure</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Blockchain infrastructure for Web3 is a crucial component of the decentralized web, providing businesses with the tools and technologies needed to harness the power of blockchain technology. At its core, Web3 represents a new way of interacting with the internet, where individuals and businesses have control over their data and digital assets. By leveraging blockchain technology, Web3 enables secure and transparent transactions without the need for intermediaries.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">At the forefront of this revolution is Bisonai, a Singapore-based company founded in 2022 by CEO Tae-goo Kim, specializing in Web3 infrastructure. Bisonai offers a range of blockchain development services, including smart contract development, decentralized application (dApp) development, and custom blockchain development. Their team of experienced developers uses the latest tools and technologies to create scalable and secure blockchain solutions that meet the unique needs of each client.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai, through its Web3 Studio service, offers development support for a wide range of dApps and blockchain infrastructure. Bisonai collaborates with Web2 and Web3 companies, as well as Layer 1 foundations, providing development consulting, product launch, and operational services based on diverse requirements. Some of the broad categories they specialize in include NFT smart contract, NFT marketplace, blockchain oracle, block explorer, and non-custodial wallet.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In addition to its products and services, Bisonai has a thriving community of developers and blockchain enthusiasts. SeoulWeb3 community regularly hosts events and meetups to promote blockchain education and collaboration among developers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai also offers Web3 infrastructure services. These services include node hosting, blockchain monitoring, and network optimization, enabling businesses to build and operate decentralized applications on the blockchain. By leveraging Bisonai's expertise in Web3 infrastructure, businesses can take advantage of the benefits of blockchain technology while focusing on their core competencies.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information on Bisonai and their services, please visit their website at&nbsp;https://bisonai.com/.</p>ContactBisonai teamBisonaibusiness@bisonai.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">Singapore-based blockchain startup to help businesses of all sizes overcome challenges to build cutting-edge infrastructure for Web3.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai, a Singapore-based company specializing in Web3 infrastructure, has joined forces with Polygon Supernet, a blockchain developer that provides a Layer 2 scaling solution for Ethereum, to revolutionize enterprise blockchain solutions, offering scalable and customizable Web3 infrastructure to businesses worldwide.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As companies increasingly look to adopt blockchain technology, they often encounter significant challenges related to scalability and complex infrastructure requirements. Bisonai's partnership with Polygon represents a significant milestone in its mission to provide innovative and cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure for Web3 to businesses of all sizes.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Traditional blockchain networks, such as Ethereum, are limited in their capacity to handle large volumes of transactions, which can result in slow transaction times and high fees.&nbsp;Moreover, setting up and maintaining a blockchain infrastructure can be a daunting and costly task, requiring specialized technical knowledge and resources that many companies may not possess. Bisonai will leverage Polygon's Supernet program to deliver blockchain solutions that meet the unique needs of each client.</p>"We are thrilled to partner with Polygon and join their Supernet program as a technology implementation partner. The Supernet has already been adopted by major global enterprises such as Starbucks and Disney, offering customization services that allow companies to issue their own native tokens or adjust gas fees," said Tae-goo Kim, CEO of Bisonai.&nbsp;"Our expertise in blockchain development and Web3 infrastructure, combined with Polygon's scalable and customizable blockchain services, will offer businesses of all sizes the opportunity to benefit from the power of blockchain technology,&rdquo; Kim added.<p class="ql-align-justify">With collaborations with industry leaders such as Netmarble and Altava Group, Bisonai is rapidly expanding its business into various sectors after recently raising seed investment. As a technology implementation partner with Polygon, Bisonai is well-positioned to offer businesses of all sizes innovative and cutting-edge blockchain infrastructure for Web3.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Bisonai &amp; its services in Web3 infrastructure</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Blockchain infrastructure for Web3 is a crucial component of the decentralized web, providing businesses with the tools and technologies needed to harness the power of blockchain technology. At its core, Web3 represents a new way of interacting with the internet, where individuals and businesses have control over their data and digital assets. By leveraging blockchain technology, Web3 enables secure and transparent transactions without the need for intermediaries.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">At the forefront of this revolution is Bisonai, a Singapore-based company founded in 2022 by CEO Tae-goo Kim, specializing in Web3 infrastructure. Bisonai offers a range of blockchain development services, including smart contract development, decentralized application (dApp) development, and custom blockchain development. Their team of experienced developers uses the latest tools and technologies to create scalable and secure blockchain solutions that meet the unique needs of each client.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai, through its Web3 Studio service, offers development support for a wide range of dApps and blockchain infrastructure. Bisonai collaborates with Web2 and Web3 companies, as well as Layer 1 foundations, providing development consulting, product launch, and operational services based on diverse requirements. Some of the broad categories they specialize in include NFT smart contract, NFT marketplace, blockchain oracle, block explorer, and non-custodial wallet.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In addition to its products and services, Bisonai has a thriving community of developers and blockchain enthusiasts. SeoulWeb3 community regularly hosts events and meetups to promote blockchain education and collaboration among developers.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bisonai also offers Web3 infrastructure services. These services include node hosting, blockchain monitoring, and network optimization, enabling businesses to build and operate decentralized applications on the blockchain. By leveraging Bisonai's expertise in Web3 infrastructure, businesses can take advantage of the benefits of blockchain technology while focusing on their core competencies.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information on Bisonai and their services, please visit their website at&nbsp;https://bisonai.com/.</p>ContactBisonai teamBisonaibusiness@bisonai.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US crypto companies look to Hong Kong for regulatory clarity]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/us-crypto-companies-look-to-hong-kong-for-regulatory-clarity</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hong-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 12:56:53 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/us-crypto-companies-look-to-hong-kong-for-regulatory-clarity</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Several crypto companies in the US are facing major regulatory challenges and have announced their plans to relocate offshore.&nbsp;</p>
US exit by crypto companies
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a more stringent regulatory approach, and therefore, companies like Coinbase, Kraken and Binance have warned they might leave the US in the event that regulators do not come up with clear regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has taken several steps, including ending partnerships and trading activities in the US, while Coinbase has recently received a licence for the Bahamas, which has excited the crypto community.</p>
<p>Huobi and OKX - both founded on the mainland, but having exited after earlier crackdowns, announced they are applying for SFC licences. Crypto firms are now opening accounts in the city, as the licensing requirement is just a few weeks away.</p>
<p>However, representatives from Hashkey, OSL, and other crypto firms say that the process for a licence is difficult, since it requires much resources, time, and money to be spent on professional companies skilled in compliance.&nbsp;</p>
Hong Kong seen as a viable crypto hub
<p>In response to the SEC's and other regulators' actions, other crypto firms are convinced that Hong Kong could become a major hub for crypto and have started applying for a licence. Hong Kong's crypto platforms are opening bank accounts and partnering up with local banks to attract more players in the market ahead of its new licensing regime.</p>
<p>Hong Kong is committed to virtual assets. Its new, crypto-friendly policy has set it apart from other markets, such as the US, which has developed a seemingly anti-crypto stance, and mainland China where cryptocurrencies have been banned.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Signature Bank and SVB were attractive because they offered 24-hour service to settle cryptocurrency transactions quickly. Hong Kong's virtual banks can now attract some of this business due to their 24/7 offerings.</p>
<p>Smaller banks in Hong Kong may be more open to working with unlicensed crypto firms, despite the high compliance standards.</p>
<p>Hong Kong is now seen as a possible new hub by many crypto companies. The process is not simple and requires compliance assessments. Hong Kong is committed to virtual assets despite the challenges. The city is poised to become a major player within the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several crypto companies in the US are facing major regulatory challenges and have announced their plans to relocate offshore.&nbsp;</p>
US exit by crypto companies
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has taken a more stringent regulatory approach, and therefore, companies like Coinbase, Kraken and Binance have warned they might leave the US in the event that regulators do not come up with clear regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance has taken several steps, including ending partnerships and trading activities in the US, while Coinbase has recently received a licence for the Bahamas, which has excited the crypto community.</p>
<p>Huobi and OKX - both founded on the mainland, but having exited after earlier crackdowns, announced they are applying for SFC licences. Crypto firms are now opening accounts in the city, as the licensing requirement is just a few weeks away.</p>
<p>However, representatives from Hashkey, OSL, and other crypto firms say that the process for a licence is difficult, since it requires much resources, time, and money to be spent on professional companies skilled in compliance.&nbsp;</p>
Hong Kong seen as a viable crypto hub
<p>In response to the SEC's and other regulators' actions, other crypto firms are convinced that Hong Kong could become a major hub for crypto and have started applying for a licence. Hong Kong's crypto platforms are opening bank accounts and partnering up with local banks to attract more players in the market ahead of its new licensing regime.</p>
<p>Hong Kong is committed to virtual assets. Its new, crypto-friendly policy has set it apart from other markets, such as the US, which has developed a seemingly anti-crypto stance, and mainland China where cryptocurrencies have been banned.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Signature Bank and SVB were attractive because they offered 24-hour service to settle cryptocurrency transactions quickly. Hong Kong's virtual banks can now attract some of this business due to their 24/7 offerings.</p>
<p>Smaller banks in Hong Kong may be more open to working with unlicensed crypto firms, despite the high compliance standards.</p>
<p>Hong Kong is now seen as a possible new hub by many crypto companies. The process is not simple and requires compliance assessments. Hong Kong is committed to virtual assets despite the challenges. The city is poised to become a major player within the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance full steam ahead in crypto positive MENA region]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/binance-full-steam-ahead-in-crypto-positive-mena-region</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mena.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mena.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mena.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:58:54 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/binance-full-steam-ahead-in-crypto-positive-mena-region</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Virtual asset laws in the Middle East and North Africa region (MENA) have given it a competitive advantage in cryptocurrency markets and trading. Binance is taking advantage.</p>
Binance licenced in MENA
<p>Binance, the largest cryptocurrency trading platform in the world, has praised Bahrain and the UAE's laws as they have given the cryptocurrency market more depth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Binance's General Manager Alex Chehade, governments in the MENA regions have decided to promote the Web3 Economy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Obviously, some jurisdictions are moving quicker with crypto regulation, and this is why we&rsquo;ve established a large footprint in MENA. Because governments have decided that the Web3 economy is something they want to foster. They set frameworks that enable building the ecosystems.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Binance can onboard global clients with the Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority licence in Dubai. It meets their criteria, and Binance has a crypto custody licence in Abu Dhabi. VARA licences include crypto exchange, custody and brokerage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance's global operations have remained untouched by the US federal investigations despite intense scrutiny, and despite the crypto industry being affected by the collapse of FTX, Binance's impact is undeniable.</p>
MENA to lead the world in crypto regulation
<p>In recent years, cryptocurrency trading has grown in popularity in the MENA. The UAE Securities and Commodities Authority introduced cryptocurrency regulations in 2021. The SCA's goal is to promote innovation and protect investors while improving the financial stability of the country.</p>
<p>Dubai Multi Commodities Centre has taken steps to make the emirate a centre for cryptocurrency trading. The DMCC has launched the Crypto Centre, a platform which allows cryptocurrency companies to set up shop in Dubai.</p>
<p>Saudi Arabia's Monetary Authority has created a regulatory sandbox in order to encourage financial technology innovation, including cryptocurrency. The sandbox is a place where fintech startups can test their products in a controlled setting before they launch them on the market.</p>
<p>The MENA region has a set of cryptocurrency regulations that have placed it at the forefront in the global cryptocurrency market. The region's innovative regulatory frameworks offer greater opportunities to investors and cryptocurrency firms looking to expand.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virtual asset laws in the Middle East and North Africa region (MENA) have given it a competitive advantage in cryptocurrency markets and trading. Binance is taking advantage.</p>
Binance licenced in MENA
<p>Binance, the largest cryptocurrency trading platform in the world, has praised Bahrain and the UAE's laws as they have given the cryptocurrency market more depth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Binance's General Manager Alex Chehade, governments in the MENA regions have decided to promote the Web3 Economy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Obviously, some jurisdictions are moving quicker with crypto regulation, and this is why we&rsquo;ve established a large footprint in MENA. Because governments have decided that the Web3 economy is something they want to foster. They set frameworks that enable building the ecosystems.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Binance can onboard global clients with the Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority licence in Dubai. It meets their criteria, and Binance has a crypto custody licence in Abu Dhabi. VARA licences include crypto exchange, custody and brokerage.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance's global operations have remained untouched by the US federal investigations despite intense scrutiny, and despite the crypto industry being affected by the collapse of FTX, Binance's impact is undeniable.</p>
MENA to lead the world in crypto regulation
<p>In recent years, cryptocurrency trading has grown in popularity in the MENA. The UAE Securities and Commodities Authority introduced cryptocurrency regulations in 2021. The SCA's goal is to promote innovation and protect investors while improving the financial stability of the country.</p>
<p>Dubai Multi Commodities Centre has taken steps to make the emirate a centre for cryptocurrency trading. The DMCC has launched the Crypto Centre, a platform which allows cryptocurrency companies to set up shop in Dubai.</p>
<p>Saudi Arabia's Monetary Authority has created a regulatory sandbox in order to encourage financial technology innovation, including cryptocurrency. The sandbox is a place where fintech startups can test their products in a controlled setting before they launch them on the market.</p>
<p>The MENA region has a set of cryptocurrency regulations that have placed it at the forefront in the global cryptocurrency market. The region's innovative regulatory frameworks offer greater opportunities to investors and cryptocurrency firms looking to expand.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Revolutionising Bitcoin Mining: The Emergence of Hashrate Collectibles]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/revolutionising-bitcoin-mining-the-emergence-of-hashrate-collectibles</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hash.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hash.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/hash.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/revolutionising-bitcoin-mining-the-emergence-of-hashrate-collectibles</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin mining has faced increasing scrutiny in recent years due to its significant energy consumption and environmental impact. According to estimates, the energy consumption of the Bitcoin network exceeds that of entire countries, and the carbon footprint of mining is equivalent to that of a small country. This has led to concerns about the sustainability of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies and their impact on the environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitcoin has been mined through a process known as Proof-of-Work (PoW) since its inception in 2009. However, the environmental impact and centralisation issues associated with traditional Bitcoin mining have reared their head in recent years. Emerging solutions in the Web3 space may offer a more sustainable and decentralised path forward.</p>
Traditional Bitcoin Mining
<p>PoW mining requires powerful computers to solve complex mathematical equations, which consumes massive amounts of energy. According to some estimates, Bitcoin mining alone consumes more electricity than the entire country of Argentina. This figure has been contested by pro-bitcoin advocates, however it gives an indication of the amount of electricity consumed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a further blow to the decentralised ethos of the blockchain, PoW mining has become increasingly centralised, with the majority of mining power controlled by a small number of large mining pools. This concentration of power poses a threat to the decentralisation that is supposed to be a core tenet of blockchain technology. Some mining operations are exploring more sustainable methods, such as renewable energy sources, but the issue remains a significant challenge for the industry.</p>
<p>Proof-of-Stake (PoS) is one such solution, where instead of using computational power to mine new coins, users can "stake" their coins as collateral to validate transactions and create new blocks. This process consumes far less energy and eliminates the need for expensive hardware, making it a more environmentally friendly and accessible option.</p>
Sustainable NFT solutions
<p>Other solutions, such as decentralised storage and computing platforms, also offer alternatives to the energy-intensive PoW mining. These platforms allow users to rent out their unused computing power and storage space, creating a more decentralised and sustainable ecosystem.</p>
<p>And while the Web3 space is still in its nascence, the innovation within Web3 is considerable. CUDOS Markets is a marketplace created by the founders of the sustainable and carbon-neutral Cudos blockchain and Cudo Compute, that provides a unique solution to Bitcoin mining. The platform offers a simplified and user-friendly approach to cryptocurrency mining and brings utility to the world of digital collectibles. By tokenizing hashrate, it enables anyone to participate in the mining process, regardless of technical knowledge or access to expensive hardware.&nbsp;</p>
<p>NFTs are tied to sustainable mining farms, which allow users to purchase a share of a mining pool's computational resources, providing them with a direct stake in the mining rewards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users can sell their collectibles on the open marketplace whenever they want. The platform also offers instant liquidity and daily rewards, making it an attractive option for those looking to earn cryptocurrencies without the complexities of traditional mining.</p>
Transparency and Due Diligence&nbsp;
<p>CUDOS Markets is built to be fully transparent, with each seller&rsquo;s collection displaying maintenance costs. CUDOS Markets&rsquo;s strict due diligence process ensures that new BTC mining farms are financially sound, environmentally and sustainably responsible, and have a solid team before they list their collections on CUDOS Markets.</p>
<p>As well as facilitating the viewing, buying, and trading of hashrate collections, users also have access to gaming. By allowing users to battle each other for one another&rsquo;s hashrate, CUDOS Markets provides a rewarding gaming experience that opens up the marketplace for future metaverse functions. As part of this, NFT or CUDOS token holders will be given voting power to determine which games will be built next.</p>
Towards a Sustainable Crypto Ecosystem
<p>The emergence of hashrate NFTs has the potential to democratise the mining industry, while also providing people with new revenue streams. This could lead to increased innovation in the space and ultimately, a more robust and sustainable crypto ecosystem. As the world becomes increasingly concerned with the environmental impact of our technological advancements, the emergence of sustainable and decentralised alternatives to traditional Bitcoin mining is a promising development. While there are still challenges to overcome, the Web3 space offers exciting new possibilities for the future of cryptocurrency.</p>


<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>

]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin mining has faced increasing scrutiny in recent years due to its significant energy consumption and environmental impact. According to estimates, the energy consumption of the Bitcoin network exceeds that of entire countries, and the carbon footprint of mining is equivalent to that of a small country. This has led to concerns about the sustainability of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies and their impact on the environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Bitcoin has been mined through a process known as Proof-of-Work (PoW) since its inception in 2009. However, the environmental impact and centralisation issues associated with traditional Bitcoin mining have reared their head in recent years. Emerging solutions in the Web3 space may offer a more sustainable and decentralised path forward.</p>
Traditional Bitcoin Mining
<p>PoW mining requires powerful computers to solve complex mathematical equations, which consumes massive amounts of energy. According to some estimates, Bitcoin mining alone consumes more electricity than the entire country of Argentina. This figure has been contested by pro-bitcoin advocates, however it gives an indication of the amount of electricity consumed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a further blow to the decentralised ethos of the blockchain, PoW mining has become increasingly centralised, with the majority of mining power controlled by a small number of large mining pools. This concentration of power poses a threat to the decentralisation that is supposed to be a core tenet of blockchain technology. Some mining operations are exploring more sustainable methods, such as renewable energy sources, but the issue remains a significant challenge for the industry.</p>
<p>Proof-of-Stake (PoS) is one such solution, where instead of using computational power to mine new coins, users can "stake" their coins as collateral to validate transactions and create new blocks. This process consumes far less energy and eliminates the need for expensive hardware, making it a more environmentally friendly and accessible option.</p>
Sustainable NFT solutions
<p>Other solutions, such as decentralised storage and computing platforms, also offer alternatives to the energy-intensive PoW mining. These platforms allow users to rent out their unused computing power and storage space, creating a more decentralised and sustainable ecosystem.</p>
<p>And while the Web3 space is still in its nascence, the innovation within Web3 is considerable. CUDOS Markets is a marketplace created by the founders of the sustainable and carbon-neutral Cudos blockchain and Cudo Compute, that provides a unique solution to Bitcoin mining. The platform offers a simplified and user-friendly approach to cryptocurrency mining and brings utility to the world of digital collectibles. By tokenizing hashrate, it enables anyone to participate in the mining process, regardless of technical knowledge or access to expensive hardware.&nbsp;</p>
<p>NFTs are tied to sustainable mining farms, which allow users to purchase a share of a mining pool's computational resources, providing them with a direct stake in the mining rewards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Users can sell their collectibles on the open marketplace whenever they want. The platform also offers instant liquidity and daily rewards, making it an attractive option for those looking to earn cryptocurrencies without the complexities of traditional mining.</p>
Transparency and Due Diligence&nbsp;
<p>CUDOS Markets is built to be fully transparent, with each seller&rsquo;s collection displaying maintenance costs. CUDOS Markets&rsquo;s strict due diligence process ensures that new BTC mining farms are financially sound, environmentally and sustainably responsible, and have a solid team before they list their collections on CUDOS Markets.</p>
<p>As well as facilitating the viewing, buying, and trading of hashrate collections, users also have access to gaming. By allowing users to battle each other for one another&rsquo;s hashrate, CUDOS Markets provides a rewarding gaming experience that opens up the marketplace for future metaverse functions. As part of this, NFT or CUDOS token holders will be given voting power to determine which games will be built next.</p>
Towards a Sustainable Crypto Ecosystem
<p>The emergence of hashrate NFTs has the potential to democratise the mining industry, while also providing people with new revenue streams. This could lead to increased innovation in the space and ultimately, a more robust and sustainable crypto ecosystem. As the world becomes increasingly concerned with the environmental impact of our technological advancements, the emergence of sustainable and decentralised alternatives to traditional Bitcoin mining is a promising development. While there are still challenges to overcome, the Web3 space offers exciting new possibilities for the future of cryptocurrency.</p>


<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>

]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mattel to Introduce Its Own P2P Virtual Collectibles Marketplace]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/mattel-to-introduce-its-own-p2p-virtual-collectibles-marketplace</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mattel-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mattel-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/mattel-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:50:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/mattel-to-introduce-its-own-p2p-virtual-collectibles-marketplace</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Mattel Inc. has announced an upcoming update to the Mattel Creations Virtual Collectibles Platform. The update will change its virtual platform into a peer-to-peer marketplace for collectors.&nbsp;</p>
A New Peer-To-Peer Marketplace&nbsp;
<p>Mattel announced the update in a press release on Thursday. According to the statement, owners of Mallet virtual collectibles will be able to display, trade, and sell their collectibles starting from the 27th of April on the Mattel Creations Virtual Collectibles Platform. The vice president at Mattel Future Lab, Ron Friedman, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When we first set out to launch our own Virtual Collectibles Platform, we did so with the intention of creating an unrivaled, best-in-class experience for the fans of Mattel&rsquo;s iconic brands. In adding a marketplace feature to our easy-to-navigate platform that enables users to sell and trade their virtual collectibles, we&rsquo;ve taken another step toward realizing that vision. Especially as we unveil Series 5 of the Hot Wheels NFT Garage, we can&rsquo;t wait for fans and collectors of all ages to experience the updated platform.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The marketplace will be powered by Rarible, a blue-chip company specializing in virtual collectibles. Wallet-as-a-Service provider Magic will assist Rarible. Thanks to Magic&rsquo;s non-custodial wallet, SDK, Mattel could greatly simplify the wallet-generation experience and give users a seamless onboarding experience.&nbsp;</p>
Mattel To Debut Its Hot Wheels NFT Garage&nbsp;
<p>Mattel also revealed that it is debuting the fifth iteration of its Hot Wheels NFT Garage to coincide with the marketplace&rsquo;s launch. According to Mattel&rsquo;s press release,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Developed by the same team behind Hot Wheels die-cast cars, Series 5 of the Hot Wheels NFT Garage is the latest way for fans to collect digital artwork featuring Mattel&rsquo;s iconic IP, and features some of Hot Wheels&rsquo; most popular car designs in an all-new, digital format.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Series 5 of Hot Wheels NFT Garage features 40 unique cars, which include Aston Martin, Pagani, Mclaren, Porsche, and Chevrolet, along with several Hot Wheels Originals. All are sold in packs which are priced at $25 each. The IP (Intellectual Property) has been especially valuable to Mattel, especially when the company had stated earlier in the year that it was working on a strategy to leverage its IP in new areas such as theme parks and entertainment. CEO Ynon Kreiz had stated back in February,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We continued to strengthen our relationships with the major entertainment companies with additions or extensions of key licenses, including Disney Princess and Disney Frozen, Pok&eacute;mon, and Universal&rsquo;s Trolls. We have grown Mattel Creations, our collector [D2C] business, which is capitalizing on the strength of our franchises and built-in fan base, increasing traffic by over 40% and volume by over 85%.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Mattel&rsquo;s Virtual Collectibles Platform made its debut in November 2022, offering a range of collectibles that drew inspiration from the company&rsquo;s iconic brands, offering a seamless user experience and a practical price point. Every prior release of the company&rsquo;s Hot Wheels NFT Garage digital collectibles have sold out instantly, with Series 4 selling thirty thousand packs in less than twelve hours. Mattel currently owns one of the strongest catalogs of family and children&rsquo;s entertainment franchises in the world.&nbsp;</p>
Other Retailers Moving Away?&nbsp;
<p>Mattel was the first toy company to launch NFTs and continues to expand in the digital ecosystem. Mattel&rsquo;s investment into a digital marketplace comes at a time when other retailers are moving away from the digital and virtual worlds. Walmart shut down its Universe of Play metaverse experience on Roblox mere months after launch. However, the retail giant stated it always intended to shutter the experience after some time. Disney has also shuttered its division tasked with creating metaverse strategies and experiences. The decision came shortly after Meta announced that its Metaverse arm had seen a staggering $4.3 billion loss in the fourth quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mattel Inc. has announced an upcoming update to the Mattel Creations Virtual Collectibles Platform. The update will change its virtual platform into a peer-to-peer marketplace for collectors.&nbsp;</p>
A New Peer-To-Peer Marketplace&nbsp;
<p>Mattel announced the update in a press release on Thursday. According to the statement, owners of Mallet virtual collectibles will be able to display, trade, and sell their collectibles starting from the 27th of April on the Mattel Creations Virtual Collectibles Platform. The vice president at Mattel Future Lab, Ron Friedman, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;When we first set out to launch our own Virtual Collectibles Platform, we did so with the intention of creating an unrivaled, best-in-class experience for the fans of Mattel&rsquo;s iconic brands. In adding a marketplace feature to our easy-to-navigate platform that enables users to sell and trade their virtual collectibles, we&rsquo;ve taken another step toward realizing that vision. Especially as we unveil Series 5 of the Hot Wheels NFT Garage, we can&rsquo;t wait for fans and collectors of all ages to experience the updated platform.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The marketplace will be powered by Rarible, a blue-chip company specializing in virtual collectibles. Wallet-as-a-Service provider Magic will assist Rarible. Thanks to Magic&rsquo;s non-custodial wallet, SDK, Mattel could greatly simplify the wallet-generation experience and give users a seamless onboarding experience.&nbsp;</p>
Mattel To Debut Its Hot Wheels NFT Garage&nbsp;
<p>Mattel also revealed that it is debuting the fifth iteration of its Hot Wheels NFT Garage to coincide with the marketplace&rsquo;s launch. According to Mattel&rsquo;s press release,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Developed by the same team behind Hot Wheels die-cast cars, Series 5 of the Hot Wheels NFT Garage is the latest way for fans to collect digital artwork featuring Mattel&rsquo;s iconic IP, and features some of Hot Wheels&rsquo; most popular car designs in an all-new, digital format.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Series 5 of Hot Wheels NFT Garage features 40 unique cars, which include Aston Martin, Pagani, Mclaren, Porsche, and Chevrolet, along with several Hot Wheels Originals. All are sold in packs which are priced at $25 each. The IP (Intellectual Property) has been especially valuable to Mattel, especially when the company had stated earlier in the year that it was working on a strategy to leverage its IP in new areas such as theme parks and entertainment. CEO Ynon Kreiz had stated back in February,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We continued to strengthen our relationships with the major entertainment companies with additions or extensions of key licenses, including Disney Princess and Disney Frozen, Pok&eacute;mon, and Universal&rsquo;s Trolls. We have grown Mattel Creations, our collector [D2C] business, which is capitalizing on the strength of our franchises and built-in fan base, increasing traffic by over 40% and volume by over 85%.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Mattel&rsquo;s Virtual Collectibles Platform made its debut in November 2022, offering a range of collectibles that drew inspiration from the company&rsquo;s iconic brands, offering a seamless user experience and a practical price point. Every prior release of the company&rsquo;s Hot Wheels NFT Garage digital collectibles have sold out instantly, with Series 4 selling thirty thousand packs in less than twelve hours. Mattel currently owns one of the strongest catalogs of family and children&rsquo;s entertainment franchises in the world.&nbsp;</p>
Other Retailers Moving Away?&nbsp;
<p>Mattel was the first toy company to launch NFTs and continues to expand in the digital ecosystem. Mattel&rsquo;s investment into a digital marketplace comes at a time when other retailers are moving away from the digital and virtual worlds. Walmart shut down its Universe of Play metaverse experience on Roblox mere months after launch. However, the retail giant stated it always intended to shutter the experience after some time. Disney has also shuttered its division tasked with creating metaverse strategies and experiences. The decision came shortly after Meta announced that its Metaverse arm had seen a staggering $4.3 billion loss in the fourth quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Brazilian Authorities To Probe Binance After Stop Order Fiasco]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/brazilian-authorities-to-probe-binance-after-stop-order-fiasco</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/brazilian-authorities-to-probe-binance-after-stop-order-fiasco</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, is facing a probe in Brazil, with authorities confirming the launch of an official investigation into the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Authorities allege that Binance failed to respond to a stop order, directing it to stop selling crypto derivatives.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Accused Of Financial Crimes In Brazil&nbsp;
<p>Brazilian authorities have launched an official investigation into Binance, alleging financial crimes facilitated through its derivatives offerings. Authorities also stated that the exchange failed to respond to a stop order, ordering the exchange to stop selling crypto derivatives. Brazilian media speculated that the probe was launched following a tip-off from the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission (Comiss&atilde;o de Valores Mobili&aacute;rios - CVM), the country&rsquo;s primary market regulator.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to reports, the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission informed the Attorney General of Sao Paolo that the cryptocurrency exchange allegedly ignored a &ldquo;stop order&rdquo; issued by the state. As a result, the exchange allegedly offered crypto derivatives to Brazil users in violation of the law. As a result of the tip-off, the Federal Police and the Federal Prosecutor&rsquo;s Office have launched an investigation into the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Remains Mum&nbsp;
<p>Binance has, so far, refused to comment on the ongoing situation. While the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission has submitted documents in support of its claims, Binance has categorically denied offering derivatives in Brazil. The exchange stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance does not comment on ongoing investigations. However, we do not offer derivatives in Brazil. We take a collaborative approach in working with regulators, and we take our compliance obligations very seriously.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The Comiss&atilde;o de Valores Mobili&aacute;rios revealed that it had issued the stop order in 2020, after which the exchange stated that it would cease offering crypto derivatives in Brazil. However, staff members discovered that they could still access derivatives offerings on Binance by changing the language on the Binance app or website.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On its part, Binance added that it was in contact with authorities overseeing the crypto space in Brazil and other jurisdictions around the world.&nbsp;</p>
Troubles Mount For Brazil&nbsp;
<p>Binance has had a difficult start to 2023, with the exchange facing growing headaches thanks to a number of issues. In the first week of April, it was revealed that the Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) had revoked Binance&rsquo;s derivatives license. The license allowed the exchange to offer derivatives services to users based in Australia since July 2022. The cancellation of the license came in response to a request submitted by the exchange and took effect immediately. ASIC directed that all derivatives trades and dealings on Binance should cease by the 14th of April.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Just last week, Dubai&rsquo;s Virtual Regulatory Authority (VARA) requested Binance to provide additional information about the platform&rsquo;s ownership structure and auditing procedures as it applied for an operating license. It also requested for additional details when it came to the platform&rsquo;s governance. Binance responded to the request, stating that it had disclosed all necessary replies and answers to VARA on a proactive basis, all of which were in line with its regulatory and fiduciary responsibilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Reports also emerged that Binance&rsquo;s US arm was facing considerable difficulty in securing a banking partner following the collapse of Slvergate Bank and increased regulatory scrutiny on the crypto space. Before the ongoing banking crises, all customer deposits were either sent to Signature Bank or Silvergate Capital Corp. As a result, Binance has informed users that certain USD deposit services will be temporarily unavailable until it transitions to a new banking partner.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, is facing a probe in Brazil, with authorities confirming the launch of an official investigation into the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Authorities allege that Binance failed to respond to a stop order, directing it to stop selling crypto derivatives.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Accused Of Financial Crimes In Brazil&nbsp;
<p>Brazilian authorities have launched an official investigation into Binance, alleging financial crimes facilitated through its derivatives offerings. Authorities also stated that the exchange failed to respond to a stop order, ordering the exchange to stop selling crypto derivatives. Brazilian media speculated that the probe was launched following a tip-off from the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission (Comiss&atilde;o de Valores Mobili&aacute;rios - CVM), the country&rsquo;s primary market regulator.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to reports, the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission informed the Attorney General of Sao Paolo that the cryptocurrency exchange allegedly ignored a &ldquo;stop order&rdquo; issued by the state. As a result, the exchange allegedly offered crypto derivatives to Brazil users in violation of the law. As a result of the tip-off, the Federal Police and the Federal Prosecutor&rsquo;s Office have launched an investigation into the exchange.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Remains Mum&nbsp;
<p>Binance has, so far, refused to comment on the ongoing situation. While the Brazil Securities and Exchange Commission has submitted documents in support of its claims, Binance has categorically denied offering derivatives in Brazil. The exchange stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Binance does not comment on ongoing investigations. However, we do not offer derivatives in Brazil. We take a collaborative approach in working with regulators, and we take our compliance obligations very seriously.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The Comiss&atilde;o de Valores Mobili&aacute;rios revealed that it had issued the stop order in 2020, after which the exchange stated that it would cease offering crypto derivatives in Brazil. However, staff members discovered that they could still access derivatives offerings on Binance by changing the language on the Binance app or website.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On its part, Binance added that it was in contact with authorities overseeing the crypto space in Brazil and other jurisdictions around the world.&nbsp;</p>
Troubles Mount For Brazil&nbsp;
<p>Binance has had a difficult start to 2023, with the exchange facing growing headaches thanks to a number of issues. In the first week of April, it was revealed that the Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) had revoked Binance&rsquo;s derivatives license. The license allowed the exchange to offer derivatives services to users based in Australia since July 2022. The cancellation of the license came in response to a request submitted by the exchange and took effect immediately. ASIC directed that all derivatives trades and dealings on Binance should cease by the 14th of April.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Just last week, Dubai&rsquo;s Virtual Regulatory Authority (VARA) requested Binance to provide additional information about the platform&rsquo;s ownership structure and auditing procedures as it applied for an operating license. It also requested for additional details when it came to the platform&rsquo;s governance. Binance responded to the request, stating that it had disclosed all necessary replies and answers to VARA on a proactive basis, all of which were in line with its regulatory and fiduciary responsibilities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Reports also emerged that Binance&rsquo;s US arm was facing considerable difficulty in securing a banking partner following the collapse of Slvergate Bank and increased regulatory scrutiny on the crypto space. Before the ongoing banking crises, all customer deposits were either sent to Signature Bank or Silvergate Capital Corp. As a result, Binance has informed users that certain USD deposit services will be temporarily unavailable until it transitions to a new banking partner.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[MOOI Network Lists on MEXC, Increasing Accessibility for its Ecosystem]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/mooi-network-lists-on-mexc-increasing-accessibility-for-its-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/First_Listing_cover_16818106638rrll9rthG.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/First_Listing_cover_16818106638rrll9rthG.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/First_Listing_cover_16818106638rrll9rthG.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 07:06:49 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/mooi-network-lists-on-mexc-increasing-accessibility-for-its-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network, the blockchain ecosystem designed for game projects, is thrilled to announce the listing of its governance token, $MOOI, on MEXC Global, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange. The listing is scheduled for April 25 at 10:00 UTC and reflects MOOI Network's commitment to lowering barriers for new users and providing accessible options for engagement within its ecosystem.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Company Background</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network was created by POST VOYAGER, a subsidiary of Cocone, a Japan-based avatar styling &amp; gaming social app developer with users across 74 countries. Over the past 14 years, Cocone&rsquo;s flagship projects have attracted over 130 million downloads and 4.7M monthly active users. Meanwhile, in 2022 the highest daily profit from selling digital beauty and fashion items topped $1.7 million.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network</p><p class="ql-align-justify">With Cocone's roots in the Web2-based virtual world, MOOI Network was established to help the company&rsquo;s Web3 transition. Since the launch of MOOI Network on June 30th, 2022, POST VOYAGER and Cocone have built an outstanding portfolio filled with high-quality gaming titles and dapps, including MetaLivly, PKCL Twins, ClawKiss, and JANKEN. At the heart of the MOOI Network&rsquo;s economy is Jellyme, an NFT marketplace for blockchain-based games. Recently, the marketplace has seen a significant surge in popularity: according to DappRadar, the dapp&rsquo;s usage was up 7,312% in April, reaching 11,630 weekly active wallets.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bringing Access to the MOOI Ecosystem</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network remains dedicated to its mission of creating an open and inclusive metaverse world that is accessible to users from all backgrounds. The listing of MOOI on MEXC is a significant milestone for the project, and MOOI Network looks forward to introducing more ways to grow and expand its ecosystem by offering users a convenient and user-friendly way to participate in MOOI Network's vision through the listing of MOOI on MEXC Global.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Recent Updates</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Recently, MOOI launched the 'Space Flea Market' collection, featuring game items from Pokecolo, one of the Cocone's legendary avatar services. This collection has consistently ranked in the top-5 DappRadar NFT collectibles chart for over a month, attracting thousands of new users to the Web3 space. This success has propelled MOOI's marketplace, Jellyme, into the top 10 during March-April 2023, further solidifying MOOI's ability to attract and engage a growing community of users.</p><p class="ql-align-center"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">Further Plans</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Currently, MOOI Network is actively preparing for Q2 with upcoming exchange listings, on-ramp features, and other product launches. Stay tuned for exciting updates as MOOI Network continues to expand its offerings. In the long run, MOOI aims to become a first-tier game-tailored ecosystem, attracting fun and high-quality services to join Web3 and build thriving play-and-own economies using MOOI Network.</p><p>About MOOI Network</p><p>MOOI Network is creating a sustainable metaverse world by onboarding metaverse, GameFi, dApps, and NFT projects in a seamless way, providing a crypto wallet, NFT marketplace, and swap all within its ecosystem. MOOI Network ensures bringing in projects that are high-quality and provides a seamless onboarding experience.</p><p>To learn more about MOOI visit:&nbsp;</p><p>Official website | NFT Marketplace- Jellyme | Medium | Discord | Twitter</p>ContactHead of Business PlanningOleg SmaginPOST VOYAGERml_media@postvoyager.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network, the blockchain ecosystem designed for game projects, is thrilled to announce the listing of its governance token, $MOOI, on MEXC Global, a prominent cryptocurrency exchange. The listing is scheduled for April 25 at 10:00 UTC and reflects MOOI Network's commitment to lowering barriers for new users and providing accessible options for engagement within its ecosystem.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Company Background</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network was created by POST VOYAGER, a subsidiary of Cocone, a Japan-based avatar styling &amp; gaming social app developer with users across 74 countries. Over the past 14 years, Cocone&rsquo;s flagship projects have attracted over 130 million downloads and 4.7M monthly active users. Meanwhile, in 2022 the highest daily profit from selling digital beauty and fashion items topped $1.7 million.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network</p><p class="ql-align-justify">With Cocone's roots in the Web2-based virtual world, MOOI Network was established to help the company&rsquo;s Web3 transition. Since the launch of MOOI Network on June 30th, 2022, POST VOYAGER and Cocone have built an outstanding portfolio filled with high-quality gaming titles and dapps, including MetaLivly, PKCL Twins, ClawKiss, and JANKEN. At the heart of the MOOI Network&rsquo;s economy is Jellyme, an NFT marketplace for blockchain-based games. Recently, the marketplace has seen a significant surge in popularity: according to DappRadar, the dapp&rsquo;s usage was up 7,312% in April, reaching 11,630 weekly active wallets.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Bringing Access to the MOOI Ecosystem</p><p class="ql-align-justify">MOOI Network remains dedicated to its mission of creating an open and inclusive metaverse world that is accessible to users from all backgrounds. The listing of MOOI on MEXC is a significant milestone for the project, and MOOI Network looks forward to introducing more ways to grow and expand its ecosystem by offering users a convenient and user-friendly way to participate in MOOI Network's vision through the listing of MOOI on MEXC Global.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Recent Updates</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Recently, MOOI launched the 'Space Flea Market' collection, featuring game items from Pokecolo, one of the Cocone's legendary avatar services. This collection has consistently ranked in the top-5 DappRadar NFT collectibles chart for over a month, attracting thousands of new users to the Web3 space. This success has propelled MOOI's marketplace, Jellyme, into the top 10 during March-April 2023, further solidifying MOOI's ability to attract and engage a growing community of users.</p><p class="ql-align-center"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">Further Plans</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Currently, MOOI Network is actively preparing for Q2 with upcoming exchange listings, on-ramp features, and other product launches. Stay tuned for exciting updates as MOOI Network continues to expand its offerings. In the long run, MOOI aims to become a first-tier game-tailored ecosystem, attracting fun and high-quality services to join Web3 and build thriving play-and-own economies using MOOI Network.</p><p>About MOOI Network</p><p>MOOI Network is creating a sustainable metaverse world by onboarding metaverse, GameFi, dApps, and NFT projects in a seamless way, providing a crypto wallet, NFT marketplace, and swap all within its ecosystem. MOOI Network ensures bringing in projects that are high-quality and provides a seamless onboarding experience.</p><p>To learn more about MOOI visit:&nbsp;</p><p>Official website | NFT Marketplace- Jellyme | Medium | Discord | Twitter</p>ContactHead of Business PlanningOleg SmaginPOST VOYAGERml_media@postvoyager.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Take Out 28479 - 21 April 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-take-out-28479-21-april-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-april-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-april-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-20-april-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 21:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-take-out-28479-21-april-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Take Out 28479:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 21 April 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent pullback early in the Asian session as the pair remained heavy below the 29000 figure after crashing below the 28428.91 area, a previous price objective associated with buying pressure around the 27564.10 area in early April.&nbsp; Traders knocked BTC/USD as low as the 28353.10 area after Stops were elected below the 28479.91 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 30500 area.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 28274, 28034, 27758, 27283, 27119, 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical resistance include the 29159, 29383, 29408, 29657, 29701, 29965, 30012, 30413, and 30472 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical support include the 27370, 26664, 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, and 21415 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29176.01 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29535.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;28034.13/ 27887.62/ 26297.85 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Take Out 28479:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 21 April 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent pullback early in the Asian session as the pair remained heavy below the 29000 figure after crashing below the 28428.91 area, a previous price objective associated with buying pressure around the 27564.10 area in early April.&nbsp; Traders knocked BTC/USD as low as the 28353.10 area after Stops were elected below the 28479.91 area, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 30500 area.&nbsp; Downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 28274, 28034, 27758, 27283, 27119, 26533, 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical resistance include the 29159, 29383, 29408, 29657, 29701, 29965, 30012, 30413, and 30472 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, retracement levels and areas of potential technical support include the 27370, 26664, 25309, 25094, 23954, 23255, and 21415 levels.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Another important price objective is the 31846.88 area, a level that represents the 50% retracement of the depreciating range from 48233.76 to 15460.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29176.01 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29535.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;28034.13/ 27887.62/ 26297.85 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Pink Moon Studios Launches its Highly Anticipated Free-to-Play Mode for KMON Genesis]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/pink-moon-studios-launches-its-highly-anticipated-free-to-play-mode-for-kmon-genesis</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/unnamed_2_1682003132swCkElBPo5.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/unnamed_2_1682003132swCkElBPo5.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/unnamed_2_1682003132swCkElBPo5.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:25:32 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/04/pink-moon-studios-launches-its-highly-anticipated-free-to-play-mode-for-kmon-genesis</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Rebranding from Kryptomon to KMON Genesis, the move will significantly lower the barriers of entry to one of the world's most popular web3 games.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Today, Pink Moon Studios, a leading web3 gaming company, announced the launch of a free-to-play mode for its renowned strategy game, KMON Genesis (formerly Kryptomon). KMON Genesis allows players to breed, collect, and trade unique creatures as they traverse the enthralling KMON universe. As one of the first web3 games in the world, KMON Genesis gives players a seamless gaming experience without the need to purchase NFTs in advance, further lowering barriers to entry to a broader range of players.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Set in the Kryptomon universe, community members play as &ldquo;Trainers,&rdquo; taking care of their own NFT pets, which have a unique and mutable genetic code made up of 38 randomized parameters that determine their physical and behavioral characteristics. Kryptomons can learn, fall sick, get hungry, and protect their trainers when out on an adventure in the physical world. In turn, trainers will have to care for, feed, and train their Kryptomon partners in order to grow and prepare for the battles ahead. To incentivize gameplay, Pink Moon Studios shares revenue from KMON Genesis with its players by distributing weekly monetary rewards when they complete in-game challenges, which average $50 in tokens.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">"Our core mission has always been to make the enthralling KMON Genesis universe accessible to everyone.&rdquo; stated Umberto Canessa Cerchi, Founder &amp; CEO of Pink Moon Studios,&nbsp;&ldquo;The introduction of the free-to-play mode is a game-changer, inviting players from all backgrounds to experience the innovative and exciting world we've developed, without any financial barriers or web3-related technological hurdles."</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In a recent partnership with Playdex, Pink Moon Studios also introduced exclusive rental features for KMON on-chain assets, further enhancing the gaming experience and offering players even more flexibility and opportunities for growth within the game. To commemorate the launch of the free-to-play mode, Pink Moon Studios will host a community event showcasing its upcoming mobile MMORPG, World of Kogaea, which is currently under development. Players can obtain a unique digital collectible throughout the event by completing specified quests. Space for the special event is limited, and interested players are encouraged to register early to secure their spots. Further information about the event will be available on the Pink Moon Studios' official website in the near future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">"We are eager to offer players a sneak peek into the mesmerizing digital realm of World of Kogaea,&rdquo; said Brian Bento, Chief Product Officer and SVP of Game Development at Pink Moon Studios, shared his enthusiasm, stating, &ldquo;Our dedicated team has poured countless hours into crafting a visually spectacular and engaging experience that players will find truly captivating."</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Pink Moon Studios</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Pink Moon Studios is revolutionizing web3 gaming by delivering immersive, captivating, and groundbreaking gaming experiences that defy traditional norms. With extensive expertise in web3, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and augmented reality (AR) technology, Pink Moon Studios is uniquely positioned to create gaming solutions that bridge the gap between the digital and physical worlds.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For additional details about KMON Genesis, the revolutionary free-to-play mode, and the latest developments from Pink Moon Studios, please visit https://pink-moon.studio/</p>ContactCBDOTomer Warschauer NuniPink Moon Studio Ltdtomer@pink-moon.studio+972547000765]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, April 20th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Rebranding from Kryptomon to KMON Genesis, the move will significantly lower the barriers of entry to one of the world's most popular web3 games.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Today, Pink Moon Studios, a leading web3 gaming company, announced the launch of a free-to-play mode for its renowned strategy game, KMON Genesis (formerly Kryptomon). KMON Genesis allows players to breed, collect, and trade unique creatures as they traverse the enthralling KMON universe. As one of the first web3 games in the world, KMON Genesis gives players a seamless gaming experience without the need to purchase NFTs in advance, further lowering barriers to entry to a broader range of players.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Set in the Kryptomon universe, community members play as &ldquo;Trainers,&rdquo; taking care of their own NFT pets, which have a unique and mutable genetic code made up of 38 randomized parameters that determine their physical and behavioral characteristics. Kryptomons can learn, fall sick, get hungry, and protect their trainers when out on an adventure in the physical world. In turn, trainers will have to care for, feed, and train their Kryptomon partners in order to grow and prepare for the battles ahead. To incentivize gameplay, Pink Moon Studios shares revenue from KMON Genesis with its players by distributing weekly monetary rewards when they complete in-game challenges, which average $50 in tokens.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">"Our core mission has always been to make the enthralling KMON Genesis universe accessible to everyone.&rdquo; stated Umberto Canessa Cerchi, Founder &amp; CEO of Pink Moon Studios,&nbsp;&ldquo;The introduction of the free-to-play mode is a game-changer, inviting players from all backgrounds to experience the innovative and exciting world we've developed, without any financial barriers or web3-related technological hurdles."</p><p class="ql-align-justify">In a recent partnership with Playdex, Pink Moon Studios also introduced exclusive rental features for KMON on-chain assets, further enhancing the gaming experience and offering players even more flexibility and opportunities for growth within the game. To commemorate the launch of the free-to-play mode, Pink Moon Studios will host a community event showcasing its upcoming mobile MMORPG, World of Kogaea, which is currently under development. Players can obtain a unique digital collectible throughout the event by completing specified quests. Space for the special event is limited, and interested players are encouraged to register early to secure their spots. Further information about the event will be available on the Pink Moon Studios' official website in the near future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify"></p><p class="ql-align-justify">"We are eager to offer players a sneak peek into the mesmerizing digital realm of World of Kogaea,&rdquo; said Brian Bento, Chief Product Officer and SVP of Game Development at Pink Moon Studios, shared his enthusiasm, stating, &ldquo;Our dedicated team has poured countless hours into crafting a visually spectacular and engaging experience that players will find truly captivating."</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Pink Moon Studios</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Pink Moon Studios is revolutionizing web3 gaming by delivering immersive, captivating, and groundbreaking gaming experiences that defy traditional norms. With extensive expertise in web3, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and augmented reality (AR) technology, Pink Moon Studios is uniquely positioned to create gaming solutions that bridge the gap between the digital and physical worlds.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For additional details about KMON Genesis, the revolutionary free-to-play mode, and the latest developments from Pink Moon Studios, please visit https://pink-moon.studio/</p>ContactCBDOTomer Warschauer NuniPink Moon Studio Ltdtomer@pink-moon.studio+972547000765]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
