<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:30:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Visa Pilots Innovative Approach for Paying On-Chain Gas Fees with Visa Card</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/visa-pilots-innovative-approach-for-paying-on-chain-gas-fees-with-visa-card/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 14:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Visa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265862</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/visa_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/visa_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Visa is working on a solution to eliminate the need for users to hold ETH merely for paying gas fees.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American payment goliath Visa is exploring ways to facilitate payment of on-chain gas fees through the use of a Visa card.</p>
<p>In a recent report, Visa&#8217;s Product Manager Mustafa Bedawala emphasized a challenge associated with cryptocurrency wallets faced by users which requires them to constantly manage their ETH balance to cover gas fees.</p>
<p>The company is experimenting with an option to enable users to pay their on-chain gas fees directly in fiat money through card payments, thereby simplifying blockchain transactions.</p>
<h2>Visa&#8217;s Solution for Gas Fees</h2>
<p>Under Visa&#8217;s scenario, users may no longer need to hold native tokens specific to a blockchain exclusively to cover gas fees. This resolution would leverage Ethereum&#8217;s ERC-4337 standard and a &#8216;Paymaster&#8217; contract, allowing customers to utilize a Visa card for the direct payment of gas fees.</p>
<p>This approach is not only expected to be a major relief for existing users but is also designed to help streamline the onboarding process for new ones.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our proposed solution liberates users from the need to hold native blockchain tokens or constantly engage in bridging tokens merely to cover gas fees. From a user’s perspective, this solution is appealing in its simplicity and ease of adoption.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Visa suggests a solution that involves receiving the user&#8217;s gas fee payment off-chain through a Visa card and subsequently covering the equivalent sum on-chain on their behalf. This process simplifies the gas fee experience, resembling a typical card payment transaction.</p>
<p>The setup implemented by the payments firm to permit the off-chain gas payment capability is centered around a &#8216;Verifying Paymaster,&#8217; which is essentially a smart contract that delegates all necessary checks and sourcing of information to an off-chain component.</p>
<p>The on-chain paymaster smart contract can then utilize the information and authorization provided by the off-chain component to validate and execute the payment for the gas fee.</p>
<p>The payment is processed via Cybersource, and the web service produces a digital signature. Successful verification of the signature indicates that the web service has indeed received the card payment to facilitate the operational expenses. In such a case, the paymaster contract will operate without any errors and will cover the associated gas fee accordingly.</p>
<h2>Gasless Transactions</h2>
<p>Visa has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-deploys-paymaster-contracts-on-ethereum-testnest-for-gasless-transactions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">experimented</a> with this idea on the Ethereum Goerli testnet, making use of accessible open-source tools like Stackup&#8217;s userop.js library. The trial transactions successfully handled fees via the Paymaster, eliminating the need for ETH in the process.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/visa-pilots-innovative-approach-for-paying-on-chain-gas-fees-with-visa-card/" rel="nofollow">Visa Pilots Innovative Approach for Paying On-Chain Gas Fees with Visa Card</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Are Whales Investing in on Coinbase&#8217;s Base Network? Nansen Investigates</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-whales-investing-in-on-coinbases-base-network-nansen-investigates/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Whale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265921</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/whale_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/whale_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The first “crypto native degens” to use Base had a surprisingly large allocation to memecoins.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nansen – a blockchain market intelligence firm – released a report on Tuesday analyzing how the earliest whales to onboard Coinbase’s layer 2 blockchain – Base – are using their money.</p>
<p>Here’s what the company found.</p>
<ul>
<li>Early whales largely allocated to Ethereum and its layer 2 networks. As of August 7, the most value held by these whales ($19.6 million) was on Ethereum itself, followed by Base ($17.6 million), Arbitrum, and Optimism.</li>
<li>Regarding tokens, ETH was the most common holding at $11.6 million. Beneath it were relatively large memecoin allocations, including Bald at $2.7 million (skewed by the BALD deployer), UNIBOT ($284,000), and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-exploded-by-300-in-a-week-but-its-definitely-not-what-you-think/" data-wpel-link="internal">BITCOIN</a> ($273,000).</li>
<li>Some of the most common entities these whales are interacting with include commonly used decentralized exchanges, such as Uniswap and 1Inch.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“Most of their activity comprises DEXs, stables, L2s, and common DeFi apps,” <a href="https://research.nansen.ai/articles/what-are-early-base-whales-doing-on-chain" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wrote</a> Nansen. Much like token and chain allocation, protocol usage tends to congregate around a few “trustworthy” DeFi apps.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The analysis pertains to whales who bridged assets to Base before its official launch this week, meaning they had to access the ecosystem without a prepared front-end.</li>
<li>Based on this, Nansen assumes many of those early depositors were “crypto native degens.”</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“In reviewing the landscape of Early Base Bridgers, it&#8217;s evident that the crypto-native segment is actively engaging with the BASE platform even prior to its official launch,” concluded the report.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Base <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-notches-4th-rank-in-daily-tps-among-layer-2-solutions-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">officially launched</a> on August 9, accruing 136,000 daily active users within the first two days.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-whales-investing-in-on-coinbases-base-network-nansen-investigates/" rel="nofollow">What Are Whales Investing in on Coinbase&#8217;s Base Network? Nansen Investigates</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Labs Commits 10 Million USD to Helio Protocol to Advance the LSDfi Revolution</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-commits-10-million-usd-to-helio-protocol-to-advance-the-lsdfi-revolution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265957</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-12_10-55-47_1691817954HU8L5sBWju.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/photo_2023-08-12_10-55-47_1691817954HU8L5sBWju.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, UK, August 12th, 2023] Binance Labs, the venture capital and incubation arm of Binance, has committed 10 Million USD to Helio Protocol, a project combining over-collateralized lending of its native decentralized stablecoin, HAY, with staking-as-a-service (StaaS) and LSDfi infrastructure, with approximately combined 300 million USD in TVL, of which 260 million [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, UK, August 12th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Binance Labs, the venture capital and incubation arm of Binance, has committed 10 Million USD to <a href="https://helio.money/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Helio Protocol</a>, a project combining over-collateralized lending of its native decentralized stablecoin, HAY, with staking-as-a-service (StaaS) and<a href="https://research.binance.com/en/analysis/lsdfi-when-liquid-staking-meets-defi" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> LSDfi</a> infrastructure, with approximately combined 300 million USD in TVL, of which 260 million USD is parked under staked assets. This strategic funding round emphasizes Binance Labs&#8217; dedication to supporting innovative projects that are set to shape the next era of DeFi.</p>
<p>In July 2023, Helio Protocol acquired <a href="https://www.synclub.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Synclub</a> to unleash the full potential of HAY by incorporating additional LSTs as collateral, thus empowering users by increasing capital efficiency for maximum rewards. The addition of Synclub’s staking infrastructure and expertise will also further cultivate the product innovation required to secure a safer and more refined staking experience for users. The upgrade brings a variety of product revamps, including new collateral conversion and withdrawal opportunities.</p>
<blockquote><p>Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, commented: “Binance Labs is committed to supporting DeFi projects and founders driving innovation for the future of the Web3 industry. We have seen tremendous potential in the LSDfi sector, which plays a crucial role in driving the overall growth of the DeFi ecosystem. We look forward to working with Helio and Synclub, and hope to see the project grow as a leading LSDfi protocol on BNB Chain and other blockchains.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Unlocking the Complete Potential of Liquid Staking Tokens</h2>
<p>Helio Protocol will allocate the funds to expand its team, further diversify the collateral across liquid staking providers, and bolster support for future multi-chain growth. These initiatives will ensure that Helio and Synclub deliver a robust, secure, and diversified platform for the LSDfi community. The team is also set to release a development roadmap for the community and refresh the project’s branding to signal this new chapter of growth and innovation.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our mission is to provide the community with access to a quality, high-security LSDfi infrastructure, helping users enhance the capital efficiency and the rewards of their on-chain assets in a secure space,&#8221; said Toru, Founder and CEO of Helio Protocol. &#8220;This investment will also bring critical resources and connections to Helio to drive further growth.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>About Helio Protocol</h2>
<p>Helio Protocol combines over-collateralized, decentralized stablecoin lending and borrowing on BNB Chain with multi-chain StaaS and LSDfi services through its Synclub offerings. Currently, Helio Protocol has achieved 11,000 HAY holders and an estimated 300 million USD in TVL, of which 260 million USD are assets under management on Synclub&#8217;s validator node, positioning Synclub as the second-largest validator on BNB Chain.</p>
<p>For more information, follow <a href="http://helio.money" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Helio Protocol</a> on<a href="https://twitter.com/Helio_Money" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Twitter. </a></p>
<h2>About Binance Labs</h2>
<p>As the venture capital arm and accelerator of Binance, Binance Labs has now grown to be worth over 9 billion USD. Its portfolio covers 200 projects from over 25 countries across six continents and has a return on investment rate of over 10X. Fifty of Binance Labs’ portfolio companies are projects that have gone through our incubation programs. For more information, follow Binance Labs on<a href="https://twitter.com/BinanceLabs" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Twitter</a>.</p>
<p><em><strong>Disclaimer</strong>: BNB Chain is a public, decentralized, and permissionless blockchain. We do not and cannot control activity and data on BNB Chain or the activities that community participants or independent third-party projects may develop using BNB Chain. </em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-commits-10-million-usd-to-helio-protocol-to-advance-the-lsdfi-revolution/" rel="nofollow">Binance Labs Commits 10 Million USD to Helio Protocol to Advance the LSDfi Revolution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu Meets Pomerdoge (POMD) &#8211; Which Coin Has the Bite for Long-Term Growth?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-meets-pomerdoge-pomd-which-coin-has-the-bite-for-long-term-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 12:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265935</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-3.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-3.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coins have become a hot investment option in the crypto world. Moreover, if a meme coin comes with a utility, investors are waiting to pounce on the project. Such projects carry the popularity and market growth of meme coins and the stability of utility tokens. Therefore, no sooner did Pomerdoge launch its presale, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coins have become a hot investment option in the crypto world. Moreover, if a meme coin comes with a utility, investors are waiting to pounce on the project.</p>
<p>Such projects carry the popularity and market growth of meme coins and the stability of utility tokens. Therefore, no sooner did Pomerdoge launch its presale, it became one of the top-performing assets in the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Summary:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Pomerdog’s presale token is currently costing $0.007.</li>
<li>Its ecosystem is comprised of multiple initiatives to foster long-term growth.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://pomerdoge.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</a></p>
<h2>Pomerdoge &#8211; A Revolutionary P2E Game</h2>
<p>The play-2-earn games are dominating the blockchain gaming space. The recent market records have suggested that P2E is one of the most exciting gaming platforms. Hence, some experts believe that Pomergame can reach the moon with its growth-oriented business roadmap.</p>
<h2>What Does <a href="https://pomerdoge.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Pomerdoge</a> Consist Of?</h2>
<p>Pomerdoge has announced that it will soon launch a new P2E game. This new platform will combine the characteristics of meme coins, and P2E games. Pomerdoge will enable users to play and earn simultaneously. Its new P2E game will be called Pomergame, where users can create characters. Gamers can also use their creativity, and customize in-game items like skins. Besides, gamers can sell or trade in-game items to generate income after they get a gold status Pomer.</p>
<p>Pomerplace will be the marketplace where gamers will get to sell, buy, or trade their in-game assets. Interestingly, it will also serve as the arena where battles between players will take place. At Pomerplace, users will be able to battle against other members using their Pomerdoge. Since the arena follows the concept of “winners take all,” gamers will have to maintain their best form in the battle.</p>
<p>Pomerdoge will also release a collection of 7,777 NFTs during its presale round. Each NFT will have unique utility and value in the ecosystem. Moreover, the buying price of each NFT will be just 0.2 ETH and provide its holders with multiple benefits. However, the developers have not revealed the benefits yet. They will do so near the project’s launch date. Nevertheless, only POMD token holders will get an opportunity to purchase these NFTs.</p>
<h2>A Secure And Profitable Option</h2>
<p>The platform’s token smart contract has undergone thorough audits by Solid Proof and Cyber Scope. Moreover, its liquidity will be locked for life to make it the safest investment for buyers. Given all these benefits and use cases, Pomerdoge has emerged as the most attractive investment option.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We will shortly be showing you what the pomerplace looks like!</p>
<p>This is a marketplace and arena where you can battle one and other in a winner takes all situation for your pomerdoge!</p>
<p>Collect and purchase skins, items and give your pomerdoge better attributes to be the king of… <a href="https://t.co/WBKGwzo4vV" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/WBKGwzo4vV</a></p>
<p>— Pomerdoge (@pomerdoge) <a href="https://twitter.com/pomerdoge/status/1689929061944999936?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Currently, the platform’s presale is in the first stage, and a POMD token is available to purchase at just $0.007. Since the platform’s presale follows a dynamic model, the token’s price will increase at every stage.</p>
<p>Besides, Pomerdoge will also offer weekly giveaways. The platform will give a $50,000 mega Pomer prize alongside $100,000 in giveaways. As the launch date of the game comes near, more investors are joining Pomerdoge. So, you may have to hurry if you want to lock fast-selling <a href="https://pomerdoge.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">POMD</a> tokens.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today</p>
<p>Website: <a href="https://pomerdoge.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://pomerdoge.com/</a></p>
<p>Telegram Community: <a href="https://t.me/pomerdoge" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://t.me/pomerdoge</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-meets-pomerdoge-pomd-which-coin-has-the-bite-for-long-term-growth/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu Meets Pomerdoge (POMD) &#8211; Which Coin Has the Bite for Long-Term Growth?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SHIB, APE, PEPE Jump 8% Daily, Bitcoin Maintains $29K: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shib-ape-pepe-jump-8-daily-bitcoin-maintains-29k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265946</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba_Inu_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba_Inu_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SHIB continues to gain momentum, and so has done another asset from the Shiba Inu ecosystem - BONE.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price performance continues to be rather underwhelming, with the asset remaining at essentially the same spot as yesterday at just over $29,000.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also quite stagnant today, with little-to-no movements from ETH, BNB, XRP, and others. Shiba Inu is the only exception from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>SHIB, APE, PEPE on the Rise</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s largest digital asset &#8211; SHIB &#8211; has been among the best performers lately, gaining double digits in the past week, as <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-returns-to-29k-after-failing-at-30k-shiba-inu-pumps-16-in-7-days-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a>. Furthermore, the past 24 hours were quite positive for the second-largest meme coin as well, as it soared by another 8%. As a result, SHIB now trades close to $0.000011.</p>
<p>The situation with ApeCoin and Pepe is quite similar, at least on a daily scale. Both have jumped by somewhere between 7-8%. Consequently, APE has returned to $2, while PEPE is up to $0.000001333 on CMC.</p>
<p>The larger-cap alts have stalled since yesterday. ETH, DOGE, and TRX are slightly in the green, while BNB, XRP, ADA, and MATIC have posted insignificant losses.</p>
<p>Expectedly, the cumulative market cap of all crypto assets has remained at the same spot at just over $1.170 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265950" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265950" style="width: 1878px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265950" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1878" height="844" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg 1878w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-1024x460.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-768x345.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-1536x690.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1878px) 100vw, 1878px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265950" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bitcoin Stalls</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency had a rather volatile start to the week as it dipped below $29,000 on Monday to register a weekly low. The bulls quickly intercepted the move and pushed the asset north. By Wednesday, BTC had bounced off to over $30,000.</p>
<p>Yet, that turned out to be another short-lived adventure for bitcoin above that level, and it quickly retraced to $29,500. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unfazed-as-cpi-for-july-increases-by-0-2-mom/" data-wpel-link="internal">US CPI numbers</a> on Thursday didn&#8217;t change the landscape all that much.</p>
<p>In fact, BTC has been quite stagnant since then and has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stagnant-above-29k-as-rlb-skyrockets-to-0-2-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">remained</a> in a tight range between $29,000 and $29,500 for the past 48 hours.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization stands just inches above $570 billion, while its dominance is below 49% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265951" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265951" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="869" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-1024x485.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-768x364.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-1536x727.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265951" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-ape-pepe-jump-8-daily-bitcoin-maintains-29k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">SHIB, APE, PEPE Jump 8% Daily, Bitcoin Maintains $29K: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should the World Move Forward with Decentralization?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/should-the-world-move-forward-with-decentralization/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265788</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/13042023_LFPR-The-Three-Layers-of-LFi-and-Its-Promise-to-Crypto-Users-Copy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/13042023_LFPR-The-Three-Layers-of-LFi-and-Its-Promise-to-Crypto-Users-Copy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Imagine making an online payment to a stranger without going through a bank and you still get a reliable and verifiable transaction history. This is how decentralization works. It is the type of process that gives cryptocurrencies the upper hand against traditional currencies. It eliminates the need for intermediaries and allows parties to engage in [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine making an online payment to a stranger without going through a bank and you still get a reliable and verifiable transaction history. This is how decentralization works. It is the type of process that gives cryptocurrencies the upper hand against traditional currencies. It eliminates the need for intermediaries and allows parties to engage in different transactions without relying on any third party.</p>
<p>The concept has hugely influenced the crypto space, which led the crypto community to revolutionize financial services and other markets. For example, DeFi, or decentralized finance, and DAO, or decentralized autonomous organizations are two famous offsprings of decentralization. As these ideas become more widespread, it is essential to learn what decentralization has to offer to the crypto world.</p>
<h2>Do We Need to Decentralize Our Payment System?</h2>
<p>Cash and banks have existed for decades, and everyone put their trust in this form of centralized structure until the financial crisis that occurred in 2008. This worldwide economic crisis made it evident that a single entity should not be making decisions that will affect everyone. Thus, the need for decentralized currencies became apparent.</p>
<p>In October 2008, Satoshi Nakamoto published the Bitcoin whitepaper, where the idea of a global currency that would be managed and owned by the people was born. More than decades later, the question still remains: should we use decentralized currencies?</p>
<p>Decentralization transfers control and decision-making to the users, enabling the system to not be reliant on a single authority and eliminating the risk of a corrupt or compromised authority. Through this, decentralized systems can ensure better protection and independence. Moreover, decentralization promotes trustless connections, wherein the verification of transactions relies on the collective wisdom of numerous devices that are working together. This prevents the system from being compromised by keeping any bad actors at bay.</p>
<p>Moreover, decentralization reduces vulnerabilities by distributing them across the network. Trustless connections prevent single bad actors from forging transactions or corrupting the system. Cooperation from more than 50 percent of the nodes is required to gain influence, making it increasingly difficult in larger systems. Distributed networks also mitigate threats, as compromising a single node does not jeopardize the entire system.</p>
<h2>Moving Forward with Decentralization</h2>
<p>Decentralization is the defining and exceptional characteristic of cryptocurrency. And as we progress, there will be new decentralized cryptocurrencies and exchanges that will preserve the benefits of decentralization and address its limitations. These will strengthen the innovative structure and revolutionize the world of finance in the future.</p>
<p>To find out more please visit: <a href="https://lfi.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lfi.io</a></p>
<p>White paper: <a href="https://white-paper.lfi.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://white-paper.lfi.io/</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/lfiofficial" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.me/lfiofficial</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/LFioff" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/LFioff</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/should-the-world-move-forward-with-decentralization/" rel="nofollow">Should the World Move Forward with Decentralization?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Sent to Jail for Witness Tampering: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265939</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The founder of the crypto exchange FTX could spend at least two months in jail ahead of its trial. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried was reportedly sent to jail on Friday as US Judge Lewis Kaplan denied his lawyers&#8217; request to delay detention.</p>
<p>The former crypto mogul&#8217;s court date is set for October 2nd, and he could sit in a jail cell until then if the appeal is unsuccessful.</p>
<ul>
<li><em>CryptoPotato</em> reported last month the allegations presented by the New York Times that SBF had tried to intimidate one of the key witnesses in his legal battle against US authorities &#8211; the former leader of Alameda Research &#8211; Caroline Ellison.</li>
<li>Prosecutors were quick to request Bankman-Fried&#8217;s detention, claiming he could not be trusted while residing in his parents&#8217; home.</li>
<li>Expectedly, his lawyers refuted the allegations, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-shouldnt-be-detained-for-leaking-details-from-ellisons-diary-lawyers-claim/" data-wpel-link="internal">indicating</a> that he didn&#8217;t try to intervene or intimidate anyone, especially his former girlfriend.</li>
<li>According to more recent <a href="https://twitter.com/innercitypress/status/1690061503645229056" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>, though, the attorneys&#8217; requests for delayed detention were denied by Judge Lewis Kaplan.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;My conclusion is there is probable cause to believe the defendant tried to tamper with witnesses at least twice,&#8221; reportedly said the Judge.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Interestingly, SBF will most likely be sent to a jail in Putnam, New York, and will have access to a laptop with an internet connection to prepare for his defense. The other option was sending him to Brooklyn&#8217;s Metropolitan Detention Center, where internet access is limited for prisoners.</li>
<li>SBF&#8217;s court date over his alleged involvement in defrauding investors and the massive crash of his former crypto empire is set to begin on October 2nd. He could spend the next almost two months in jail unless his lawyer&#8217;s appeal to revert Judge Kaplan&#8217;s ruling is successful.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-report/" rel="nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried Sent to Jail for Witness Tampering: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This E-Gaming Company Earmarks $5M for Bitcoin, Ether Purchases</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-e-gaming-company-earmarks-5m-for-bitcoin-ether-purchases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 04:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265827</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Boyaa said that the purchase of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) aligns with the interests of the company as well as its shareholders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent Hong Kong-based e-gaming player &#8211; Boyaa Interactive International Limited &#8211; announced that its board of directors has approved a budget of $5 million to purchase cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Informing the company&#8217;s shareholders and future potential investors, Boyaa said it will buy mainly Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) on regulated and licensed trading platforms in the coming year.</p>
<ul>
<li>The purchases will be financed using cash reserves derived from the Group activities both in Hong Kong and internationally and will be executed at its discretion, taking into account the current market conditions. The Group essentially consists of Boyaa Interactive Limited and its subsidiaries.</li>
<li>According to the official <a href="https://www1.hkexnews.hk/listedco/listconews/sehk/2023/0810/2023081001308.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release,</a> the move aligns with the intention of shaping Boyaa&#8217;s future business strategy within the Web3 space.</li>
<li>Despite earmarking the $5 million budget for cryptocurrency purchases, the company reminded its investors and shareholders that the digital asset market is volatile in the near term.</li>
<li>Boyaa also advised them to exercise caution while dealing with its shares.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Company will strictly comply with the relevant management and control policies on cryptocurrencies in relevant jurisdictions with regard to the purchases of cryptocurrencies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Boyaa Interactive is an established developer and operator of chess and card games in Hong Kong.</li>
<li>The latest allocation depicted the increasing inclination to venture into Web3 in the city-state owing to favorable policies fostering the digital asset sector.</li>
<li>Hong Kong has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/in-a-first-for-hong-kong-hashkey-exchange-awarded-license-to-serve-retail-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">demonstrated</a> a serious commitment to advancing Web3 prompting more than 150 such firms to <a href="https://www.fso.gov.hk/chi/blog/blog20230618.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">establish</a> operations in Cyberport &#8211; a digital hub launched by the government to promote innovation.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-e-gaming-company-earmarks-5m-for-bitcoin-ether-purchases/" rel="nofollow">This E-Gaming Company Earmarks $5M for Bitcoin, Ether Purchases</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Delays Approval Of Ark&#8217;s Revised Bitcoin ETF For Public Comment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-delays-approval-of-arks-revised-bitcoin-etf-for-public-comment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 23:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265914</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC wants to know what the public thinks of using Coinbase as a surveillance-sharing partner.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed to postpone its decision on whether to approve or deny the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF for listing on BZX.</p>
<p>This marks the agency’s first delay on the latest wave of Bitcoin spot ETF applications, possibly indicating a similar short-term fate for rival applicants.</p>
<h2>Questions For the Public</h2>
<p>In its Friday <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-98112.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">letter</a>, the SEC said it seeks public comment on BZX’s application, which would list the very first Bitcoin spot ETF on a U.S.-regulated exchange.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Institution of proceedings is appropriate at this time in view of the legal and policy issues raised by the proposed rule change,” wrote the SEC. “Institution of proceedings does not indicate that the Commission has reached any conclusions with respect to any of the issues involved.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This is a STANDARD delay letter. There&#39;s some confusion but only the first few paragraphs of this letter are written by the SEC and its very standardized. The rest is just a copy paste of the 19b-4 application written by CBOE (&amp; Ark/21Shares) There isnt much to read into here IMO <a href="https://t.co/7HOMA6kLK4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/7HOMA6kLK4</a></p>
<p>&mdash; James Seyffart (@JSeyff) <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1690022142664945664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Firstly, the agency asked for the public’s thoughts on whether the proposed ETF would be protected from “fraudulent and manipulative acts and practices,” and whether the Bitcoin market is inherently susceptible to manipulation. This issue is central to the agency’s hesitancy in approving a Bitcoin spot ETF until this point.</p>
<p>In the past, ETF applicants have attempted to form surveillance-sharing agreements with the CME Bitcoin Futures market to meet the SEC’s market monitoring needs. However, between ARK’s previous applications as well as those from Grayscale, the SEC has contended that this market cannot meet its benchmark.</p>
<p>That’s what its second public question pertains to: “Do commenters agree with the Exchange that the CME, on which CME Bitcoin Futures trade, represents a regulated market of significant size related to spot bitcoin?” asked the SEC. The regulator specifically wishes to know it someone attempting to manipulate the Bitcoin market would necessarily have to trade on the CME.</p>
<p>The SEC’s last question touched on Coinbase – America’s largest spot Bitcoin exchange, and ARK’s newly preferred surveillance sharing partner. 8 rival applicants have named the same exchange in their most recent filings, following the footsteps of both Fidelity and BlackRock.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Do commenters agree with the Exchange’s assertion that such an agreement with Coinbase would be “helpful in detecting, investigating, and deterring fraud and manipulation in the Commodity-Based Trust Shares”?” wrote the SEC.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Next Deadlines</h2>
<p>After ARK, the next approval deadlines for rival Bitcoin spot ETFs are in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-an-approximate-list-of-all-bitcoin-etf-approval-deadlines-bbg/" data-wpel-link="internal">early September</a>, including BlackRock’s – but decisions on those applications can be similarly delayed.</p>
<p>ARK’s true final deadline at which the SEC can delay its decision no longer is on January 10. Given its virtually identical structure to competitors, ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood expects that its approval will mean that of rival firms as well – and likely <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-sec-might-approve-numerous-spot-btc-etfs-at-the-same-time-cathie-wood-thinks/" data-wpel-link="internal">all at the same time</a>.</p>
<p>Before that, Grayscale expects to receive a ruling in its lawsuit with the SEC by the end of September. Bloomberg ETF analysts <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloomberg-boosts-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval-odds-to-65-heres-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">predict</a> that this lawsuit is still the most likely route to spot ETF approval.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-delays-approval-of-arks-revised-bitcoin-etf-for-public-comment/" rel="nofollow">SEC Delays Approval Of Ark&#8217;s Revised Bitcoin ETF For Public Comment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Embattled Crypto Exchange to Pay a $24 Million Penalty to Settle With SEC (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/embattled-crypto-exchange-to-pay-a-24-million-penalty-to-settle-with-sec-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 22:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265734</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[William Shihara - co-founder of the company which filed for bankruptcy protection in May - called the settlement plan "a good outcome."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The once-prominent cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex has reportedly agreed to pay $24 million in penalties to resolve its quarrel with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency has previously accused the platform of offering services to American clients without obtaining the necessary registration.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange shuttered its US operations and filed for bankruptcy protection shortly after the regulator targeted it.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bittrex-to-pay-24-million-penalty-over-sec-crypto-allegations-1.1957621" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Bloomberg, Bittrex and its non-US subsidiary will part with $24 million to settle allegations that it violated several securities rules while providing cryptocurrency services to American users.</span></li>
<li>The company&#8217;s co-founder William Shihara called the settlement plan &#8220;a good outcome,&#8221; raising hopes that it could help the US authorities create a balance between safeguarding investors and promoting innovation.</li>
<li>Bittrex and Shihara have been coping with severe issues over the past several months caused by the hostile stance of the SEC.</li>
<li>The firm <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-to-close-operations-in-the-us-due-to-regulatory-hurdles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">terminated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> operations in the States at the end of March this year, citing the nation&#8217;s &#8220;regulatory and economic environment.&#8221; Nonetheless, it assured that &#8220;customer funds are safe, here and ready for retrieval.&#8221;</span></li>
<li>A few weeks later, the exchange <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-receives-wells-notice-from-sec-for-violating-investor-protection-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Wells Notice from the SEC. The latter alleged that Bittrex operated as an unregistered exchange, broker-dealer, and clearinghouse for securities. </span></li>
<li>The company <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-bittrex-files-for-us-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the US approximately three weeks after the SEC&#8217;s attack. According to the filing, it had more than 100,000 creditors, with estimated liabilities and assets both worth between $500 million and $1 billion. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/embattled-crypto-exchange-to-pay-a-24-million-penalty-to-settle-with-sec-report/" rel="nofollow">Embattled Crypto Exchange to Pay a $24 Million Penalty to Settle With SEC (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
