<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:58:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New ATH: Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Peaks Amid Institutional Interest (Bitfinex Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-ath-bitcoins-unmoved-supply-peaks-amid-institutional-interest-bitfinex-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259805</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-6.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-6.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the report, the unmoved BTC has led to a decrease in liquidity for bitcoin traders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading crypto exchange Bitfinex released its latest Bitfinex Alpha report, a weekly publication that offers on-chain data and insights into the dynamic crypto market. This week&#8217;s document found that the amount of unmoved bitcoin has reached its highest point.</p>
<p>The report further highlights an intriguing development in liquidity trends. Bitcoin liquidity has experienced a decrease, while that of Tether USDT has witnessed a noteworthy increase.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Hits ATH</h2>
<p><a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitfinex-Alpha-62.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Bitfinex Alpha</a> attributes the surge in unmoved bitcoin to the growing interest of institutional investors in the digital asset.</p>
<p>Citing data from Ark Invest, an investment firm headed by the renowned <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-wood-reiterates-her-1-million-bitcoin-bet/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cathie Wood</a>, the paper stated that about 70% of BTC&#8217;s circulating supply has been unmoved for at least a year, the highest ever recorded.</p>
<p>The increasing involvement of these big players indicates strong bullish sentiment and unwavering confidence in bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<p>According to the report, the BTC balance held on over-the-counter (OTC) desks, which serves as a reliable indicator of institutional activity, reached a one-year high in June. The balance surged by an impressive 60% by the end of the third quarter. This growth suggests that institutions and large investors are actively embracing the cryptocurrency as an attractive investment option.</p>
<p>The researchers also found that the bitcoin holdings of crypto-related hedge funds, investment firms, and private funds have significantly increased as institutional investors accumulate BTC at the current price level.</p>
<h2>Derivatives Traders Dominating the Market</h2>
<p>However, per the report, there has been a notable surge in Bitcoin Open Interest, exceeding a substantial 38% increase since the initial spot Bitcoin ETF <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> by the world&#8217;s largest asset manager BlackRock.</p>
<p>This rise indicates a potential shift in market dynamics, with derivatives traders potentially exerting greater influence on the current momentum, dethroning spot traders.</p>
<p>Bitfinex researchers caution that increased positions in futures contracts typically indicate short-term downward pressure on BTC&#8217;s price. As such, traders should monitor the trend closely, as it could impact market performance in the short run.</p>
<h2>A Decreased Bitcoin Liquidity</h2>
<p>The report also found that there has been a decline in bitcoin&#8217;s liquidity, contrasted with a substantial increase in the liquidity of Tether USDT, the largest stablecoin in the market. The decreased BTC liquidity aligns with the trend of long-term bitcoin holdings, as outlined in the publication.</p>
<blockquote><p>The researchers shed light on the development, stating, &#8220;As more investors hold onto their Bitcoin, less of it is available for trading, leading to decreased liquidity. This trend of &#8216;HODLing&#8217; is often perceived as a testament to the confidence placed in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term value, despite temporary market fluctuations.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, it is worth noting that insufficient liquidity can give rise to increased price volatility. When less BTC is available for trading, price changes can become more drastic, which may pose risks for traders.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-ath-bitcoins-unmoved-supply-peaks-amid-institutional-interest-bitfinex-report/" rel="nofollow">New ATH: Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Peaks Amid Institutional Interest (Bitfinex Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Approving a Spot BTC ETF Would be &#8216;Hard to Resist,&#8217; Former SEC Chair Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/approving-a-spot-btc-etf-would-be-hard-to-resist-former-sec-chair-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259798</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/JayClayton-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/JayClayton-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Clayton finds it "pretty remarkable" that BlackRock and many other leading finance firms are ready to put their reputation by involving with BTC. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jay Clayton &#8211; former Chairman of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8211; believes the agency should approve a spot Bitcoin ETF in America if the interested companies prove the safety of the product. However, he could not predict when such a green light would come.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Multiple behemoths, including BlackRock, Invesco, and Fidelity Digital Assets, have recently filed to launch such a fund. The SEC has previously given its nod to a futures BTC ETF but has been reluctant to approve a spot one. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Surprised Clayton</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American lawyer who served as the SEC Chairman between May 2017 and December 2020 revealed in a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/SquawkCNBC/status/1678381857367289856" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that he was initially &#8220;very skeptical&#8221; about bitcoin. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Let&#8217;s go back to 2015-2016, this is an offshore, retail, nothing close to what I would say the core of our financial markets. At that time, if you look at the trading of bitcoin, the emergence of bitcoin, it looked like stocks, but it was nothing like it.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_259799" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259799" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Jay-Clayton.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259799" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Jay-Clayton.jpg" alt="Jay Clayton" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Jay-Clayton.jpg 630w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Jay-Clayton-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Jay-Clayton-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259799" class="wp-caption-text">Jay Clayton, Source: Politico</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Several years later, though, prominent finance firms have backed the asset with their reputation. He described the recent spree of filings for spot BTC ETFs as an &#8220;incredible development&#8221; and not the one he expected. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Clayton claimed that the SEC approved several futures Bitcoin ETFs in the past as it saw that the products were sufficiently safe for investors, something that it has not observed in a spot product yet. Institutions, though, believe those distinctions have gone away.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If you can demonstrate that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market, it would be hard to resist approving a Bitcoin ETF,&#8221; the American concluded. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Market&#8217;s Revival After the Filings</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The cryptocurrency market has been in rather good shape ever since the world&#8217;s largest asset manager </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">displayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> intentions to introduce a spot BTC ETF in the USA. The organization has a remarkable record with the SEC, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">having</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> only 1 out of 576 ETFs rejected over the years. In addition, it refiled an amended version, tapping Coinbase as a surveillance partner to comply with the Commission&#8217;s requirements. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous finance giants, such as Fidelity Digital Assets, WisdomTree, Invesco, Valkyrie, and Ark Invest, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">followed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> BlackRock&#8217;s example.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The USD valuation of most crypto assets, including bitcoin, headed north in the following weeks. The leading digital asset has surged by over 20% since June 15 (the day of BlackRock&#8217;s filing).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The development has also infused high optimism among investors. One example is the Bitcoin Fear and Greed Index, which has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in the &#8220;Greed&#8221; zone for the past three weeks. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, BTC sharks, whales, and long-term holders have been on an accumulation spree. The latest data revealed that LTHs </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-of-btcs-circulating-supply-is-owned-by-long-term-holders-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hold</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> almost 14.5 million BTC, or about 75% of the circulating supply.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/approving-a-spot-btc-etf-would-be-hard-to-resist-former-sec-chair-says/" rel="nofollow">Approving a Spot BTC ETF Would be &#8216;Hard to Resist,&#8217; Former SEC Chair Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vanguard Group Buys 10% Stake In Bitcoin Miner Riot</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vanguard-group-buys-10-stake-in-bitcoin-miner-riot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259957</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Vanguard-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Vanguard-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Vanguard’s total stake in Bitcoin mining firms now exceeds $500 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The $7 trillion asset management giant Vanguard Group now owns a 10.24% stake in Riot Blockchain (NASDAQ: RIOT) – the world’s largest Bitcoin mining company.</p>
<ul>
<li>A <a href="https://fintel.io/doc/sec-vanguard-group-inc-1167419-sc-13ga-2023-july-10-19548-7901" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a> with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Monday showed that Vanguard has upped its exposure to the firm from 15.2 million shares to 17.9 million.</li>
<li>Based on Riot’s current share price, Vanguard’s stake is now worth $295 million.</li>
<li>The company also bought millions of shares in competing firm Marathon Digital, increasing its holdings from 10.9 million shares to 17.5 million. The investment is of roughly equal value to Vanguard’s Riot stake at $296 million.</li>
<li>Both Riot and Marathon are up roughly 400% year to date, mimicking the trajectory of other mining firms, and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-vs-btc-companies-whats-the-better-buy/" data-wpel-link="internal">outperforming</a> the already strong gains of Bitcoin (BTC) itself.</li>
<li>Like many other mining firms, Riot has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-firm-riot-secures-33280-mining-rigs-ahead-of-halving/" data-wpel-link="internal">invested</a> tens of millions of dollars into expanding mining infrastructure capacity this year in preparation for Bitcoin’s “halving” next year, which is widely believed to catalyze Bitcoin bull markets.</li>
<li>Two years ago, Vanguard claimed on its <a href="https://www.vanguard.com.au/personal/learn/smart-investing/markets-and-economy/cryptocurrencies-and-vanguard" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">site</a> that the investment potential in cryptocurrencies is “weak”, yet its half-a-billion dollar stake in the mining industry may indicate a change of heart.</li>
<li>Fellow asset manager BlackRock has also grown more fond of the industry with time. Once a skeptic, CEO Larry Fink <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-btc-etf-filing-could-democratize-crypto-ceo-larry-fink-says/" data-wpel-link="internal">likened</a> Bitcoin to “digital gold” earlier this month, shortly after his firm applied to launch the first Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vanguard-group-buys-10-stake-in-bitcoin-miner-riot/" rel="nofollow">Vanguard Group Buys 10% Stake In Bitcoin Miner Riot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Will Explode to $120K in 2024, the US Dollar Will Die: Robert Kiyosaki</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-explode-to-120k-in-2024-the-us-dollar-will-die-rober-kiyosaki/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259804</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kiyosaki remains determined that BTC, gold, and silver will thrive in the following years.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert Kiyosaki &#8211; an American investor, motivational speaker, and author of the book &#8220;Rich Dad, Poor Dad&#8221; &#8211; forecasted a grim future for the US dollar, advising people to focus on precious metals and bitcoin. He believes the primary cryptocurrency can skyrocket to $120,000 in 2024. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading British banking institution – Standard Chartered &#8211; also thinks the asset can reach that milestone next year.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Bullish Prediction</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">South Africa will host the leaders of Brazil, Russia, India, and China (a group of countries known as BRICS) in August this year to discuss the possible creation of a new currency. Kiyosaki <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1678652054951317504" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">expects</a> the nations to introduce a new cryptocurrency backed by gold, which could harm the American dollar:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;US $ will die. Trillions of US $ rush home. Inflation through the roof.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_259888" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259888" style="width: 311px" class="wp-caption alignright"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259888" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert.jpg" alt="Robert Kiyosaki" width="311" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert.jpg 330w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert-233x300.jpg 233w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Robert-39x50.jpg 39w" sizes="(max-width: 311px) 100vw, 311px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259888" class="wp-caption-text">Robert Kiyosaki, Source: Wikipedia</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He urged consumers to invest in gold and silver as a protection measure. Like his previous statements, he touched upon Bitcoin, seeing it rise to $120,000 in 2024. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kiyosaki, who was among the few to forecast the 2008 economic collapse, believes BTC is the right investment tool in times of a severe financial crash or inflation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1250414727609470978" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">argued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in April 2020 that the Fed&#8217;s mass printing during the global COVID-19 pandemic could be beneficial for precious metals and bitcoin, calling them &#8220;best investments.&#8221; Recall that the leading digital asset was trading at around $6,800 at the time.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-believes-buying-bitcoin-now-will-make-you-smile-later/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">remained</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a BTC proponent during the 2022 bear market, recommending to investors that this was a great opportunity to buy the dip. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">$500K by 2025?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kiyosaki </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-rich-dad-poor-dad-author-believes-btc-will-reach-500k-in-3-years/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">criticized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the US dollar once again in February, describing it as &#8220;fake money.&#8221; He envisioned that the undermined trust in the world&#8217;s reserve currency could push investors towards bitcoin, gold, and silver. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As a result, he believes BTC could reach $500,000 by 2025, whereas the yellow metal and silver could tap $5,000 and $500, respectively. He also labeled bitcoin as &#8220;people&#8217;s $,&#8221; while naming the precious metals &#8220;God&#8217;s money.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Others like MicroStrategy&#8217;s Executive Chairman &#8211; Michael Saylor &#8211; and Ark Invest&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Cathie Wood &#8211; have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/we-see-btc-at-1-million-michael-saylor-and-cathie-wood-at-bitcoin-2022-in-miami/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">predicted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an even brighter future for BTC, suggesting its price could hit $1 million, albeit within a different timeframe.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similar to Kiyosaki, Wood opined that the digital asset is a &#8220;huge hedge&#8221; against inflation. She also thinks it could be employed against deflation and counterparty risk.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-explode-to-120k-in-2024-the-us-dollar-will-die-rober-kiyosaki/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Will Explode to $120K in 2024, the US Dollar Will Die: Robert Kiyosaki</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Tumbles 5% Weekly, Here&#8217;s the Imminent Support to Watch (ETH Price Chart)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-tumbles-5-weekly-heres-the-imminent-support-to-watch-eth-price-chart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259663</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-10-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-10-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price has been oscillating in a tight range below the $2,000 psychological resistance level, failing to break higher. Yet, several support zones are available for investors to feel confident that the market will not crash. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily chart, the price has been going through choppy action, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has been oscillating in a tight range below the $2,000 psychological resistance level, failing to break higher. Yet, several support zones are available for investors to feel confident that the market will not crash.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: Edris</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price has been going through choppy action, following the breakout above the $1,800 level and the 50-day moving average around the $1,850 mark.</p>
<p>The aforementioned moving average is currently providing support for the market. However, in case of a breakdown, the $1,800 level and the 200-day moving average trending around the $1,700 mark are potential support elements for the price to rebound.</p>
<p>Moreover, the RSI indicator provides little insight into this timeframe, as it has been running flat around the 50% threshold, indicating momentum equilibrium.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259921" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259921" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259921 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1107231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-11-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259921" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Things look a bit clearer on the 4-hour chart, as the price has been rejected from the $1,920 resistance level recently. The short-term support level at the $1,840 mark is currently being tested, holding ETH from dropping further.</p>
<p>However, there is a high probability for the mentioned level to break down, resulting in a sharp decline toward the $1,760 support zone. On the other hand, if ETH breaks above the $1,920 area, the market will likely enter a bullish phase once more, with the price surging toward the $2,000 level and even higher in the coming weeks.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259922" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259922" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259922 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1107232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-11-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259922" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<p>By: Edris</p>
<h3>Ethereum Taker Buy Sell Ratio</h3>
<p>Ethereum has been consolidating lately, failing to break above the key $2,000 level. While the spot market seems strong, the derivatives market is seemingly responsible for the price&#8217;s failure to rally higher.</p>
<p>This chart represents the taker buy-sell ratio (with a 100-day exponential moving average applied), which is a useful metric in evaluating the futures market sentiment. Values above 1 indicate aggressive buying pressure; values below 1 are associated with dominant selling pressure.</p>
<p>Analyzing the chart, it is evident that the metric has once again failed to rise above 1 and is currently on a steep decline. This signal indicates that futures traders are aggressively shorting ETH, as they do not expect the market to break above the $2,000 level.</p>
<p>The resulting selling pressure is currently preventing the market from continuing its uptrend. However, in case the spot market demand prevails against the futures market supply, a bullish breakout higher would be imminent.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259666" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259666" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259666 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_taker_buy_sell_ratio_chart_1107231" width="2560" height="1616" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-768x485.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-1536x970.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-2048x1293.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-Jul-10-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259666" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-tumbles-5-weekly-heres-the-imminent-support-to-watch-eth-price-chart/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Tumbles 5% Weekly, Here&#8217;s the Imminent Support to Watch (ETH Price Chart)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calm Before the Storm? XRP Consolidates Under $0.5 Resistance (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-xrp-consolidates-under-0-5-resistance-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259669</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s XRP has exhibited turbulent price action and high volatility since early April, leaving traders uncertain about the market’s future direction. However, it is likely that the price will continue to consolidate within the range defined by the 100-day and 200-day moving averages in the medium term. XRP Price Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s XRP has exhibited turbulent price action and high volatility since early April, leaving traders uncertain about the market’s future direction.</p>
<p>However, it is likely that the price will continue to consolidate within the range defined by the 100-day and 200-day moving averages in the medium term.</p>
<h2>XRP Price Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By Shayan</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Taking a look at the daily chart, XRP&#8217;s price underwent a corrective consolidation phase, pulling back towards the 200-day moving average situated at $0.44.</p>
<p>This retracement occurred after failing to surpass the key resistance region of $0.55. The $0.55 zone holds significant psychological resistance, as it has repeatedly hindered XRP price movements in the past. Notably, there is a considerable amount of supply in this region, indicating aggressive selling pressure.</p>
<p>Nonetheless, the price is expected to remain within a dynamic range bounded by the resistance level of the 100-day moving average at $0.4828 and the support level of the 200-day moving average at $0.4372 in the short term. Consequently, a breakout from this critical range will likely determine Ripple&#8217;s next move.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259924" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259924" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259924 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_1107231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259924" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour timeframe, there has been a decline in the price below the mid-boundary of the channel, followed by a retracement and pullback. However, after completing the pullback to the broken level, XRP has started another downward movement, indicating a prevailing bearish sentiment in the market.</p>
<p>Simultaneously, a descending wedge pattern has formed on the 4-hour timeframe, characterized by white trendlines. This pattern typically suggests a potential bullish move if the XRP price breaks above the upper trendline.</p>
<p>Therefore, the cryptocurrency seems more likely to continue ranging within the descending wedge pattern until a breakout occurs. In the event of a breakout above the upper threshold, there is a possibility of an attempt toward the $0.55 resistance level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259925" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259925" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259925 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_1107232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259925" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-xrp-consolidates-under-0-5-resistance-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Calm Before the Storm? XRP Consolidates Under $0.5 Resistance (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New AI Crypto yPredict Generates Huge Interest &#038; Nears $3M Presale Milestone</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259905</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ypredict_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ypredict_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The fields of Web3 and artificial intelligence have been flourishing lately, helping produce an array of exciting crypto startups. Among these, yPredict ($YPRED) is creating quite a buzz with its innovative and ambitious features. Leveraging the power of advanced AI technology, yPredict offers an array of tools to provide crypto analytics, SEO solutions, and much [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fields of Web3 and artificial intelligence have been flourishing lately, helping produce an array of exciting crypto startups.</p>
<p>Among these, <a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict ($YPRED)</a> is creating quite a buzz with its innovative and ambitious features.</p>
<p>Leveraging the power of advanced AI technology, yPredict offers an array of tools to provide crypto analytics, SEO solutions, and much more.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-9.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259912" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-9.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="213" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-9.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-9-300x106.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-9-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<h2>Reinventing SEO Strategies with yPredict’s Backlink Estimator</h2>
<p>One of the key tools rolled out by yPredict is its AI-powered backlink estimator – a tool designed to revolutionize SEO strategies.</p>
<p>This marks a significant milestone for yPredict as it expands its scope to offer content solutions for medium to large-scale teams, widening its target audience.</p>
<p>This backlink estimator feature is trained on over 100 million links, with its main function being to predict the backlink profile needed for a site to rank a specific keyword.</p>
<p>In turn, this eradicates the guesswork in SEO and allows for more precise strategies.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259911" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-11.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="252" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-11.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-11-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-11-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Originally launched as a free preview, the backlink estimator garnered over 5,000 requests within the first 24 hours.</p>
<p>However, after its immediate success, the yPredict team has launched the tool to the masses – with a pricing structure of $99/query, per a recent <a href="https://twitter.com/yPredict_ai/status/1677305434636517376" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Tweet</a> from the official yPredict account.</p>
<p>Interestingly, those who purchase $YPRED tokens through yPredict&#8217;s ongoing presale will have complete access to the backlink estimator tool and other models the development team has in the pipeline.</p>
<p>This arrangement has further fueled interest in the yPredict ecosystem, with the project&#8217;s presale rapidly nearing the $3 million funding mark.</p>
<p>Currently, would-be investors can purchase <a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$YPRED tokens</a> through this presale for just $0.09 &#8211; a discount on the planned exchange listing price.</p>
<h2>yPredict’s Game-Changing Platform Revolutionizes Crypto Analytics</h2>
<p>While the SEO tools mark a thrilling expansion of yPredict&#8217;s offerings, the core features of the platform are centered around crypto analytics.</p>
<p>Per yPredict’s <a href="https://docs.ypredict.ai/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the platform seeks to be a game changer by offering state-of-the-art AI-powered tools that provide objective insights to traders worldwide.</p>
<p>The yPredict platform uses machine learning models to analyze colossal amounts of price data, which allows it to identify trends and provide valuable market guidance to users.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259910" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-11.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="353" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-11.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-11-300x176.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-11-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Not only that, but the platform will also provide AI-driven trading signals, automated pattern recognition, and market sentiment analysis.</p>
<p>yPredict has recently unveiled a beta version of the platform, inviting interested users to explore its capabilities by joining the project’s <a href="https://s.surveyplanet.com/h7p13rld" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">waitlist</a>.</p>
<p>However, even if users choose not to utilize the yPredict Analytics suite, they can still access the yPredict Predictions platform for free, as long as they hold $YPRED tokens.</p>
<p>This approach is designed by the yPredict team to make AI-powered crypto and stock price predictions accessible to all, effectively democratizing the process.</p>
<h2>Alt_Pump_001 Model Unravels the Potential of Altcoins</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> is also making strides by announcing Alt_Pump_001 – an AI-powered model designed to offer insights into the altcoin market.</p>
<p>This groundbreaking tool equips investors with the means to identify future altcoins that have the potential to surge by 100x or more.</p>
<p>Despite being available through a subscription model priced at over $1,000 per month, Alt_Pump_001 can be accessed for free by presale buyers who purchase a minimum of $500 in $YPRED.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259909" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-5.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="305" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-5-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-5-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Naturally, the development of Alt_Pump_001 further underlines the development team’s commitment to leveraging the power of AI to maximize trading outcomes.</p>
<p>Given the potential of the altcoin market, this tool could be of tremendous value to investors – a fact that has helped prompt an influx of new members into the yPredict <a href="https://t.me/ypredict" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<h2>$YPRED Token Fuels yPredict’s Cutting-Edge Ecosystem</h2>
<p>As hinted at throughout this article, $YPRED will serve as the core of yPredict’s revolutionary platform.</p>
<p>This AI utility token will be built using the power of the Polygon blockchain, ensuring it remains fast and secure.</p>
<p>Alongside being used to access yPredict’s premium features, the token can also be staked to earn monthly rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259908" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-2.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="252" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-2-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-2-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Not only that, but the development team has structured $YPRED’s tokenomics in such a way as to decrease the chance of a rug pull occurring once it is listed on the open market.</p>
<p>A whopping 80% of the total $YPRED supply is being made available through the ongoing public presale, with the remaining 20% allocated for liquidity, treasury, and developmental purposes.</p>
<p>This fair token structure is another key reason yPredict has been generating traction in the market, with high-profile YouTuber Michael Wrubel <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KwoCQl5h4qE&amp;t=459s&amp;pp=ygUPeXByZWRpY3QgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">stating</a> that he is “bullish” on the project.</p>
<p>All in all, yPredict’s combination of AI-powered analytics tools and its revolutionary approach to SEO strategies set the stage for what could be a transformative experience in the world of digital assets.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-ai-crypto-ypredict-generates-huge-interest-nears-3m-presale-milestone/" rel="nofollow">New AI Crypto yPredict Generates Huge Interest &#038; Nears $3M Presale Milestone</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Things to Watch in Q3 2023 as Bitcoin Price Almost Doubled Since January</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/6-things-to-watch-in-q3-2023-as-bitcoin-price-almost-doubled-since-january/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259165</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price is doing rounds in 2023. As we enter the third quarter for the year, here are six factors worth your consideration.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price doubled in the first half of 2023 after melting off the ice of crypto winter in early January. Is it time to take profits, or does this six-month BTC rally have more in store for Q3?</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With persistent interest rate hikes, weakness in the banking sector and debt ceiling concerns, investors see bitcoin now more than ever as a sovereign, safe haven asset that has held strong and steady in the face of market uncertainty.&#8221; -Alex Adelman, CEO of Bitcoin app Lolli.</p></blockquote>
<p>Since rallying to $29,900 on June 22, Bitcoin has been trading sideways in a range-bound channel between $30,100 and $31,100. That follows a surge upward from the $25,000 level in the middle of June, the lowest price for the coin since March.</p>
<p>Before that, Bitcoin price fell in a two-month tumble from the $30,300 level in mid-April.</p>
<p>Current spot prices happen <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/07/06/bitcoin-13-month-high-valkyrie-refiles-spot-bitcoin-etf-crypto-world.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">to be</a> close to a 13-month high level for Bitcoin. Is the market overheated or gearing up for another rally?</p>
<p>The following six factors in the Bitcoin price are overall bullish in the Q3 outlook, but they&#8217;re a mixed bag. There are also some headwinds rising for the OG cryptocurrency to weather.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin ETF Fervor on Wall Street</h2>
<p>Institutional investors are, by this time, chomping at the bit to get the private keys to blockchain assets into their portfolios. ETF buzz has already pushed Bitcoin&#8217;s price higher, but there&#8217;s room left to rally if anyone&#8217;s SEC application actually gets approved.</p>
<p>As Forbes <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/spot-bitcoin-etf/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> near the end of June:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The SEC has already approved plenty of Bitcoin ETFs and other types of crypto exchange-traded funds. But so far, the market regulator has only been comfortable greenlighting funds that track cryptocurrency futures or own the stocks of companies with indirect exposure to crypto.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, investors on Wall Street are clamoring for a spot Bitcoin ETF. Crypto markets are anxiously awaiting the SEC&#8217;s approval of the first one. Because of market uncertainty over the SEC&#8217;s resistance to a spot ETF, the approval of one would likely cause an immediate reevaluation of the Bitcoin price.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s a list of companies that have filed <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">spot Bitcoin ETF</a> applications with the SEC. They include BlackRock, Ark Invest Management, Invesco, Fidelity Digital Assets, WisdomTree, and Valkyrie.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259900" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1.jpg" alt="bitcoin_binary_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Bitcoin DeFi, Ordinals, and BTC NFTs</h2>
<p>Loathe to allow Ethereum, Solara, and Polkadot to have all the fun minting NFTs, some enterprising devs introduced the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-lauds-bitcoin-ordinals-believes-brc-20-standard-could-revive-stagnancy/" data-wpel-link="internal">BRC-20 standard</a> for minting non-fungible tokens on Bitcoin&#8217;s blockchain earlier this year.</p>
<p>As a result, Bitcoin has never seen anything like the record daily transaction volume the network serviced last quarter on May 1. That day, the old Satoshi blockchain&#8217;s <a href="https://ycharts.com/indicators/bitcoin_transactions_per_day" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">users made</a> 682,281 transactions in a 24-hour period.</p>
<p>Since then, daily transactions have driven a level of network activity that we haven&#8217;t seen since the first half of 2021 during that year&#8217;s hot crypto bull market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, this key metric of fundamental value is already on track in July to set another record. On July 9, Bitcoin processed and completed 594,265 transactions.</p>
<p>Much of this season&#8217;s intense transaction volume consisted of Bitcoin NFT sales. In fact, so-called &#8220;Ordinals&#8221; <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/currencies/bitcoin-record-daily-transactions-network-ordinals-protocol-cryptocurrency-btc-crypto-2023-5" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">made up</a> over half of BTC&#8217;s record-setting total on May 1, at some 54.6%.</p>
<h2>A Spike in Institutional Interest</h2>
<p>As time goes on, institutional interest in cryptocurrencies has only increased, not abated. That&#8217;s especially true for blue chips like BTC and ETH.</p>
<p>The recent launch of the first leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF on June 27, for example, triggered a wave of on-chain BTC token purchases by funds.</p>
<p>Starting on June 18th, ahead of the SEC&#8217;s approval of the new 2x leveraged futures product, funds <a href="https://terminal.bytetree.com/bitcoin/flows/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">hoovered up</a> 19,083 BTC over 21 days. At a spot price of $30,500 per 1 BTC, that was an over half-a-billion dollar blitz for institutional investors.</p>
<p>They didn&#8217;t stop buying up on-chain tokens in June. Bitcoin futures on the Chicago Mercantile Exchange saw contract volumes <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/institutional-interest-spikes-btc-eth-024341255.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">increase by</a> 28.6% in June to $37.9 billion.</p>
<p>In another sign of institutional appetite, the Bitcoin futures premium for BTC contracts <a href="https://www.binance.com/en-NG/feed/post/735119" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recently doubled</a> in a week&#8217;s time to 6.4% on July 3 from 3.2%. That&#8217;s a bullish portent for the Bitcoin price, and furthermore, there seems to be more room left for it to rise.</p>
<p>This could mean reversion, as futures premiums ran low over the past year, but it might indicate healthy demand for open interest in the future Bitcoin price moving forward.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-169779" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" alt="bitcoinbull_cover (1)" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Bitcoin Fundamentals</h2>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The year after Bitcoin halving is usually the bull year.&#8221;<br />
<em>-Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao, Twitter Spaces (July 5, 2023)</em></p></blockquote>
<p>BTC daily transaction volume, <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/charts/hash-rate" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">network hash rate</a>, and <a href="https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-stock-to-flow-model/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stock-to-flow against price</a> numbers are all running at bullish levels and are backed by real momentum going into Q3. This bodes well for a continuing rally.</p>
<p>Bear markets are for builders, and with the overwhelming enthusiasm for the new Bitcoin products we&#8217;ve seen in H1, it really shows.</p>
<p>While transaction volume is higher than ever with these new use cases for Bitcoin, most holders of BTC are doing just that. <a href="https://ark-invest.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/The-Bitcoin-Monthly-June-2023.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According to</a> Ark Invest&#8217;s June monthly Bitcoin report, 70% of the BTC supply hasn&#8217;t moved for a year.</p>
<p>Because Bitcoin is an economic currency (not a financial one) with a limited supply, the BTC economy&#8217;s tightness with the supply over the past 12 months is an indicator of possibly higher prices on crypto exchanges for the precious digital asset.</p>
<h2>Global Regulatory Hawkishness</h2>
<p>As the old Wall Street saying goes: Markets abhor uncertainty.</p>
<p>The unfolding saga of SEC regulation by lawsuit and enforcement against cryptocurrencies has certainly raised a number of questions about the nascent industry&#8217;s future.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the IRS is missing in action as the industry and crypto holders await tax rules for digital assets. As Politico <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/06/26/crypto-tax-regulations-00101937" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported on</a> June 26:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The long-awaited IRS tax compliance rules are stuck in an unexplained delay even as the SEC aggressively targets the crypto industry for regulation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Even as Bitcoin and its rivals continue to post ROIs beyond the pale of what investors are accustomed to expecting on stock exchanges (even from high-flying stocks like Tesla and Nvidia), institutions are still cautious to enter the blockchain space because of regulatory ambiguity.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s a drag on crypto prices across the board, including BTC. Bitcoin is taking some heat from regulators in the U.S. and around the world, but not nearly like its competitors are.</p>
<p>Most notably, the SEC&#8217;s push to regulate many blockchain tokens as securities has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-coinbase-and-binance-lawsuits-super-bullish-for-btc-and-eth-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">conspicuously left</a> Bitcoin and Ether, among others, out of the hot seat. So, regulatory threats to the Bitcoin price may be balanced by worse threats to some of its competitors.</p>
<h2>Global Macro Financial Factors</h2>
<p>Like regulatory concerns for blockchain, global macro factors in crypto prices are a mixed bag for Bitcoin in the next quarter and beyond.</p>
<p>June&#8217;s pause on months of interest rate hikes by the Federal Reserve and ECB was the most pivotal financial event of the previous quarter.</p>
<p>BTCUSD markets seemed to love it, or at least not mind it at all, as they rallied from $25,000 in mid-June to above $30,000 in under a week&#8217;s time.</p>
<p>Relief from rising prices to borrow money to make capital investments in businesses, or buy stocks and cryptocurrencies, is a tailwind for markets. But it seemed to get priced into BTC&#8217;s chart within days, and more interest rate hikes may await markets later this year if the current regime does not whip inflation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, analysts are pushing back U.S. recession projections to next year or even projecting a <a href="https://www.bigcountrynewsconnection.com/news/state/washington/washington-state-forecast-predicts-u-s-economic-slowdown-not-recession/article_88042da4-7fdf-5f41-87cd-56cd345a2203.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">slowdown instead</a> of a recession. On balance, that&#8217;s good news for just about everyone, not the Bitcoin price especially, and not excluding BTC prices.</p>
<p>But of particular importance to Bitcoin: Energy prices have been falling worldwide for a year. Oil prices <a href="https://markets.businessinsider.com/commodities/oil-price?type=wti" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">closed at</a> $121/barrel a year ago. This month, oil closed at $73 on July 10.</p>
<p>Given the importance of electricity to Bitcoin&#8217;s proof-of-work blockchain, as one of the main costs for miners to deliver the network&#8217;s services, this is very bullish for the oldest cryptocurrency&#8217;s spot prices.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/6-things-to-watch-in-q3-2023-as-bitcoin-price-almost-doubled-since-january/" rel="nofollow">6 Things to Watch in Q3 2023 as Bitcoin Price Almost Doubled Since January</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will ADA Explode Above $0.3 This Week? Three Things to Watch (Cardano Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-ada-explode-above-0-3-this-week-three-things-to-watch-cardano-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259834</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cardano looks like it&#8217;s about to make a significant move soon. Here are three technical indicators to watch. Key Support levels: $0.26, $0.24 Key Resistance levels: $0.30, $0.32 1. Ascending Triangle The price action of this cryptocurrency has formed a clear ascending triangle, as highlighted in the below chart. This makes a possible breakout above [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Cardano looks like it&#8217;s about to make a significant move soon. Here are three technical indicators to watch.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.26, $0.24</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.30, $0.32</strong></p>
<h2>1. Ascending Triangle</h2>
<p>The price action of this cryptocurrency has formed a clear ascending triangle, as highlighted in the below chart. This makes a possible breakout above the resistance at $0.30 likely. Since the price is being compressed at the apex of this formation, ADA will have to decide fairly soon on the way forward.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259868" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259868" style="width: 1826px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259868" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01" width="1826" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01.png 1826w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01-768x379.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-24-01-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1826px) 100vw, 1826px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259868" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. MACD Bullish Crossover</h2>
<p>The 3-day MACD of Cardano shows that a bullish crossover may happen this week. If so, then a breakout above $0.30 becomes more probable. On the daily timeframe, the MACD is already positive, which gives bulls the upper hand right now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259867" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259867" style="width: 1825px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259867" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55" width="1825" height="902" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55.png 1825w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55-1536x759.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-29-55-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1825px) 100vw, 1825px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259867" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>3. Resistance Under Pressure</h2>
<p>The resistance at $0.30 has kept ADA from moving higher in June, but in July, it seems this cryptocurrency has a great chance to finally break it. Every time a key resistance is tested by the price, the likelihood of it breaking increases. Currently, the buyers seem as if they&#8217;re about to make a third attempt at moving the price higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259882" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259882" style="width: 1826px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259882" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55" width="1826" height="844" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55.png 1826w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55-300x139.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55-1024x473.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55-768x355.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55-1536x710.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ADAUSDT_2023-07-11_13-50-55-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1826px) 100vw, 1826px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259882" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for ADA is neutral right now but can quickly turn bullish as soon if the key resistance is broken.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for ADA Price</h2>
<p>If buyers manage to break above $0.30, then ADA&#8217;s price will quickly move to $0.32 and $0.35, which are the next targets. However, if the breakout fails, then this cryptocurrency has good support at $0.26.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-ada-explode-above-0-3-this-week-three-things-to-watch-cardano-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Will ADA Explode Above $0.3 This Week? Three Things to Watch (Cardano Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Will The Ripple-SEC Ruling Come? XRP CTO and Known Attorney Speculate on a Deadline</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/when-will-the-ripple-sec-ruling-come-xrp-cto-and-known-attorney-speculate-on-a-deadline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259855</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Untitled-design.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/Untitled-design.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple's CTO and the well-known XRP attorney John Deaton shared some thought as to when the ruling in the case against the SEC might come.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The case between the United States Securities and Exchange Commission and Ripple is one that the entire cryptocurrency community is looking at. The outcome of the lawsuit is likely to determine whether XRP is a security &#8211; a decision that might have considerable implications for the rest of the industry.</p>
<h2>Ripple v. SEC Case: When Ruling?</h2>
<p>John E. Deaton, an attorney representing thousands of XRP holders, as well as David Schwartz, have laid out some thoughts on when they think a ruling in the case against the SEC might be coming.</p>
<p>Deaton made it clear that there&#8217;s nothing so unusual in the fact that Judge Analisa Torres is taking relatively long to pass a ruling. Per Deaton, it&#8217;s been seven months so far, but Ripple isn&#8217;t the only one in the waiting room.</p>
<blockquote><p>In the Thor Equities case, also before Judge Torres, the Reply Briefs were also filed in December. Judge Torres hasn&#8217;t yet ruled.</p>
<p>In the N.Y. Disctrict Carpenter&#8217;s fund case, Judge Torres&#8217;summary judgment took over eight months from the Reply Briefs.</p>
<p>Quiller Inc. VS U.S.A took SEVEN months for Judge Torres&#8217; Decision. The Fitzgerald case, and several others I could name, took SIX months for Judge Torres to rule.</p></blockquote>
<p>Deaton concluded that even though he believed a ruling would have been out by now, &#8220;there are other cases and examples that have taken an equal amount of time.&#8221; He also said that the judge is likely aware of the magnitude of her decision.</p>
<h2>September&#8217;s the Month?</h2>
<p>Commenting under Deaton&#8217;s Twitter thread was none other than Ripple&#8217;s CTO &#8211; David Schwartz. He said that it&#8217;s understandable that people are annoyed as waiting itself is annoying. However, he added that he wouldn&#8217;t think something was wrong, unusual, or strange &#8220;until at least the end of September.&#8221;</p>
<p>John Deaton agreed:</p>
<blockquote><p>On September 30th [corrected by editorial], Judge Torres would be placed on the 6-month naughty judge list for the first time and her decision would be pending over 9 months. I didn&#8217;t review every case she has had but I didn&#8217;t find any that were longer than 9 months (although one was slightly longer than 8 months).</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/when-will-the-ripple-sec-ruling-come-xrp-cto-and-known-attorney-speculate-on-a-deadline/" rel="nofollow">When Will The Ripple-SEC Ruling Come? XRP CTO and Known Attorney Speculate on a Deadline</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
