<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Trader Predicts the Shiba Inu, Pepe &amp; Wojak Price Explosion, Makes $1 Million Profit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trader-predicts-shiba-inu-pepe-wojak-price-explosion-makes-1-million-profit.htm</link><description>Twitter crypto analyst @lookonchain tracked one account that is really good at buying meme coins early, and the right ones. &lt;br /&gt;
Not only did the crypto expert make over a million dollars profiting from the Shiba Inu bull run back in 2021 - and still holds some of that SHIB - he's been holding PEPE and WOJAK tokens from a lot lower down too....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trader-predicts-shiba-inu-pepe-wojak-price-explosion-makes-1-million-profit.htm"&gt;Read More: Trader Predicts the Shiba Inu, Pepe &amp; Wojak Price Explosion, Makes $1 Million Profit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/trader-predicts-shiba-inu-pepe-wojak-price-explosion-makes-1-million-profit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113032/273575/pepe-crypto-price-bybit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="372830"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Interest Rate Decision Sends BTC Down Before Bouncing Back Up – Where is BTC Heading Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-interest-rate-decision-sends-btc-down-before-bouncing-back-up-where-btc-heading-now.htm</link><description>The recent US interest rate decision has sent Bitcoin's price on a downward trajectory before experiencing a bounce back – raising questions about where BTC is heading now.  &lt;br /&gt;
As investors and market analysts try to decipher the future direction of Bitcoin's value, this update aims to provide valuable insights and predictions to help navigate the ever-changing cryptocurrency landscape....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-interest-rate-decision-sends-btc-down-before-bouncing-back-up-where-btc-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US Interest Rate Decision Sends BTC Down Before Bouncing Back Up – Where is BTC Heading Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 23:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-interest-rate-decision-sends-btc-down-before-bouncing-back-up-where-btc-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112969/273449/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1158750"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Consolidates Ahead of Key US Jobs Data, But Falling Yields Could Signal Incoming BTC Price Pump</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-consolidates-ahead-of-key-us-jobs-data-but-falling-yields-could-signal-incoming-btc-price-pump.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) continues to consolidate within familiar ranges close to $29,000 ahead of the release of key US jobs data on Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
The data, which is expected to show that the pace of hiring and wage growth in the US remains robust, and that the unemployment rate remains close to historic lows, come on the heels of a 25 bps rate hike from the US Federal Reserve earlier this week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-consolidates-ahead-of-key-us-jobs-data-but-falling-yields-could-signal-incoming-btc-price-pump.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Consolidates Ahead of Key US Jobs Data, But Falling Yields Could Signal Incoming BTC Price Pump&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Yields</category><category>Fed</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 22:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-consolidates-ahead-of-key-us-jobs-data-but-falling-yields-could-signal-incoming-btc-price-pump.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113031/273573/btc-36.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="10256470"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Reports Increased Earnings in First Quarter, While Making the Call for “Crypto Specific Rules”</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-reports-increased-earnings-first-quarter-while-making-call-for-crypto-specific-rules.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Coinbase reported higher revenue in its first quarter, while also pushing for “crypto specific rules,” in its latest earnings report. &lt;br /&gt;
Total revenue grew 23 percent quarter over quarter to $773 million, according to a Coinbase shareholder letter released on Thursday afternoon.  &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange also included a chapter in that letter about what it sees as “regulation by enforcement,” in the U.S. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-reports-increased-earnings-first-quarter-while-making-call-for-crypto-specific-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Reports Increased Earnings in First Quarter, While Making the Call for “Crypto Specific Rules”&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Earnings</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 21:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-reports-increased-earnings-first-quarter-while-making-call-for-crypto-specific-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113027/273570/brian-armstrong-coinbase-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="140569"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as Bulls Hold Key $0.00010 Level – Where is LUNC Headed Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-key-000001-level-where-lunc-headed-next.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) bulls are currently holding the cryptocurrency above the key psychological $0.00010. &lt;br /&gt;
Nonetheless, price predictions are becoming more bearish. &lt;br /&gt;
LUNC is the cryptocurrency that powers the original Terra blockchain that experienced catastrophe last May when its algorithmic stablecoin TerraUSD (UST) lost its 1:1 peg to the US dollar, triggering sudden capital flight from Terra’s Decentralized Finance ecosystem and hyperinflation in the LUNC supply....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-key-000001-level-where-lunc-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as Bulls Hold Key $0.00010 Level – Where is LUNC Headed Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 20:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-key-000001-level-where-lunc-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113025/273563/lunc.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="720961"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 4 May – Rocket Pool, Stacks, Render</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-may-rocket-pool-stacks-render.htm</link><description>Bitcoin is presently hovering just below the $29,000 mark following a successful close of yesterday's trading session above the highly-monitored level, with a 1.89% price increase in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite achieving an intraday high of $29,387 earlier in the day, the digital currency is currently trading at $28,900. &lt;br /&gt;
Given Bitcoin's recent performance amidst an uncertain macroeconomic backdrop, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-may-rocket-pool-stacks-render.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 4 May – Rocket Pool, Stacks, Render&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-may-rocket-pool-stacks-render.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113021/273561/best-crypto-4-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="363196"/></item><item><title>House Financial Services and Agriculture Subcommitees To Hold Digital Assets Hearing</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-agriculture-subcommitees-hold-digital-assets-hearing.htm</link><description>A House Financial Services Committee panel together with a House Agriculture subcommittee plan to unpack digital asset regulation during a hearing next week. &lt;br /&gt;
Both of those subcommittees’ digital asset focused subcommittees will jointly hold the hearing titled “The Future of Digital Assets: Measuring the Regulatory Gaps in the Digital Asset Markets”  on May 10. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-agriculture-subcommitees-hold-digital-assets-hearing.htm"&gt;Read More: House Financial Services and Agriculture Subcommitees To Hold Digital Assets Hearing&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Congress</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Digital asset</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-financial-services-agriculture-subcommitees-hold-digital-assets-hearing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113018/273552/pexels-kubra-tokur-14344435.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="72833"/></item><item><title>Former Coinbase CTO Loses $1 Million Bitcoin Bet, Warns About US Hyperinflation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-cto-loses-1-million-bitcoin-bet-warns-about-us-hyperinflation.htm</link><description>Coinbase’s former chief technology officer Balaji Srinivasan has settled his bet from March that Bitcoin would reach $1 million in just 90 days, while warning the public that he still believes hyperinflation is coming. &lt;br /&gt;
“I just burned a million to tell you they're printing trillions,” Srinivasan started his Twitter thread by saying, while explaining that he made the bet not to make money, but to rather as way to get people’s attention....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-cto-loses-1-million-bitcoin-bet-warns-about-us-hyperinflation.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Coinbase CTO Loses $1 Million Bitcoin Bet, Warns About US Hyperinflation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-coinbase-cto-loses-1-million-bitcoin-bet-warns-about-us-hyperinflation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112991/273466/balaji.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="981632"/></item><item><title>What's Next for Crypto Prices After Interest Rate Decision? – yPredict Tool Makes AI Price Predictions Easy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-after-interest-rate-decision-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm</link><description>Traders are asking where is next for crypto prices in wake of the US Federal Reserve’s latest interest rate decision. &lt;br /&gt;
At current levels just under the $29,000 and $1,900 levels respectively, Bitcoin and Ethereum are both not much changed in wake of the Fed raising interest rates by 25 bps to 5.0-5.25% on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-after-interest-rate-decision-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm"&gt;Read More: What's Next for Crypto Prices After Interest Rate Decision? – yPredict Tool Makes AI Price Predictions Easy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Crypto Prices</category><category>Interest Rate</category><category>yPredict</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/whats-next-for-crypto-prices-after-interest-rate-decision-ypredict-tool-makes-ai-price-predictions-easy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113013/273544/coins-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6827508"/></item><item><title>North Carolina House Passes Bill Banning State Agencies From Accepting CBDCs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-carolina-house-passes-bill-banning-state-agencies-from-accepting-cbdcs.htm</link><description>The North Carolina House of Representatives passed a bill that would ban state agencies from accepting payments in central bank digital currencies. &lt;br /&gt;
Lawmakers passed that bill 118-0 on Wednesday.   &lt;br /&gt;
The bill would encompass “any institution, bureau, board, commission, officer, or political subdivision of the State.”  &lt;br /&gt;
Republican lawmakers Harry Warren and Mark Brody sponsored the bill....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-carolina-house-passes-bill-banning-state-agencies-from-accepting-cbdcs.htm"&gt;Read More: North Carolina House Passes Bill Banning State Agencies From Accepting CBDCs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>North Carolina</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>Treasury</category><category>Ron DeSantis</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-carolina-house-passes-bill-banning-state-agencies-from-accepting-cbdcs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113009/273502/pexels-mark-stebnicki-9407524.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="95579"/></item><item><title>U.S. Regulator Cuts Digital Assets Out of Hedge Fund Rule</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-cuts-digital-assets-out-of-hedge-fund-rule.htm</link><description>The Securities and Exchange Commission has decided to leave digital assets out of a new rule requiring more information from hedge fund and private equity advisers.  &lt;br /&gt;
The agency voted to adopt new changes to private fund reporting, specifically to Form PF — a reporting form for registered investment advisers to private funds.  &lt;br /&gt;
Those changes include requiring disclosures of events that “could indicate significant stress,” such as “extraordinary investment losses."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-cuts-digital-assets-out-of-hedge-fund-rule.htm"&gt;Read More: U.S. Regulator Cuts Digital Assets Out of Hedge Fund Rule&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Digital asset</category><category>Hedge Fund</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-regulator-cuts-digital-assets-out-of-hedge-fund-rule.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112993/273471/chair-gary-gensler-01-2022.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="46638"/></item><item><title>Coinbase to Cease New Loan Issuance Through Bitcoin Borrow Service</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-plans-end-loan-services-as-regulatory-pressure-rises.htm</link><description>Global crypto giant Coinbase has announced plans to shutter its loan services.  &lt;br /&gt;
Effective May 10, Bloomberg reports, Bitcoin-backed loans will cease to be available to customers. &lt;br /&gt;
The exchange emphasized a focus on prioritizing offerings of utmost importance to clientele, resulting in continuous evaluation of its products. &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, this decision coincides with mounting regulatory scrutiny from the US SEC and ongoing customer litigation....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-plans-end-loan-services-as-regulatory-pressure-rises.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase to Cease New Loan Issuance Through Bitcoin Borrow Service&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-plans-end-loan-services-as-regulatory-pressure-rises.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112980/273459/securities-and-exchange-g.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="187992"/></item><item><title>State Regulators Target Fraudulent Cryptos Posing as 'Elon Musk AI Tokens' and 'TruthGPT Coin' – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/state-regulators-target-fraudulent-cryptos-posing-as-elon-musk-ai-tokens-truthgpt-coin-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>The influx of new crypto projects in the market, seeking to leverage the growing interest in artificial intelligence, has attracted US regulators.  &lt;br /&gt;
Several US state regulators are initiating crackdown actions on AI-focused crypto projects touted as investments. &lt;br /&gt;
A May 3 press release revealed that Texas led a coordinated state action against an AI crypto called TruthGPT and Elon Musk AI Token. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/state-regulators-target-fraudulent-cryptos-posing-as-elon-musk-ai-tokens-truthgpt-coin-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: State Regulators Target Fraudulent Cryptos Posing as 'Elon Musk AI Tokens' and 'TruthGPT Coin' – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/state-regulators-target-fraudulent-cryptos-posing-as-elon-musk-ai-tokens-truthgpt-coin-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112982/273462/elon-g97156c7e3-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="147409"/></item><item><title>French Senators Propose Allowing Influencers to Promote Registered Crypto Firms</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/french-senators-propose-allowing-influencers-promote-registered-crypto-firms.htm</link><description>The French Senate’s Committee on Economic Affairs has proposed a new law allowing social media influencers to promote cryptocurrency on their platforms.  &lt;br /&gt;
If approved, the proposal would significantly shift how these influencers market and advertise digital currencies in France. &lt;br /&gt;
Surprisingly, the Senate’s proposal surfaced just a few months following the National Assembly legislation ban on influencers’ promotion of digital asset products and services....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/french-senators-propose-allowing-influencers-promote-registered-crypto-firms.htm"&gt;Read More: French Senators Propose Allowing Influencers to Promote Registered Crypto Firms&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/french-senators-propose-allowing-influencers-promote-registered-crypto-firms.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112987/273497/adobestock-197728036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="913365"/></item><item><title>Celsius Network's Mashinsky Refutes Blame for Crypto Lender's Collapse in Legal Battle – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-mashinsky-refutes-blame-for-crypto-lenders-collapse-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Celsius Network co-founder and former CEO Alex Mashinsky has denied any wrongdoing and shrugged off blame for the collapse of the crypto lender. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Tuesday filing, Mashinsky’s lawyers called claims by New York Attorney General Letitia James that he misled investors about the financial health of Celsius while he was chief executive “baseless” and rooted in misinformation circulated online....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-mashinsky-refutes-blame-for-crypto-lenders-collapse-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Celsius Network's Mashinsky Refutes Blame for Crypto Lender's Collapse in Legal Battle – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Alex Mashinsky</category><category>Celsius</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-mashinsky-refutes-blame-for-crypto-lenders-collapse-legal-battle-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112994/273475/ace6f8f293.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="47984"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Nigeria's Government Approves a National Blockchain Policy, CEX Trade Volumes Fall for 1st Time in 3 Months, INX Works with BitGo to Launch a Pilot Wallet Management Solution for Regulated Security Tokens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nigerias-government-approves-a-national-blockchain-policy-cex-trade-volumes-fall-for-1st-time-in-3-months-inx-works-with-bitgo-to-launch-a-pilot-wallet-management-solution-for-regulated-security-tokens.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nigerias-government-approves-a-national-blockchain-policy-cex-trade-volumes-fall-for-1st-time-in-3-months-inx-works-with-bitgo-to-launch-a-pilot-wallet-management-solution-for-regulated-security-tokens.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Nigeria's Government Approves a National Blockchain Policy, CEX Trade Volumes Fall for 1st Time in 3 Months, INX Works with BitGo to Launch a Pilot Wallet Management Solution for Regulated Security Tokens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Market</category><category>Bitget</category><category>INX</category><category>BitGo</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Scam</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Payments</category><category>Latin America</category><category>Investment</category><category>Mongolia</category><category>DeFi</category><category>DEX</category><category>Curve Finance</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nigerias-government-approves-a-national-blockchain-policy-cex-trade-volumes-fall-for-1st-time-in-3-months-inx-works-with-bitgo-to-launch-a-pilot-wallet-management-solution-for-regulated-security-tokens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112951/273414/adobestock-faraz-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="68573"/></item><item><title>Argentinian Lawmaker Suggests Saving in Crypto, Not USD</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-lawmaker-suggests-saving-crypto-not-usd-1.htm</link><description>An Argentinian lawmaker has suggested that citizens should save their money in crypto, rather than United States dollars. &lt;br /&gt;
The comments came from the MP Martin Tetaz, a member for the city of Buenos Aires. &lt;br /&gt;
Tetaz was responding to a tweet from a fellow Buenos Aires MP, Ramiro Marra who asked “politicians who oppose the dollarization” of the Argentine economy “in what currency they keep their savings.” &lt;br /&gt;
To this, Tetaz responded: &lt;br /&gt;
“In crypto.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-lawmaker-suggests-saving-crypto-not-usd-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentinian Lawmaker Suggests Saving in Crypto, Not USD&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentinian-lawmaker-suggests-saving-crypto-not-usd-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112955/273426/adobestock-343494872-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="640712"/></item><item><title>Sui Blockchain Price Prediction as SUI Token Launches on Binance Exchange and Sees $1 Billion Trading Volume in 24 Hours</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-blockchain-price-prediction-as-sui-token-launches-binance-exchange-sees-1-billion-trading-volume-24-hours.htm</link><description>Sui launched its mainnet yesterday, with the layer-one blockchain seeing its native SUI token surpass $1 billion in 24-hour trading volume on Binance. &lt;br /&gt;
As of writing, SUI's price stands at $1.33, with the proof-of-stake token initially being offered at $0.10 as part of a public sale to users of participating exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;
This means it has effectively risen by over 1,000% since its launch, although the coin has declined by 38% after reaching an all-time high of $2.16 yesterday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-blockchain-price-prediction-as-sui-token-launches-binance-exchange-sees-1-billion-trading-volume-24-hours.htm"&gt;Read More: Sui Blockchain Price Prediction as SUI Token Launches on Binance Exchange and Sees $1 Billion Trading Volume in 24 Hours&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-blockchain-price-prediction-as-sui-token-launches-binance-exchange-sees-1-billion-trading-volume-24-hours.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112952/273429/sui-blockchain-price-pred.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1329032"/></item><item><title>Blockstream Infrastructure Firm Foresees Rapid Growth in Bitcoin's Layer 2 Technologies</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-infrastructure-firm-foresees-rapid-growth-bitcoins-layer-2-technologies.htm</link><description>An engineer at the Bitcoin-focused development firm Blockstream has said she sees a “Cambrian explosion” coming for the development of layer 2 technologies on the Bitcoin network....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-infrastructure-firm-foresees-rapid-growth-bitcoins-layer-2-technologies.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockstream Infrastructure Firm Foresees Rapid Growth in Bitcoin's Layer 2 Technologies&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Blockstream</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockstream-infrastructure-firm-foresees-rapid-growth-bitcoins-layer-2-technologies.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112956/273424/firework.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="377385"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Meme Coins Surge in Price – Time to Buy DOGE?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-surge-price-time-buy-doge.htm</link><description>The Dogecoin price has risen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, reaching $0.079494 after the cryptocurrency market reacted positively to the Federal Reserve's latest rate hike. &lt;br /&gt;
This means that DOGE has gained by a modest 1% in the past week but is down by 17% in the last 30 days, although the original meme token has gained by 13% since the start of 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-surge-price-time-buy-doge.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as Meme Coins Surge in Price – Time to Buy DOGE?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-meme-coins-surge-price-time-buy-doge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112940/273413/dogecoin-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1649342"/></item></channel></rss>
