<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chinese Police Detain Team Behind Yuan-Backed CNHC Stablecoin: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-police-detain-team-behind-yuan-backed-cnhc-stablecoin-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253164</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/PoliceArrest-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/PoliceArrest-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[People familiar with the matter said the company's cross-border payment business could be the reason for the arrest.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chinese police have reportedly arrested and detained some employees of Trust Reserve, the company behind the yuan-backed CNHC stablecoin.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.panewslab.com/zh/sqarticledetails/7pomrdow.html?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=auto&amp;_x_tr_hl=en-GB" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> from local media PANews, the Trust Reserve&#8217;s core team was apprehended at noon on May 29, and their family members have been notified.</p>
<h2>Police Arrest CNHC Issuance Team</h2>
<p>Representatives for PANews visited the company&#8217;s office in Pudong, Shanghai, and found a vacant workspace with a seal that read &#8220;Judicial Seizure, Strictly No Vandalism&#8221; at the door. The notice was signed on May 29.</p>
<p>While the reason for the arrest remains unclear, people familiar with the matter told the local news agency that Trust Reserve&#8217;s cross-border payment business might be the reason for the case.</p>
<p>Trust Reserve owns two stablecoins &#8211; an offshore Chinese yuan-backed asset (CNHC) and a Hong Kong dollar-backed token (HKDC). The stablecoin issuer recently secured $10 million for CNHC in a funding round led by KuCoin Ventures, the investment arm of Seychelles-based cryptocurrency exchange KuCoin.</p>
<p>Circle Ventures, the investment division of USDC stablecoin issuer Circle, and multinational investment firm IDG Capital also participated in the round.</p>
<p>CNHC, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/conflux-to-bring-uniswap-v3-and-curve-to-chinas-public-blockchain/" data-wpel-link="internal">backed</a> by permissionless layer 1 blockchain network Conflux, is pegged 1:1 with the offshore yuan (CNH), whose reserves are kept at a Hong Kong depository institution.</p>
<h2>Fear and Uncertainty</h2>
<p>News of the arrest comes amid unverified rumors of Chinese authorities allegedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/multichain-token-crashes-over-20-amid-reports-of-users-funds-being-stuck/" data-wpel-link="internal">arresting</a> the Multichain project team. Multichain is a cross-chain router protocol with over $1 billion in assets locked in its contract.</p>
<p>In the past week, transactions on the protocol have been delayed and stuck with multiple offline cross-chain bridge pathways, including Polygon zxEVM, Kava, and zkSync. The team initially said the issue was from a backend upgrade, which is taking longer than expected. However, the narrative was later changed to problems stemming from uncontrollable events.</p>
<p>The Multichain team has failed to confirm or refute the ongoing rumors and has remained silent on social media platforms, including their Telegram group and Discord server.</p>
<p>On May 25, Multichain co-founder DJ Qian, who no longer works with the project, <a href="https://twitter.com/djqianfusion/status/1661580864504078336?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">disclosed</a> on Twitter that the current CEO, Zhaojun, was unavailable when asked to provide technical help for the ongoing issue.</p>
<p>The sudden disappearance of the Multichain and Trust Reserve teams may spark fear and uncertainty among their users, causing a panic sale of their products.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-police-detain-team-behind-yuan-backed-cnhc-stablecoin-report/" rel="nofollow">Chinese Police Detain Team Behind Yuan-Backed CNHC Stablecoin: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Reserve Says Higher Rates Could Exacerbate Stress For Banks, But What of Bitcoin?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-says-higher-rates-could-exacerbate-stress-for-banks-but-what-of-bitcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federal Reserve]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253284</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Federal_Reserve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Federal_Reserve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve might “skip” a rate hike this June as pressure mounts on banks and indebted businesses.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Historically high-interest rates in the United States could “exacerbate” stress in an already shaky banking system, said a member of the Federal Reserve’s Board of Governors on Wednesday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The governor also hinted that the central bank might decide not to raise its benchmark interest rate at the next Federal Open Markets Committee (FOMC) meeting, which could have implications for Bitcoin’s price.</span></p>
<h2>Rising Rates and Mounting Debt</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Fed Governor Philip N. Jefferson </span><a href="https://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/speech/jefferson20230531a.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">remarked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on the U.S. financial system’s economic outlook during a speech at the 22nd Annual International Conference on Policy Challenges for the Financial Sector in Washington D.C.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While claiming that the banking system had “stabilized” following multiple bank runs and foreclosures in March, the governor recognized the risks associated with elevated short-term interest rates, which are “5 percentage points higher than they were a little over a year ago.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As Jefferson explained, the effects of monetary policy work with “long and variable lags,” which aren’t fully accounted for in one year alone. Throughout the rest of the year, he predicts slow growth amid “heightened uncertainty” and a decline in household savings and tight financial conditions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though the governor doesn’t predict a recession, he claimed that the combination of low earnings and high rates could “test the ability of businesses to service debt. “ </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“In addition… higher interest rates could further exacerbate stress at banking organizations, especially those that are highly exposed to longer-duration assets and have a relatively high ratio of uninsured deposits to total deposits,” he continued. </span></p></blockquote>
<h2>Will The Fed ‘Skip’ A Rate Hike?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) experienced a bank run in March, it occurred after the company disclosed a $1.8 billion realized loss on its long-duration bonds.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Insurance coverage ultimately didn’t matter for SVB, as the Federal Reserve, Treasury Department, and FDIC agreed at the time to fully bail out all depositors as a “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/european-regulators-blast-federal-reserve-for-svb-depositor-bailout/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">systemic risk exception</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Critics of the move </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/buy-the-fing-pivot-arthur-hayes-on-bank-bailouts-and-bitcoins-endgame/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">noted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> how the central bank’s rescue activity reversed much of its progress in attempting to withdraw liquidity from the economy, which could contribute to inflation for assets like Bitcoin again. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The governor floated the idea that the Fed might “hold” its policy rate constant at a “coming meeting,” but that this shouldn’t be interpreted as the Fed reaching “the peak rate for this cycle.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Indeed, skipping a rate hike at a coming meeting would allow the Committee to see more data before making decisions about the extent of additional policy firming,&#8221; he concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Rising rates drove Bitcoin and stock down throughout 2022, making an approaching peak rate potentially bullish for the asset. That said, analysis </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-showing-promising-rise-potential-after-fed-rate-decision-santiment/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">suggests</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Bitcoin may not be as affected by rate hikes as it was last year.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-reserve-says-higher-rates-could-exacerbate-stress-for-banks-but-what-of-bitcoin/" rel="nofollow">Federal Reserve Says Higher Rates Could Exacerbate Stress For Banks, But What of Bitcoin?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nansen Slashes 30% of Work Force, Aims to Prioritize Sustainable Business</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nansen-slashes-30-of-work-force-aims-to-prioritize-sustainable-business/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253163</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/nansen_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/nansen_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the layoff,  Nansen's CEO is optimistic about the future of the "young and learning" organization.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain data analytics firm Nansen Research is slashing its workforce by 30%. Layoffs have been widespread across crypto businesses in the past year.</p>
<p>Following the latest move, Nansen joins the growing list of companies such as Coinbase, Blockchain.com, ConsenSys, Gemini, Huobi Polygon Labs, Elliptic, Messari, Dapper Labs, Chainalysis, Immutable, etc., which have trimmed their staff amid heightened crypto winter.</p>
<h2>Nansen Layoff</h2>
<p>CEO Alex Svanevik <a href="https://twitter.com/ASvanevik/status/1663565124970610688" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced </a>on Twitter the &#8220;extremely difficult decision&#8221; and took full responsibility. The exec pointed out that Nansen&#8217;s attempt to expand into business areas that were not core to the company&#8217;s strategy backfired. Svanevik added that the team will focus on targeting fewer things but doing them &#8220;extremely well.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Firstly, we scaled up the team on the back of breakneck growth in our first years of operating. We wanted to invest and build in a tough market when others needed to scale back. This organic growth led the organization to taking on surface areas that’s not truly part of Nansen’s core strategy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Nansen was founded in 2019 and gained tremendous traction in less than three years. During the same period, the company witnessed the diversification of revenues via enterprise as well institutional clients. However, owing to the brutal market condition in the past year, Nansen&#8217;s cost base surged too high relative to where the company is today. As a result, the priority is to build a sustainable business, according to the CEO.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I’m endlessly grateful to the incredible people we are parting ways with. They will go on to achieve great things, and we&#8217;ll ensure they get a soft landing, with severance and support.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Besides, Nansen <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-analytics-firm-nansen-raises-75-million-in-funding-led-by-accel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raised</a> $75 million via a Series B funding round led by the venture capital firm Accel in December 2021. Other participants of the round included GIC, Andreessen Horowitz (a16z), and Tiger Global.</p>
<h2>Launch of Nansen Query</h2>
<p>In March, the Singapore-based company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nansen-launches-data-platform-for-crypto-investors-and-projects/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a new solution built on the Google Cloud platform, dubbed &#8216;Nansen Query,&#8217; that is designed to offer a comprehensive data solution to crypto-focused teams and projects.</p>
<p>According to the report, the new offering was expected to improve multi-chain data access, assisting entities to make better customer, product, and investment decisions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nansen-slashes-30-of-work-force-aims-to-prioritize-sustainable-business/" rel="nofollow">Nansen Slashes 30% of Work Force, Aims to Prioritize Sustainable Business</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bybit Pulls Out of Canada Amid New Crypto Regulations </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-pulls-out-of-canada-amid-new-crypto-regulations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 21:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253148</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bybit_Canada.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bybit_Canada.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bybit becomes the latest cryptocurrency exchange to pull out of the Canadian market.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Popular cryptocurrency exchange Bybit announced it will be exiting the Canadian market, citing recent regulatory developments in the country as the reason behind its decision. The move follows similar decisions made by other exchanges that ceased operations in the North American nation.</p>
<p>Starting May 31, new account openings will be unavailable, while existing customers will have until July 31 to make further deposits and enter into new contracts. The company also promised that old users would be able to withdraw or reduce their positions after the closing date.</p>
<h2>A Difficult But Necessary Decision</h2>
<p>Bybit&#8217;s decision to leave Canada comes after the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) <a href="https://www.osc.ca/en/news-events/news/canadian-securities-regulators-strengthen-oversight-enhance-expectations-crypto-asset-trading" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">issued</a> new guidance for crypto entities, which forces digital asset trading platforms to obtain approval from the CSA. The new regulations include passing various due diligence checks.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It has always been Bybit&#8217;s primary objective to operate our business in compliance with all relevant rules and regulations in Canada. In light of recent regulatory development, Bybit has made the difficult but necessary decision to pause the availability of our products and services,&#8221; Bybit <a href="https://announcements.bybit.com/article/notice-on-exit-from-canadian-market-bltc1bfb8746d077fda/#" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> in a statement.</p></blockquote>
<p>The current regulatory environment in Canada has become increasingly challenging for some crypto exchanges to navigate, causing several high-profile exits, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-close-canadian-shop-citing-recent-regulatory-changes/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance</a> and others who have also pulled out of the country.</p>
<h2>Not All Exchanges Are Leaving</h2>
<p>In contrast, Coinbase, the largest crypto exchange in the U.S., is expanding in Canada. In March, the company <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/building-for-canada-and-the-world-from-canada" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">hired</a> over 200 engineers in the country to support its global product portfolio. The exchange also stated that its global leadership team would frequently engage with regulators, partners, and the community in Canada to better understand the market and its unique needs.</p>
<p>The diverging strategies of crypto exchanges toward the Canadian market reflect the uncertainty surrounding the regulatory regime in the country. Bybit&#8217;s exit, along with the withdrawal of Binance, signals a setback for the Canadian crypto industry.</p>
<p>However, Coinbase&#8217;s expansion highlights the confidence of some firms in the Canadian market, despite regulatory challenges. Bybit becomes the latest cryptocurrency exchange to pull out of the Canadian market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-pulls-out-of-canada-amid-new-crypto-regulations/" rel="nofollow">Bybit Pulls Out of Canada Amid New Crypto Regulations </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Would Happen to Bitcoin If The US Debt Ceiling Cracks (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-happen-to-bitcoin-if-the-us-debt-ceiling-cracks-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 19:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253116</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although an initial deal was reached, the US' debt issues are still a growing concern among investors. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Watch that little blue line on Google Trends for &#8220;bitcoin&#8221; hit the ceiling if the U.S. defaults on its debt. BTC might suffer at first as markets go risk-off, but could easily shine in another global financial crisis.</p>
<p>House Republicans <a href="https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/us-debt-ceiling-deadline-talks-05-30-23/index.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reached</a> a tentative deal with President Joe Biden&#8217;s White House over the Memorial Day Weekend. The deal would help raise the debt limit imposed by Congress on federal borrowing.</p>
<p>But it isn&#8217;t yet assured. House Democrats are unhappy with some of the last-minute concessions made by the Biden Administration. Meanwhile, Republicans may not back the bill born of the recent debt limit deal. U.S. Senator Rand Paul (R-KY) says he will not be voting for it in the Senate.</p>
<h2>U.S. Debt Deal Reached, but not Final</h2>
<p>The Treasury <a href="https://apnews.com/article/debt-limit-deal-biden-mccarthy-default-01657c829be119850cd65ab9ffb0626a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">could begin</a> running short to meet bills due as soon as June 5th if the debt ceiling isn&#8217;t raised:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In the United States, a default could cause financial markets to freeze up and spark an international financial crisis. Analysts say millions of jobs would vanish, borrowing and unemployment rates would jump, and a stock-market plunge could erase trillions of dollars in household wealth. It would all but shatter the $24 trillion market for Treasury debt.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>So what would happen to Bitcoin and the price of other cryptocurrencies if the U.S. defaults on its obligations? A debt default would put the economy in an enormous jam. That could easily push crypto prices down across the board.</p>
<h2>Default Would Tank Crypto Prices&#8230; at First</h2>
<p>Crypto and stock prices <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-high-bitcoin-and-ethereum-correlation-with-wall-street-continues/" data-wpel-link="internal">were in</a> correlation for 18 months when crypto winter thawed in January. Throughout the first half of 2023, the correlation <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stocks-correlation-surges-after-decoupling-from-wall-st-amid-ftx-drama/" data-wpel-link="internal">has remained</a> significant.</p>
<p>What if the economy locks up, stocks take a dive, and there&#8217;s another global financial crisis? Crypto prices moving in correlation with stocks would be apt to crater. So if the U.S. defaults instead of extending the debt ceiling soon, the macro outlook for crypto prices will likely be very bearish.</p>
<p>On the other hand, a U.S. default would throw financial markets into total disarray. That could make Bitcoin look much better by comparison. In fact, it would tend to support the thesis of Bitcoin permabulls that centrally managed financial systems inevitably disappoint their users with corruption and mismanagement.</p>
<p>So after an initial drop in crypto prices, while markets go risk-off, Bitcoin could get some legs under it for a stout bull run. That&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-bitcoin-price-rally-continue-in-q2-7-key-considerations-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">what happened</a> after the series of major bank failures in March.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-happen-to-bitcoin-if-the-us-debt-ceiling-cracks-opinion/" rel="nofollow">What Would Happen to Bitcoin If The US Debt Ceiling Cracks (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ECOS: Cryptocurrency Mining Made Easy</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ecos-cryptocurrency-mining-made-easy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253246</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Mining is at the forefront of the security and overall concept of many digital currencies, including Bitcoin and many others. However, setting up a mining operation is difficult. The upfront cost to make it economically viable is considerable, but it also requires a lot of technical knowledge, ongoing fine-tuning, and a myriad of other activities [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mining is at the forefront of the security and overall concept of many digital currencies, including Bitcoin and many others.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253248" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover.jpg" alt="ecos_mining_cover" width="1200" height="700" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover.jpg 1200w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover-300x175.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover-1024x597.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover-768x448.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ecos_mining_cover-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" /></a></p>
<p>However, setting up a mining operation is difficult. The upfront cost to make it economically viable is considerable, but it also requires a lot of technical knowledge, ongoing fine-tuning, and a myriad of other activities that many regular users simply don’t have.</p>
<p>This is where solutions such as cloud mining come into play. The following takes a closer look at ECOS &#8211; a cryptocurrency investment platform that also offers cloud mining services.</p>
<h2>What is ECOS?</h2>
<p><a href="https://ecos.am/en/cloud-mining?ref=WXyIoO4d&amp;utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=article&amp;utm_campaign=%3Futm_source%3Dmailchimp+utm_medium%3Demail+utm_campaign%3D20230526_cloud-mining_none_usa_all_regular&amp;utm_content=cryptopotato" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>ECOS</strong></a> is a company that’s registered in Armenia with its data center facility located at Hrazdan. According to the official website, the company has been fully operational since 2017. It also reveals that it has founded  the free economic zone that’s supported by the local government.</p>
<p>In essence, ECOS is a cryptocurrency investment platform for earnings from the best in class digital assets. It has a mission of providing its users with simple, quick, and effective tools for a wide variety of investment strategies, from passive to speculative ones.</p>
<p>It boasts four core products, which include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Cloud mining</li>
<li>Mining Farm</li>
<li>Cryptocurrency wallet &amp; exchange</li>
<li>Investment portfolio</li>
<li>NFT</li>
</ul>
<p>Speaking of cloud mining, it’s important to highlight the necessity of carefully vetting the platforms to work with because a lot of them are not trustworthy. According to the official website, ECOS also owns its very own mining farm and has a number of reputable partners. It also has more than 400k registered clients from all over the world.</p>
<p>Commenting on the matter was Ilya Goldberg, Founder &amp; CEO at ECOS, who said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We use green energy for our ASICs in the amount of up to 40% of the consumed energy and planning to go for 100% &#8211; that&#8217;s why we establish contracts with hydroelectric power stations. Our asics are among the greenest in the world&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>What is Cloud Mining?</h2>
<p>Cloud mining has been a very hot topic for everyone in the past few years. It’s a concept which allows users to take advantage of rented cloud computing power without having to install hardware and all the associated software that’s necessary for mining crypto.</p>
<p><a href="https://ecos.am/en/cloud-mining?ref=WXyIoO4d&amp;utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=article&amp;utm_campaign=%3Futm_source%3Dmailchimp+utm_medium%3Demail+utm_campaign%3D20230526_cloud-mining_none_usa_all_regular&amp;utm_content=cryptopotato" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>ECOS</strong></a> allows people to participate in Bitcoin mining remotely for a certain cost. In theory, this makes mining more accessible to a broader group of people, regardless of where they are located. Of course, they would still need access to the internet.</p>
<p>To start investing via cloud mining, users have to buy a certain cloud mining contract. This, in essence, is an agreement to rent a certain amount of hash power. The higher the cost of the contract, the higher the amount of power one can purchase.</p>
<p>The website has a calculator which provides some examples of the different contracts that ECOS offers and users can take advantage of.</p>
<p>One of the main benefits of cloud mining is that users won’t have to buy any equipment. Once they purchase a mining contract, they would rent a part of the equipment that ECOS owns and uses to mine BTC every day.</p>
<p>On the homepage of their website, you will find a comprehensive calculator which shows exactly what types of contracts a user can buy, how much money it would cost, the duration of the contract, the hash power rented, as well as an indication of the expected revenue. Of course, this is based on projected prices of BTC in the future, so it’s important to keep in mind that price fluctuation will impact the generated revenue. This is something that impacts every miner, regardless of whether they use rented hash power or they have their own setup.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253247" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-6.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="474" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-6-300x236.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture1-6-50x39.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Of course, ECOS charges a service fee, which is to be expected. According to their website:</p>
<p><em>“The service charge is the payment for electricity and maintenance by ECOS. The service charge is indicated for 1 TH/s per day. It will be deducted daily from the BTC earning. You can choose a contract with no service charge. However, in this case you will get less hash power.”</em></p>
<p>Therefore, the service fee would be entirely dependent on the user’s preference and the specified contract.</p>
<p>There’s also a minimum and maximum contract duration that users can go for, as depicted above.. ECOS accepts payments in BTC and other cryptocurrencies, by card and invoices.</p>
<p>As mentioned previously, ECOS also provides a myriad of other services. For more information on ECOS and its investment products, please visit the official website.</p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ecos-cryptocurrency-mining-made-easy/" rel="nofollow">ECOS: Cryptocurrency Mining Made Easy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mass Layoffs At Binance? Company Admits to “Reevaluating” Roles</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mass-layoffs-at-binance-company-admits-to-reevaluating-roles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance could let go of up to 20% of its current workforce in June, but refuses to call its resource allocation plans a "rightsizing."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance – the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange – has confirmed that its “reevaluating” its talent base following an external report that the firm plans to lay off roughly 20% of its workforce next month. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The report presents a stark contrast to Binance’s position of strength last year, having stood out among industry leaders for continuing to expand during the bear market. </span></p>
<h2>Binance to Cut Workers</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Wednesday, popular Chinese crypto reporter Colin Wu </span><a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1663890209526927373" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> he’d confirmed with “multiple sources” that Binance had begun to lay off workers. Though the current proportion remains uncertain, estimates suggested the number of fired employees could be as high as 20% of Binance’s 8000-person workforce. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Some departments are still continuing to recruit,” clarified Wu. “The layoffs may be related to the poor overall market and the large expansion before.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nearly one year ago, Binance CEO Changpneg Zhao </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-expanding-hirings-amid-falling-crypto-market/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">boasted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the exchange was sitting on a “healthy war chest” thanks to relatively frugal spending during the previous year’s bull market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Unlike rival exchanges such as </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-announces-18-layoff-amid-impending-recession/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Crypto.com which were cutting their headcount, Binance </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1537013824666095617?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1537013824666095617%7Ctwgr%5E%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reuters.com%2Ftechnology%2Fbinance-opens-2000-positions-hiring-ceo-2022-06-15%2F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">confirmed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that it would be hiring over 2000 employees at the time. </span></p>
<h2>Not a &#8220;Rightsizing&#8221;</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Apparently, things haven’t changed on that front. In a message to </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Wednesday, a Binance spokesperson maintained that the firm is still seeking out new talent to “fill hundreds of open roles.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“As we prepare for the next major bull cycle, it has become clear that we need to focus on talent density across the organization to ensure we remain nimble and dynamic,” the spokesperson said. “This is not a case of rightsizing, but rather, reevaluating whether we have the right talent and expertise in critical roles.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The representative added that the company would look into “certain products and business units” to ensure its resources were allocated properly. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance’s Chief Communications Officer, Patrick Hillman, also stressed that the company was not enacting a 20% layoff “as a cost-cutting measure.” Rather, it’s part of a “talent density audit and resource allocation exercise,” the company conducts on a cyclical 6-month basis. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We have amazing talent at Binance and we will continue to retain and hire more top talent,” he added. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We have amazing talent at Binance and we will continue to retain and hire more top talent. When we do have to part ways with an employee, they immediately become a high-value target for recruiters across the globe with clients looking to explore digital assets.</p>
<p>&mdash; Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) <a href="https://twitter.com/PRHillmann/status/1663925659226320896?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite slowing business activity last year, major crypto companies like </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Block reported sizable quarter-to-quarter revenue improvements in Q1 2023 as the crypto market bounced well away from its November lows. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mass-layoffs-at-binance-company-admits-to-reevaluating-roles/" rel="nofollow">Mass Layoffs At Binance? Company Admits to “Reevaluating” Roles</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bumper’s Breakthrough DeFi Protocol Set to Reshape Options Pricing</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bumpers-breakthrough-defi-protocol-set-to-reshape-options-pricing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253222</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/imageedit_2_3411670161_1685531273hA1ICLC3D5.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/imageedit_2_3411670161_1685531273hA1ICLC3D5.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, May 31st, 2023] Marking a seismic shift in the digital asset landscape, DeFi platform Bumper today unveiled the findings of their comprehensive simulation, exhibiting new pricing efficiencies over traditional options desks ahead of the protocol launch in August 2023. This report delineates a milestone in financial technology, showcasing an [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, United Kingdom, May 31st, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Marking a seismic shift in the digital asset landscape, DeFi platform <a href="https://www.bumper.fi/?utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_source=chainwire&amp;utm_campaign=sim-report" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Bumper</a> today unveiled the findings of their comprehensive simulation, exhibiting new pricing efficiencies over traditional options desks ahead of the protocol launch in August 2023.</p>
<p>This <a href="https://bumper.fi/resources/simulation-report?utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_source=chainwire&amp;utm_campaign=sim-report" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> delineates a milestone in financial technology, showcasing an altogether new financial instrument that consistently outperforms existing options desks in generating both competitive premia and sustainable yields, backtested against genuine, multi-year historical cryptocurrency market data and options prices.</p>
<p>The report is the culmination of a two-year exercise in Research and Development powered by a $20m investment and derived in collaboration with CADLabs and the Swiss Centre for Cryptoeconomics.</p>
<p><strong>Key highlights from the simulation report:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>On average, Bumper Takers paid 9.3% cheaper premia than buyers of traditional put options.</li>
<li>During the 2022 bear market, Bumper’s simulation showed a yield improvement of 46.2% for Makers compared to options pricing without resorting to token incentives.</li>
<li>The protocol remained solvent throughout the simulated conditions.</li>
<li>Despite having different inputs and methodology, Bumper’s results reveal a remarkable correlation with the Nobel Prize-winning Black-Scholes model.</li>
</ul>
<p>These results have been pivotal in understanding and honing the resilience of the Bumper protocol across diverse market conditions.</p>
<blockquote><p>On the release of the report, Bumper CEO Jonathan DeCarteret expressed, &#8220;By challenging and potentially reshaping the accepted norms of options pricing, Bumper stands to revolutionise not just the crypto options market, but also has the potential to penetrate traditional finance and disrupt the colossal $13T derivatives market in the future.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The report underscores the anticipated outcomes of Bumper&#8217;s dynamic pricing, based on forward volatility rather than the usual implied volatility.</p>
<p>The findings of the simulation report position Bumper as an immensely appealing prospect for institutions and fund managers, in addition to retail crypto investors.</p>
<p>The economic simulation report released today marks the most significant validation of Bumper&#8217;s innovative approach to date and signals what could be one of the most substantial challenges to the Black-Scholes derived pricing in half a century.</p>
<p><a href="https://bumper.fi/resources/simulation-report?utm_medium=pr&amp;utm_source=chainwire&amp;utm_campaign=sim-report" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Read Bumper’s simulation report here</a>, and for more information on the protocol, visit https://bumper.fi.</p>
<h2>About Bumper</h2>
<p>Bumper is a DeFi risk market that provides protection from downside volatility in the price of crypto assets. Users buying protection (Takers) set a price at which they wish to protect their crypto should the price fall, but they don’t lose out if the market heads upwards. Conversely, other users (Makers) earn a yield by providing stablecoin liquidity to the protocol.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bumpers-breakthrough-defi-protocol-set-to-reshape-options-pricing/" rel="nofollow">Bumper’s Breakthrough DeFi Protocol Set to Reshape Options Pricing</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Expands Presence in Georgia With Investment in Payment Processing Company</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-expands-presence-in-georgia-with-investment-in-payment-processing-company/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253202</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Georgia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Tether_Georgia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether's expansion comes as USDT hit a record high of $83 billion market cap. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether &#8211; the issuer of stablecoin USDT &#8211; announced expanding its presence in Georgia with an investment in a payment processing company called, CityPay.io.</p>
<p>The move is deemed as an &#8220;important milestone&#8221; for the payment processing industry benefiting customers across Georgia and CIS.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the official <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-expands-its-presence-in-georgia-with-investment-in-citypayio/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a>, Tether aims to bring greater efficiency and convenience to the payment industry in Georgia with the latest investment.</li>
<li>Commenting on the development, Paolo Ardoino, Chief Technology Officer at Tether, said,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Tether is committed to supporting companies that share our vision of building a more connected and accessible financial system. This investment in CityPay.io is an important step towards achieving that goal.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Tether said the investment in CityPay.io is the first step towards its expansion in the transcontinental country, which is reportedly one of the most crypto-friendly countries in the world.</li>
<li>In fact, data cited by the Tether revealed that nearly 3% of Georgians own some form of cryptocurrency.</li>
<li>Crypto ATMs are also easily accessible to users in most cities, with a total of 130 ATMs located across the country.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, a study conducted by Forex Suggest ranked Georgia as the fourth most crypto-ready nation in the world.</li>
<li>The latest development comes a day after the stablecoin issuer <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-to-launch-sustainable-bitcoin-mining-operations-in-uruguay/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> investing resources into energy production and the launch of sustainable Bitcoin mining operations in Uruguay.</li>
<li>Earlier this month, Tether <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-will-buy-bitcoin-allocating-15-of-net-realized-operating-profits-regularly-in-btc/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">outlined</a> plans to allocate 15% of its net realized operating profits in Bitcoin, including regular purchases of BTC and funding infrastructure.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-expands-presence-in-georgia-with-investment-in-payment-processing-company/" rel="nofollow">Tether Expands Presence in Georgia With Investment in Payment Processing Company</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple vs. SEC Lawsuit to Wrap up as Soon as June: Charles Hoskinson</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-to-wrap-up-as-soon-as-june-charles-hoskinson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252805</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ripple_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hoskinson believes the resolution of the high-profile case could be within the next month.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ripple lawsuit is now rounding out its 29th month. Ripple Labs (XRP) has spent over $200M defending itself in court. Cardano and Ethereum founder Charles Hoskinson said it will probably be resolved in June.</p>
<p>During a recent &#8220;Surprise AMA&#8221; interview on YouTube, a viewer asked Hoskinson:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Charles, do you think the Ripple case gets resolved soon?&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>To which Mr. Hoskinson answered:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Yes, I do. I think it&#8217;s probably next month.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The co-founder of Ethereum and founder and driving force behind Cardano (ADA) had no further comment in response to the question. He went on to the next after predicting the Ripple lawsuit will be resolved next month.</p>
<p>AMA is an acronym for &#8220;Ask Me Anything,&#8221; a social community-oriented live interview with a special guest. The format originated on Reddit, but Hoskinson does his AMAs on YouTube live streams and uploads the videos of them to other platforms like Twitter.</p>
<h2>Ripple Labs CEO Increasingly Confident</h2>
<p>Ripple Labs CEO Brad Garlinghouse has grown more confident in recent weeks as the case wears on. A string of small victories for Ripple against the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-lawyer-blasts-secs-ripple-lawsuit-as-case-drags-on/" data-wpel-link="internal">has emboldened</a> XRP investors as well.</p>
<p>The unsealing of the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-obtains-hinman-documents-optimistic-about-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">Hinman documents</a> in the case earlier this month was a huge victory for Ripple Labs.</p>
<p>They contain the transcript of a 2018 speech by William Hinman, in which the former SEC director argues cryptocurrencies are commodities. The current chair of the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/clear-as-mud-cftc-chair-says-cryptos-are-commodities-former-commissioner-says-they-can-be-both/" data-wpel-link="internal">CFTC agrees</a>.</p>
<h2>Ripple Lawsuit Has Been Costly for XRP Holders</h2>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has been pressing its case against Ripple Labs since December 2020. At the time, the price of the native token <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-face-sue-sec-xrp-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">crashed</a> 17% in 24 hours.</p>
<p>While fending off the SEC in a long-running suit to classify XRP tokens as securities, Ripple prices at exchanges have reflected the uncertainty of what will happen next.</p>
<p>So a resolution one way or the other to the case will likely be positive as far as letting markets know what to expect. Then crypto investors will be able to evaluate XRP market prices with more confidence.</p>
<p>Additionally, markets will be able to move on to evaluating other aspects of Ripple&#8217;s value, like trends in its network activity and development roadmap.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-to-wrap-up-as-soon-as-june-charles-hoskinson/" rel="nofollow">Ripple vs. SEC Lawsuit to Wrap up as Soon as June: Charles Hoskinson</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
