<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 11:27:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Scammer Sentenced to 9 Years for Draining Almost $250 Million From Victims</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scammer-sentenced-to-9-years-for-draining-almost-250-million-from-victims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 14:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261948</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["Cryptocurrency executives who lie and cheat their customers will be held to account for their crimes," US attorney Damian Williams asseted.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Valley Stream, New York resident &#8211; Eddy Alexandre &#8211; received a nine-year prison sentence for engaging in commodities fraud. He was found guilty of swindling $248 million from over 25,000 investors through his cryptocurrency trading platform called EminiFX.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The investigation determined that Alexandre used some of the funds to purchase luxurious items for himself, such as expensive cars.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The &#8216;Brazen&#8217; Fraud</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Department of Justice (DOJ) <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/ceo-cryptocurrency-and-forex-trading-platform-sentenced-nine-years-prison-240-million" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> Alexandre&#8217;s punishment on its official website, explaining his crime in detail. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He led the dubious crypto investment platform EminiFX between September 2021 and May 2022 and offered &#8220;guaranteed&#8221; high investment returns to clients via special technology. The feature, referred to as his &#8220;trade secret,&#8221; promised customers they would double their money within five months.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">To make it seem legit, each week EminiFX&#8217;s website was falsely representing to users some returns on their investment. In fact, though, Alexandre invested only a small portion of the money entrusted to him and pocketed the rest. He even sustained millions of dollars in losses on the funds he distributed in crypto: a fact that he never revealed to the victims. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The DOJ claimed he misdirected at least $14,700,000 to his personal bank account and purchased a BMW car for himself for $155,000.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">United States Attorney for the Southern District of New York &#8211; Damian Williams &#8211; said Alexandre&#8217;s fraud was &#8220;brazen&#8221; and included &#8220;fabricating weekly investment returns of at least 5% out of thin air.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Most egregiously, Alexandre recruited many of his investors by exploiting his position of trust within his church and the Haitian community, even going so far as to enlist members of the church to help recruit EminiFX investors. As today&#8217;s sentence demonstrates, cryptocurrency executives who lie and cheat their customers will be held to account for their crimes,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from the nine years in jail, Alexandre was slammed with three years of supervised release and ordered to pay forfeiture in the amount of $248 million and restitution worth $213 million. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Father-Son Duo That Face 20 Years in Prison</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">There are many examples of wrongdoers who have conned crypto investors over the past few years only to steal their money and fund a lavish lifestyle.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Such is the case of Brandon Austin and his father &#8211; Eugene &#8220;Hugh&#8221; Austin, who were arrested earlier this year over accusations that they &#8220;victimized both sophisticated and novice cryptocurrency investors alike out of millions.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similar to Alexandre, the family <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/father-and-son-face-up-to-20-years-in-jail-for-orchestrating-a-10m-crypto-scam-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">encouraged</a> people to purchase cryptocurrencies through them by promising great returns. Instead, they embezzled every cent and employed the money for their benefit. According to the officials, they stayed in posh hotels, bought luxurious vehicles, and visited expensive restaurants with the $10 million stolen from investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The alleged criminals now face up to 20 years in prison on charges like money laundering and wire fraud. Brandon has already pleaded guilty, agreeing to forfeit $3.4 million and to pay $2 million in restitution. The magistrates are expected to announce his sentence on September 6. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scammer-sentenced-to-9-years-for-draining-almost-250-million-from-victims/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Scammer Sentenced to 9 Years for Draining Almost $250 Million From Victims</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Swan Author Sees &#8216;Crypto Fad Starting to Peter out&#8217; as Youngsters Turn to AI</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/black-swan-author-sees-crypto-fad-starting-to-peter-out-as-youngsters-turn-to-ai/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261957</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/methode_sundaytimes_prod_web_bin_0f95063e-9736-11e8-b2a8-453c9f590323-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/methode_sundaytimes_prod_web_bin_0f95063e-9736-11e8-b2a8-453c9f590323-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Taleb believes cryptocurrencies and Artificial Intelligence (AI) are both "infatuation."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nassim Nicholas Taleb &#8211; the author of the book &#8220;The Black Swan&#8221; who is among crypto&#8217;s biggest critics &#8211; launched another bashing manifest against the asset class.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes the mania surrounding bitcoin and the alternative coins have started fading out because young people have turned their focus toward Artificial Intelligence (AI).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Latest Dose of Criticism</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In one of his recent tweets, Taleb claimed that the crypto hype is &#8220;starting to peter out&#8221; due to youngsters&#8217; new passion: Artificial Intelligence (AI). However, he was also not kind to the latter, describing it as an &#8220;infatuation&#8221; (just like digital currencies).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He concluded his post with the Latin phrase &#8220;successore novo vincitur omnis amor,&#8221; which is literary translated as &#8220;all love is conquered by a new successor.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The crypto fad is starting to peter out as many of those fanciful young adults who like to play w/computers in their mothers&#8217; basements are now getting enamored with AI.</p>
<p>You need another infatuation to displace an infatuation: successore novo vincitur omnis amor.</p>
<p>— Nassim Nicholas Taleb (@nntaleb) <a href="https://twitter.com/nntaleb/status/1682203721395052545?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 21, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some Twitter users who commented on Taleb&#8217;s post shared different stances. For example, the graphic designer, artist, and author Mike Sheratt </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/mikesherratt83/status/1682396811745538049" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that crypto &#8220;is still thriving and grabbing everyone&#8217;s attention.&#8221; He agreed that AI is intriguing, but it can not replace the digital asset sector.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto has shown signs of revival since the beginning of the year, and it seems like it is gradually escaping from the grip of the prolonged bear market. Bitcoin has surged by over 80% YTD.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading digital asset has also grabbed the attention of numerous finance giants, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">BlackRock</a>, Fidelity, Invesco, VanEck, and others who filed to launch a spot BTC ETF in the United States.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A potential green light from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) could fuel additional enthusiasm among investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The alternative coins have also shown impressive performance, with XRP being the most obvious example. It recently skyrocketed to almost $1 (a valuation last seen over a year ago) after Ripple <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">notched</a> a landmark victory in its legal battle against the SEC.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Taleb-Peterson Dispute</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/black-swan-author-and-jordan-peterson-clash-over-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in March, &#8220;The Black Swan&#8221; author started a quarrel on Twitter with the Canadian professor of psychology – Jordan Peterson. They have entirely different views on Bitcoin, which seemed like the main reason for the clash.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It all began when Peterson shared the news about the leading Australian bank &#8211; ANZ &#8211; and its intention to cease cash withdrawals from some of its branches. Experts have warned that the policy could affect older clients and such with disabilities who predominantly rely on physical cash. &#8220;Bitcoin fixes this,&#8221; Peterson maintained.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">True to his anti-crypto vision, Taleb disagreed with the psychologist. He went even further, claiming that Peterson &#8220;is owned by the Bitcoin cartel.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/black-swan-author-sees-crypto-fad-starting-to-peter-out-as-youngsters-turn-to-ai/" rel="nofollow">Black Swan Author Sees &#8216;Crypto Fad Starting to Peter out&#8217; as Youngsters Turn to AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Collection Dimension X Set to Launch on August 8</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nft-collection-dimension-x-set-to-launch-on-august-8/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 11:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262015</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image_1689789548f6VIlhJjj8.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/image_1689789548f6VIlhJjj8.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; San Diego, CA, July 22nd, 2023] NFT collection Dimension X has announced that it is to launch on Ethereum on August 8. The Ethereum-based digital cards can be used in a corresponding RPG game. Community members have the opportunity to register for a chance to mint an allowlisted NFT. The allowlist raffle [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; San Diego, CA, July 22nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>NFT collection <a href="https://twitter.com/DimensionX_NFT" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Dimension</a> X has announced that it is to launch on Ethereum on August 8. The Ethereum-based digital cards can be used in a corresponding RPG game. Community members have the opportunity to <a href="https://www.alphabot.app/dimensionx-allowlist" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">register</a> for a chance to mint an allowlisted NFT.</p>
<p>The allowlist raffle for Dimension X closes on July 31 at 10am PST. The total supply for the collection has been set at 10,000 NFTs comprising 7,197 raffle mints and 2,803 reserved snapshot spots. Unclaimed reserved snapshot spots will be added to the raffle. The allowlist raffle is subject to final team approval as well as US laws and regulations.</p>
<p>Dimension X started as a free-to-play strategic RPG on the Flow blockchain set in a comic book universe. Within this world, a pan-dimensional explosion has created humans, aliens and monsters with terrifying superpowers.</p>
<p>Players can use NFT heroes to fight villains and monsters, level up, and support their faction in an ever-changing world. They are tasked with preparing their super-teams and competing with other players. During the course of the game, players must compete for THUL that can be used to mint new heroes.</p>
<p>The Dimension X team is actively developing and improving the game, adding new features that are built with the aid of feedback from the community. Interested parties can join the project’s <a href="https://discord.com/invite/dimensionx" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a> and check out their <a href="https://twitter.com/DimensionX_NFT" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> for more information and updates.</p>
<p><strong>About Crypthulhu Studios</strong></p>
<p>Crypthulhu Studios is a collection of veteran mobile game developers with a passion for games, gaming, crypto, blockchain technology, and NFTs. They are passionate about making great games in the Web3 space and embracing the opportunities presented by blockchain. Their flagship project is Dimension X.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-collection-dimension-x-set-to-launch-on-august-8/" rel="nofollow">NFT Collection Dimension X Set to Launch on August 8</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Fights For $30K While Altcoins Bleed Out (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-fights-for-30k-while-altcoins-bleed-out-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262038</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_trx_mw_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_trx_mw_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is fighting to reclaim the $30K level while the altcoin market bleeds out.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has been bleeding out slowly throughout the past 24 hours, losing some $9 billion in the process. This comes on the back of losses from altcoins, which have been charting slight declines across the board.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bitcoin&#8217;s price keeps stagnating at the same place it was yesterday.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Fights For $30K</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin price has failed to overcome the $30K level. What is more &#8211; it appears that the bears are attempting to take control of the action and even managed to push the price down toward $29.6K.</p>
<p>Buyers stepped in, however, and brought it back to where it currently trades at around $29.9K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_262039" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262039" style="width: 1183px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-262039" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33.png" alt="BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33" width="1183" height="491" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33.png 1183w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33-300x125.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33-1024x425.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33-768x319.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD_2023-07-23_11-42-33-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1183px) 100vw, 1183px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262039" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s interesting to note that the Bitcoin dominance has increased by around 0.2% in the past 24 hours. While this might seem like an insignificant increase, the fact is that it shows that BTC fared better than altcoins and claimed a larger market share.</p>
<p>Speaking of altcoins, most of them are bleeding out.</p>
<h2>Altcoins On the Low</h2>
<p>Most of the altcoin market, especially across those with a higher capitalization, are posting consistent declines during the past 24 hours, as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure style="width: 1486px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-262040 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231.jpg" alt="crypto_heatmap_2307231" width="1486" height="780" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231.jpg 1486w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231-300x157.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231-1024x537.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231-768x403.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/crypto_heatmap_2307231-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1486px) 100vw, 1486px" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency that stands out from the pack is Kaspa, which is up a considerable 14.4% over the past 24 hours, followed by XDC Network, which is also up around 9%. It&#8217;s worth noting that XDC was yesterday&#8217;s best performer.On the other end of the spectrum, Stellar&#8217;s XLM is today&#8217;s worst performer, dropping by 6.5% , closely followed by XRP, which lost 4.5%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-fights-for-30k-while-altcoins-bleed-out-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Fights For $30K While Altcoins Bleed Out (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DEX Trading Volume Down by 28% in Q2: CoinGecko Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dex-trading-volume-down-by-28-in-q2-coingecko-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 04:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261309</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Decentralized_Exchanges.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Decentralized_Exchanges.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Uniswap has managed to solidify its position as the largest DEX for yet another quarter. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Signs of recovery during the later stages of Q1 dampened as trading volumes failed to continue the upward trend in Q2. While centralized crypto exchanges were the biggest losers due to the mounting pressure from regulators, the resultant choppy market conditions didn&#8217;t spare the decentralized counterparts either.</p>
<p>The latest data compiled by CoinGecko revealed that the spot trading volume on decentralized exchanges plummeted by over 28%. Uniswap, however, maintained its dominance in the space.</p>
<h2>Decentralized Exchange (DEX): Q2 Recap</h2>
<p>Prominent crypto data aggregator CoinGecko rolled out its industry <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/research/publications/2023-q2-crypto-report#read-the-report-coingecko-s-2023-q2-crypto-industry-report" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, which noted that spot trading volume across the top 10 decentralized exchanges (DEX) totaled $155 billion in 2023 Q2. This represented over a 30% drop from Q1.</p>
<p>Despite the memecoin resurgence led by the PEPE <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-meme-coins-to-watch-as-pepe-coin-mania-winds-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">explosion</a> in Q2, volumes on DEXs failed to witness a noticeable uptick. The decline was considerably less compared to the volume of CEXs which was down by more than 43% QoQ.</p>
<p>Uniswap, on the other hand, solidified its position as the largest DEX. Its trading volume <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-surpasses-1-5t-trading-volume-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">picked up pace</a> in the first quarter itself due to the regulatory clampdown in the US and a banking crisis that caused the USDC stablecoin to de-peg. This, in turn, triggered an influx of investors in decentralized exchanges which continued to boost investors&#8217; rush to the platform even in Q2. Data suggested that the dominance surged as high as 70% in May.</p>
<p>Besides, CoinGecko revealed that the release of crvUSD stablecoin did not have a positive impact on Curve, which experienced a downfall in its volume. The report said that the stableswap concluded June with 11% of the market share.</p>
<p>TraderJoe also witnessed a similar fate. The volume of the Binance Smart Chain-based decentralized exchange also noted a drop in its volume. Despite breaking into the top 10 in the previous quarter, TraderJoe ended Q2 with a mere 0.3% of the market share.</p>
<h2>Breakdown by Chain</h2>
<p>CoinGecko observed that despite a waning dominance, Ethereum was the most popular chain for DEX trading, with a 57% market share. It captured $87.8 billion of DEX trading volume in the second quarter, representing 57% of all chains. The Ethereum blockchain was down by more than 44% QoQ when it recorded $158 billion in trading volume with a 74% market share.</p>
<p>Contrastingly, Arbitrum has performed significantly well, pulling itself to the second position accounting for 17% of the market share by June-end. Trailing behind is Binance Smart Chain (BSC), capturing a market share of 10% during the same period, followed by Polygon with the fourth highest trading volume and 6% market share.</p>
<p>As of June, these top four chains contribute over 95% of volume.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dex-trading-volume-down-by-28-in-q2-coingecko-report/" rel="nofollow">DEX Trading Volume Down by 28% in Q2: CoinGecko Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale BTC Trust Dominates ARK&#8217;s Q2 2023 ETF Rankings, Coinbase Tops in Asset Allocation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-btc-trust-dominates-arks-q2-2023-etf-rankings-coinbase-tops-in-asset-allocation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 23:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261618</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Grayscale BTC Trust shares accounted for nearly 7.5% of total ARKW holdings in Q2 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest revealed some interesting details on its portfolio in the second quarter of 2023. The latest report suggested that Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) stood out as one of the top-performing assets within the investment firm&#8217;s portfolio.</p>
<p>However, when it comes to asset allocation, GBTC trailed behind Coinbase at ARKW.</p>
<h2>GBTC Tops Chart</h2>
<p>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) played a crucial role as one of the top five contributors driving ARKW&#8217;s impressive growth of over 9%. Alongside other performers such as Tesla, Shopify, Unity Software, and DraftKings, GBTC secured the fifth position in this ranking.</p>
<p>Within ARKW&#8217;s portfolio, the trust accounted for 108 basis points, whereas Tesla, as the leading asset, represented 232 basis points, according to ARK’s latest quarterly ETF <a href="https://etfs.ark-funds.com/hubfs/2_Download_Files_For_ARK_Funds/Reports/ARK_ETF_Trust_Quarterly_Report.pdf?utm_medium=email&amp;_hsmi=267007556&amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-87tkgpuq29CO0j-K7jrVWLqtUhYvB8gAIx3URjQhQNkmhsbzQTJnTGA5RFQkb4aS5zAikqcP9d4YUBpcV2cCEJeYvbEw&amp;utm_content=267007556&amp;utm_source=hs_email" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>.</p>
<p>ARKW has depicted impressive year-to-date gains of nearly 50%. In the second quarter, the leading ETF allocated roughly 20% of its assets to cloud computing and around 19% to blockchain as part of its strategy to capitalize on internet-based products and services, cloud computing, artificial intelligence, and e-commerce sectors.</p>
<p>Besides, the GBTC has been trading at an increasingly widening discount to the value of the Bitcoin it holds for over two years. However, the discount has narrowed significantly in recent weeks, which, in turn, has rewarded investors. Such a trend could potentially signal increasing confidence in the trust or rising demand for shares.</p>
<h2>Top Assets by Allocation</h2>
<p>Coinbase emerged as the biggest allocated asset, amassing weightage of 8.7%. Trailing behind is Tesla accounting for 7.6%, and GBTC, with 7.4% in the second and third positions, respectively. Jack Dorsey-backed platform Block made it to the fourth position with 7%.</p>
<p>The quarterly report, however, does not include the July sales of Coinbase shares. Cathie Wood&#8217;s investment firm had accumulated a significant chunk of COIN during the bear market. As the price of COIN hit a yearly high, ARK resorted to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-offloads-over-88m-worth-coinbases-coin-shares-in-2-weeks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">offloading</a> some of the shares to rake in profit. Over the last two weeks, the investment fund led by the Bitcoin Bull has sold over $88 million worth of COIN shares in tranches.</p>
<p>Despite the sales, ARK’s CEO Wood reiterated a bullish on Coinbase.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-btc-trust-dominates-arks-q2-2023-etf-rankings-coinbase-tops-in-asset-allocation/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale BTC Trust Dominates ARK&#8217;s Q2 2023 ETF Rankings, Coinbase Tops in Asset Allocation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Will Reach its ATH of $69,000 This Year: 25% of Americans Believe (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-reach-its-ath-of-69000-this-year-25-of-americans-believe-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261398</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bitcoin_America.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Bitcoin_America.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Only 8% think bitcoin will never tap its peak again.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent study conducted by CryptoVantage estimated that 23% of US residents expect bitcoin to climb to its all-time high price of almost $70,000 by the end of 2023. 47% think this would happen in the next five years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The majority of respondents also believe the high inflation that has recently spread across the globe will make the cryptocurrency industry more attractive to investors. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Americans&#8217; Latest Thoughts on Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey, which questioned 1,000 US residents who had purchased some cryptocurrencies in the past, <a href="https://www.cryptovantage.com/future-of-crypto/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">showed</a> that 70% expect BTC to shoot back to approximately $70K in the next five years. In comparison, only 8% believe the leading digital asset will never climb to that level again.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_261513" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261513" style="width: 832px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261513" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3.png" alt="CryptoVantage" width="832" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3.png 1516w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3-300x144.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3-1024x492.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3-768x369.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chart3-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 832px) 100vw, 832px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261513" class="wp-caption-text">BTC Future Price, Source: CryptoVantage</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity behind the analysis highlighted the overall positive stance of the respondents on bitcoin&#8217;s future valuation, reminding that the next BTC halving is due in the spring of 2024.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Still, the fact that 78% of people in total believe that BTC will eventually set a new ATH is heartening, as is the fact that only 8% believe it will &#8220;never&#8221; equal or top $69,044. And in terms of what might help the cryptocurrency regain former levels, it should be noted that the next Bitcoin halving is due to take place by the end of April 2024.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The event happens every four years and reduces the awards for miners in half, thus ensuring that the speed of production of new BTC slows down. It is worth mentioning that the price of the primary cryptocurrency has headed north following all previous halvings.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The participants were also quite bullish on Ethereum (ETH), with 46% saying it has the best chance of surpassing bitcoin as the biggest crypto asset in the future. 20.8% expect Dogecoin (DOGE) to flip BTC, while 7.8% believe BNB could achieve that.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At the same time, they expressed concerns that the infamous volatility in the market could negatively impact the prices of digital currencies. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Inflation to Push People Toward Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Most survey respondents think that &#8220;global financial trends,&#8221; such as the galloping inflation, rising interest rates, and the overall economic growth, could play a key role in the future valuation of cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recall that the US Federal Reserve adopted an aggressive interest rate hike strategy shortly after the outbreak of the COVID-19 pandemic. Lifting the benchmark has reduced investor interest in risk-on assets, such as digital currencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Regarding inflation, 54% of the participants believe it will trigger additional enthusiasm toward the crypto sector. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argentina and Turkey are two examples where residents have embraced the asset class amid the severe monetary problems in their homelands. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-hits-ath-against-egp-on-binance-amid-egypts-economic-crisis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the high inflation and the devaluation of the Egyptian pound have caused some locals to seek alternative investment options like cryptocurrencies. The country&#8217;s official currency has depreciated so much that the price of BTC measured in EGP recently tapped an all-time high on exchanges like Binance and Changelly.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-reach-its-ath-of-69000-this-year-25-of-americans-believe-survey/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Will Reach its ATH of $69,000 This Year: 25% of Americans Believe (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Caroline Ellison Felt Unsuited To Run Alameda Amid SBF Relationship Drama</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/caroline-ellison-felt-unsuited-to-run-alameda-amid-sbf-relationship-drama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alameda Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261911</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alameda_liquidation.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Alameda_liquidation.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Someone leaked Caroline Ellison’s personal diary to the media. The US Government thinks it was Sam Bankman-Fried.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Caroline Ellison – former CEO of the fallen crypto trading desk Alameda Research – felt “unhappy and overwhelmed” with her job, and strongly doubted that she was well suited to the role, according to newly leaked excerpts from her online diary.</p>
<p>The excerpts shed light on many of her inner thoughts heading preceding FTX’s demise, including her troubled relationship with Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF).</p>
<h2>Boyfriend Pressure and Imposter Syndrome</h2>
<p>As reported by <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/technology/ftx-caroline-ellison-bankman-fried.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">The New York Times</a> on Thursday, the 27-year-old crypto executive told SBF in an April 2022 writing that her previous breakup with SBF had “significantly decreased my excitement about Alameda,” due to the job’s association with the exchange founder.</p>
<p>Bankman-Fried founded Alameda in 2017 and promoted Ellison to a co-CEO position in 2021, alongside Sam Trabucco. While Sam did not formally control Alameda’s operations, Ellison wrote in February 2022 that she had “an instinct to shrink and become smaller and quieter and defer to others” when he was around.</p>
<p>After one of the couple’s many breakups, Ellison deliberately ghosted Bankman-Fried. “Not giving you the contact you wanted felt like the only way I could regain a sense of power,” she wrote in April.</p>
<p>Ellison’s Alameda was one of the few trading desks that seemingly managed to survive the immediate aftermath of Terra (LUNA)’s collapse in May 2022, which took out rival hedge fund Three Arrow Capital.</p>
<p>However, as prosecutors now allege, FTX was responsible for keeping Alameda alive at the time using billions of customers’ deposits. FTX’s new CEO and bankruptcy lawyer <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/john-ray-says-reviving-ftx-is-on-the-table-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">John Ray</a> has confirmed that FTX and Alameda effectively shared a balance sheet.</p>
<p>Even in the April before Terra’s downfall, Ellison wrote about how doubtful she was of her own abilities, lacking in areas like “leadership” and “decisiveness.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“Running Alameda doesn’t feel like something I’m that comparatively advantaged at or well suited to do,” she wrote.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Did SBF Leak Ellison’s Diary?</h2>
<p>Shortly after The New York Times published its article, the Justice Department accused SBF of being responsible for leaking Ellison’s diary to reporters.</p>
<p>The government requested that the court prevent Bankman-Fried from releasing any more non-public information that could potentially interfere with a fair trial.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Such an order is necessary because of a substantial likelihood that the defendant’s extrajudicial comments will undermine a fair trial by tainting the jury pool and chilling the testimony of prospective trial witnesses,” wrote the DOJ in a Thursday <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.176.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>The DOJ has already slapped Bankman-fried with over a dozen charges related to financial fraud and campaign finance violations. FTX itself also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-sues-sbf-and-other-former-execs-to-recover-over-1-billion-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> SBF and other executives this week to recover over $1 billion in lost customer assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/caroline-ellison-felt-unsuited-to-run-alameda-amid-sbf-relationship-drama/" rel="nofollow">Caroline Ellison Felt Unsuited To Run Alameda Amid SBF Relationship Drama</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Unable to Breach $2K But is a Massive Move Coming? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2k-but-is-a-massive-move-coming-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 14:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261973</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum buyers have been struggling to push the price above the significant resistance region of $2K. Nevertheless, the price is currently navigating a crucial range bounded by that level and the dynamic support provided by the 100-day moving average. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart On June 21st, Ethereum managed to surpass the 100-day [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum buyers have been struggling to push the price above the significant resistance region of $2K. Nevertheless, the price is currently navigating a crucial range bounded by that level and the dynamic support provided by the 100-day moving average.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On June 21st, Ethereum managed to surpass the 100-day moving average and continued its prevailing uptrend after a pullback, eventually reaching the critical resistance area at $2K. Yet, the bullish momentum faded due to increased selling pressure around this level, resulting in minor rejections.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the price finds support at the 100-day MA, currently situated at $1,867, which has prevented further declines over the past few weeks. A breakout from this significant price range will likely play a pivotal role in determining Ethereum&#8217;s overall prospects in the mid-term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261978" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261978" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261978 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2207231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261978" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Upon analyzing the 4-hour timeframe, a bearish trend for Ethereum becomes evident as the price broke below its multi-week upward trendline after facing rejection at the $2K resistance zone. A subsequent pullback confirmed the breakout.</p>
<p>At present, ETH remains confined between two critical price levels: the static resistance at $2K and the critical support at $1,850. This suggests the potential for a range-bound market stage characterized by consolidation candles and the absence of a strong trend.</p>
<p>The price is expected to remain within this range until a breakout occurs, revealing the upcoming direction for Ethereum.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261979" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261979" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261979 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2207232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETH-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261979" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>The provided chart displays the Estimated Leverage Ratio in correlation with ETH&#8217;s price. This metric gauges the average leverage employed by participants in the futures market. Generally, higher values indicate more investors are taking on greater leverage and risk in the derivatives market.</p>
<p>In recent weeks, the Estimated Leverage Ratio has seen a slight increase, suggesting that the futures market may be getting overheated due to the recent bullish price trends. However, it hasn&#8217;t reached concerning levels yet. Nonetheless, if the metric continues to surge, caution is advised as it could lead to a short or long-squeeze event.</p>
<p>In such a scenario, Ethereum&#8217;s price could experience a sudden and significant movement.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261977" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261977" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261977 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_leverage_ratio_chart_2207231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Estimated-Leverage-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261977" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2k-but-is-a-massive-move-coming-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Unable to Breach $2K But is a Massive Move Coming? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Posts 6% Weekly Gains, But is a Correction Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-posts-6-weekly-gains-but-is-a-correction-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 14:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261983</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-4-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After a sudden surge, Ripple&#8217;s price has reached a critical resistance region, which represents its previous major swing high formed in late April. However, after such an explosive move, it&#8217;s typical for the price to enter into consolidation. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Upon analyzing the daily chart, it becomes evident that Ripple [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a sudden surge, Ripple&#8217;s price has reached a critical resistance region, which represents its previous major swing high formed in late April. However, after such an explosive move, it&#8217;s typical for the price to enter into consolidation.</p>
<h2><strong>Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Upon analyzing the daily chart, it becomes evident that Ripple experienced a significant price jump after finding support at the 100-day moving average. However, it now confronts a significant resistance zone at $0.85, marked by substantial selling pressure.</p>
<p>This development indicates a bullish sentiment among Ripple traders. Nevertheless, it&#8217;s important to acknowledge that a consolidation correction stage is essential following impulsive price surges to confirm the strength of the trend and let the market rest for a while.</p>
<p>Hence, it is expected that the price will enter a short-term correction phase, leading to higher volatility and pullback legs before the next notable upward movement takes place.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261980" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261980" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261980 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2207231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261980" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The 4-hour chart reveals that the price has successfully broken above the upper edge of a channel, evident from a large green candle resulting from a recent explosive rally. Nonetheless, a pullback to the broken level is required to validate the breakout.</p>
<p>Therefore, based on the price action, it seems likely that the price will undergo a correction period, retracing back to the upper boundary and completing a pullback. Consequently, if successful, the market can anticipate continuing the bullish rally, pushing the price to higher regions.</p>
<p>However, in the event of a decline below the channel&#8217;s upper boundary, the static support at $0.56 will become Ripple&#8217;s next target.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261980" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261980" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261980 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2207232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261980" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-posts-6-weekly-gains-but-is-a-correction-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Posts 6% Weekly Gains, But is a Correction Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
