<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction As Tether Depegs From $1 – Is BTC in Trouble As Well?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-depegs-from-1-btc-trouble-as-well.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price is trading choppy above the $29,000 threshold, and has captured the attention of traders and investors. The current live price of Bitcoin stands at $29,040, with a 24-hour trading volume of $11.3 billion.  &lt;br /&gt;
As per the recent data, Bitcoin has experienced a nearly 0.50% decline over the past 24 hours. The market is closely monitoring the situation as Tether, the popular stablecoin, undergoes a depegging event from its $1 value. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-depegs-from-1-btc-trouble-as-well.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction As Tether Depegs From $1 – Is BTC in Trouble As Well?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 07:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-tether-depegs-from-1-btc-trouble-as-well.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121644/322161/5-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="532527"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 4 August – GMX, XDC Network, Injective</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-august-gmx-xdc-network-injective.htm</link><description>One of the largest pieces of news impacting crypto markets today is that Coinbase has requested the dismissal of a lawsuit filed against them by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), according to an announcement made today by Paul Grewal, the company's Chief Legal Officer. &lt;br /&gt;
Grewal disseminated the news on X, stating, "Coinbase filed our brief asking the Court to dismiss the SEC's case against us."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-august-gmx-xdc-network-injective.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 4 August – GMX, XDC Network, Injective&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>GMX</category><category>Cowabunga</category><category>XDC Network</category><category>Chimpzee</category><category>Injective</category><category>Gmx Price</category><category>XDC price</category><category>INJ price</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-4-august-gmx-xdc-network-injective.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121634/322121/bc4a-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="334896"/></item><item><title>Alameda-Backed Coins Experienced Suspected Bot-Driven Price Surge on FTX, Study Suggests</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/alameda-backed-coins-experienced-suspected-bot-driven-price-surge-on-ftx-study-suggests.htm</link><description>Several digital tokens that Sam Bankman-Fried’s trading firm Alameda Research had ties to pumped in price after they were listed on now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, according to a report from Network Contagion Research Institute (NCRI). &lt;br /&gt;
The tokens, which included well-known names like BOBA, GALA, IMX, RNDR, and SPELL, surged by as much as 30% after FTX officially listed them, helped by a flurry of “inauthentic” Twitter activity, the report said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/alameda-backed-coins-experienced-suspected-bot-driven-price-surge-on-ftx-study-suggests.htm"&gt;Read More: Alameda-Backed Coins Experienced Suspected Bot-Driven Price Surge on FTX, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Alameda Research</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/alameda-backed-coins-experienced-suspected-bot-driven-price-surge-on-ftx-study-suggests.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121623/322084/sam-bankman-fried.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="42542"/></item><item><title>Warren and Sanders Urge IRS and Treasury to Enforce Rules Against Crypto Tax Evaders</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/warren-sanders-urge-irs-treasury-enforce-rules-against-crypto-tax-evaders.htm</link><description>Almost two years after Biden’s infrastructure bill became law, two high-profile Democrat senators are keen on ensuring that crypto reporting requirements within the bill are properly enforced. &lt;br /&gt;
Senators Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.), Bob Casey (D-Pa.), and Richard Blumenthal (D-Conn.) joined Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) on Tuesday in signing a letter to the IRS and Treasury Department to publish tax reporting guidelines for digital assets “brokers,” for which the deadline approaches fast....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/warren-sanders-urge-irs-treasury-enforce-rules-against-crypto-tax-evaders.htm"&gt;Read More: Warren and Sanders Urge IRS and Treasury to Enforce Rules Against Crypto Tax Evaders&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/warren-sanders-urge-irs-treasury-enforce-rules-against-crypto-tax-evaders.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121630/322100/elizabeth-warren-media-li.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="91592"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Coinbase Narrows Losses Thanks to Cost Reduction Strategy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-narrows-losses-thanks-cost-reduction-strategy.htm</link><description>Major US-based crypto exchange Coinbase has reported a smaller loss in the second quarter this year compared to the same quarter last year, while its revenue exceeded analysts’ expectations. &lt;br /&gt;
Coinbase’s loss for the quarter came in at $97 million, down from $1.1 billion a year before, the firm’s financial report for the second quarter showed....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-narrows-losses-thanks-cost-reduction-strategy.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Coinbase Narrows Losses Thanks to Cost Reduction Strategy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-coinbase-narrows-losses-thanks-cost-reduction-strategy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121612/322046/coinbase.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="499238"/></item><item><title>Robinhood's Q2 Earnings Show 18% Decline in Crypto Trading Revenue</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhoods-q2-earnings-show-18-decline-crypto-trading-revenue.htm</link><description>In its Q2 2023 earnings report, Robinhood (HOOD), the online trading platform known for its crypto-friendly approach, revealed crypto trading revenue of $31 million, representing an 18% decrease from the previous quarter's $38 million.  &lt;br /&gt;
Despite this decline, Robinhood achieved profitability for the first time since going public....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhoods-q2-earnings-show-18-decline-crypto-trading-revenue.htm"&gt;Read More: Robinhood's Q2 Earnings Show 18% Decline in Crypto Trading Revenue&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Robinhood</category><category>Report</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhoods-q2-earnings-show-18-decline-crypto-trading-revenue.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121627/322091/4535b28a-b049-429c-8fed-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="79724"/></item><item><title>Lithuanian Financial Intelligence Arm Lists Several Crypto Firms as New AML Violators</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lithuanian-financial-intelligence-arm-lists-several-crypto-firms-as-new-aml-violators.htm</link><description>The Financial Intelligence Unit (FNTT) of Lithuania has released a new list of anti-money laundering (AML) violators, featuring several crypto service providers in the country. &lt;br /&gt;
Lithuania is fast becoming a significant player in the European digital asset market, with its progressive approach to the asset class. The country launched a new regulation for Virtual Asset Service Providers (VASPs), early this year, which saw an increased influx of crypto-related businesses....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lithuanian-financial-intelligence-arm-lists-several-crypto-firms-as-new-aml-violators.htm"&gt;Read More: Lithuanian Financial Intelligence Arm Lists Several Crypto Firms as New AML Violators&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lithuanian-financial-intelligence-arm-lists-several-crypto-firms-as-new-aml-violators.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121624/322085/trading-6531134-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="472536"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Rallies 5% on Binance Collateral Announcement – Could A Break Above This Key Level Spark Next Bull Run?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-rallies-5-binance-collateral-announcement-could-break-above-key-level-spark-next-bull-run.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), a Shiba Inu dog-themed token that is the second largest meme coin by market capitalization behind Dogecoin (DOGE), is rallying on Friday amid news that Binance will allow the asset to be used as collateral on its platform. &lt;br /&gt;
As per an update from Binance, the platform users will now be able to borrow against their SHIB balance....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-rallies-5-binance-collateral-announcement-could-break-above-key-level-spark-next-bull-run.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Rallies 5% on Binance Collateral Announcement – Could A Break Above This Key Level Spark Next Bull Run?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Binance</category><category>Shibie Coin</category><category>Shibie</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Barbie</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-rallies-5-binance-collateral-announcement-could-break-above-key-level-spark-next-bull-run.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121622/322081/shib-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="563113"/></item><item><title>Binance Appoints New Deputy Chief Compliance Officer and Global Money Laundering Reporting Officer</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-appoints-new-deputy-chief-compliance-officer-global-money-laundering-reporting-officer.htm</link><description>On Thursday, Binance announced Kristen Hecht as the new Deputy Chief Compliance Officer (CCO) and Global Money Laundering Reporting Officer (GMLRO), a new role amid potential fraud charges from U.S. regulators. &lt;br /&gt;
Amid ongoing investigations into its practices, Binance has witnessed the departure of several key legal and compliance executives in recent weeks. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-appoints-new-deputy-chief-compliance-officer-global-money-laundering-reporting-officer.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Appoints New Deputy Chief Compliance Officer and Global Money Laundering Reporting Officer&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-appoints-new-deputy-chief-compliance-officer-global-money-laundering-reporting-officer.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121542/321834/65c4362d-da14-485a-be13-5.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="176023"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Holds Above $29,000 Following Mixed US Jobs Report – Where Next for the BTC Price?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-holds-above-29000-following-mixed-us-jobs-report-where-next-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin (BTC) price is holding within recent ranges to the north of the $29,000 level in the wake of the latest mixed US jobs report for July. &lt;br /&gt;
The report revealed that the US economy added 187,000 jobs in July, below the expected gain of 200,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, June’s job gain of 209,000 was revised lower to a job gain of 185,000. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a separate survey of households revealed that the unemployment rate had unexpectedly declined to 3.5% from 3.6% in June....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-holds-above-29000-following-mixed-us-jobs-report-where-next-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Holds Above $29,000 Following Mixed US Jobs Report – Where Next for the BTC Price?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>NFP</category><category>US jobs</category><category>Fed</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-holds-above-29000-following-mixed-us-jobs-report-where-next-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121619/322071/btc-10.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131590"/></item><item><title>Curve Price Prediction as CRV Rallies on Hopes Hacker Will Return Funds – Here’s Why CRV’s Outlook Remains Murky</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/curve-price-prediction-as-crv-rallies-hopes-hacker-will-return-funds-heres-why-crvs-outlook-remains-murky.htm</link><description>Curve (CRV), the native token of the Curve Finance decentralized exchange (DEX) and the governance token of the Curve DAO (decentralized autonomous organization) rallied 7% on Friday to $0.61 after a hacker who stole millions in funds from the exchange and other decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols began returning funds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/curve-price-prediction-as-crv-rallies-hopes-hacker-will-return-funds-heres-why-crvs-outlook-remains-murky.htm"&gt;Read More: Curve Price Prediction as CRV Rallies on Hopes Hacker Will Return Funds – Here’s Why CRV’s Outlook Remains Murky&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><category>Curve</category><category>CRV</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Hack</category><category>Curve Finance</category><category>Decentralized Exchange</category><category>DEX</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/curve-price-prediction-as-crv-rallies-hopes-hacker-will-return-funds-heres-why-crvs-outlook-remains-murky.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121615/322052/crv.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="633503"/></item><item><title>Sid Gandhi, CEO of Polybase, on ZK Proofs and Decentralized Databases | Ep. 253</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sid-gandhi-ceo-of-polybase-zk-proofs-decentralized-databases-ep-253.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Sid Gandhi, CEO of Polybase, talks about building products for Cruise, US Navy &amp; Apple, the story of Polybase, and leveraging ZK proofs. &lt;br /&gt;
Sid Gandhi is a technology leader, entrepreneur, and investor, currently CEO of web3 infrastructure company Polybase....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sid-gandhi-ceo-of-polybase-zk-proofs-decentralized-databases-ep-253.htm"&gt;Read More: Sid Gandhi, CEO of Polybase, on ZK Proofs and Decentralized Databases | Ep. 253&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sid-gandhi-ceo-of-polybase-zk-proofs-decentralized-databases-ep-253.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121614/322048/sid-gandhi-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="108266"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Bank of Russia Reveals Official CBDC Logo, Revolut Shuts Down Crypto Platform for its US Customers, US DoJ Asks Sam Bankman-Fried's 'Bail be Revoked and Defendant be Detained'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-russia-reveals-official-cbdc-logo-revolut-shuts-down-crypto-platform-for-its-us-customers-us-doj-asks-sam-bankman-frieds-bail-be-revoked-and-defendant-be-detained.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-russia-reveals-official-cbdc-logo-revolut-shuts-down-crypto-platform-for-its-us-customers-us-doj-asks-sam-bankman-frieds-bail-be-revoked-and-defendant-be-detained.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Bank of Russia Reveals Official CBDC Logo, Revolut Shuts Down Crypto Platform for its US Customers, US DoJ Asks Sam Bankman-Fried's 'Bail be Revoked and Defendant be Detained'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Revolut</category><category>USA</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Education</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>China</category><category>Exchange</category><category>DeFi</category><category>DEX</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Digital Ruble</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Fees</category><category>Adoption</category><category>DOJ</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Legal</category><category>Court</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-russia-reveals-official-cbdc-logo-revolut-shuts-down-crypto-platform-for-its-us-customers-us-doj-asks-sam-bankman-frieds-bail-be-revoked-and-defendant-be-detained.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121582/321981/adobestock-vejaa-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="207300"/></item><item><title>Bernstein Report: Top Crypto Miners Set to Benefit Most as Capacity Surges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-report-top-crypto-miners-set-benefit-most-as-capacity-surges.htm</link><description>Wealth management company, Berstein has said that digital asset mining firms with high capacity and a low production cost will become the biggest gainers in the wake of recent trends.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to the report released on Aug 3, the top 4 largest miners who have invested heavily in equipment and capacity will make the most profit with Bitcoin (BTC) hovering around $30,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-report-top-crypto-miners-set-benefit-most-as-capacity-surges.htm"&gt;Read More: Bernstein Report: Top Crypto Miners Set to Benefit Most as Capacity Surges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>btc</category><category>Miners</category><category>Bernstein</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-report-top-crypto-miners-set-benefit-most-as-capacity-surges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121605/322039/bitcoin-gf8a75ed9e-1280-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="214511"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Optimism? OP Price Rockets Up as Coinbase Announces Base Launch Date and Viral Meme Coin Shibie is the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rockets-up-as-coinbase-announces-base-launch-date-viral-meme-coin-shibie-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution Optimism (OP) has been on a multi-month climb as markets brace with anticipation for a huge upcoming Coinbase BASE listing. &lt;br /&gt;
Coinbase's decision to list BASE (an Ethereum layer-2 blockchain developed in-house by Coinbase) has ignited a frenzy in the markets for OP, with traders emboldened by the idea that BASE is built using Optimism-based technology....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rockets-up-as-coinbase-announces-base-launch-date-viral-meme-coin-shibie-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Optimism? OP Price Rockets Up as Coinbase Announces Base Launch Date and Viral Meme Coin Shibie is the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-optimism-op-price-rockets-up-as-coinbase-announces-base-launch-date-viral-meme-coin-shibie-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121577/321948/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1683787"/></item><item><title>Unlock the Power of AI and Trading Edge with Launchpad XYZ – The Gateway to Successful Web3 Trading</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/unlock-power-of-ai-trading-edge-with-launchpad-xyz-gateway-successful-web3-trading.htm</link><description>Trading in the crypto space is challenging, especially for novices. It's not just about understanding market trends and knowing when to make a trade, but also about managing one's emotions. An emotionally charged decision can lead to massive losses or missed opportunities. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unlock-power-of-ai-trading-edge-with-launchpad-xyz-gateway-successful-web3-trading.htm"&gt;Read More: Unlock the Power of AI and Trading Edge with Launchpad XYZ – The Gateway to Successful Web3 Trading&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>AI coin</category><category>Ai Crypto</category><category>Price Predictions</category><category>Web3 Wallet</category><category>Crypto Hub</category><category>All In One Coin</category><category>Utility Coin</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/unlock-power-of-ai-trading-edge-with-launchpad-xyz-gateway-successful-web3-trading.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121597/322030/ai-generated-g270461fc9-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293256"/></item><item><title>Digital Bank Revolut to Suspend Crypto Services For US Customers Citing Regulatory Uncertainty</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-bank-revolut-suspend-crypto-services-for-us-customers-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm</link><description>Crypto-friendly British neobank Revolut has announced plans to halt its crypto services for US customers.  &lt;br /&gt;
The digital bank cited the market uncertainty and changes to the local regulatory landscape in the country for suspending crypto services.  &lt;br /&gt;
The England-based fintech firm will suspend US users’ ability to buy cryptocurrencies via its app from September 2, a Revolut spokesperson told Bloomberg. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-bank-revolut-suspend-crypto-services-for-us-customers-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm"&gt;Read More: Digital Bank Revolut to Suspend Crypto Services For US Customers Citing Regulatory Uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Revolut</category><category>USA</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/digital-bank-revolut-suspend-crypto-services-for-us-customers-citing-regulatory-uncertainty.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121601/322023/revolut.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="91470"/></item><item><title>Grab a Slice of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles with Cowabunga Coin – 6 Day Countdown Begins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/grab-slice-of-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-with-cowabungo-coin-6-day-countdown-begins.htm</link><description>If you ever enjoyed watching Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (TMNT) on TV as a child, or even as an adult, chances are you've heard the term "Cowabunga!" quite a few times. The iconic catchphrase has not only seeped into popular culture but also become the namesake of an upcoming cryptocurrency project, Cowabunga Coin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grab-slice-of-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-with-cowabungo-coin-6-day-countdown-begins.htm"&gt;Read More: Grab a Slice of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles with Cowabunga Coin – 6 Day Countdown Begins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</category><category>Tmnt</category><category>Best Meme Coin</category><category>New Meme Coin</category><category>Best Crypto Presale</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/grab-slice-of-teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-with-cowabungo-coin-6-day-countdown-begins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121589/321972/f2iipu3xwagej7o.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="198291"/></item><item><title>Canadian Digital Asset Ownership Plummets Amid Global Regulatory Uncertainty: Bank Of Canada</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-digital-asset-ownership-plummets-amid-global-regulatory-uncertainty-bank-of-canada.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency ownership in Canada declined in 2022 due to a plethora of factors including uncertainty in regulation, fear of digital asset scams, and unfavorable market conditions. &lt;br /&gt;
A new survey, the Bitcoin Omnibus Survey (BTCOS)  by the Bank of Canada highlights the trend of digital assets in the country from an analysis involving 4,996 participants....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-digital-asset-ownership-plummets-amid-global-regulatory-uncertainty-bank-of-canada.htm"&gt;Read More: Canadian Digital Asset Ownership Plummets Amid Global Regulatory Uncertainty: Bank Of Canada&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bank of Canada</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Survey</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-digital-asset-ownership-plummets-amid-global-regulatory-uncertainty-bank-of-canada.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121591/321973/canadian-lawmakers-call-f.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="130131"/></item><item><title>Jack Dorsey's Block Q2 Revenue Soars to $5.5 Billion, Led by Strong Bitcoin Sales</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorseys-block-q2-revenue-soars-55-billion-led-by-strong-bitcoin-sales.htm</link><description>Block, the payments firm led by Twitter founder Jack Dorsey, saw its revenue soar to $5.5 billion in the second quarter, partly thanks to strong growth in Bitcoin (BTC) sales on the platforms. &lt;br /&gt;
Out of the total $5.5 billion in revenue, a whopping $2.4 billion came from sales of Bitcoin, a year-over-year increase of 34%, the company said in its quarterly shareholder letter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorseys-block-q2-revenue-soars-55-billion-led-by-strong-bitcoin-sales.htm"&gt;Read More: Jack Dorsey's Block Q2 Revenue Soars to $5.5 Billion, Led by Strong Bitcoin Sales&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>block</category><category>Jack Dorsey</category><category>Cash App</category><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorseys-block-q2-revenue-soars-55-billion-led-by-strong-bitcoin-sales.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121590/321963/jack-dorsey.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="32169"/></item></channel></rss>
