<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:35:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dubai Takes Enforcement Action Against Middle East Crypto Exchange BitOasis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-takes-enforcement-action-against-middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259776</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Dubai.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dubai has been widely considered as a crypto-friendly destination but that hasn’t stopped local regulators from taking action against companies that are not in compliance.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 10, the Emirate’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) issued a market alert stating that it had initiated an enforcement action against the BitOasis crypto exchange.</p>
<p>BitOasis is one of the largest crypto platforms focused on customers in the Middle East.</p>
<h2>Dubai Regulators on Alert</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.vara.ae/en/regulations/regulatory-notices/market-alert-bitoasis-technologies-fze-bitoasis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">alert</a>, BitOasis is under review for “not meeting mandated conditions, required to be satisfied within 30-60 day timeframes prior to being permitted to undertake any VARA regulated market activity.”</p>
<p>BitOasis was awarded the first of Dubai’s “minimum viable product operational licenses,” earlier this year but the regulator may rescind that license.</p>
<p>The Dubai regulator stated that it was “exercising its authority to supervise and monitor compliance,” adding that enforcement actions could include “holding BitOasis’ license status as non-operational.”</p>
<p>The license allows the firm to offer broker-dealer services for crypto assets to qualified retail and institutional investors from its Dubai headquarters.</p>
<p>BitOasis, which operates in 14 countries across MENA (Middle East and North Africa), claims more than $3 billion in trading volume, according to its website.</p>
<p>Last year, the exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis-cuts-staff-citing-recession-and-market-turmoil/" data-wpel-link="internal">axed 5% of its staff</a>, citing recession and market turmoil.</p>
<p>It is not the first time Dubai regulators have issued warnings and reprimands. In April, VARA issued a reprimand to Kyle Davies and Su Zhu, co-founders of the bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>In May, the regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-regulator-reprimands-opnx-founders-for-conducting-unregulated-activity/" data-wpel-link="internal">reprimanded</a> OPNX founders Mark Lamb and Sudhu Arumugam, as well as its Chief Executive Officer Leslie Lamb, for conducting unregulated activities.</p>
<p>In late June, Dubai-based crypto exchange Bybit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-scores-preparatory-license-by-dubais-virtual-assets-regulatory-authority/" data-wpel-link="internal">landed</a> a minimum viable product preparatory license from VARA. Bybit has also slashed staff during the crypto bear market.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Markets are up marginally, but volume remains low, and trading remains sideways. Total capitalization has reached $1.23 trillion at the time of writing, following a 1.6% gain on the day.</p>
<p>Bitcoin spiked to $31,000 briefly during late trading on July 10 but could not hold that level and sharply retreated back to yesterday’s levels around $30,400.</p>
<p>Ethereum was up 1.3% on the day at $1,881 at the time of writing. Binance Coin (BNB) and Polygon (MATIC) were performing well, gaining 5% and 8%, respectively</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-takes-enforcement-action-against-middle-east-crypto-exchange-bitoasis/" rel="nofollow">Dubai Takes Enforcement Action Against Middle East Crypto Exchange BitOasis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Twitter&#8217;s New Rival Threads Hits 100 Million Users in 4 Days </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/twitters-new-rival-threads-hits-100-million-users-in-4-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259729</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Threads_Twitter.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Threads_Twitter.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Zuckerberg's Threads has attracted over 100 million users less than four days after launch. Will it overtake its rival platform, Twitter?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 6, Mark Zuckerberg, the CEO and founder of Facebook&#8217;s parent company Meta Platforms, launched a new platform dubbed Threads in 100 countries across the globe. The social media network is considered a rival to the micro-blogging platform Twitter.</p>
<p>Speaking against the newly launched platform, Twitter owner and former CEO Elon Musk hauled Threads as a copycat project.</p>
<h2>Will Threads Overpower Twitter?</h2>
<p>In a Monday Threads <a href="https://www.threads.net/t/CuhOXGmr74R/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post</a>, Zuckerberg wrote that the new project attained 100 million sign-ups over the weekend, only four days after launch. It took Twitter five years to <a href="https://blog.twitter.com/en_us/a/2011/one-hundred-million-voices" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">achieve</a> this feat.</p>
<p>Threads function as a sister app for Instagram, as users need to own an Instagram account before creating a Threads page. The platform also has features similar to Twitter&#8217;s, such as liking, commenting, reposting, and sharing. It also freely offers some features only available to subscribed Twitter users, like 500 characters per thread, and allows up to five minutes of videos.</p>
<p>However, Threads doesn&#8217;t support direct messaging, hashtags, and trending stories – features existing within the Twitter ecosystem.</p>
<p>Stressing the purpose of the Threads platform, Instagram CEO Adam Mosseri said in an <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/5/23784870/instagram-threads-adam-mosseri-interview-twitter-competitor" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with The Verge:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Obviously, Twitter pioneered the space. And there are a lot of good offerings out there for public conversations. But just given everything that was going on, we thought there was an opportunity to build something that was open and something that was good for the community that was already using Instagram.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Mosseri was likely referring to Musk&#8217;s recent actions to bolster Twitter&#8217;s revenue by encouraging the subscription to its paid verification option. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-chief-elon-musk-to-pass-on-mantle-to-new-ceo-takes-ceo-role/" data-wpel-link="internal">former Twitter CEO</a> also limited the number of tweets viewable by users daily.</p>
<p>Still, Mosseri claimed that Threads was not introduced to replace Twitter.</p>
<h2>A Lawsuit Threat?</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, the popular micro-blogging platform is taking the offensive as the internet buzzes about the similarities and differences between Threads and Twitter.</p>
<p>In a legal letter <a href="https://cdn.sanity.io/files/ifn0l6bs/production/27109f01431939c8177d408d3c9848c3b46632cd.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> last Thursday, Twitter attorney Alex Spiro alleged that Meta employed former Twitter employees to design Threads using insider information from Twitter. Meta, however, denied these allegations. The issue is yet to exacerbate to constitute a lawsuit case.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitters-new-rival-threads-hits-100-million-users-in-4-days/" rel="nofollow">Twitter&#8217;s New Rival Threads Hits 100 Million Users in 4 Days </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital Shrinks Portfolio by Nearly 40%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-digital-shrinks-portfolio-by-nearly-40/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voyager Digital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259643</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Voyager.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Voyager recorded outflows of more than $250 million worth of crypto assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt crypto lender &#8211; Voyager &#8211; is slowly working towards making customers whole.</p>
<p>Voyager held nearly $413 million in multiple crypto-assets at one point. However, since enabling withdrawals to users on June 23rd, it has recorded a steady stream of outflow totaling $250 million worth of crypto assets. As a result, Voyager&#8217;s crypto portfolio has shrunk by 39.46%.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the <a href="https://dune.com/21co/potential-contagion?Voyager+Interval_ee9bc0=weekly" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> compiled by Dune Analytics, Voyager currently holds $176.38 million worth of crypto. This includes $69,02 million in Bitcoin, $50,99 million in Ether, $18,56 million worth of USDC, $15,70 million worth of SHIB, and $2,46 million MATIC, among others.</li>
<li>The bankrupt firm has a Clean Asset ratio of 96.15% (excluding its native token VGX) and sits at a stablecoin balance of nearly $19 million.</li>
<li>The United States Bankruptcy Judge Michael Wiles <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-approved-to-start-repaying-frozen-customers-accounts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">greenlighted</a> Voyager&#8217;s proposed liquidation plan in May this year.</li>
<li>The move enabled the crypto lender to compensate about $1.33 billion in crypto assets to customers and end its efforts to reorganize under Chapter 11.</li>
<li>Voyager soon announced that customers will be able to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/voyager-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-this-month/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">recover</a> around 36% of their cryptocurrency deposits.</li>
<li>More recently, Gemini <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-allows-voyager-victims-to-claim-funds-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that it would be allowing withdrawals for victims of the Voyager bankruptcy case.</li>
<li>The firm had been crippled by the implosion of Zhu Su-led crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC) last year, which had earlier defaulted on a $665 million Voyager loan.</li>
<li>It later suffered two failed recovery deals from FTX and Binance.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-lender-voyager-digital-shrinks-portfolio-by-nearly-40/" rel="nofollow">Bankrupt Crypto Lender Voyager Digital Shrinks Portfolio by Nearly 40%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arcadia Finance Hit by $455K Exploit on Both Ethereum, Optimism Networks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arcadia-finance-hit-by-455k-exploit-on-both-ethereum-optimism-networks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 23:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259680</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Hack.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Hack.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The team behind Arcadia said that it has initiated contact with the attacker.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Non-custodial decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, Arcadia Finance, is the latest victim of a $455,000 exploit that occurred on both the Ethereum and Optimism networks. Confirming the hack, Arcadia revealed that it is working with security partners to minimize the damage after pausing the contracts.</p>
<p>The platform has also roped in law enforcement to deal with the issue.</p>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain security expert PeckShield was first to notify the attack on Arcadia and <a href="https://twitter.com/peckshield/status/1678263478774013952" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">claimed</a> that it was caused due to &#8220;the lack of untrusted input validation,&#8221; which is exploited to drain funds from both darcWETH and darcUSDC vaults.</li>
<li>The firm highlighted another vulnerability in the DeFi protocol &#8211; &#8220;lack of reentrancy protection&#8221; &#8211; which enables instant liquidation to bypass the internal vault health check.</li>
<li>The stolen funds from the Optimism network portion were washed on the controversial coin mixer, Tornado Cash. But the Ethereum portion of the stolen funds, worth over $103,000, continued to remain parked in a <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x5c75e94dd0ab9c10bfd1b8073dafef031d3c050d#code" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">flagged</a> wallet address.</li>
<li>Arcadia has not yet confirmed the validity of the root cause identified by PeckShield, but it said that an investigation is being carried out. The protocol&#8217;s latest <a href="https://twitter.com/ArcadiaFi/status/1678310473832312833" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We will continue to work with our security partners, law enforcement, and the broader community to resolve this as best we can. Our number one priority is recovering funds for Arcadia protocol users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Arcadia is a non-custodial, permissionless protocol that was launched on Ethereum and Optimism in March this year. The platform essentially enables users to trade spot with leverage and boost staked ether.</li>
<li>The latest exploit surfaces amid rampant hacks recorded in the digital asset sector.</li>
<li>In the first of 2023 alone, Web3 security firm Beosin <a href="https://twitter.com/BeosinAlert/status/1674618821766971392" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">identified</a> a loss of $470 million across 108 DeFi protocol attacks.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arcadia-finance-hit-by-455k-exploit-on-both-ethereum-optimism-networks/" rel="nofollow">Arcadia Finance Hit by $455K Exploit on Both Ethereum, Optimism Networks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouTuber Turned NFT Scammer? On-Chain Sleuth Investigates $1.5 Million Crypto Thief</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/youtuber-turned-nft-scammer-on-chain-sleuth-investigates-1-5-million-crypto-thief/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 22:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259756</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/hackers_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/hackers_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A 16-year-old NFT scammer appears connected to the infamous Monkey Drainer responsible for stealing $24 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain detective ZachXBT has implicated a YouTuber with over 120,000 subscribers in over $1.5 million worth of crypto scams over the past two years.</p>
<p>Some of those scams are connected to the infamous Monkey Drainer, an anonymous and boastful phishing scammer known for stealing people’s NFTs.</p>
<h2>Linking “Blue” to Monkey Drainer</h2>
<p>Before entering the world of crypto scams in July 2021, the scammer – known as either “BlueXBT” or “JB Adventures” (Jack) – had grown his YouTube following “by uploading gaming and trolling videos,” <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1678384939048263682" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a> ZachXBT on Monday.</p>
<p>The on-chain sleuth connected Jack to the ENS address cool-breeze.eth, which he was shown publicly sharing in a leaked image from his Snapchat account.</p>
<p>That same address <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xc9a4fe3da7fb38e57fa14b273f05f190b535e395" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">purchased</a> BAYC 8668 in October 2022. However, had also received inflows of over 85 ETH from 8 Ethereum addresses connected to Monkey Drainer’s phishing scams.</p>
<p>Monkey Drainer is known for stealing over $24 million worth of NFTs using a technique called “ice phishing.” With this tactic, rather than soliciting a victim’s private keys directly, one baits them into signing a transaction that gives the hacker control of a user’s funds, using fraudulent crypto and NFT websites.</p>
<p>In November, CryptoPotato <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/monkey-drainer-on-hacking-spree-steals-another-520-eth-worth-nfts/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that Monkey Drainer has stolen over 1200 ETH worth of NFTs, including from collections like BAYC, CryptoPunks, and Otherside.</p>
<p>ZachXBT shared screenshots from Discord in which Blue bragged about his BAYC purchase, while also instructing his workers assisting with his scams.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">5/ On Discord Blue flexed his BAYC purchase and would share his methods scamming. </p>
<p>The second and third screenshot is from an internal Discord server where Blue would instruct his workers. <a href="https://t.co/l22ZubSCAc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/l22ZubSCAc</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1678384963836604416?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“Unfortunately Blue was robbed of his BAYC in late 2022 after allegedly scamming Monkey out of his cut from a phishing scam,” continued ZachXBT.</p>
<h2>Blue’s Scams</h2>
<p>Blue got back to scamming in short order, however, using new ENS addresses. He spent his stolen funds on luxury items like cars, watches, and shoes, while using others to gamble on Stake.</p>
<p>One of Blue’s more recent scams included 61.5k ETH and 93.3k USDT stolen rom <a href="https://twitter.com/g13m" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">LoveMake.eth</a>. “Blue received 49 ETH and 74K USDT for himself after the drainer fee,” said ZachXBT.</p>
<p>Another included a Milady &amp; Squiggle NFT phished from <a href="https://twitter.com/ystrickler" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">yancey.eth</a> to Blue’s ENS purplelobster.eth. The NFTs were worth roughly 12 ETH, of which Blue kept 10.3 ETH after the drainer fee.</p>
<p>“It’s disgusting to see these phishing scammers show zero remorse and spend the funds on tasteless items,&#8221; concluded ZachXBT. He said that information about Blue (Jack) has been shared with many of his victims to help eventually bring legal action against him.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/youtuber-turned-nft-scammer-on-chain-sleuth-investigates-1-5-million-crypto-thief/" rel="nofollow">YouTuber Turned NFT Scammer? On-Chain Sleuth Investigates $1.5 Million Crypto Thief</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Holds Bitcoin (BTC)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-holds-bitcoin-btc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 20:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259601</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Robert-F.-Kennedy-Jrs.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[JFK's nephew previously vowed to apply a pro-crypto regulatory framework should he win the 2024 US Presidential elections. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy &#8211; a US presidential candidate from the Democratic party and an outspoken advocate of the cryptocurrency industry &#8211; revealed owning between $100,001 and $250,000 worth of bitcoin. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The disclosure comes approximately two months after the Miami BTC conference, where he said he is not a crypto investor.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy Owns Over 3 BTC</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a financial disclosure report seen by CNBC, the Kennedy family <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/07/rfk-jr-bitcoin-investment-raises-ethics-concerns.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">held</a> up to $250K in bitcoin as of June 30. While this could be another example outlining the American&#8217;s pro-crypto stance, some might argue that the situation could cause a conflict of interest. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy attended the Miami Bitcoin conference in May this year and told the crowd that he had not invested in the primary digital asset. On the other hand, he assured that he would accept BTC donations for his political campaign.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I am not an investor, and I am not here to give investment advice,&#8221; he said at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Former Democratic Rep. Dennis Kucinich &#8211; who serves as Kennedy&#8217;s campaign manager &#8211; claimed that the BTC purchase occurred after the speech and prior to the June 30 filing deadline.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The list of American politicians holding the leading digital asset does not end with John F. Kennedy&#8217;s nephew. US Senator Cynthia Lummis </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-cynthia-lummis-bought-up-to-100000-worth-of-btc-in-august/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">bought</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> between $50,001 to $100,000 worth of bitcoin in the summer of 2021. It is worth mentioning that she jumped on the bandwagon in 2013 when BTC was worth a mere $300 apiece. Senators Pat Toomey and Ted Cruz have also joined the ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Presidential candidate and current mayor of Miami &#8211; Francis Suarez &#8211; has gone even further, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-continues-to-receive-his-salary-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">receiving</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his salary in bitcoin instead of fiat currency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kennedy&#8217;s Crypto Vision</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 69-year-old environmental lawyer has expressed some controversial views over the years. For one, he is an opponent of conventional nuclear power and promoted multiple conspiracy theories regarding COVID-19 and the vaccination program.</span></p>
<p>Kennedy is also in favor of the cryptocurrency sector and against the US Federal Reserve&#8217;s actions. He <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-f-kennedy-to-enforce-pro-bitcoin-laws-should-he-become-president/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to impose BTC-friendly laws should he become President:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I will make sure that we have policies that support Bitcoin and the freedom to transact and that allow individuals to manage their own Bitcoin wallets, nodes, and passwords.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, he assured that his cabinet will implement only necessary control to the industry (to prevent money laundering) and not hamper its development. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) will most likely not receive much support should Kennedy win the elections since he described them as financial tools used for &#8220;oppression.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-proponent-robert-f-kennedy-announces-run-for-president-of-the-usa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">criticized</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the US Fed, suggesting it had collaborated with some banks to print a considerable amount of money between 2008-2022. According to him, this has negatively impacted the American economy, while BTC could serve as an &#8220;escape route from the splatter zone.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-holds-bitcoin-btc/" rel="nofollow">US Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Holds Bitcoin (BTC)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Banking Giant Standard Chartered Sees Bitcoin Tapping $50K in 2023 and $120K in 2024 (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/banking-giant-standard-chartered-sees-bitcoin-tapping-50k-in-2023-and-120k-in-2024-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259657</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinMoon.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinMoon.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BTC's price appreciation could force miners to hold the asset and maintain cash inflows, analyst Kendrick argued.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the biggest British banking institutions &#8211; Standard Chartered &#8211; has reportedly forecasted that bitcoin&#8217;s price could reach $50,000 by the year&#8217;s end and skyrocket to $120,000 by the end of 2024. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The bank has not always been that bullish. Eric Robertsen – Global Head of Research at Standard Chartered &#8211; suggested in December 2022 (shortly after the FTX crash) that bitcoin could sink to $5,000 in 2023, whereas gold could soar to $2,250 per ounce. Those predictions have been quite inaccurate (at least for now).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Betting Even Higher</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/standard-chartered-bumps-up-bitcoin-forecast-120000-2023-07-10/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">informed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Reuters, Standard Chartered envisioned that bitcoin&#8217;s USD valuation could surge by over 65% and tap $50K by the end of 2023. The last time the primary cryptocurrency stood at that level was in December 2021. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The bank believes the rally will intensify next year, seeing bitcoin reaching $120K by the end of it. According to Geoff Kendrick &#8211; an analyst at the institution &#8211; the price jump will cause miners to sell less, &#8220;reducing net BTC supply and pushing BTC prices higher.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kendrick has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/major-bank-u-turns-on-bitcoin-with-100000-price-prediction/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">opined</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the banking crisis in the USA this spring (prompted by the collapse of Silvergate, Signature Bank, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/svb-financial-group-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection-as-btc-tapped-27k/" data-wpel-link="internal">Silicon Valley Bank</a>, and First Republic Bank) has solidified bitcoin as a &#8220;decentralized, trustless, and scarce digital asset.&#8221; As such, he saw the potential for the cryptocurrency to reach the $100K milestone at the end of 2024. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The analyst has also forecasted that BTC&#8217;s dominance over the alternative coins will exceed 50%. Current data shows that the dominance is 51.5% (per TradingView). It reached 52.2% on June 29: a figure last seen in mid-April 2021.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_259675" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259675" style="width: 1445px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259675" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance.png" alt="BTC Dominance" width="1445" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance.png 1843w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance-300x83.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance-1024x283.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance-768x213.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance-1536x425.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Dominance-50x14.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1445px) 100vw, 1445px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259675" class="wp-caption-text">BTC Dominance, Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Not so Bullish Last Year</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin, just like many other cryptocurrencies, nosedived shortly after the FTX meltdown last year. Eric Robertsen – Global Head of Research at Standard Chartered &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/standard-chartered-analyst-explains-why-btc-will-suffer-even-more-in-2023-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">predicted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in December 2022 (when the asset was worth around $17,000) that the event&#8217;s negative outcome could last in 2023, leading to BTC&#8217;s crash to $5,000.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Yields plunge along with technology shares, and while the Bitcoin sell-off decelerates, the damage has been done,&#8221; he stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the grim prediction, BTC has climbed over 80% since the year&#8217;s start, becoming an appealing bite for institutional investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, Robertsen touched upon gold, suggesting it could trade at $2,250 per ounce this year. It has been up almost 4% year-to-date, currently hovering around $1,930.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/banking-giant-standard-chartered-sees-bitcoin-tapping-50k-in-2023-and-120k-in-2024-report/" rel="nofollow">Banking Giant Standard Chartered Sees Bitcoin Tapping $50K in 2023 and $120K in 2024 (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Challenging Shiba Inu, An ICO Presale, &#038; Becoming Top Meme Coin of 2023: An Interview With Golden Inu&#8217;s Founder</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/challenging-shiba-inu-an-ico-presale-becoming-top-meme-coin-of-2023-an-interview-with-golden-inus-founder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259575</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Untitled-design-4.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Untitled-design-4.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Golden Inu has quickly become the topic of conversations entering the 2nd quarter of 2023.  The brand’s $Golden token outpaced all other memecoin cryptos in terms of ROI in June, and the brand is working on further expansion. However, most traders might not realize other factors of Golden Inu and its crypto ecosystem: First, it’s [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Golden Inu has quickly become the topic of conversations entering the 2nd quarter of 2023.  The brand’s $Golden token outpaced all other memecoin cryptos in terms of ROI in June, and the brand is working on further expansion.</p>
<p>However, most traders might not realize other factors of Golden Inu and its crypto ecosystem:</p>
<p>First, it’s a DAO-structured ecosystem. The community will be able to elect leaders and have an influence on who’s hired to work on various aspects of the $Golden token-related projects.</p>
<p>Second, it’s the first crypto ecosystem to function from the use of two official tokens, one that’s BEP-20, and another of these two tokens is ERC-20. The brand coined the phrase “dual-blockchain ecosystem,” as this will allow users from both Ethereum-Blockchain and Binance-chain to use the Golden Inu ecosystem’s applications and games seamlessly.</p>
<p>Lastly, the founder of Golden Inu is known as “Golden Takeishi.” He’s verified on two crypto verification systems.  Professionally, he’s a technology whiz that was once a bag holder of Shiba Inu. That all changed at the end of 2022 after the $SHIB token creators failed to materialize plans that would make the token of long-term value.</p>
<p>That founder then decided to launch a token that would be transparent to traders and offer long-term value with constant crypto product development — and less talk.</p>
<p>CryptoPotato has gotten in touch with the founder to have an open dialogue about <a href="https://goldeninutoken.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Golden Inu</a> and provide answers to some of the traders&#8217; biggest questions.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259733" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpg" alt="1" width="703" height="240" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1.jpg 703w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-300x102.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1-50x17.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 703px) 100vw, 703px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>Why did you name this token “Golden Inu,” knowing many traders are wary of the Inu branding?</strong></p>
<p>A: I understand the skepticism that surrounds Inu-branded tokens. The name &#8216;Golden Inu&#8217; came to my mind from three things. First, I felt slighted by Shiba Inu and its failure to deliver on multiple promises. I felt they were like pirite, aka false gold. Shining bright from marketing, but in reality, it was false gold. Instead of calling the token the ‘<a href="https://www.analyticsinsight.net/shib-burn-token-value-see-incredible-losses-shibarmy-now-buying-into-shiba-inu-killer-ico-presale/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><em>Shiba Inu Killer</em></a>” from frustrations, my goal became to take action.</p>
<p>Instead of thinking to ‘kill their brand’ I decided to make a token that’s really ‘Golden’ and will have long-term value and allow traders to have a prosperous cryptocurrency experience.</p>
<p>From there, I also thought of the ‘Golden Horde’ back in the 13th century and how ShibArmy mates could rebrand themselves into something new and get back some of their losses.</p>
<p>Our goal is to merge the infectious appeal of Inu tokens with robust, branded crypto technology and an effective economic model.   A model that ensures sustainable growth, utility, and passive income. We are confident that our actions will speak louder than the perceptions tied to our brand name.</p>
<p>Hence I started releasing applications before we finished our ERC-20 token’s presale to prove we have the team to produce apps and solutions for this evolving crypto world.</p>
<p><strong>What makes Golden Inu’s $GOLDEN tokens better than your primary rival, Shiba Inu, and its $SHIB token?</strong></p>
<p>A: While we respect what Shiba Inu has achieved, we believe that $GOLDEN tokens offer a more comprehensive proposition. <a href="https://goldeninutoken.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Golden Inu</a> is more than just two cool-looking meme tokens &#8211; we&#8217;re creating an entire ecosystem that includes gaming, e-commerce, DEX, and other crypto apps, all driven by our tokens.</p>
<p>Our approach is strategic and user-focused, designed to create sustainable growth and value for our token holders. Also, we will be providing opportunities.</p>
<p>One of my biggest goals is to change people’s lives.  I believe in the quote credited to Jeff Bezos about changing lives. If I can change crypto traders&#8217; lives in a positive way with Golden Inu apps, I know my life will forever be Golden as well.</p>
<p><strong>How many professionals are involved with the Golden Inu token and its development process?</strong></p>
<p>A: Currently, our Golden Inu team consists of 12 professionals and 3 community members.</p>
<p>Each person has a unique set of skills and experiences. Every person in our teams is an expert in their very own fields, ranging from blockchain development and financial technology to marketing, design, and community management. Their collective efforts are integral to the ongoing development and growth of Golden Inu Token and our $GOLDEN tokens.</p>
<p><strong>Why do you use two tokens for your ecosystem instead of launching your own blockchain and native coin?</strong></p>
<p>A: Our strategy is to build on established and trusted blockchain platforms, which allows us to focus on creating engaging and innovative products. As much as everyone loves to think we can do it all ourselves, we can’t. Teamwork makes the dream work — I’ve learned from life experiences how true this quote is.</p>
<p>And the ecosystem is using two tokens based on Ethereum and BNB Chain to ensure compatibility and accessibility for a wide range of crypto users that have already integrated those brands into their lifestyles.</p>
<p>In the future, however, the possibility of launching our own blockchain is not ruled out completely.  Possibly once our ecosystem has matured and branding value and equity is maximized.</p>
<p><strong>Why will the $Golden token have value long term? What reason is there to HODL?</strong></p>
<p>A: The $GOLDEN token is designed for long-term value. Our ecosystem is continuously expanding with new products and services, all of which drive demand for the token.</p>
<p>Moreover, our focus on community engagement and rewarding loyal token holders further enhances the attractiveness of holding $GOLDEN tokens.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re not just creating a token, we&#8217;re building an economic model that will reward our investors/holders as we grow our ecosystem. The more volume and usage our ecosystem has, the more our holders will generate passive rewards from our project, and everything will be handled by the Golden Treasury smart contract.</p>
<p><strong>Golden Inu’s play-to-earn game, <a href="https://captainaltcoin.com/golden-inuverse-p2e-game-website-complete-new-nft-character-leaked/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><em>$Golden Inuverse</em></a>, is buzzing around the crypto gaming community.   It’s your first major crypto product release and has major upside potential.  When will it officially release &amp; do you think this will have a positive impact on the $Golden [both] tokens values? </strong></p>
<p>A: We are planning for the official release of $Golden Inuverse in the fourth quarter of 2023. Given the growing trend of play-to-earn games and the excitement surrounding it, we believe this will positively impact the value of $GOLDEN tokens.</p>
<p>I encourage everyone to remember it&#8217;s more than just a game &#8211; it&#8217;s an opportunity for users to engage with our tokens in a fun and rewarding way.</p>
<p>And once our team has launched the Ecosystem’s marketplace, $Golden Bazaar,  people will be able to use our tokens for many things.</p>
<figure id="attachment_259734" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259734" style="width: 1145px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-259734" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu.jpg" alt="img2_golden_inu" width="1145" height="584" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu.jpg 1145w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu-300x153.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu-1024x522.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu-768x392.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/img2_golden_inu-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1145px) 100vw, 1145px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259734" class="wp-caption-text">Golden Inu Roadmap. Source: Official Website</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Will the BEP-20 or ERC-20 version of the $GOLDEN token be used for the game?</strong></p>
<p>A: We designed $Golden Inuverse to be inclusive and accessible. Therefore, both the BEP-20 and ERC-20 versions of the $GOLDEN token will be utilized. Most of the intake transactions will use the BEP-20 token, though.<br />
However, this flexibility of having 2 tokens will allow us to create special events for our ERC-20 holders. More info will come in due time.</p>
<p><strong>What crypto product will be released next after the play-to-earn game?</strong></p>
<p>A: Following the launch of our play-to-earn game, $Golden Inuverse, our developers are going to complete and reveal the $Golden Bazaar.   This is the innovative e-commerce platform I mentioned earlier.</p>
<p>$Golden Bazaar will allow users to buy and sell goods or services using cryptocurrency, revolutionizing the way e-commerce operates. This will be a decentralized platform with community moderation, more or less like how Twitter handles fake news with the Community Notes.</p>
<p><strong>In an earlier news story, it says you want to use this “$Golden Bazaar” platform to change lives. Why do you call this the “Amazon meets shopify” of crypto commerce?</strong></p>
<p>A: We view the $Golden Bazaar as a revolutionary platform that brings together the best aspects of e-commerce giants like Amazon and Shopify. It provides the variety and scale of Amazon with the customizable and entrepreneurial spirit of Shopify. The significant difference is the integration of the Decentralised Finance, making it more inclusive and accessible, particularly to those without traditional banking accounts and facilities.</p>
<p><strong>How much of a positive impact do you think this will have on the value of the $Golden tokens?</strong></p>
<p>A: We view the $Golden Bazaar as a revolutionary platform that brings together the best aspects of e-commerce giants like Amazon and Shopify. It provides the variety and scale of Amazon with the customizable and entrepreneurial spirit of Shopify. The significant difference is the integration of Decentralised Finance, making it more inclusive and accessible, particularly to those without traditional banking facilities.</p>
<p><strong>In your eyes, what are the hurdles that Golden Inu faces in the future that could have a contrary impact to the positives?</strong></p>
<p>A: Future challenges include regulatory uncertainties that come with the evolving landscape of cryptocurrency and blockchain. As we know, the SEC is hunting right now…</p>
<p>Market volatility is another concern. However, we are well-prepared with a dedicated team and strategic planning to navigate these potential challenges. Our focus is always on innovation and user value, and we believe that these guiding principles will help us overcome any hurdles.</p>
<p><strong>Some debate that the $Golden token has a meme character for its logo, but it’s an altcoin and not a Memecoin. Would you agree with this? Most tokens do not have crypto product development the way you all have started out.</strong></p>
<p>A: I agree. While our logo and mascot may have a meme character, the fundamentals of Golden Inu are far beyond that of a typical Memecoin.</p>
<p>Our commitment to providing value to our token holders through continuous product development sets us apart from many memecoins in the market. We can’t define Golden Inu as you would other memecoins because Golden Inu was created with crypto products ready in accessory to our $GOLDEN token launch, and this is a project born from long-term vision.</p>
<p>We’re not like others that are just saying, “ Buy this you will make millions “.</p>
<p><strong>An interesting fact — though you’re the founder, you released ownership of the token after its creation. Why did you do this?</strong></p>
<p>I decided to renounce ownership of the $GOLDEN [BEP-20] BNB Chain token. This decision was made to reinforce the values of decentralization and community ownership. That’s the heart of blockchain and crypto to me. By renouncing ownership, I have ensured that $GOLDEN [BEP-20] is truly a community token, and this demonstrates our commitment to transparency and trust.</p>
<p><strong>Lastly, let&#8217;s talk about liquidity. One of the most valuable and most overlooked factors of Golden Inu token is how its liquidity pool is formed.   </strong></p>
<p><strong>Can you explain the way the fiat reserves that back the token are generated? And how long will it be before Golden Inu has a $1-to-$1 liquid reserve? </strong></p>
<p>A: Our liquidity pool is built by pairing a portion of $GOLDEN tokens from transactions with BNB or ETH. The fiat reserves backing the token come from trading volume and the continuous growth of our ecosystem ( every time someone buys or sells, 3% of slippage goes into the liquidity and is being burnt ).</p>
<p>While it&#8217;s challenging to predict exact timelines, we aim to have a $1-to-$1 liquid reserve within the next 1 to 2 years, given our current growth trajectory and future plans.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="How to Buy Golden Inu Token Presale with Wallet Connect or Zerion." src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WaIFENttq-Y" width="1045" height="588" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<p>The Golden Inu project is an ambitious one, but it seems to be for the right reasons. With a myriad of meme-themed &#8220;inu&#8221; tokens, Golden Inu stands out as one with a clear road ahead and a mindset of delivering what&#8217;s promised.</p>
<p>The ecosystem appears robust, and, as clarified by the founder, the team has its feet firmly on the ground but with sights in the future.</p>
<p>Golden Inu aims to differentiate itself from the avalanche of tokens that fail to deliver on their massive promises and, instead, develop a platform that aims to truly empower its users. It&#8217;s really exciting to see how all of it will unfold.</p>
<p>Fond out more about Golden Inu Token: <a href="https://goldeninutoken.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Website</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/GoldenInuToken" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://t.me/goldenhorde" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Telegram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/challenging-shiba-inu-an-ico-presale-becoming-top-meme-coin-of-2023-an-interview-with-golden-inus-founder/" rel="nofollow">Challenging Shiba Inu, An ICO Presale, &#038; Becoming Top Meme Coin of 2023: An Interview With Golden Inu&#8217;s Founder</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FUD and External Pressure Unites the Binance Community, CZ Claims</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fud-and-external-pressure-unites-the-binance-community-cz-claims/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 16:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259689</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FUD and pressure creates tight teams internally, while collaboration and cooperation builds trust externally, Zhao said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Changpeng Zhao &#8211; CEO of crypto exchange Binance &#8211; believes his company has formed &#8220;a tight team&#8221; partly due to the &#8220;Fear, Uncertainty, Doubt&#8221; (FUD) that surrounds it on a regular basis. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm has been coping with regulatory issues with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the Department of Justice (DOJ), and other watchdogs over the years. CEO Zhao has been constant in his statements, claiming Binance cooperates with regulators, whereas some media outlets have wrongly reported negative news about the marketplace.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Fighting in the Trenches&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In one of his most recent Twitter posts, Changpeng Zhao (known in the crypto community as CZ) explained that the external pressure and FUD that have been hitting Binance are key factors that formed a &#8220;strong/tight team.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It&#8217;s not fancy team building dinners, outings, etc. It&#8217;s not the coaching exercises, mentors, or magical shrinks. It&#8217;s not the rah-rah speeches of inspirational leaders. All of the above helps but fades over time, but the secret is just … some external pressure.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_259698" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259698" style="width: 400px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259698" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp" alt="Changpeng Zhao (CZ)" width="400" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp 1200w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-300x300.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-1024x1024.webp 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-100x100.webp 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-768x768.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-239x239.webp 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-50x50.webp 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-45x45.webp 45w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259698" class="wp-caption-text">Changpeng Zhao (CZ), Source: The Guardian</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO claimed his team is &#8220;constantly in the trenches together,&#8221; which has built &#8220;reliance, alliance, resilience and most importantly trust&#8221; between the members. In addition, that struggle has united the Binance community, making them support the exchange even more.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This, in turn, makes us more determined to drive towards our mission, to increase the freedom of money for people all around the world,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the regular attacks, Binance (which turned six years this earlier this month) remains the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange. Its market share in spot trading </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-26/binance-s-market-share-is-stuck-near-one-year-low-kaiko-data#xj4y7vzkg" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stood</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at almost 56% (in June), whereas its rivals Coinbase and OKX marked less than 7%.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some of the Charges</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Modern Media Company Limited (an organization that manages content for Bloomberg in Hong Kong) portrayed CZ as the leader of a Ponzi scheme last summer. The bashing manifest included money-laundering charges and possible connections with the Dark Web and North Korean hackers.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Zhao called Bloomberg &#8220;unprofessional,&#8221; disagreeing with their story. He went even further, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-ceo-cz-sues-bloomberg-businessweek-for-defamation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the media outlet for defamation. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reuters has also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-fires-back-at-reuters-over-report-about-confiscated-accounts-linked-to-terrorism/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">fired</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> shots at Binance, claiming the authorities of Israel have confiscated approximately 190 cryptocurrency accounts from the platform in 2021. According to the news agency, some of the addresses were tied to the terrorist groups – Hamas and Islamic State.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange maintained that a certain reporter from the media outlet has been &#8220;deliberately leaving out critical facts&#8221; to present Binance in a bad light.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The recent disputes with the US SEC and the DOJ are also worth mentioning. The regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a lawsuit against Binance in June, accusing it of violating several rules and offering trading services with unregistered securities such as BNB and BUSD. The DOJ targetted Zhao, claiming he might have been involved in money-laundering operations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latest accusation coincided with the departure of some Binance executives. Nonetheless, Zhao </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1677092535871602691" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the reasons were not the ones &#8220;dreamed up by the &#8220;news.&#8221;&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fud-and-external-pressure-unites-the-binance-community-cz-claims/" rel="nofollow">FUD and External Pressure Unites the Binance Community, CZ Claims</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Massive Gaming Celebrates Global Launch of House of Blackjack with USDC Earning Race</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/massive-gaming-celebrates-global-launch-of-house-of-blackjack-with-usdc-earning-race/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 15:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259710</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/IMG_7409_1688642771myFtuYe7EI.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/IMG_7409_1688642771myFtuYe7EI.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Sydney, Australia, July 10th, 2023] Massive Gaming has announced the launch of House of Blackjack, a realistic Vegas-style online blackjack game. To mark the milestone, Massive Gaming is hosting an Unlimited USDC Earning Race with Free Bonus Rewards. The event offers players the chance to win a total prize pool of at [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Sydney, Australia, July 10th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Massive Gaming has announced the launch of House of Blackjack, a realistic Vegas-style online blackjack game. To mark the milestone, Massive Gaming is hosting an Unlimited USDC Earning Race with Free Bonus Rewards. The event offers players the chance to win a total prize pool of at least $6,000 worth of Gems and USDC.</p>
<p>The event aims to engage players in a thrilling competition while providing them with exciting bonus rewards. The total prize pool may increase as more participants join the event, adding to the excitement and competitiveness.</p>
<p>Players reaching Weekly Chest level 6 or above will receive additional Gems, with a 100% guaranteed reward. The top 80 players who earn the most USDC by playing House of Blackjack will share a prize pool of $3,000 USDC. Players can unlock additional rewards by inviting friends to join House of Blackjack. The more friends invited, the greater the distribution of rewards up to a total prize of $2,100 of Gems.</p>
<p>House of Blackjack boasts GLI RNG certification, ensuring fair and unbiased gameplay. It offers an extensive range of Blackjack 21 tournament content, allowing players to experience thrilling competitions and test their skills against opponents worldwide. Additionally, House of Blackjack includes a live face chat feature, enabling players to engage with opponents in real-time and enhancing the social aspect of gameplay.</p>
<p>Embracing innovation, House of Blackjack adopts a decentralized Play and Earn system, empowering players to earn rewards while enjoying the game. The integration of USDC ensures seamless and secure transactions, offering players a convenient and trustworthy gaming experience.</p>
<p>The latest news and developments from Massive Gaming can be found on their <a href="https://massivegaming.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">official homepage</a>. House of Blackjack is now available for download on Google Play and the App Store, providing an immersive Vegas-style blackjack experience.</p>
<p><strong>House of Blackjack Download Links:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://houseofblackjack.onelink.me/tzTo/locx4pr2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Google &amp; Apple Store </a> | <a href="https://houseofblackjack.onelink.me/2ufn/e9sa0iil" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Mycard APK</a></p>
<h2>About Massive Gaming</h2>
<p><a href="https://massivegaming.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Massive Gaming</a> is an affiliate of NEOWIZ, focused on the production and publication of crypto-enabled games and services. Learn more at Massive Gaming’s <a href="https://medium.com/massivegaming" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Medium</a>.</p>
<p>Massive Gaming is the source of this content. Cryptocurrency investments and gaming involve risks, and participants should understand and assess them independently. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/massive-gaming-celebrates-global-launch-of-house-of-blackjack-with-usdc-earning-race/" rel="nofollow">Massive Gaming Celebrates Global Launch of House of Blackjack with USDC Earning Race</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
