<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Consolidates within $25,400 to $26,200 Range, What Comes Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-consolidates-within-25400-26200-range-what-comes-next.htm</link><description>The price of Bitcoin has entered a consolidation phase, trading within a range of $25,400 to $26,200.  &lt;br /&gt;
This period of consolidation suggests a temporary pause in the upward or downward momentum of Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors are now closely observing the market to determine the next move for Bitcoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
The key question that remains is whether Bitcoin will break out of this range and continue its upward trend or experience a reversal and move lower. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-consolidates-within-25400-26200-range-what-comes-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Consolidates within $25,400 to $26,200 Range, What Comes Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-consolidates-within-25400-26200-range-what-comes-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116711/312715/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1520844"/></item><item><title>Chinese Police Warn of a Rise in Digital Yuan-themed Scams</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-police-warn-of-a-rise-in-digital-yuan-themed-scams.htm</link><description>Chinese police have warned there has been an increase in digital yuan-themed scams, as the nation’s CBDC rollout gathers pace. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the state-run news outlet CCTV (via Xinhua), officers in Shandong Province claimed they had seen a rise in digital yuan-themed “fraud.” &lt;br /&gt;
They said one recent scam had ensnared “tens of thousands of people.” &lt;br /&gt;
Officers said that “some criminal suspects” have “seen opportunities” to strike amid e-CNY adoption drives....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-police-warn-of-a-rise-in-digital-yuan-themed-scams.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Police Warn of a Rise in Digital Yuan-themed Scams&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-police-warn-of-a-rise-in-digital-yuan-themed-scams.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116673/312696/adobestock-592327042-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="493699"/></item><item><title>Binance Lawyers Push Back Against US SEC Claims That Binance.US Customer Assets Are at Risk</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-lawyers-push-back-against-us-sec-claims-that-binanceus-customer-assets-are-at-risk.htm</link><description>Attorneys for Binance.US and Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao argued that the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s temporary restraining order to freeze its assets should be denied.  &lt;br /&gt;
There is no risk to customer assets, the lawyers said on Monday in a court filing ahead of a Tuesday hearing to discuss the SEC’s proposed restraining order. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-lawyers-push-back-against-us-sec-claims-that-binanceus-customer-assets-are-at-risk.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Lawyers Push Back Against US SEC Claims That Binance.US Customer Assets Are at Risk&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-lawyers-push-back-against-us-sec-claims-that-binanceus-customer-assets-are-at-risk.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116708/312710/adobestock-494313732-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="247808"/></item><item><title>China Hopes Hard Wallets Will Spur Digital Yuan Adoption – CBDC Focuses on ‘Elderly &amp; Children’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-hopes-hard-wallets-will-spur-digital-yuan-adoption-cbdc-focuses-elderly-children.htm</link><description>A Chinese city says it is rolling out offline digital yuan “hard wallets,” with the nation targeting CBDC uptake among “elderly citizens and children.” &lt;br /&gt;
Per Changsha Evening News, the city of Changsha, Hunan Province, has announced it will debut “elderly and children-friendly” digital yuan hard wallets. &lt;br /&gt;
The CBDC’s adoption drive could be hampered by the preponderance of non-smartphone-owning individuals, banks have explained....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-hopes-hard-wallets-will-spur-digital-yuan-adoption-cbdc-focuses-elderly-children.htm"&gt;Read More: China Hopes Hard Wallets Will Spur Digital Yuan Adoption – CBDC Focuses on ‘Elderly &amp; Children’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-hopes-hard-wallets-will-spur-digital-yuan-adoption-cbdc-focuses-elderly-children.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116589/312580/china-1206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="738191"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 June – Polygon, Aptos, ApeCoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-june-polygon-aptos-apecoin.htm</link><description>The regulation of the financial markets in the United States could undergo a significant shift in the coming days as Republican congressmen propose a radical alteration of the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) governance structure through the "SEC Stabilization Act."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-june-polygon-aptos-apecoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 12 June – Polygon, Aptos, ApeCoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Aptos</category><category>ApeCoin</category><category>MATIC</category><category>Apt</category><category>APE</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto Presale</category><category>Best Crypto Project</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-12-june-polygon-aptos-apecoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116709/312711/bc-12j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="371470"/></item><item><title>eToro US Customers Will No Longer Be Able To Open New Positions in ALGO, MATIC, MANA and DASH</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-us-customers-will-no-longer-able-open-new-positions-algo-matic-mana-dash.htm</link><description>US customers using social investing platform eToro US will no longer be able to open new positions in Algorand, Decentraland, Dash and Polygon after those cryptocurrencies got caught in a US regulator’s crosshairs. &lt;br /&gt;
Beginning on July 12, customers will no longer be able to open those new positions, eToro US tweeted on Monday afternoon. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-us-customers-will-no-longer-able-open-new-positions-algo-matic-mana-dash.htm"&gt;Read More: eToro US Customers Will No Longer Be Able To Open New Positions in ALGO, MATIC, MANA and DASH&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>eToro</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Algorand</category><category>Decentraland</category><category>Dash</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-us-customers-will-no-longer-able-open-new-positions-algo-matic-mana-dash.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116704/312709/adobestock-416912673-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="341367"/></item><item><title>Binance.US Adds to Its Legal Defense in Wake of SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-adds-its-legal-defense-wake-of-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-news.htm</link><description>Binance.US has bulked up its legal expertise and added four lawyers to fight recent charges from the US Securities and Exchange Commission.  &lt;br /&gt;
One of those lawyers includes former co-director of the SEC’s enforcement division, George Canellos, according to Bloomberg News. &lt;br /&gt;
Canellos was also the SEC’s acting director and deputy director in the enforcement division where he set enforcement priorities and policies, according to his bio. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-adds-its-legal-defense-wake-of-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-news.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance.US Adds to Its Legal Defense in Wake of SEC Lawsuit: Bloomberg News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binanceus-adds-its-legal-defense-wake-of-sec-lawsuit-bloomberg-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116688/312706/adobestock-456009336-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="126355"/></item><item><title>House Republicans Introduce Bill To Fire US SEC Chair Gary Gensler and Make Other Reforms</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republicans-introduce-bill-fire-us-sec-chair-gary-gensler-make-other-reforms.htm</link><description>House Republicans filed a bill on Monday that would fire US Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler and restructure the agency. &lt;br /&gt;
Reps. Tom Emmer and Warren Davidson introduced the SEC Stabilization Act, to “remove Chairman Gensler following his long series of abuses that have been permitted under the current SEC structure,” according to a statement released from House Majority Whip Emmer’s office....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republicans-introduce-bill-fire-us-sec-chair-gary-gensler-make-other-reforms.htm"&gt;Read More: House Republicans Introduce Bill To Fire US SEC Chair Gary Gensler and Make Other Reforms&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Tom Emmer</category><category>Warren Davidson</category><category>SEC</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/house-republicans-introduce-bill-fire-us-sec-chair-gary-gensler-make-other-reforms.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116681/312705/adobestock-230599906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="533273"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 12, 2023 - $FERC, $HABIBI, $BERC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-12-2023-ferc-habibi-berc.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Profit Blue (BLUE)Jim (JIM)OXBT (OXBT)Meme (MEME)Piza (PIZA)SATS (SATS)Oshi (OSHI)FairERC20 (FERC)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-12-2023-ferc-habibi-berc.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: June 12, 2023 - $FERC, $HABIBI, $BERC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-june-12-2023-ferc-habibi-berc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116605/312611/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Secure the $25,000 Level – Has BTC Bottomed Already?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-secure-25000-level-btc-bottomed-already.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin's price hovers around the $25,000 level, cryptocurrency enthusiasts and investors are eager to determine whether the market has reached its bottom or if further price fluctuations lie ahead.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the bulls managing to secure the crucial support level, there is optimism among some observers that Bitcoin may have bottomed out....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-secure-25000-level-btc-bottomed-already.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Secure the $25,000 Level – Has BTC Bottomed Already?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-secure-25000-level-btc-bottomed-already.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116676/312700/11.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481939"/></item><item><title>Can $100 in Terra Classic Make You a Millionaire If This LUNC Burn Forecast Happens?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-100-terra-classic-make-you-millionaire-if-lunc-burn-forecast-happens.htm</link><description>Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) bulls are fighting back against building sell pressure on Monday, with the cryptocurrency last up around 1.5% on the day in the $0.000089 area and up close to 15% from the fresh yearly lows printed over the weekend in the $0.000077 area....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/can-100-terra-classic-make-you-millionaire-if-lunc-burn-forecast-happens.htm"&gt;Read More: Can $100 in Terra Classic Make You a Millionaire If This LUNC Burn Forecast Happens?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna Classic</category><category>LUNC</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-100-terra-classic-make-you-millionaire-if-lunc-burn-forecast-happens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116677/312702/terra.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="77596"/></item><item><title>Hong Kong Legislator Invites Coinbase Amidst SEC Scrutiny</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-legislator-invites-coinbase-amidst-sec-scrutiny.htm</link><description>The US SEC has been actively examining the operations of digital asset exchanges, raising concerns about investor protection and market integrity.  &lt;br /&gt;
It slammed the top crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, with lawsuits alleging securities laws violations on June 5 and 6.  &lt;br /&gt;
But despite the US Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) lawsuit against Coinbase,  a Hong Kong legislator has extended an invitation to the cryptocurrency exchange. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-legislator-invites-coinbase-amidst-sec-scrutiny.htm"&gt;Read More: Hong Kong Legislator Invites Coinbase Amidst SEC Scrutiny&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hong-kong-legislator-invites-coinbase-amidst-sec-scrutiny.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116674/312708/pexels-david-mcbee-730564.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="499146"/></item><item><title>Andreessen Horowitz's Crypto Arm to Establish London Office – Next Crypto Hub?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/andreessen-horowitzs-crypto-arm-establish-london-office-next-crypto-hub.htm</link><description>Many US-based crypto firms have been keen on expansion moves amid heightened regulatory uncertainty in the United States. &lt;br /&gt;
The latest firm to announce its expansion plans is the crypto investment subsidiary of VC Andreessen Horowitz, a16z crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm announced its plans to launch its first international office in London a few days following the US SEC lawsuit against two top cryptocurrency exchanges. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/andreessen-horowitzs-crypto-arm-establish-london-office-next-crypto-hub.htm"&gt;Read More: Andreessen Horowitz's Crypto Arm to Establish London Office – Next Crypto Hub?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/andreessen-horowitzs-crypto-arm-establish-london-office-next-crypto-hub.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116669/312695/pexels-chris-schippers-427679.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="139360"/></item><item><title>New Report: North Korea's Cyber Army Allegedly Stole $3 Billion in Crypto to Fund Nuclear Program</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-north-koreas-cyber-army-allegedly-stole-3-billion-crypto-fund-nuclear-program.htm</link><description>North Korea's cyber army has stolen $3 billion in cryptocurrencies, with 50% of the funds being used to fund the country’s ballistic missile program.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a recent analysis by The Wall Street Journal, state-sponsored hackers from North Korea have netted more than $3 billion from crypto thefts over the past five years....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-north-koreas-cyber-army-allegedly-stole-3-billion-crypto-fund-nuclear-program.htm"&gt;Read More: New Report: North Korea's Cyber Army Allegedly Stole $3 Billion in Crypto to Fund Nuclear Program&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hack</category><category>Hackers</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-north-koreas-cyber-army-allegedly-stole-3-billion-crypto-fund-nuclear-program.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116662/312682/adobestock-554683865-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="34525"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Bounces 14% From Recent Bottom and This New AI Crypto Platform May Be the Next Best Performer – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-bounces-14-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-platform-may-next-best-performer-heres-why.htm</link><description>Investors are asking whether it might be too late to buy Solana (SOL) in wake of its 14% bounce from weekend lows. &lt;br /&gt;
Did investors miss their opportunity to buy the SOL dip? &lt;br /&gt;
Solana, the cryptocurrency that powers the high-performance, smart-contract-enabled Solana layer-1 blockchain, saw a cascade of sell pressure that week in wake of the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s claim in its lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase that Solana is actually a security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-bounces-14-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-platform-may-next-best-performer-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Bounces 14% From Recent Bottom and This New AI Crypto Platform May Be the Next Best Performer – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>SEC</category><category>yPredict</category><category>AI coin</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-bounces-14-from-recent-bottom-new-ai-crypto-platform-may-next-best-performer-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116672/312694/solana.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1285872"/></item><item><title>Axie Infinity Price is Going to Zero after SEC Lawsuit Calls AXS a Security But Green Crypto Ecoterra Just Raised $5 Million – 100x Potential in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/axie-infinity-price-going-zero-after-sec-lawsuit-calls-axs-security-but-green-crypto-ecoterra-just-raised-5-million-100x-potential-2023.htm</link><description>Last week was catastrophic for Axie Infinity Shards (AXS), the native token that powers web3 play-to-earn (P2E) gaming ecosystem Axie Infinity. &lt;br /&gt;
AXS dropped more than 30% from around $7.6 per token to fresh near two-year lows under $5.0 per token, its worst one-week performance in more than two years....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/axie-infinity-price-going-zero-after-sec-lawsuit-calls-axs-security-but-green-crypto-ecoterra-just-raised-5-million-100x-potential-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Axie Infinity Price is Going to Zero after SEC Lawsuit Calls AXS a Security But Green Crypto Ecoterra Just Raised $5 Million – 100x Potential in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>AXS</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/axie-infinity-price-going-zero-after-sec-lawsuit-calls-axs-security-but-green-crypto-ecoterra-just-raised-5-million-100x-potential-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116668/312690/axs.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="385838"/></item><item><title>Web3 Freelancing and Recruitment Platform DeeLance Races Toward $1.5 Million – Huge Price Pump Incoming</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-recruitment-platform-deelance-races-toward-15-million-huge-price-pump-incoming.htm</link><description>The freelancing industry has experienced substantial transformations in recent years, primarily driven by globalization and the increased digitization of work. &lt;br /&gt;
Technological advancements, particularly the emergence of blockchain technology, have provided new opportunities for transparency, cost reduction, and efficiency across various sectors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-recruitment-platform-deelance-races-toward-15-million-huge-price-pump-incoming.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 Freelancing and Recruitment Platform DeeLance Races Toward $1.5 Million – Huge Price Pump Incoming&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-freelancing-recruitment-platform-deelance-races-toward-15-million-huge-price-pump-incoming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116635/312678/screenshot-2023-06-12-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1084889"/></item><item><title>Dubai Coin Blasts Up 2,000% Just Hours After Launch and Experts Say Wall Street Memes is the Next Crypto to Explode – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-coin-blasts-up-2000-just-hours-after-launch-experts-say-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>A new crypto token called Dubai Coin blasted up over 2,000% in the immediate aftermath of its launch on Uniswap late on Saturday. &lt;br /&gt;
Dubai Coin, an ERC-20 token that was built around the theme of the crypto industry moving to Dubai given an increasingly unfavorable regulatory environment in the US, was last changing hands at around $0.0008 per token, up from an initial launch price of around $0.00002....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-coin-blasts-up-2000-just-hours-after-launch-experts-say-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Dubai Coin Blasts Up 2,000% Just Hours After Launch and Experts Say Wall Street Memes is the Next Crypto to Explode – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Meme coin</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dubai-coin-blasts-up-2000-just-hours-after-launch-experts-say-wall-street-memes-next-crypto-explode-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116664/312683/wsm-web.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="721296"/></item><item><title>Is Andrew Tate Still Bullish on Crypto as New Interview Comes Out - Will There Ever Be An Official Tate Token?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/is-andrew-tate-still-bullish-on-crypto-as-new-interview-comes-out-will-there-ever-be-an-official-tate-token.htm</link><description>A highly anticipated new interview conducted by Valuetainment with controversial influencer Andrew Tate is premiering on YouTube right now. &lt;br /&gt;
The former champion kickboxer turned entrepreneur, internet troll and motivational influencer Andrew Tate has previously said that he is bullish on blue-chip cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/is-andrew-tate-still-bullish-on-crypto-as-new-interview-comes-out-will-there-ever-be-an-official-tate-token.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Andrew Tate Still Bullish on Crypto as New Interview Comes Out - Will There Ever Be An Official Tate Token?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Andrew Tate</category><category>chatGPT</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/is-andrew-tate-still-bullish-on-crypto-as-new-interview-comes-out-will-there-ever-be-an-official-tate-token.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116657/312671/tate.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="137163"/></item><item><title>Defying SEC: Solana, Cardano, and Polygon Disagree with 'Security' Label</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/defying-sec-solana-cardano-polygon-disagree-with-security-label.htm</link><description>In an ongoing battle against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Solana, Cardano, and Polygon have united forces to challenge the classification of their cryptocurrencies as securities. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes as lawsuits unfold against major exchanges Binance and Coinbase, these prominent projects are pushing back, seeking regulatory clarity that fosters innovation while safeguarding consumer interests....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/defying-sec-solana-cardano-polygon-disagree-with-security-label.htm"&gt;Read More: Defying SEC: Solana, Cardano, and Polygon Disagree with 'Security' Label&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Cardano</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/defying-sec-solana-cardano-polygon-disagree-with-security-label.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116652/312669/gavel-g53397310e-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="183410"/></item></channel></rss>
