<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:04:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>DEX Top Performer Token TET Listed on MEXC Exchange on July 18th, 3 PM UTC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dex-top-performer-token-tet-listed-on-mexc-exchange-on-july-18th-3-pm-utc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261258</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/f1u9ravayaaejxj_1689697687fkga3SjIKw.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/f1u9ravayaaejxj_1689697687fkga3SjIKw.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, July 18th, 2023] We are thrilled to announce that $TET, the top-performing token on Uniswap, has been listed on the esteemed MEXC Exchange. This listing represents a significant milestone for the Tectum project and opens up exciting opportunities for investors and traders worldwide. The highly anticipated listing on MEXC Exchange [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, July 18th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>We are thrilled to announce that $TET, the top-performing token on Uniswap, has been listed on the esteemed MEXC Exchange. This listing represents a significant milestone for the Tectum project and opens up exciting opportunities for investors and traders worldwide.</p>
<p>The highly anticipated listing on MEXC Exchange took place on July 18th at 3 pm UTC. MEXC Exchange is renowned for its robust trading infrastructure, high liquidity, and wide range of trading pairs. With this strategic move, $TET aims to provide its community with enhanced trading capabilities and a seamless trading experience.</p>
<p>TET has garnered significant attention in the DEX space due to its exceptional performance on Uniswap, innovative features of the SoftNote, and strong community support. The team hopes that the token&#8217;s consistent growth and positive market sentiment will continue due to its global long-term utility.</p>
<p>By listing on MEXC Exchange, TET gains exposure to a vast network of traders, institutional investors, and crypto enthusiasts. This increased visibility and accessibility will contribute to the further expansion of the $TET ecosystem and its adoption within the broader crypto community.</p>
<p>The $TET team has been working diligently to ensure a smooth listing process on MEXC Exchange. The team is committed to providing ongoing support and maintaining transparent communication channels with the community throughout this exciting phase.</p>
<p>For more information about TET and the upcoming listing on MEXC Exchange, please visit the official website, <a href="https://www.softnote.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">www.softnote.com</a>. Stay tuned for further updates on social media channels, including <a href="https://twitter.com/tectumsocial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://t.me/tectumglobal" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a>, and <a href="https://discord.gg/TXREkPY8C7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a>.</p>
<h2>About Tectum:</h2>
<p>From the Cybersecurity company CrispMind, The Tectum SoftNote is the ultimate Bitcoin/Crypto Layer 2 solution that overcomes the pitfalls of the lightning network. It is built on the Layer 1 Blockchain, Tectum, which is the fastest blockchain in the world and transacts at 1.3 million TPS. With SoftNote, users can enjoy instant, trustless, anonymous, and decentralized crypto payments for free. With a strong community backing and a commitment to innovation, $TET aims to shape the future of the crypto payments for private and retail transactions and revolutionize the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dex-top-performer-token-tet-listed-on-mexc-exchange-on-july-18th-3-pm-utc/" rel="nofollow">DEX Top Performer Token TET Listed on MEXC Exchange on July 18th, 3 PM UTC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The US Will Become a &#8216;Highly Competitive Market&#8217; Once it Embraces Crypto, Circle CEO Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-will-become-a-highly-competitive-market-once-it-embraces-crypto-circle-ceo-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261174</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Blockchain technology will be among the key factors to transform commerce and trade in the following decade, Allaire added.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jeremy Allaire &#8211; Chief Executive Officer of Circle &#8211; believes American regulators should open arms to the cryptocurrency industry to prevent falling behind other nations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He said the US government was among the first to propose recommendations regarding stablecoin regulation, adding that the White House, the Federal Reserve, and the Treasury Department are all focused on that mission. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;The US may be Late to the Party&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/18/future-of-finance-circle-jeremy-allaire-crypto-regulations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Allaire </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">regretted that the American government has not been as supportive of the digital asset industry over the years as other countries. In his view, this could push talent abroad and affect &#8220;where capital will go.&#8221; Still, he raised hopes that the US will quickly catch up once it enforces a regulatory framework due to the size of its economy and implement certain policies &#8220;in an election year:&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The US may be late to the party in terms of getting these policies done, but it is the biggest economy and has the biggest technology industry and the biggest financial system in the world. And when the US does lay down its rules, it&#8217;s going to be a highly competitive market.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_261204" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261204" style="width: 607px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261204" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg" alt="Jeremy Allaire" width="607" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-300x198.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-1024x675.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-768x506.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-1536x1012.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-2048x1350.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 607px) 100vw, 607px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261204" class="wp-caption-text">Jeremy Allaire, Source: The Boston Globe</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Allaire </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/regulatory-uncertainty-and-banking-crisis-could-push-investors-outside-the-us-circle-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">argued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this year that the regulatory chaos and the banking crisis in America could prompt local investors to move abroad.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also gave his two cents on the numerous financial giants that have recently filed to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs in the States, such as the world&#8217;s largest asset manager <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">BlackRock</a>. According to him, one factor behind the increasing interest from such companies is the end of the turbulence caused by<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the FTX implosion</a> last year. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;But we&#8217;re well past that, and at the same time, the technological progress just keeps cranking along,&#8221; he maintained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Circle&#8217;s CEO suggested the current condition of the crypto sector is much similar to the market after the Dot-com crash in the late 1990s. Back then, phrases like &#8220;e-commerce&#8221; or &#8220;consumer internet&#8221; were frowned upon due to the high uncertainty. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, &#8220;the next generation of browser technology, the next generation of digital media technology, broadband infrastructure, Wi-Fi infrastructure, mobile devices&#8221; lit up &#8220;a whole new era,&#8221; Allaire concluded.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">What Does the Future Hold?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Allaire described the next five to ten years as &#8220;the programable money era,&#8221; where blockchain technology, AI, smart contracts, and entrepreneurship will reshape trade and commerce.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He went further, saying the financial system will transform the way smartphones are modified after the success of the iPhone.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It&#8217;s similar to when you lit up broadband for everyone, and you enabled Wi-Fi-connected devices—what became possible, right? Television was reinvented; gaming was reinvented,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-will-become-a-highly-competitive-market-once-it-embraces-crypto-circle-ceo-says/" rel="nofollow">The US Will Become a &#8216;Highly Competitive Market&#8217; Once it Embraces Crypto, Circle CEO Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO to Meet US House Democrats on Crypto Legislation: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-to-meet-us-house-democrats-on-crypto-legislation-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261215</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brian Armstrong, the chief executive officer of America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, will privately meet with Democrats from the House of Representatives on Wednesday morning.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-17/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-set-to-meet-with-house-democrats?sref=3REHEaVI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, Democratic aides disclosed that the meeting would focus on crypto legislation and related issues like taxes, privacy, and national security.</p>
<h2>Coinbase CEO to Meet With House Democrats</h2>
<p>The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House that is made up of 100 members who are committed to pro-economic growth, pro-innovation, and fiscally responsible policies.</p>
<p>Armstrong’s meeting with the New Democratic Coalition comes as Coinbase faces a lawsuit from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over allegations of securities law violations. Recall that the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> the crypto exchange of operating as an unregistered national securities exchange, clearing agency, and broker last month.</p>
<p>While Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/" data-wpel-link="internal">fights</a> the SEC’s allegations, Armstrong launched a campaign seeking clearer crypto rules in the U.S. Before the lawsuit, Coinbase petitioned the agency in July 2022, asking for clarity on crypto regulation. After ignoring the exchange’s request, the agency finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-responds-to-coinbase-request-for-crypto-clarity-wants-more-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">asked</a> for more time to file a concrete response.</p>
<h2>Armstrong Seeks Clear Crypto Rules</h2>
<p>The Coinbase chief has urged U.S. lawmakers to consider two crypto bills that have been circulating and promise to provide guidance on which regulators will oversee digital assets. Lawmakers from the House and Senate introduced the bills to provide clarity on crypto regulation.</p>
<p>The first one, <a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=100652X1574425&amp;isjs=1&amp;jv=15.4.2-stackpath&amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coindesk.com%2Fpolicy%2F2023%2F06%2F02%2Fus-house-republicans-push-for-crypto-oversight-with-bill-to-make-sec-play-ball%2F&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Ffinancialservices.house.gov%2Fnews%2Fdocumentsingle.aspx%3FDocumentID%3D408838&amp;xs=1&amp;xtz=-60&amp;xuuid=e221d84af2894b01674d9afbd13b765a&amp;xjsf=other_click__auxclick%20%5B2%5D" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">proposed</a> by Republican chairs of the House Financial Services Committee and the House Committee on Agriculture, would enable crypto exchanges to register with the SEC and trade digital securities, commodities, and stablecoins all in one place.</p>
<p>The second, introduced by crypto-friendly Senator Cynthia Lummis and Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, would require the Commodity Futures Trading Commission to oversee exchanges while regulated depository institutions handle stablecoin issuers. The bill was initially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-cynthia-lummis-bill-and-what-does-it-mean-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">proposed</a> in June 2022 but <a href="https://www.lummis.senate.gov/wp-content/uploads/Lummis-Gillibrand-2023.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">re-introduced</a> last week.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Coinbase’s COIN stock is up over 25% since a federal court <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled</a> in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit with the SEC concerning XRP’s recognition as a security or investment contract. The partial victory was considered a win for the crypto industry at large. The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-to-meet-us-house-democrats-on-crypto-legislation-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO to Meet US House Democrats on Crypto Legislation: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Meme Token Evil Pepe Coin Launches Presale &#8211; Next $PEPE Rival to Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evil_pepe_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evil_pepe_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin market has a new contender looking to challenge the dominance of $PEPE – Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE). Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE) This brand-new project launched its presale phase today, aiming to capture the meme coin hype with an edgy twist on the popular Pepe the Frog character. With the frenzy around meme [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin market has a new contender looking to challenge the dominance of $PEPE – Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE).</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE)</a> This brand-new project launched its presale phase today, aiming to capture the meme coin hype with an edgy twist on the popular Pepe the Frog character.</p>
<p>With the frenzy around meme coins showing no signs of dissipating, $EVILPEPE could be the next viral hit when it makes its open market debut in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Evil Pepe Coin Unleashes Exciting Opportunity to Harness Meme Coin Magic</h2>
<p>Evil Pepe Coin has burst onto the scene with an appealing presale phase, generating excitement throughout the crypto scene.</p>
<p>This presale offers a golden opportunity for investors and meme enthusiasts, with 90% of the total $EVILPEPE supply on offer.</p>
<p>Priced at just $0.000333, $EVILPEPE beckons investors to embrace their dark side and engage in the exciting world of meme culture.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261246" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="256" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21-300x128.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Early investors have the option to purchase tokens using $ETH or $USDT, without the constraint of any minimum or maximum investment size.</p>
<p>Per the project’s <a href="https://evilpepecoin.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the presale&#8217;s hard cap is just $1,996,002, hastening the token&#8217;s debut on the open market.</p>
<p>Although 90% of the total $EVILPEPE supply has been set aside for the presale, the remaining 10% will be used for decentralized exchange (DEX) liquidity – a solid foundation for the token&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p>Importantly, this liquidity will be locked for one month, helping stabilize the price and prevent a dreaded rug pull from occurring.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Evil Pepe Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Evil Pepe Coin Looks to Challenge Dominance of Meme King $PEPE</h2>
<p>As indicated by its name, Evil Pepe Coin seeks to capitalize on the triumphant performance of the enormously successful meme coin Pepe ($PEPE).</p>
<p>$PEPE experienced a meteoric rise of over 10,000% earlier this year, kickstarting the meme coin frenzy that has been sustained until this day.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261245" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="309" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21-300x154.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Evil Pepe Coin looks to tap into the existing enthusiasm surrounding $PEPE, which has demonstrated the massive potential (and profitability) of low-cap cryptos.</p>
<p>However, $EVILPEPE puts its own spin on things with a rebellious nature and dark branding – providing scope to attract investors who missed out on the original $PEPE’s ascent.</p>
<p>Describing itself as &#8220;unapologetic and audacious,&#8221; Evil Pepe Coin looks primed and ready to ride the hype wave and offer huge gains potential for early adopters.</p>
<h2>Ambitious $EVILPEPE Roadmap Hints at Token’s Future Potential</h2>
<p>Given $EVILPEPE’s stable price point throughout its presale phase, many members of the token’s <a href="https://t.me/Evilpepetoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a> believe that it&#8217;s positioned for a remarkable take-off once it hits exchanges.</p>
<p>Importantly, $EVILPEPE will only be listed on a decentralized exchange (DEX) initially – a decision that has been taken to promote community engagement.</p>
<p>This is because a DEX listing aligns with the project’s vision of inclusivity, allowing for broader access to $EVILPEPE.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261244" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="141" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14-300x70.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14-50x12.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>As such, by launching exclusively on a DEX, the project&#8217;s creators ensure everyone has an equal opportunity to engage with the token and contribute to its growth.</p>
<p>With this solid foundation of inclusivity and community engagement, Evil Pepe Coin&#8217;s roadmap seeks to drive the project towards ambitious goals.</p>
<p>These goals include high-profile marketing campaigns, strategic partnerships, and a lofty market cap of $100 million.</p>
<p>All in all, Evil Pepe Coin&#8217;s roadmap reflects a vision of embracing the devilish side of meme culture – positioning $EVILPEPE as a potentially prominent player in the crypto landscape.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Evil Pepe Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch/" rel="nofollow">New Meme Token Evil Pepe Coin Launches Presale &#8211; Next $PEPE Rival to Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Unable to Breach $2,000 as Bulls Running Out of Steam: Ethereum Price Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2000-as-bulls-running-out-of-steam-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261190</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price rally has slowed down in recent weeks. The price has yet to break above the $2,000 level, which is making many market participants worried. Ethereum Price Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the price has been forming higher highs and higher lows since rebounding from the 200-day moving [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price rally has slowed down in recent weeks. The price has yet to break above the $2,000 level, which is making many market participants worried.</p>
<h2><strong>Ethereum Price Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price has been forming higher highs and higher lows since rebounding from the 200-day moving average earlier in June.</p>
<p>However, there is a clear lack of bullish momentum, as the ETH price keeps pulling back towards the 50-day moving average located around the $1,900 mark. In case it breaks, there are two close support levels available: the $1,800 static level and the 200-day moving average close to the same price mark.</p>
<p>Therefore, while the momentum is seemingly fading, there is still hope that a rebound from either of these levels would initiate the next rally higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261196" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261196" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261196 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1807231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261196" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Recent PA developments become clearer on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The ETH price has broken above the $1,930 resistance level a couple of times since the beginning of July but has failed in both instances, as it has rapidly dropped back below the level.</p>
<p>Currently, the price is seemingly targeting the $1,850 short-term support level once again, with the $1,750 level available as the next target in line in case the former level fails to hold. The RSI indicator, while previously signaling the potential fake breakout and drop, is offering little insight at the moment, as it is oscillating around the 50% value. This behavior confirms the indecisiveness of the market participants and the equilibrium in momentum.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261194" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261194" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261194 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1807232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261194" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>Ethereum Coinbase Premium Index</h3>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has remained relatively stagnant over the past few months, consolidating around the $2,000 level. However, interesting activity has been going on in the background.</p>
<p>The chart displays the Ethereum Coinbase premium gap, which is calculated based on the gap between ETH&#8217;s price on Coinbase and Binance, two of the largest exchanges in the world. This metric shows whether US investors are buying or selling on aggregate compared to other investors. Positive values indicate buying pressure from the United States.</p>
<p>As the image demonstrates, there has been a significant shift in the US market sentiment, as the premium gap index has mostly been positive. Considering that many US investors are wealthy individuals or institutions, this could be a positive signal for ETH, pointing out that it might be in the accumulation phase at the beginning of a new bull market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261195" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261195" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261195 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_coinbase_premium_index_chart_1807231" width="2560" height="1619" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-300x190.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-1024x647.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-768x486.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-1536x971.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-2048x1295.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261195" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2000-as-bulls-running-out-of-steam-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Unable to Breach $2,000 as Bulls Running Out of Steam: Ethereum Price Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Price Analysis: Can Ripple Bulls Push Toward $1 or is a Correction Imminent?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-analysis-can-ripple-bulls-push-toward-1-or-is-a-correction-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261198</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price has experienced a significant surge after finding strong support around the 100-day moving average at $0.497. It is now approaching a crucial resistance level at $0.85, indicating a prevailing buying pressure in the market and a positive outlook for Ripple&#8217;s medium-term prospects. Ripple Price Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Analyzing the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price has experienced a significant surge after finding strong support around the 100-day moving average at $0.497. It is now approaching a crucial resistance level at $0.85, indicating a prevailing buying pressure in the market and a positive outlook for Ripple&#8217;s medium-term prospects.</p>
<h2><strong>Ripple Price Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Analyzing the daily chart, it is apparent that the XRP price increased after finding support at the 100-day moving average. However, it now faces a strong resistance zone at $0.85, characterized by high selling pressure and increased supply.</p>
<p>This development suggests a bullish sentiment among traders, increasing the likelihood of a breakthrough above the resistance region. However, it&#8217;s important to note that every significant upward movement is typically followed by a consolidation or correction phase, and Ripple&#8217;s price is no exception.</p>
<p>Therefore, it seems likely that the price will enter a short-term correction phase, accompanied by higher volatility and pullback periods before the next significant upward movement occurs.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261192" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261192" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261192 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_1807231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-Daily-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261192" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>The 4-Hour Chart</strong></h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, it can be seen that the price has successfully broken above the upper edge of a channel, evidenced by a large green candle resulting from a recent explosive rally. However, for a valid breakout confirmation, a pullback to the broken level should occur.</p>
<p>Therefore, based on the price action, it appears more likely that the price will retrace back to the upper boundary and complete a pullback. If this occurs, the market can expect the bullish rally to continue, reaching higher resistance levels.</p>
<p>However, in the event that the recent breakout proves to be false, Ripple may face significant rejection and a subsequent decline.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261193" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261193" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261193 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_1807232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/XRP-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261193" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-analysis-can-ripple-bulls-push-toward-1-or-is-a-correction-imminent/" rel="nofollow">XRP Price Analysis: Can Ripple Bulls Push Toward $1 or is a Correction Imminent?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Axelar Launches &#8216;Interchain Token Service&#8217; to Enable ERC-20 Interoperability Across Multiple Chains</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/axelar-launches-interchain-token-service-to-enable-erc-20-interoperability-across-multiple-chains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261207</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BF96E01E-A9E6-4DE2-8D63-1200683FF351_1689623265WmJUCIbIt9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BF96E01E-A9E6-4DE2-8D63-1200683FF351_1689623265WmJUCIbIt9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, July 18th, 2023] Sushi to deploy Interchain Tokens, powered by new Axelar product suite delivering cross-chain fungibility and customization.  Axelar, the blockchain interoperability leader, is announcing the launch of Interchain Token Service (ITS), a product suite that extends tokens cross-chain, preserving their native functionality and allowing teams to easily manage [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Paris, France, July 18th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><em><strong>Sushi to deploy Interchain Tokens, powered by new Axelar product suite delivering cross-chain fungibility and customization. </strong></em></p>
<p class="ql-align-justify"><a href="https://axelar.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Axelar</a>, the blockchain interoperability leader, is announcing the launch of <a href="https://axelar.network/its" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Interchain Token Service (ITS)</a>, a product suite that extends tokens cross-chain, preserving their native functionality and allowing teams to easily manage supply and features.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">ERC-20 tokens have unlocked powerful interoperability between Ethereum-based applications. In a similar way, Interchain Token Service creates Interchain Tokens that unlock new possibilities for interconnected applications spanning all EVM-compatible ecosystems. Sushi, the popular decentralized exchange (DEX) &amp; automated market maker (AMM), is among the first deployment partners to embrace Interchain Tokens.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Interchain Token Service delivers:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fungibility: Wrapped versions on connected chains are fungible with one another.</li>
<li>Custom functionality: Custom tokens keep their features, cross-chain.</li>
<li>Low overhead: Smart contracts and developer tools automate complex developer tasks.</li>
</ul>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Sushi will employ Interchain Token Service to give SUSHI, its native token, seamless interoperability across multiple chains. To start, Interchain SUSHI tokens will be interoperable across Arbitrum, Ethereum, Optimism and Polygon. Sushi will manage its multichain deployments with minimal overhead, deploying and updating Interchain Tokens with a single click.</p>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Traditionally, in order for Web3 applications to reach multiple blockchain ecosystems, they would rely on <a href="https://axelar.network/blog/cross-chain-bridges-benefits-limitations-risks" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">bridged versions</a> of their tokens: risky, limited in function and nonfungible with each other. <a href="https://axelar.network/blog/blockchain-interoperability-how-to-achieve-it-securely" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Alternatively</a>, they may deploy copies of the native token on multiple chains, incurring significant developer overhead. Using the Axelar network&#8217;s full-stack interoperability, Interchain Token Service delivers smart contracts and developer tools that automate away this overhead: developers can manage Interchain Tokens with the click of a button.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Axelar&#8217;s Interchain Token Service unlocks a more seamless, interchain experience for Sushi users,&#8221; said Sushi&#8217;s head chef, Jared Grey. &#8220;Currently, there are many bridged versions of $SUSHI – lacking fungibility, carrying bridge risk. With Interchain Tokens, Sushi can achieve true cross-chain interoperability, simply and securely.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Sergey Gorbunov, co-founder of Axelar, highlighted the significance of Interchain Tokens. &#8220;With Interchain Token Service, we are empowering developers to unlock the full potential of their tokens and extend their reach across multiple chains,&#8221; he said. &#8220;This new extension of Axelar&#8217;s secure and programmable interoperability layer will be the catalyst to a more connected and inclusive blockchain economy.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Read more and <a href="https://axelar.network/its" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">explore the Legend of Interchain</a>. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/26a1.png" alt="⚡" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Axelar</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Axelar is the full-stack interoperability layer for Web3. The network enables blockchain as a new kind of development platform, integrating diverse networks into a seamless “Internet of blockchains.” Axelar is programmable and decentralized, secured by a proof-of-stake token, AXL. Application users access any digital asset or application with one click. Developers work with a simple API and access an ecosystem of tools and service providers.</p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Sushi</h2>
<p class="ql-align-justify">Sushi is building a decentralized, comprehensive DeFi ecosystem complete with AMM, cross-chain capabilities, NFT artist platform and more. Follow our socials to keep up with our product launches and find out more on how you can make the most of your cryptocurrency assets with Sushi’s secure and powerful DeFi tools!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/axelar-launches-interchain-token-service-to-enable-erc-20-interoperability-across-multiple-chains/" rel="nofollow">Axelar Launches &#8216;Interchain Token Service&#8217; to Enable ERC-20 Interoperability Across Multiple Chains</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Has Ripple (XRP) Won or Will the SEC Appeal: What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/has-ripple-xrp-won-or-will-the-sec-appeal-what-will-happen-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261183</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/ripple_xrp_ta-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/ripple_xrp_ta-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple may have won the battle but the war rages on. Will the SEC let go?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The legal clash between Ripple and the US Securities and Exchange Commission has turned into a cornerstone case for the entire cryptocurrency industry. According to many, it may have serious implications for future lawsuits, regardless of how it ends.</p>
<p>Most recently, Judge Analisa Torres ruled that secondary sales of XRP didn&#8217;t constitute investment contracts &#8211; a move that the market perceived as a major win for Ripple. But is there more to the story? Did Brad Garlinghouse and Co. win?</p>
<p>To answer that, we first need to understand what exactly happened so far.</p>
<h2>Massive Victory but Partial Nonetheless</h2>
<p>The crux of the SEC&#8217;s charges is that Ripple &#8211; the company behind XRP &#8211; conducted an unregistered sale of securities in violation of existing regulations.</p>
<p>However, the Commission also alleged that secondary sales of XRP (read: sold on centralized exchanges like Coinbase) also constituted investment contracts. To this, it&#8217;s important to take a closer look at the <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082/gov.uscourts.nysd.551082.874.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recent ruling</a> itself.</p>
<p>Immediately as the news broke out, XRP <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">exploded</a> by more than 70% in hours before settling down and trading at its current prices. Therefore, it&#8217;s safe to assume that the market perceived the ruling as favorable for Ripple &#8211; and it was, to a certain extent.</p>
<p>More precisely, Judge Torres ruled that secondary sales of XRP didn&#8217;t constitute investment contracts. See, because of the SEC allegations, a myriad of exchanges had previously delisted XRP in fear of repercussions. These included:</p>
<ul>
<li>Coinbase</li>
<li>Bitwise</li>
<li>CrossTower</li>
<li>OSL</li>
<li>Bitstamp</li>
<li>Crypto.com, and many more.</li>
</ul>
<p>Now that the ruling is out, some of the above, such as Coinbase, Crypto.com, Kraken, and Bitstamp, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-crypto-exchanges-re-listed-xrp-following-ripples-victory-against-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">re-listed XRP</a>.</p>
<p>So, why a partial victory?</p>
<p>Well, as we mentioned above, the allegations are two-fold, and Judge Torres confirmed the position of the SEC in regard to institutional sales.</p>
<p>More specifically, the Judge said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8230;Therefore, having considered the economic reality and totality of circumstances surrounding the <strong>Institutional Sales, </strong>the Court concludes that <strong>Ripple&#8217;s Institutional Sales of XRP </strong><em>constituted the unregistered offered and sale of investment contracts in violation of Section 5 of the Securities Act.</em></p></blockquote>
<h2>So, What&#8217;s Next?</h2>
<p>Based on the above, it seems relatively straightforward to assume that the legal battle is far from being over.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stuttering-sec-chair-gary-gensler-disappointed-at-ripple-victory/" data-wpel-link="internal">Commenting</a> on the ruling was the Chairman of the United States Securities and Exchange Commission, Gary Gensler, who didn&#8217;t hide his disappointment:</p>
<blockquote><p>While disappointed on what they said about retail investors, we&#8217;re still looking at it and assessing that opinion.</p></blockquote>
<p>His speech itself was stuttered, and it appeared at times that Gensler was at a loss for word on stage at the National Press Club on July 17th.</p>
<p>That said, it&#8217;s also clear that the SEC is likely not going to let this go. However, the fact that XRP got re-listed on multiple exchanges because of the most recent ruling is a huge victory for Ripple. More importantly, the ball is in the SEC&#8217;s court now and it&#8217;s interesting to see if they will file an appeal.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/has-ripple-xrp-won-or-will-the-sec-appeal-what-will-happen-next/" rel="nofollow">Has Ripple (XRP) Won or Will the SEC Appeal: What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest Offloads Over $88M Worth Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Shares in 2 Weeks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-offloads-over-88m-worth-coinbases-coin-shares-in-2-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Facebook (META)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261133</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ark_invest.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase is expected to release its Q2 earnings early next month.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investors are closely monitoring Coinbase&#8217;s earning reports as shares of the crypto giant COIN are up more than 214% YTD. The fresh boost was provided after the crypto exchange reached an agreement with Cboe&#8217;s BZX Exchange to maintain a surveillance-sharing agreement for five of its spot Bitcoin ETF applications.</p>
<p>As a result, funds associated with Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Investment have rushed to profit from the stock upsurge.</p>
<h2>ARK Invest Offloads COIN</h2>
<p>The investment fund led by Bitcoin bull Cathie Wood had acquired a significant amount of Coinbase shares during the bear market. While Wood is still optimistic about Coinbase in light of a court ruling against the SEC and favor of Ripple&#8217;s XRP, ARK Invest has offloaded $88.5 million worth of COIN shares in the past two weeks.</p>
<p>On July 11, the investment firm sold off $12 million worth of COIN shares just as the stock climbed near a one-year high. Nearly $50.5 million worth of shares, representing 485,000 COIN, were sold on July 14th across three different funds. Three of ARK Investment&#8217;s ETFs cashed in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coin-shares-climb-10-after-cboe-included-coinbase-in-amended-btc-etf-applications/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">COIN&#8217;s recent rally</a>, selling a total of 248,838 shares, worth $26.3 million, based on Monday’s <a href="https://www.google.com/finance/quote/COIN:NASDAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">closing price</a> of $105.5.</p>
<p>Following a rough start, Coinbase reported a net loss of $79 million in Q1 this year, down from $430 million lost during the same period last year. In a shareholder letter, Coinbase said it was a &#8220;turning point” in building a more efficient and financially disciplined company.</p>
<p>Industry players are turning increasingly bullish on Coinbase as shares of COIN witnessed a turnaround despite the crypto exchange receiving a Wells notice in March and being hammered by a lawsuit from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission in June.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange is expected to release its Q2 earnings early next month.</p>
<h2>Relocating Capital to &#8216;Laggards&#8217;</h2>
<p>The recent moves by ARK Invest are unusual as it made a series of buys of Coinbase&#8217;s stock during crypto winter. However, Wood attributed the sales to simple profit-taking. In a recent Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2023-07-17/cathie-wood-on-ark-fund-flows-coinbase-ai-investments-video" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">interview</a>, the exec said that the investment firm is instead looking to relocate &#8220;capital to perhaps some laggards.&#8221; She added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Flows are coming back. One of the reasons, ARKK established a base over the last year and it has been trading up and down through that base. I think a lot of investors and more who are technically oriented are looking now at a breakout in our strategy. We&#8217;ll see if it continues. We have enjoyed positive inflows in July, which have cut in half the outflows.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Besides COIN, ARK has also offloaded Tesla (TSLA) shares worth $13 million and instead purchased additional shares of Meta Platforms (META) and Robinhood (HOOD).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-invest-offloads-over-88m-worth-coinbases-coin-shares-in-2-weeks/" rel="nofollow">Cathie Wood&#8217;s ARK Invest Offloads Over $88M Worth Coinbase&#8217;s COIN Shares in 2 Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink’s Cross-Chain Protocol Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chainlinks-cross-chain-protocol-goes-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 10:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainlink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261145</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Chainlink.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Chainlink.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The firm behind LINK hopes to close the gap between traditional banks using their oracle system and other blockchains.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chainlink, a leading project focusing on the use of oracles to bring real-world data onto the blockchain and use it for business purposes, has been working on a way to bring its hard-earned, reputable data to partnered projects for quite some time now.</p>
<p>After a long wait, the devs at Chainlink announced the launch of CCIP, the Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol.</p>
<p>For now, CCIP is available on the mainnets of target protocols only in an invitation-based early access system – but not for long.</p>
<h2>Testnet Availability Coming Soon</h2>
<p>CCIPs mainnet launch on the Ethereum, Polygon, Avalanche, and Optimism blockchains is already in use by the teams at Synthetix and BGD Labs, who are using the Chainlink network to get around the limitations of traditional cross-chain bridges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ The Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP) has officially launched on Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism, and Polygon mainnets.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/LinkTheWorld?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#LinkTheWorld</a> <a href="https://t.co/SdLVyaapg3" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/SdLVyaapg3</a></p>
<p>— Chainlink (@chainlink) <a href="https://twitter.com/chainlink/status/1680970793331613697?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>For non-partnered projects, CCIP will be made available on the testnets of these blockchains on the 20th of July. In the meantime, devs looking to integrate their dApps with Chainlink can sign up for early access and get vetted on the project&#8217;s website.</p>
<h2>Setting New Standards</h2>
<p>According to Chainlink co-founder and acting CEO Sergey Nazarov, the project hopes that CCIP will become the new gold standard for cross-chain interoperability. In a press release celebrating the launch, he likened CCIP to the TCP/IP standard that made the Internet as we know it possible.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Just like key standards such as TCP/IP remade a fragmented early internet into the single global internet we all know and use today, we are making CCIP to connect the fragmented public blockchain landscape and the growing bank chain ecosystem into a single Internet of Contracts.”</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Nazarov also <a href="https://blog.chain.link/ccip-mainnet-early-access/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">stressed</a> that he and his team hope that other devs will find ways to improve the infrastructure he and his team built.</p>
<p>In order to facilitate further development of the protocol, Chainlink gives developers the option to build their own cross-chain solutions on top of CCIP using Arbitrary Messaging and Simplified Token Transfers – both of which will be backed up by the data that has so far enabled over $8 trillion worth of value to be moved on-chain.</p>
<p>Devs who use CCIP will also benefit from the Active Risk Management Network (ARM), a lightweight, independent network created specifically to add an extra layer of security to CCIP.</p>
<blockquote><p>“ARM is a separate, independent network that continually monitors and validates the behavior of the primary CCIP network, providing an additional layer of security by independently verifying cross-chain operations. The ARM Network utilizes a separate, minimal Rust implementation of the Chainlink node software.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The surprise announcement prompted an increase in the market value of LINK. The price of Chainlink’s proprietary token has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainlink-jumps-7-on-cross-chain-news-bitcoin-slipped-to-18-day-low-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">risen</a> by over 6% within the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko, compounding a steady increase in value over the past month.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chainlinks-cross-chain-protocol-goes-live/" rel="nofollow">Chainlink’s Cross-Chain Protocol Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
