<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bakkt Is Delisting Solana, Polygon and Cardano Citing Regulatory Uncertainty: Fortune</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-delisting-solana-polygon-cardano-citing-regulatory-uncertainty-fortune.htm</link><description>New York Stock Exchange listed company Bakkt is delisting Solana, Polygon and Cardano citing regulatory uncertainty, according to Fortune.  &lt;br /&gt;
This comes days after the US Securities and Exchange Commission said those three cryptocurrencies, among others, are securities. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-delisting-solana-polygon-cardano-citing-regulatory-uncertainty-fortune.htm"&gt;Read More: Bakkt Is Delisting Solana, Polygon and Cardano Citing Regulatory Uncertainty: Fortune&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>Cardano</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Bakkt</category><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-delisting-solana-polygon-cardano-citing-regulatory-uncertainty-fortune.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117192/313535/adobestock-349980212-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="260993"/></item><item><title>South Korean Security Tokens Market ‘May Be Worth $287B by 2030’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-security-tokens-market-may-worth-287b-by-2030.htm</link><description>South Korea’s financial industry thinks the nation’s security token offerings (STO) market could be worth $287 billion by 2030, with the biggest commercial banks in the country “lining up” to get involved. &lt;br /&gt;
Per EDaily, the Hana Financial Group’s Management Research Institute predicted that the domestic security token market will grow to almost $27 billion next year. &lt;br /&gt;
The group predicted rapid growth to follow in the remainder of the decade....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-security-tokens-market-may-worth-287b-by-2030.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Security Tokens Market ‘May Be Worth $287B by 2030’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>STO</category><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-security-tokens-market-may-worth-287b-by-2030.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117065/313293/adobestock-602931540-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="706767"/></item><item><title>Big Eyes Price Prediction - 99% Crash, Token Claim Fail, Coffeezilla Video Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/big-eyes-coin-price-prediction.htm</link><description>Big Eyes coin was listed on Uniswap on Thursday at a price 88% lower than the listing price announced by the team, then crashed further. $BIG token is now down 99%, trading at approximately $0.000007. &lt;br /&gt;
$BIG token was listed at $0.0000743 on Uniswap, compared to the stated listing price of $0.0006. The stage one price for the presale - which began back in August 2022 - was $0.0001....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/big-eyes-coin-price-prediction.htm"&gt;Read More: Big Eyes Price Prediction - 99% Crash, Token Claim Fail, Coffeezilla Video Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>ICO news</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/big-eyes-coin-price-prediction.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117190/313531/big-eyes-coin-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="549411"/></item><item><title>Nansen Report: Crypto Exchanges Kraken, Bybit, and Bitget Gain Ground After FTX Collapse</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nansen-report-crypto-exchanges-kraken-bybit-bitget-gain-ground-after-ftx-collapse.htm</link><description>Smaller crypto exchanges such as Kraken, Bybit and Bitget are finally getting their time in the spotlight after their more dominant rival FTX collapsed last year, according to findings in a new report from blockchain analytics firm Nansen. &lt;br /&gt;
In the report, Nansen said the landscape for centralized exchanges (CEXs) has changed after the FTX collapse, with most exchanges taking a hit to their trading volumes as traders got more cautious....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nansen-report-crypto-exchanges-kraken-bybit-bitget-gain-ground-after-ftx-collapse.htm"&gt;Read More: Nansen Report: Crypto Exchanges Kraken, Bybit, and Bitget Gain Ground After FTX Collapse&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Kraken</category><category>ByBit</category><category>Bitget</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nansen-report-crypto-exchanges-kraken-bybit-bitget-gain-ground-after-ftx-collapse.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117180/313500/gaining-ground.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="225004"/></item><item><title>US FDIC Says OKCoin Made False Statements About Deposit Insurance and Demands Corrections</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-fdic-says-okcoin-made-false-statements-about-deposit-insurance-demands-corrections.htm</link><description>The US Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation sent a letter to OKCoin USA, Inc., demanding the cryptocurrency exchange take action to address false and misleading statements about its deposit insurance. &lt;br /&gt;
The FDIC sent three letters to OKCoin USA, Inc., Bodega Importadora de Pallets and Money Avenue LLC, on Thursday, making those demands, and warning that certain statements could harm consumers. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-fdic-says-okcoin-made-false-statements-about-deposit-insurance-demands-corrections.htm"&gt;Read More: US FDIC Says OKCoin Made False Statements About Deposit Insurance and Demands Corrections&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FDIC</category><category>OKCoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-fdic-says-okcoin-made-false-statements-about-deposit-insurance-demands-corrections.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117181/313503/adobestock-333531053-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="572533"/></item><item><title>Is the US's Crypto Crackdown a Blessing in Disguise for Other Nations?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uss-crypto-crackdown-blessing-disguise-for-other-nations.htm</link><description>The regulatory crackdown on crypto in the US could prove to be just what is needed for the industry to thrive elsewhere, a recent Wall Street Journal article has indicated. &lt;br /&gt;
But according to the article, which took a rather hostile tone towards crypto, the industry’s move to greener pastures overseas is not something that should be celebrated....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uss-crypto-crackdown-blessing-disguise-for-other-nations.htm"&gt;Read More: Is the US's Crypto Crackdown a Blessing in Disguise for Other Nations?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uss-crypto-crackdown-blessing-disguise-for-other-nations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117152/313451/sec.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="98216"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction As BlackRock Files for Spot Bitcoin ETF – Can BTC Hit $100,000 if It Is Approved?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrock-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-can-btc-hit-100000-if-it-approved.htm</link><description>As BlackRock, one of the world's largest asset management companies, files for a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF), speculation arises about the potential impact on Bitcoin's price.  &lt;br /&gt;
The anticipation of regulatory authorities' approval for such an ETF has led to discussions among investors and analysts regarding the possibility of Bitcoin reaching the significant milestone of $100,000. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrock-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-can-btc-hit-100000-if-it-approved.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction As BlackRock Files for Spot Bitcoin ETF – Can BTC Hit $100,000 if It Is Approved?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-blackrock-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-can-btc-hit-100000-if-it-approved.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117162/313470/16-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="483761"/></item><item><title>Tether Counted Securities Issued by Chinese Firms Among Its Reserves: Bloomberg News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-counted-securities-issued-by-chinese-companies-among-its-reserves-bloomberg-news.htm</link><description>Tether Holdings Ltd. at one point counted securities issued by Chinese companies among the reserves backing its USDT stablecoin, according to Bloomberg News.  &lt;br /&gt;
Tether at a point in time held securities issued by state-owned Chinese companies including Industrial &amp; Commercial Bank of China Ltd., China Construction Bank Corp. and Agricultural Bank of China Ltd, according to documents Bloomberg obtained from the New York State Attorney General’s office. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-counted-securities-issued-by-chinese-companies-among-its-reserves-bloomberg-news.htm"&gt;Read More: Tether Counted Securities Issued by Chinese Firms Among Its Reserves: Bloomberg News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Tether</category><category>New York Attorney General</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-counted-securities-issued-by-chinese-companies-among-its-reserves-bloomberg-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117178/313495/adobestock-474455787-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="497258"/></item><item><title>Confirmed: $10 Trillion Asset Manager BlackRock Takes Leap into Crypto, Files for Spot Bitcoin ETF with SEC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/confirmed-10-trillion-asset-manager-blackrock-takes-leap-into-crypto-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-sec.htm</link><description>Investment giant BlackRock has filed for a spot bitcoin ETF, a product that is yet to get the green light from the Securities and Exchange Commission. &lt;br /&gt;
On Thursday, the firm filed an application with the SEC to launch the iShares Bitcoin Trust, which is intended to allow investors to get direct exposure to the flagship cryptocurrency in a secure way. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/confirmed-10-trillion-asset-manager-blackrock-takes-leap-into-crypto-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-sec.htm"&gt;Read More: Confirmed: $10 Trillion Asset Manager BlackRock Takes Leap into Crypto, Files for Spot Bitcoin ETF with SEC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>Bitcoin ETF</category><category>ETF</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/confirmed-10-trillion-asset-manager-blackrock-takes-leap-into-crypto-files-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-with-sec.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117173/313482/a08fe9ae12.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99613"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Mark Cuban Criticizes SEC for Throwing Crypto Startups 'Under the Bus'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-criticizes-sec-for-throwing-crypto-startups-under-bus.htm</link><description>Billionaire tech investor and Shark Tank star Mark Cuban called out the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) earlier this week for throwing crypto startups “under the bus” with its approach to regulating the blockchain industry. &lt;br /&gt;
His comments were part of a lengthy debate with former SEC official John Reed Stark – a crypto skeptic who disagrees with the “number one talking point of crypto-enthusiasts” about a “lack of regulatory clarity in the cryptoverse.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-criticizes-sec-for-throwing-crypto-startups-under-bus.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Mark Cuban Criticizes SEC for Throwing Crypto Startups 'Under the Bus'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-criticizes-sec-for-throwing-crypto-startups-under-bus.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117167/313472/adobestock-399339731-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="176654"/></item><item><title>FTX Founder Sam Bankman Fried's Attempt to Dismiss Charges Stumbles in Court</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-frieds-attempt-dismiss-charges-stumbles-court.htm</link><description>Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the founder and former CEO of the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, made an effort to have several charges against him dismissed in court.  &lt;br /&gt;
Although the defense team's arguments faced skepticism from the US federal judge in New York, the judge did agree to divide the charges. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the judge’s decision, the government will treat some of the charges against Bankman-Fried as part of a different criminal trial. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-frieds-attempt-dismiss-charges-stumbles-court.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Founder Sam Bankman Fried's Attempt to Dismiss Charges Stumbles in Court&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-frieds-attempt-dismiss-charges-stumbles-court.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117132/313407/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-f.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="123287"/></item><item><title>NFT Artwork Seized From Three Arrows Capital Fetches $10.9 Million in Sotheby's Auction</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-artwork-seized-from-three-arrows-capital-fetches-109-million-sothebys-auction.htm</link><description>Recent information disclosed by Sotheby's auction house reveals that the digital collectibles owned by Three Arrows Capital (3AC) were sold for a total of $10.9 million in a New York auction held on June 15. &lt;br /&gt;
In the aftermath of Luna and TerraUSD cryptocurrencies collapsing, 3AC was the first major crypto firm to file for bankruptcy in 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-artwork-seized-from-three-arrows-capital-fetches-109-million-sothebys-auction.htm"&gt;Read More: NFT Artwork Seized From Three Arrows Capital Fetches $10.9 Million in Sotheby's Auction&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>3AC</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>Sotheby's</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nft-artwork-seized-from-three-arrows-capital-fetches-109-million-sothebys-auction.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117134/313448/nft.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="56010"/></item><item><title>Binance Is Being Investigated by French Authorities: Bloomberg News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-being-investigated-by-french-authorities-bloomberg-news.htm</link><description>Binance is under investigation by French authorities for “acts of aggravated money laundering,” an official for the Paris public prosecutor’s office told Bloomberg.  &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange is also being investigated for the “alleged illegal provision of digital asset services, the official said. &lt;br /&gt;
A Binance spokesperson said the exchange had an onsite visit by French authorities last week, according to Bloomberg....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-being-investigated-by-french-authorities-bloomberg-news.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Is Being Investigated by French Authorities: Bloomberg News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>France</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-being-investigated-by-french-authorities-bloomberg-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117156/313455/adobestock-494313732-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="247808"/></item><item><title>Three Arrows Capital Liquidators Request Contempt Sanctions for Co-Founder Kyle Davies – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-liquidators-request-contempt-sanctions-for-co-founder-kyle-davies-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>Amid the ongoing legal proceedings surrounding the collapse of Singaporean crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), the co-founder Kyle Davies is facing potential contempt of court charges.  &lt;br /&gt;
This is due to his failure to respond to a subpoena requesting information related to the firm's bankruptcy. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-liquidators-request-contempt-sanctions-for-co-founder-kyle-davies-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Three Arrows Capital Liquidators Request Contempt Sanctions for Co-Founder Kyle Davies – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>3AC</category><category>Davies</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/three-arrows-capital-liquidators-request-contempt-sanctions-for-co-founder-kyle-davies-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117124/313398/1200x-1-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="88286"/></item><item><title>Keone Hon, CEO of Monad Labs, on High Frequency Crypto Trading, L1s, L2s, and Security | Ep. 239</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/keone-hon-ceo-of-monad-labs-high-frequency-crypto-trading-l1s-l2s-security-ep-239.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Keone Hon, CEO and Co-founder of Monad Labs, talks about the relationship between HFT and crypto trading, security on the Monad blockchain, and scaling blockchain tech at the L1 level....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/keone-hon-ceo-of-monad-labs-high-frequency-crypto-trading-l1s-l2s-security-ep-239.htm"&gt;Read More: Keone Hon, CEO of Monad Labs, on High Frequency Crypto Trading, L1s, L2s, and Security | Ep. 239&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/keone-hon-ceo-of-monad-labs-high-frequency-crypto-trading-l1s-l2s-security-ep-239.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117147/313431/keone-hon-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="110278"/></item><item><title>Texas State Securities Board Takes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Firm Abra and CEO Bill Barhydt – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-state-securities-board-takes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-firm-abra-ceo-bill-barhydt-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The Texas State Securities Board has issued an emergency cease-and-desist order against crypto lender Abra, claiming that it has been insolvent since at least March 31, 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday filing, the Texas regulator unveiled enforcement actions against Abra and its founder William Barhydt for allegedly committing securities fraud as well as engaging in deception regarding the sale of investment products through its affiliates Abra Earn and Abra Boost....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-state-securities-board-takes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-firm-abra-ceo-bill-barhydt-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Texas State Securities Board Takes Enforcement Action Against Crypto Firm Abra and CEO Bill Barhydt – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Texas</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Abra</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-state-securities-board-takes-enforcement-action-against-crypto-firm-abra-ceo-bill-barhydt-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117139/313412/gavel-3577255-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="98023"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Dominance Reaches Two-Year High Amid Regulatory Challenges for Altcoins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominance-reaches-two-year-high-amid-regulatory-challenges-for-altcoins.htm</link><description>Bitcoin’s share of the overall crypto market capitalization, the so-called Bitcoin dominance, is nearing a two-year high amid a regulatory crackdown on altcoins and crypto companies in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
As of Friday at press time, the Bitcoin dominance stood at 47.8%, just below a short-lived peak from July of 2021 that reached 48.2%. &lt;br /&gt;
The steady rise in dominance seen this year comes as crypto companies have faced tougher scrutiny by regulators, particularly in the US....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominance-reaches-two-year-high-amid-regulatory-challenges-for-altcoins.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Dominance Reaches Two-Year High Amid Regulatory Challenges for Altcoins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dominance-reaches-two-year-high-amid-regulatory-challenges-for-altcoins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117122/313397/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="152810"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Founder Do Kwon to Stay in Custody Amid South Korea's Extradition Request</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-founder-do-kwon-stay-custody-amid-south-koreas-extradition-request.htm</link><description>Do Kwon, the founder of failed blockchain project Terra, could stay in custody for up to six months while Montenegro's courts consider an extradition request from South Korea. &lt;br /&gt;
On Thursday, a Montenegro court extended Kwon's stay in custody for an additional six months as he awaits trial for possible extradition, according to a report by Radio Free Europe....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-founder-do-kwon-stay-custody-amid-south-koreas-extradition-request.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Founder Do Kwon to Stay in Custody Amid South Korea's Extradition Request&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Do Kwon</category><category>Terra</category><category>Luna</category><category>UST</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-founder-do-kwon-stay-custody-amid-south-koreas-extradition-request.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117115/313376/dok3-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="55740"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC's Struggle to Break Through $25,600 and Key Factors Affecting its Future</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btcs-struggle-break-through-25600-key-factors-affecting-its-future.htm</link><description>Bitcoin is finally showing signs of recovery, but it continues to face challenges in breaking through the $25,600 level.   &lt;br /&gt;
In the midst of this struggle, several noteworthy factors have emerged that have impacted Bitcoin's journey.  &lt;br /&gt;
MicroStrategy's CEO, Michael Saylor, envisions a future where Bitcoin reigns supreme, despite increased regulatory scrutiny in the United States. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btcs-struggle-break-through-25600-key-factors-affecting-its-future.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC's Struggle to Break Through $25,600 and Key Factors Affecting its Future&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btcs-struggle-break-through-25600-key-factors-affecting-its-future.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117085/313346/16-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="527008"/></item><item><title>Chinese Banks Roll Out More Digital Yuan Wealth Management Options</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-roll-out-more-digital-yuan-wealth-management-options.htm</link><description>Chinese banks will let their customers pay for more wealth management products using the digital yuan, as the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) continues to branch out. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the Chinese media outlet Financial Report Network (via Stockstar), the state-owned China Construction Bank (CCB) has teamed up with China International Capital Corporation and the securities firms Orient Securities and Guotai Junan Securities....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-roll-out-more-digital-yuan-wealth-management-options.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Banks Roll Out More Digital Yuan Wealth Management Options&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-banks-roll-out-more-digital-yuan-wealth-management-options.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/117061/313292/adobestock-446449413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="377848"/></item></channel></rss>
