<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>PayPal USD Fans Token is the Latest Crypto to Blast Up 20,000% Overnight and Crypto Experts Say This Lesser Known Crypto is Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-usd-fans-token-latest-crypto-blast-up-20000-overnight-crypto-experts-say-lesser-known-crypto-next.htm</link><description>In a slapstick shot at PayPal's recent announcement of a new stablecoin, PYUSDF has become the latest DEX launched meme token to undertake a sensational overnight rally. &lt;br /&gt;
The spin-off coin is a tongue-in-cheek take on PayPal's new stablecoin offering, which sent waves through markets, initially on its 1:1 cash reserve but later due to a freeze function found in the smart contract....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-usd-fans-token-latest-crypto-blast-up-20000-overnight-crypto-experts-say-lesser-known-crypto-next.htm"&gt;Read More: PayPal USD Fans Token is the Latest Crypto to Blast Up 20,000% Overnight and Crypto Experts Say This Lesser Known Crypto is Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-usd-fans-token-latest-crypto-blast-up-20000-overnight-crypto-experts-say-lesser-known-crypto-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122175/323301/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="111855"/></item><item><title>Moscow Metro to Join Russia’s Digital Ruble Trial – CBDC Gathering Pace</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/moscow-metro-join-russias-digital-ruble-trial-cbdc-gathering-pace.htm</link><description>The Russian Central Bank will pilot its digital ruble on Moscow’s metro system as the nation’s CBDC project begins to gather pace. &lt;br /&gt;
The Central Bank earlier this week suggested that the pilot – which officially begins on August 15 – would center around smaller retailers located in 11 unnamed Russian cities. &lt;br /&gt;
But the bank appears keen to fast-track the launch of its token, and has now teamed up with the capital’s famous metro system....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/moscow-metro-join-russias-digital-ruble-trial-cbdc-gathering-pace.htm"&gt;Read More: Moscow Metro to Join Russia’s Digital Ruble Trial – CBDC Gathering Pace&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/moscow-metro-join-russias-digital-ruble-trial-cbdc-gathering-pace.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122138/323211/adobestock-67481549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="904379"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Navigating Moody's Rating Cut and Banking Crisis</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-navigating-moodys-rating-cut-banking-crisis.htm</link><description>The BTC/USD pair is currently experiencing a decline of nearly 0.50%, trading at $29,597 as it braces for the impact of the upcoming US Consumer Price Index (CPI) release.  &lt;br /&gt;
Amidst this market backdrop, Bitcoin continues to demonstrate its resilience despite challenges such as Moody's rating cut and a banking crisis....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-navigating-moodys-rating-cut-banking-crisis.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Navigating Moody's Rating Cut and Banking Crisis&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-navigating-moodys-rating-cut-banking-crisis.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122150/323227/11-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="532513"/></item><item><title>Genesis Report: Crypto Derivatives Emerge as the Next Key Growth Driver in 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-report-crypto-derivatives-emerge-as-next-key-growth-driver-2023.htm</link><description>According to the Q2 2023 report from Genesis Trading, crypto derivatives is set to experience substantial expansion, fueled by a massive decrease in spot market liquidity and a notable trend towards utilizing derivative instruments. &lt;br /&gt;
"With spot market liquidity suffering and spot order book depth chronically flagging, it has become increasingly apparent that a significant portion of the future growth of crypto volumes will be in derivatives," Genesis said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-report-crypto-derivatives-emerge-as-next-key-growth-driver-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Genesis Report: Crypto Derivatives Emerge as the Next Key Growth Driver in 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Genesis Global Trading</category><category>Report</category><category>Bitcoin derivative</category><category>Crypto Derivatives</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-report-crypto-derivatives-emerge-as-next-key-growth-driver-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122161/323230/getpaidstock-com-64d59d69.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="158144"/></item><item><title>Mexico ‘Leads LATAM in Travel Rule Adoption’ as ‘Argentina Lags Behind’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mexico-leads-latam-travel-rule-adoption-as-argentina-lags-behind.htm</link><description>Mexico is “leading the way” in Latin America’s Travel Rule adoption drive, a study has found – with Argentina “lagging behind.” &lt;br /&gt;
The claims were made by the Latin American Financial Action Task Force (known locally as GAFILAT), an intergovernmental organization comprising 18 Latin American countries. &lt;br /&gt;
GAFILAT is affiliated with the Financial Action Task Force (FATF), the global anti-money laundering watchdog that created the Travel Rule....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mexico-leads-latam-travel-rule-adoption-as-argentina-lags-behind.htm"&gt;Read More: Mexico ‘Leads LATAM in Travel Rule Adoption’ as ‘Argentina Lags Behind’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Mexico</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mexico-leads-latam-travel-rule-adoption-as-argentina-lags-behind.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122002/322932/adobestock-527102651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="482874"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 August – Aptos, Rocket Pool, Maker</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-august-aptos-rocket-pool-maker.htm</link><description>U.S. inflation metrics saw a notable rise recently, with the Consumer Price Index (CPI) experiencing a 3.2% increase over the past year leading up to July. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite the financial development indicated by this data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) on Thursday, the performance of Bitcoin and Ethereum has been relatively lackluster, with both showing a modest decline of 0.27% and 0.22%, respectively. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-august-aptos-rocket-pool-maker.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 10 August – Aptos, Rocket Pool, Maker&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Aptos</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Rocket Pool</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>Maker</category><category>Apt</category><category>Apt Price</category><category>RPL</category><category>Rpl Price</category><category>MKR</category><category>MKR price</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>YPRED</category><category>LPX</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Crypto Trading</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Web3</category><category>Crypto Wallet</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-10-august-aptos-rocket-pool-maker.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122145/323221/bctbn-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="312169"/></item><item><title>SEC’s Crypto Compliance by Enforcement Push Continues as Bittrex Hit With $24 Million Fine</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/secs-crypto-compliance-by-enforcement-push-continues-as-bittrex-hit-with-24-million-fine.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s push to force the crypto industry into “regulatory compliance” via enforcement action continues, with bankrupt crypto exchange Bittrex the latest to fall foul of the agency. &lt;br /&gt;
Bittrex just agreed to pay a $24 million fine to the SEC, after the agency accused the exchange of operating as an unregistered securities exchange back in April....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/secs-crypto-compliance-by-enforcement-push-continues-as-bittrex-hit-with-24-million-fine.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC’s Crypto Compliance by Enforcement Push Continues as Bittrex Hit With $24 Million Fine&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bittrex</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/secs-crypto-compliance-by-enforcement-push-continues-as-bittrex-hit-with-24-million-fine.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122143/323219/sec.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6577063"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – STRONGX, M87, SHIB0.5</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-shib05.htm</link><description>Blue-chip cryptocurrency markets remain stuck within recent ranges and trading with a modestly negative bias on Thursday, despite US inflation data fuelling the crypto-positive narrative that the US Federal Reserve’s hiking cycle is over. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last changing hands close to $29,400, while Ether (ETH) was last trading just under $1,850....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-shib05.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – STRONGX, M87, SHIB0.5&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Shitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-strongx-m87-shib05.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122141/323218/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Swiss City of Lugano and Tether's Plan ₿ Summer School Achieves Second-Year Milestone</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/swiss-city-of-lugano-and-tethers-plan-summer-school-achieves-second-year-milestone.htm</link><description>From bill-splitting apps to solutions for urban parking, the Swiss City of Lugano and Tether's second annual Plan ₿ Summer School showcased the transformative potential of blockchain over the past 10 days. The event, which wrapped up yesterday, saw around 80 students from 28 countries dive deep into the blockchain and digital currencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/swiss-city-of-lugano-and-tethers-plan-summer-school-achieves-second-year-milestone.htm"&gt;Read More: Swiss City of Lugano and Tether's Plan ₿ Summer School Achieves Second-Year Milestone&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin Education</category><category>Cryptocurrency Education</category><category>Tether Summer School</category><category>Lugano Tether</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/swiss-city-of-lugano-and-tethers-plan-summer-school-achieves-second-year-milestone.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122137/323210/bitcoin-5675758-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="191090"/></item><item><title>Chimpzee Token: A Unique Way to Earn Income, Restore Rainforests, and Protect Wildlife</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chimpzee-token-unique-way-earn-income-restore-rainforests-protect-wildlife.htm</link><description>People are always looking for meaningful ways to invest their money, and these days, there's a growing trend toward investments that not only bring financial returns but also have a positive impact on the environment. The rise of green investments now fills this need, giving people the ability to make a difference while also securing their financial futures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chimpzee-token-unique-way-earn-income-restore-rainforests-protect-wildlife.htm"&gt;Read More: Chimpzee Token: A Unique Way to Earn Income, Restore Rainforests, and Protect Wildlife&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Chimpzee Token</category><category>Green Investment</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chimpzee-token-unique-way-earn-income-restore-rainforests-protect-wildlife.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122132/323206/f3hhq75w4aafvcw.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="272871"/></item><item><title>Fireblocks Uncovers 'BitForge' Vulnerabilities Posing Threat to Major MPC Wallets</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fireblocks-uncovers-bitforge-vulnerabilities-posing-threat-major-mpc-wallets.htm</link><description>Crypto infrastructure company Fireblocks has identified a set of vulnerabilities known as "BitForge" that pose a threat to popular crypto wallets that use multi-party computation (MPC) technology.  &lt;br /&gt;
These vulnerabilities were classified as "zero-day," meaning they were unknown to the developers of the affected software before Fireblocks disclosed them, the company said in a Wednesday press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fireblocks-uncovers-bitforge-vulnerabilities-posing-threat-major-mpc-wallets.htm"&gt;Read More: Fireblocks Uncovers 'BitForge' Vulnerabilities Posing Threat to Major MPC Wallets&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Fireblocks</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fireblocks-uncovers-bitforge-vulnerabilities-posing-threat-major-mpc-wallets.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122107/323151/adobestock-sergey-nivens-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="107717"/></item><item><title>Circle CEO Urges On-Shore Stablecoin Development for the Future of Finance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-urges-on-shore-stablecoin-development-for-the-future-of-finance.htm</link><description>Resharing Circle's video ad tweet, Jeremy Allaire, the CEO of Circle, emphasized the critical need to accelerate the progress of the digital dollar and Stablecoin development. His message highlights that this advancement is essential for maintaining the strength of the US dollar. &lt;br /&gt;
Initially posted in July, Jeremy Allaire was featured in the two-minute video released by Circle aimed at the Congress to safeguard stablecoins and foster confidence in digital dollars....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-urges-on-shore-stablecoin-development-for-the-future-of-finance.htm"&gt;Read More: Circle CEO Urges On-Shore Stablecoin Development for the Future of Finance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Jeremy Allaire</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Circle</category><category>USDC</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/circle-ceo-urges-on-shore-stablecoin-development-for-the-future-of-finance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122129/323202/getpaidstock-com-64d51d61.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="143398"/></item><item><title>France Amends Crypto Regulatory Framework In Line With MiCA Licensing Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/france-amends-crypto-regulatory-framework-line-with-mica-licensing-rules.htm</link><description>France’s financial regulator Autorité des Marchés Financiers (AMF) has announced key amendments to its digital asset regulatory regime in light of the Market in Crypto Asset (MiCA) regulation. &lt;br /&gt;
The new amendments will come into effect from Jan 1 2024 and would affect both its General Regulation and a new registration process for Digital Asset Service Providers (DASPs)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/france-amends-crypto-regulatory-framework-line-with-mica-licensing-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: France Amends Crypto Regulatory Framework In Line With MiCA Licensing Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>France</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/france-amends-crypto-regulatory-framework-line-with-mica-licensing-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122128/323200/adobestock-216458663-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="161530"/></item><item><title>Revolutionize Your Trading Strategy with yPredict's AI-Detected Chart Patterns – $3.4 Million Raised Already</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/revolutionize-your-trading-strategy-with-ypredicts-ai-detected-chart-patterns-34-million-raised-already.htm</link><description>Trading can often seem like a perplexing puzzle, with traders scrambling to piece together crucial bits of information. With the rise of cryptocurrencies, the challenge has grown. But imagine if technology could simplify making sense of it all to see the bigger picture....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/revolutionize-your-trading-strategy-with-ypredicts-ai-detected-chart-patterns-34-million-raised-already.htm"&gt;Read More: Revolutionize Your Trading Strategy with yPredict's AI-Detected Chart Patterns – $3.4 Million Raised Already&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><category>Crypto Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/revolutionize-your-trading-strategy-with-ypredicts-ai-detected-chart-patterns-34-million-raised-already.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122109/323182/f3gmcssxsaappoc.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="150258"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Slips on SEC Appeal While Safer Alternative XRP20 Fundraising Accelerates Past $1.8m</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-slips-sec-appeal-while-safer-alternative-xrp20-fundraising-accelerates-past-18m.htm</link><description>The XRP price is slipping lower after news emerged that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is appealing the judge's decision in the XRP securities case, boosting the appeal of a safer alternative, the XRP20 coin.  &lt;br /&gt;
While the XRP price has reversed from recent near-term highs, last trading at $0.62, investors have poured more than $1.84 million into the XRP20 stake-to-earn coin as a safer option for realizing consistent strong returns due to its advantages over XRP....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-slips-sec-appeal-while-safer-alternative-xrp20-fundraising-accelerates-past-18m.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Slips on SEC Appeal While Safer Alternative XRP20 Fundraising Accelerates Past $1.8m&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-slips-sec-appeal-while-safer-alternative-xrp20-fundraising-accelerates-past-18m.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122124/323191/xrp20-coin-raises-1-84m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1050816"/></item><item><title>Ether Futures ETF Applications Spike: Unveiling the Surprising Reason</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ether-futures-etf-applications-spike-unveiling-surprising-reason.htm</link><description>Though a wave of Bitcoin (BTC) spot ETF applications have stirred excitement in the crypto market over the past two months, a lesser-known bundle of Ether (ETH) ETF applications is following closely behind it....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ether-futures-etf-applications-spike-unveiling-surprising-reason.htm"&gt;Read More: Ether Futures ETF Applications Spike: Unveiling the Surprising Reason&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ether-futures-etf-applications-spike-unveiling-surprising-reason.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122115/323175/adobestock-245958487.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161909"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: India's Central Bank Proposes AI-powered Conversational Payments System, India Wants to Utilize Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents, UK Recruiting For CBDC Academic Advisory Group</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-indias-central-bank-proposes-ai-powered-conversational-payments-system-india-wants-to-utilize-crypto-to-digitally-sign-documents-uk-recruiting-for-cbdc-academic-advisory-group.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-indias-central-bank-proposes-ai-powered-conversational-payments-system-india-wants-to-utilize-crypto-to-digitally-sign-documents-uk-recruiting-for-cbdc-academic-advisory-group.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: India's Central Bank Proposes AI-powered Conversational Payments System, India Wants to Utilize Crypto to Digitally Sign Documents, UK Recruiting For CBDC Academic Advisory Group&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>India</category><category>Payments</category><category>Adoption</category><category>CBDC</category><category>UK</category><category>Treasury</category><category>Bank of England</category><category>France</category><category>European Union</category><category>EU</category><category>MiCA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Tax</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Base</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>Gaming</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-indias-central-bank-proposes-ai-powered-conversational-payments-system-india-wants-to-utilize-crypto-to-digitally-sign-documents-uk-recruiting-for-cbdc-academic-advisory-group.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122083/323144/adobestock-galyna-andrush.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="124581"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Core Inflation Data is Announced – Can BTC Blast Past $30,000?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-core-inflation-data-announced-can-btc-blast-past-30000.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin (BTC) price is little moved in the mid-$29,000s in wake of the latest core US inflation data that has reaffirmed that price pressures continue to ease in the US economy. &lt;br /&gt;
The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) rose 0.2% MoM in July, in line with expected and unchanged from June, while the YoY metric rose 4.7%, a tad lower than the expected 4.8% and down slightly from June....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-core-inflation-data-announced-can-btc-blast-past-30000.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Core Inflation Data is Announced – Can BTC Blast Past $30,000?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Core CPI</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-core-inflation-data-announced-can-btc-blast-past-30000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122112/323162/btc-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="637851"/></item><item><title>Nigeria’s National Youth Scheme To Issue Blockchain-Based Certificates To Citizens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-national-youth-scheme-to-issue-blockchain-based-certificates-to-citizens.htm</link><description>The Nigerian government has unveiled plans to deploy blockchain technology to issue and verify all National Youth Service Scheme (NYSC) certificates. &lt;br /&gt;
At a policy gathering organized by the National Information Technology Development Agency (NITDA) to promote plans around the proposed National Blockchain Policy, it was disclosed that several policies will be implemented in the coming months in partnership with the country’s Central Bank....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-national-youth-scheme-to-issue-blockchain-based-certificates-to-citizens.htm"&gt;Read More: Nigeria’s National Youth Scheme To Issue Blockchain-Based Certificates To Citizens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Nigeria</category><category>NYSC</category><category>CBN</category><category>E-Naira</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nigerias-national-youth-scheme-to-issue-blockchain-based-certificates-to-citizens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122111/323159/adobestock-faraz-1-media-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103458"/></item><item><title>Bank of England Forms Digital Pound Advisory Group to Shape CBDC Design</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-england-forms-digital-pound-advisory-group-shape-cbdc-design-1.htm</link><description>Announced on the Bank's Website on Wednesday, the Bank of England (BoE) has established a digital pound advisory group named the CBDC Academic Advisory Group (AAG) and is actively seeking specialists to join this group as the nation enters the CBDC design phase. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-england-forms-digital-pound-advisory-group-shape-cbdc-design-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of England Forms Digital Pound Advisory Group to Shape CBDC Design&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Digital Pound</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Bank of England</category><category>HM Treasury</category><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 13:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-england-forms-digital-pound-advisory-group-shape-cbdc-design-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122106/323152/adobestock-94685515-media.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="355507"/></item></channel></rss>
