<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:33:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Which Low Market Cap Crypto Might Have Upside Potential: Why Big Eyes Coin, RenQ Finance Failed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/which-low-market-cap-crypto-might-have-upside-potential-why-big-eyes-coin-renq-finance-failed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=258023</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thuglife_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/thuglife_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[One issue facing many new cryptocurrency projects in 2023 is that they set a large hard cap target for their presale fundraising stage, then launched with a high market capitalization by the time of their IEO or IDO. Crypto presales that have several price stages of incentivizing early buyers with a discount also add to [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One issue facing many new cryptocurrency projects in 2023 is that they set a large hard cap target for their presale fundraising stage, then launched with a high market capitalization by the time of their IEO or IDO.</p>
<p>Crypto presales that have several price stages of incentivizing early buyers with a discount also add to that problem &#8211; inflating the market cap and FDV further and causing the common ‘ICO dump’ chart pattern in which early investors dump their coins on the market to take profit.</p>
<p>Analysts predict one upcoming low market cap crypto with huge potential upside is <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life Token</a> (THUG), based on it having just one price stage throughout its presale &#8211; $0.0007 &#8211; and a low hard cap of $2,058,000.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Thug Life Presale</a></p>
<h2>Big Eyes Price Prediction</h2>
<p>The Big Eyes crypto presale was one of the largest public token presales of 2023, initially setting a hard cap of 51.2 million USDT, and taking almost a year from its August 2022 launch to raise close to that, with various delays and other red flags.</p>
<p>The Big Eyes presale also set fifteen price stages, with a 600% increase built in, from $0.0001 to $0.0006, which incentivized early-stage investors to want to secure that profit. Its Uniswap listing in fact took place at a considerably lower price than the final presale stage price, also angering some investors.</p>
<p>However, even if it had been listed at $0.0006, with its 200 billion total supply that would mean a fully diluted market cap valuation (FDV) of $0.0006 x 200 billion = $120 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258026" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="758" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32-300x131.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-32-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/view/memes/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap</a>, Big Eyes token would have then ranked as the 7th largest meme coin on the market instantly, with only Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, Pepe, FLOKI, Baby Doge Coin, and Bone ShibaSwap having a higher market capitalization &#8211; all of which launched much lower in their early development, before building up to a higher valuation.</p>
<p>Even if it had then held that market cap without a sell-off from early buyers looking to take profit, it would have limited upside potential &#8211; a less than 10x move would break the $1 billion mark, which very few meme coins are capable of, Pepe being one recent exception &#8211; and even Pepe has now retraced to a $600 million market cap.</p>
<p>Big Eyes coin currently has a market of $2 million and may struggle to recover to the upside and regain investor confidence after the issues surrounding its launch.</p>
<h2>RenQ Finance Price Prediction</h2>
<p>The RenQ Finance price chart is similar to that of the Big Eyes token &#8211; a post-ICO sell-off with few bounces. The RENQ market cap is currently $15 million, lower than its presale hard cap of $19.3 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258025" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="758" height="332" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30-300x131.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-30-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>The RenQ Finance presale had eight price stages, with the RENQ token price varying from $0.02 &#8211; $0.055, a 275% difference.</p>
<p>Having faced similar issues to Big Eyes coin over its launch and roadmap, the RenQ price forecast in the short term doesn’t appear bullish.</p>
<h2>Upside Potential of Low Market Cap Crypto Projects</h2>
<p>Many new meme coins that pump tend to have their blow-off top around the $100 million market cap level, even if they do have a successful launch and initial rally without investors immediately selling their tokens.</p>
<p>For that reason, it’s optimal to find low market cap cryptocurrencies &#8211; one launching at a $1 million market cap for example, will return a 100x ROI if reaching the psychological resistance level of $100 million.</p>
<p>A new coin launching at $2 million will return a 50x ROI, one launching at $20 million return only a 5x ROI, and so on. If early investors are also already in profit based on different presale stages, they make take profit earlier than expected.</p>
<h2>Thug Life Token Presale</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life presale</a> has a set a level playing field with just one presale price stage, and has a low hard cap of $2.058 million.</p>
<p>70% of the total token supply of 4.2 billion $THUG is also available to buy during the presale, with the liquidity pool locked for three months after launch.</p>
<p>15% of the supply is allocated to marketing, and 15% to community rewards.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-258024" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="758" height="381" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25.jpg 758w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25-300x151.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-25-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px" /></a></p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">thuglifetoken.com</a> website describes the meme coin project as a ‘second chance for those who have been played, influenced and used as a cash-out, leaving held tokens valueless in a blink of an eye.’</p>
<p>The project aims to build a movement fuelled by the ‘shared struggle of hustling this web3 world, turning the bitter landscape of dumped presales into a prosperous place’ &#8211; its community focus centers around addressing the issues faced by the crypto ICOs of this year.</p>
<p>Its liquidity pool is set to be locked by Team Finance, and its community rewards program will take the form of airdrops once $THUG is listed on its first DEX, Uniswap.</p>
<p>$THUG can be invested in prior to its listing at one single price &#8211; $0.0007 &#8211; using a MetaMask wallet and swapping ETH or USDT for $THUG.</p>
<p>At the time of writing, $150,000 has been raised in the 48 hours since the Thug Life presale’s launch, showing the high level of interest in its concept and tokenomics that aim to offer investors a higher potential ROI than other 2023 crypto presales.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Visit Thug Life Presale</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/which-low-market-cap-crypto-might-have-upside-potential-why-big-eyes-coin-renq-finance-failed/" rel="nofollow">Which Low Market Cap Crypto Might Have Upside Potential: Why Big Eyes Coin, RenQ Finance Failed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Much Money Does it Take to ‘Moon’ Bitcoin? Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-money-does-it-take-to-moon-bitcoin-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 17:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257869</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/bitcoin_moon_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/bitcoin_moon_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoiners have many things to be bullish about in the next few months, but analysts think the ‘halving’ may not be one of them.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The resurgence of institutional interest in Bitcoin this month has investors and analysts pondering just how high its price could go within the next two years – especially with the ‘halving’ just around the corner.</p>
<p>Here’s what analysts have to say regarding Bitcoin’s price cycles and what kind of money it would take to send it to the moon.</p>
<h2>Institutional Involvement</h2>
<p>Throughout June, a number of high net-worth asset managers, including BlackRock and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">Fidelity</a>, filed applications to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States.</p>
<p>Major banks and investment managers, including BNY Melon, Invesco, Morgan Stanley, and others, have already dabbled in launching Bitcoin-related products, such as OTC trading or custody services.</p>
<p>When taking a look at some of the largest financial companies involved in the space already, their total assets under management come out to at least $27 trillion, according to Meltem Demirors – Chief Strategy Officer of CoinShares.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ last week&#8217;s <a href="https://twitter.com/BlackRock?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@BlackRock</a> spot Bitcoin ETF filing was big news!</p>
<p>but, it&#8217;s not the only story. many of the largest financial institutions in the US are actively working to provide access to Bitcoin and more.</p>
<p>a quick glance &#8211; $27 trillion of client assets here! <a href="https://t.co/azmHZmUL2a" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/azmHZmUL2a</a></p>
<p>— Meltem Demirors (@Melt_Dem) <a href="https://twitter.com/Melt_Dem/status/1673362112653975554?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 26, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Theoretically, Bitcoin’s price could multiply by several times if these firms enter the market with just a small fraction of their wealth – especially given the market’s current liquidity levels.</p>
<p>In an email to <em>CryptoPotato</em>, James Check – Lead On-chain analyst at Glassnode – explained that roughly 450,000 BTC (~$13.5 billion) are “highly active in spot markets and predominantly participate in price discovery.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“It is extremely difficult to measure a dollar in == market move, but this at least allows us to provide a range / bound the problem,” he said.</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2021, ARK Invest’s Cathie Wood – whose firm is also trying to launch a Bitcoin ETF – predicted that Bitcoin could reach $500,000 if institutional investors allocate 5% of their portfolios to the asset.</p>
<h2>HODLer Behaviour</h2>
<p>As Bitcoin’s price rises, it&#8217;s possible that prior investors choose to take profits by selling their assets, thus absorbing the bullish impact of any liquidity entering the market.</p>
<p>However, many market intelligence firms, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-hodlers-increase-at-a-record-pace-santiment/" data-wpel-link="internal">Santiment</a> and Glassnode, have noted an “ongoing transfer of wealth from investors with high time preferences towards HODLers” in recent months. Meanwhile, Bitcoin on exchanges is also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-bitcoins-surge-above-30k-btc-on-exchanges-lowest-since-december-2017/" data-wpel-link="internal">lower than ever</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257870" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257870" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1-.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257870 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1024x590.png" alt="" width="1024" height="590" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1024x590.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--300x173.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--768x443.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--1536x885.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1--50x29.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/woc-26-03-1-.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257870" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Long and Short Term Holder Supply. Source: Glassnode</figcaption></figure>
<p>CryptoQuant data from this month appears to back this up, showing that long-term holders have largely reduced their selling activity over the past six months. “This change in LTH behavior may signal the beginning of a new bull cycle,” wrote analyst Axel Adler Jr in a <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/648eff282ec8802caad37154-The-Secret-Signal-of-Bitcoins-Rise-Why-are-LTH-Holding-Their-Assets" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post</a>.</p>
<p>Investors have noted in the past that Bitcoiners have remarkable conviction, in general, to keep their holdings on hand &#8211; regardless of price. Paul Tudor Jones, for example, added that 86% of Bitcoin holders did not sell their assets when their price dropped from $17,000 to $3,000 between 2017 and 2018. <a href="https://thehustle.co/stanley-druckenmiller-q-and-a-trung-phanin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Stanley Druckenmiller</a> was also bullish on the asset last month due to its holders being “religious zealots.”</p>
<h2>What About The Halving?</h2>
<p>Ironically, some analysts don’t think the halving – the event of Bitcoin’s inflation rate falling by 50% every four years – may have a strong impact on the market after its arrival in April 2024.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s historic bull runs in 2013, 2017, and 2021 have all followed one year after a halving. While the connection may seem self-evident, a report from Coinbase this month <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/institutional/research-insights/research/monthly-outlook/bitcoin-halvings-and-liquidity-problem-june-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">argues</a> that each cycle may not have been so connected to the halving as much as other factors.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Outside of the third halving, evidence that these halving events supported bitcoin price action is not entirely clear cut,” it states. 2013 and 2020 were coupled with central banks conducting major rounds of quantitative easing, while 2016 was when the Bank of England resumed its bond-buying program in response to Brexit.</p></blockquote>
<p>CryptoQuant’s Head of Marketing backs this more skeptical view. “I also agree with the fact that the halving impact on the Bitcoin price is decreasing as the new supply limit decreases significantly,” he told <em>CryptoPotato</em> via DM.</p>
<p>However, Chung noted other factors are worth being bullish about – such as institutional involvement after BlackRock’s ETF filing. “You can see that the fund holding volume spiked after the BlackRock announcement,” he said.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257871" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257871" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257871 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-1024x645.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="645" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29-50x31.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/photo_2023-06-29_19-49-29.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257871" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Fund Holdings. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>China’s growing involvement in crypto is also likely to increase liquidity and demand. Hong Kong is offering licenses to exchanges, such firms are giving banking access to the industry, and retail traders in the region are being allowed to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hsbc-hong-kong-lets-clients-trade-btc-and-eth-etfs-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">trade major crypto assets</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-money-does-it-take-to-moon-bitcoin-analysis/" rel="nofollow">How Much Money Does it Take to ‘Moon’ Bitcoin? Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner of Manchester City in Expansion of Partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257989</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MANCITY_X_OKX_HERO_ENDFRAME_16x9_16881336124JGrE7RzuK.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/MANCITY_X_OKX_HERO_ENDFRAME_16x9_16881336124JGrE7RzuK.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023] Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club’s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement. As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Manchester, UK, June 30th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Manchester City and OKX, one of the leading crypto exchanges by trading volume and a leading Web3 technology company, today announced OKX as the Club’s Official Sleeve Partner in a new multi-year agreement.</p>
<p>As part of the expanded deal, the OKX brand will feature on the left sleeve of both the men’s and women’s first-team playing kits and will retain its position on the left sleeve of the first-team training kits, in addition to appearing across further digital and physical club assets.</p>
<p>OKX&#8217;s partnership with Manchester City began in March 2022, first expanding in July 2022 to become the Club’s Official Training Kit Partner for the 2022/23 season. To date, the partnership has helped introduce the brand to millions of football fans around the world through innovative Web3 experiences like the <a href="https://www.okx.com/activities/okxcollectivemetaverse" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">OKX Collective</a>, through which fans can get up close and personal with Manchester City players and OKX Ambassadors such as Jack Grealish and Alex Greenwood.</p>
<p>The partnership expansion was unveiled at an exclusive reveal at the Etihad Stadium featuring City Football Group Chief Executive Officer Ferran Soriano and OKX Global Chief Marketing Officer Haider Rafique. As part of the event, the sleeve was unveiled in a &#8216;virtual reveal&#8217; with a hero video featuring player avatars. Manchester City legend Gaël Clichy was also in attendance for a media Q&amp;A.</p>
<p>In a session moderated by Manchester City presenter <a href="https://www.mancity.com/wnrh/natalie-pike" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Natalie Pike</a>, Rafique and Soriano spoke about OKX&#8217;s vision of reaching City fans around the world through the partnership. They also discussed the role Web3 technology can play in fan engagement, especially when it comes to designing engaging, immersive experiences for fans.</p>
<blockquote><p><strong>Ferran Soriano, Chief Executive Officer at City Football Group, said:</strong> &#8220;We are very proud to have OKX represented on the sleeve of the Manchester City shirt. Both OKX and Manchester City are leading companies driven by a passion for innovation. We have already seen great Web3 experiences designed by OKX for Manchester City’s global fan base and there will be many more to come. This is a very exciting partnership.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><strong>Haider Rafique, CMO at OKX, said:</strong> &#8220;The journey with the Man City team has been incredible. Manchester City was our first official global brand partnership and in just a year and a half we have come a long way. We always intended to integrate with the sport and help the Club lead on leaning into Web3. Fast forward fifteen months, we now have a metaverse, an NFT initiative and a number of other new projects that we are excited about.</p></blockquote>
<p>The sleeve partnership brings us closer to City fans across the globe, and we look forward to collaborating to create unique, exciting and innovative engagements through Web3 technology. As the Club&#8217;s Official Cryptocurrency Exchange Partner, fans can expect amazing things every time they interact with OKX.&#8221;</p>
<h2>About OKX</h2>
<p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of trading and Web3. Its leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p>
<p>OKX partners with a number of the world’s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p>
<p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Proof of Reserves</a> on a monthly basis.</p>
<p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit:<a href="http://okx.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> okx.com</a></p>
<h2 class="ql-align-justify">About Manchester City Football Club</h2>
<p>Manchester City FC is an English Premier League club initially founded in 1880 as St Mark’s West Gorton. It officially became Manchester City FC in 1894 and has since then gone onto win the UEFA Champions League, European Cup Winners’ Cup, nine League Championship titles, seven FA Cups, and eight League Cups. Manchester City FC is one of 13 clubs comprising the City Football Group.</p>
<p>Under manager Pep Guardiola, one of the most highly-decorated managers in world football, the Club plays its domestic and UEFA Champions League home fixtures at the Etihad Stadium, a spectacular 53,500-seat arena that City has called home since 2003. Today, the stadium sits on the wider Etihad Campus, which also encompasses the City Football Academy, a state-of-the-art performance training and youth development facility located in the heart of East Manchester. Featuring a 7,000-capacity Academy Stadium, the City Football Academy is also where Manchester City Women’s Football Club and the Elite Development Squad train on a daily basis and play their competitive home games.</p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p><em>OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AS THE VALUE OF YOUR ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-named-official-sleeve-partner-of-manchester-city-in-expansion-of-partnership/" rel="nofollow">OKX Named Official Sleeve Partner of Manchester City in Expansion of Partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Buys More BTC but Bitcoin Wobbles Around $30K Amid SEC-ETF Rejection Rumors: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-but-bitcoin-wobbles-around-30k-amid-sec-etf-rejection-rumors-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 15:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257987</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BCH is the undesputed top performer within the top 100 crypto assets for the past week, following a triple-digit price surge.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lot can change in the cryptocurrency industry within a week, and the waves indeed fluctuated in the past seven days. The market rejoiced recently as several multinational financial giants filed for a Bitcoin Spot ETF, but the tides could be turning now, according to a WSJ report from Friday.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s unpack.</p>
<p>BlackRock shook the crypto market two weeks ago when it filed an application to release a BTC Spot ETF in the States, which would make it the first such product greenlighted by the SEC.</p>
<p>Being the world&#8217;s largest asset manager, its actions had immediate consequences as ARK Invest <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-woods-ark-amends-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-to-copy-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">changed</a> its own application to copy that of BlackRock, while Fidelity reapplied less than a week later.</p>
<p>That also impacted the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price trajectory as BTC skyrocketed from $26,500 last week to roughly $31,000 earlier today. However, a Wall Street Journal report emerged on Friday claiming that the SEC found the recent filings &#8220;inadequate,&#8221; which prompted speculation that they could be rejected, similar to all previous ones.</p>
<p>BTC reacted immediately with a sharp price dump that drove it south by $1,500. As a result, the asset charted a 10-day low of $29,500 (on Bitstamp). It managed to bounce off rather quickly and reclaimed some ground. Nevertheless, it&#8217;s still uncertain at around $30,000.</p>
<p>This price decline erased all of BTC&#8217;s weekly gains. In comparison, numerous altcoins have charted notable 7-day price increases, such as ETC (15%), SOL (15%), Aave (18%), XLM (24%), and Bitcoin SV (36%).</p>
<p>The one that stands out the most, though, is Bitcoin Cash. The BTC hard fork has soared by over 110% on a weekly scale and earlier today charted a 14-month high above $320 amid <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/" data-wpel-link="internal">massive trading volumes</a> on smaller markets, such as the South Korean one.</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-49046" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg" alt="Bitcoin ETF" width="1000" height="668" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-768x513.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/Depositphotos_264281122_s-2019-min-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,214B | 24H Vol: $67B | BTC Dominance: 48.3%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $30,082 (+0.3%) | ETH: $1,848 (-1.0%) | BNB: $234 (-2.7%)</p>
<h2>This Week’s Crypto Headlines You Can’t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Dumps Below $30K as SEC Warns That Recent BTC Spot ETF Filings Are ‘Inadequate’ (WSJ)</strong>. As mentioned above, the WSJ <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" data-wpel-link="internal">cited</a> people familiar with the matter who claimed that the SEC believes the most recent BTC Spot ETF filings could have been &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Fidelity Refiles Bitcoin Spot ETF Application After BlackRock</strong>. But before that, Fidelity Digital Assets <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">followed</a> BlackRock&#8217;s example and reapplied for a Bitcoin Spot ETF less than a week after the world&#8217;s largest asset manager.</p>
<p><strong>FTT Explodes 35% on FTX Revival Idea</strong>. Just several months after the once-prominent crypto exchange filed for bankruptcy, the new CEO hinted that FTX could be revived at some point. As a result, the native token <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftt-explodes-35-on-ftx-revival-idea/" data-wpel-link="internal">jumped</a> to a 2-month high.</p>
<p><strong>MicroStrategy Buys 12,333 BTC for $350 Million at $28K Per Bitcoin</strong>. Perhaps fueled by BlackRock&#8217;s filing, the largest corporate holder of BTC decided to double down by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-12333-btc-for-350-million-at-28k-per-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">allocating</a> another $350 million and accumulating 12,333 BTC.</p>
<p><strong>Robinhood Cuts Staff Again as Trading Volume and Engagement Dwindle</strong>. The Vlad Tenev-spearheaded trading company continues to struggle as it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-cuts-staff-again-as-trading-volume-and-engagement-dwindle/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the lay-off of another 150 employees (7%). This is the second round of cut-offs for the Wall Street-traded firm in less than a year.</p>
<p><strong>Swiss Prosecutors Freeze $26M Worth of Do Kwon Assets Following his Prison Sentence (Report)</strong>. After being sentenced to four months in prison in Montenegro, Kwon&#8217;s situation has reportedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-prosecutors-freeze-26m-worth-of-do-kwon-assets-following-his-prison-sentence-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">worsened</a> as $26 million worth of his assets were frozen</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-but-bitcoin-wobbles-around-30k-amid-sec-etf-rejection-rumors-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Buys More BTC but Bitcoin Wobbles Around $30K Amid SEC-ETF Rejection Rumors: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Dumps Below $30K as SEC Warns That Recent BTC Spot ETF Filings Are &#8216;Inadequate&#8217; (WSJ)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257982</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shortly after the news broke, BTC dropped to a 10-day low under $30,000.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission has reportedly issued a warning that the recent Bitcoin Spot ETF filings by financial giants, such as Fidelity and BlackRock, could lack comprehensive details.</p>
<p>The agency has a long history of rejecting such products in the States, and its current war on crypto is likely not helping.</p>
<ul>
<li>BlackRock made the headlines a few weeks ago when it filed to launch a Bitcoin Spot ETF in the States, which, if approved, would be the first such product in the country.</li>
<li>The company&#8217;s record is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">quite spectacular</a>, with only one proposed ETF rejected by the SEC almost a decade ago.</li>
<li>The move was regarded as a hugely positive development for the industry that could open the doors for others as well, and Fidelity <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fidelity-refiles-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-after-blackrock/" data-wpel-link="internal">reapplied</a> shortly after.</li>
<li>However, a new report by the Wall Street Journal, citing people familiar with the matter, claims that the US securities regulator is not keen on approving either of these applications.</li>
<li><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/sec-says-spot-bitcoin-etf-filings-are-inadequate-390336e8" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to the WSJ, the SEC has informed Nasdaq and CBOE that the applications filed on behalf of BlackRock and Fidelity are not &#8220;sufficiently clear and comprehensive.&#8221;</li>
<li>Given that the agency has used that justification in the past to reject multiple Bitcoin Spot ETF applications, the news was followed by a sharp price drop from BTC.</li>
<li>The cryptocurrency flirted with the $31,000 level today, but it plummeted by over a grand within an hour after the report came out to a 10-day low of under $30,000.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumps-below-30k-as-sec-warns-that-recent-btc-spot-etf-filings-are-inadequate-wsj/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Dumps Below $30K as SEC Warns That Recent BTC Spot ETF Filings Are &#8216;Inadequate&#8217; (WSJ)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin&#8217;s Hash Rate Hits ATH as Halving Countdown Narrows and LTC Nears $100</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/litecoins-hash-rate-hits-ath-as-halving-countdown-narrows-and-ltc-nears-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257903</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/LitecoinPeak.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/LitecoinPeak.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Litecoin also noted an uptick in mining difficulty that surged above 26 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin&#8217;s upcoming halving is less than five weeks away, which is expected to happen on August 2, 2023, at block 2,520,000. Leading up to the much-anticipated fact, the network hash rate has already reached a historic high, thereby serving as a positive catalyst for the Litecoin miners</p>
<p>As a result of this increased confidence, LTC was up by more than 15% over the past week, climbing near the crucial $100 mark.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/litecoin-hashrate.html#3y" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> compiled by Bitinfohcharts, Litecoin&#8217;s hash rate &#8211; which is a measure of computing power on the network &#8211; hit a fresh high of 797.72 tera hash/second (Th/s) this week.</li>
<li>Notably, the hash rate figures have been on a steady rise despite severe turbulence in LTC&#8217;s price trajectory over the past month.</li>
<li>A similar trend was observed during the previous halving event when Litecoin&#8217;s hash rate climbed the then-all-time-high of 523 Th/s before significantly sliding down. It wasn&#8217;t until mid-2022 that the metric picked up pace yet again to fresh highs.</li>
<li>Besides the hash rate, Litecoin&#8217;s mining difficulty, recorded at 26.38 million, is also hovering new its recently established ATH. Such a trend depicts a growing challenge for miners to discover new blocks and rake in rewards.</li>
<li>The upcoming halving, expected to happen on August 2, 2023, specifically at block 2,520,000, will slash the block rewards to half from 12.5 LTC per mined block to 6.25 LTC per mined block.</li>
<li>This reduction in supply and future scarcity has not only boosted the prices higher but has also triggered an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-sees-increased-network-activity-ahead-of-halving/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">increased</a> network activity.</li>
<li>LTC&#8217;s price has also been on a roll lately. The past 24 hours alone brought a massive 15% surge, which helped the asset jump to almost $100 as of now.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoins-hash-rate-hits-ath-as-halving-countdown-narrows-and-ltc-nears-100/" rel="nofollow">Litecoin&#8217;s Hash Rate Hits ATH as Halving Countdown Narrows and LTC Nears $100</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume on Upbit Skyrockets as BCH Soars 120% Weekly</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257879</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Cash_Korea.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Cash_Korea.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinGecko's data shows that BCH/KRW trading volume on Upbit for the past 24 hours exceeded $560 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading South Korean cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Upbit &#8211; has recorded a trading volume of more than $350 million for the Bitcoin Cash (BCH)/Korean Won (KRW) pair for the past 24 hours. In comparison, trades involving Bitcoin (BTC) have been three times less.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BCH has been among the best performers in the crypto market lately, with its USD valuation up over 180% for the past two weeks.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BCH Grabs the Attention of Koreans </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As revealed by Wu Blockchain, BCH/KRW trades on South Korea&#8217;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange have accounted for approximately 24% of the total trading volume for the past day.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">South Korea may be the reason for the BCH PUMP. In the past 24h, the largest exchange in South Korea, Upbit, has recorded a trading volume of over $350 million for the BCH/KRW, contributing to 23.58% of the total trading volume for BCH. It is also the 3x the trading volume of the…</p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1674614453231562755?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/upbit" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CoinGecko&#8217;s data</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the latest figures are even more impressive, with BCH/KRW trading volume for the last 24 hours equaling over $560 million. Trades with Solana (SOL) rank second with 8.4%, whereas Bitcoin (BTC) is third, contributing 7.8% to the total volume.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash has been highly popular on other Korean crypto platforms, too. BCH/KRW trading volume on Bithumb on a daily basis has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/bithumb" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">surged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to $39 million. Trades involving BTC are first, with a mere $300,000 lead. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s Recent Rally</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The asset recently surpassed the $300 mark, a price last seen in April 2022. What&#8217;s more impressive is that its USD valuation was hovering at approximately $100 just two weeks ago.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_257890" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257890" style="width: 649px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257890" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png" alt="BCH Price" width="649" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png 1033w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-300x185.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-1024x631.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-768x474.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-50x31.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257890" class="wp-caption-text">BCH Price, Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One possible reason behind the increase could be the launch of the Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets, which </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-backed-cryptocurrency-exchange-edx-goes-live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">went live</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on June 21. The platform, supported by finance giants such as Fidelity Digital Assets, Citadel Securities, and Charles Schwab, offers services with four cryptocurrencies, with BCH being one of them.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash was also not included in the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">list</a> of alleged unregistered securities when filing lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase earlier this month. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The overall revival of the cryptocurrency market could be another factor. The industry was boosted with optimistic news, such as BlackRock&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> to launch a Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the United States and the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decision to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-trades-flat-after-federal-reserve-pauses-rate-hikes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">halt</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> interest hikes for the first time since March 2022.</span></p>
<p>As mentioned above, the blockchain journalist Colin Wu believes another factor that could be behind BCH&#8217;s massive surge is the</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume on Upbit Skyrockets as BCH Soars 120% Weekly</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How An Early Investment in Dogecoin Made This Investor a Millionaire: Which New Meme Coins Could Be Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-early-investment-in-dogecoin-made-this-investor-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-could-be-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257939</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_tl_doge_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_tl_doge_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Given the crypto market’s fast-moving nature, fortunes can be made and lost in the blink of an eye. Dogecoin ($DOGE) defied all the odds and turned early investors into millionaires during its bull run, launching an era of meme-based cryptocurrencies. Now investors are looking for the next wave of meme coins that could be the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Given the crypto market’s fast-moving nature, fortunes can be made and lost in the blink of an eye.</p>
<p>Dogecoin ($DOGE) defied all the odds and turned early investors into millionaires during its bull run, launching an era of meme-based cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Now investors are looking for the next wave of meme coins that could be the fabled crypto &#8220;millionaire makers.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Millionaire Learns Valuable Lessons in the Meme Coin Landscape</h2>
<p>Dogecoin was the first meme coin to gain significant mainstream attention, solidifying its place in the history of the crypto market.</p>
<p>From January 2021 to May 2021, the $DOGE price rocketed over 10,000%, marking the first time a crypto asset driven by social media hype had experienced such an astronomical surge.</p>
<p>This event forever altered the perception of what is possible in the world of cryptocurrencies since it demonstrated the immense power of community-driven enthusiasm.</p>
<p>One notable outcome of Dogecoin’s unprecedented surge was the emergence of the legendary “Dogecoin millionaire” – an individual who transformed an early $DOGE investment into a life-changing fortune.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/dogecoin-investor-is-no-longer-a-millionaire-but-still-buys-the-dips.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CNBC</a> article, Glauber Contessoto invested $250,000 in $DOGE in February 2021, and by April 2021, he became a millionaire on paper.</p>
<p>However, despite his initial success, Contessoto’s decision to hold onto his Dogecoin investment without taking profits proved to be a risky move.</p>
<p>As the hype around Dogecoin subsided, the price of the meme coin came crashing down – eroding a significant chunk of his paper gains.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257943" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="497" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29-300x248.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Fast forward to the present day, and Contessoto has embraced his past and become an <a href="https://twitter.com/ProTheDoge" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">influential voice on Twitter</a> – sharing insights and offering advice to fellow crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p>In retrospect, many experts suggest that he could have benefited from taking profits during the peak of Dogecoin’s surge and diversifying into other promising projects.</p>
<p>By realizing gains at the right time, Contessoto may have mitigated the potential losses incurred during the $DOGE downfall, yet this wasn&#8217;t the approach he took.</p>
<p>Ultimately, hindsight serves as a stark reminder that effective risk management is key to maximizing outcomes in the crypto market – something that meme coin investors may wish to bear in mind going forward.</p>
<h2>Which Meme Coins Could Be the Next With Potential?</h2>
<p>With Dogecoin setting a precedent for what’s possible with meme coin investing, investors are eagerly searching for the next “millionaire makers” in the market.</p>
<p>Two promising candidates have recently emerged, Wall Street Memes and Thug Life, aiming to capture the imagination of meme coin enthusiasts worldwide.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Raises $11.5m As Investor Excitement Reaches Fever Pitch</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is a community-driven project that leverages the immense power of the Reddit subculture.</p>
<p>The core values of Wall Street Memes are designed to resonate with investors who have rallied behind meme cryptos in the past, making $WSM a particularly appealing prospect.</p>
<p>Since emerging last month, Wall Street Memes has made itself known to the masses – raising a staggering $11.5 million through its ongoing presale.</p>
<p>The presale has been an instant hit due to its 30-stage setup, which increases the $WSM price incrementally between stages.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257942" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Currently, $WSM is available to purchase for just $0.0307 – although with over two-thirds of the presale allocation already gone, investors may need to act fast to take advantage of these prices.</p>
<p>The low purchase price has led to tremendous growth and momentum behind the project, evidenced by the influx of new members to the Wall Street Memes <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>Additionally, the project has already been on the radar of some high-profile crypto influencers; for example, Michael Wrubel, who boasts over 310,000 subscribers, posted a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BTdUPbXVujc&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video breakdown</a> of the project.</p>
<p>Overall, Wall Street Memes looks set to continue growing – positioning itself as a potential meme coin leader.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>New Contender Thug Life Disrupts Meme Coin Market with Huge Presale Launch</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a> is another brand-new meme coin that has gained huge attention from retail investors.</p>
<p>This fresh project centers around hip-hop culture and the essence of resilience while fostering a sense of camaraderie within the community.</p>
<p>The $THUG token has generated significant buzz through its presale phase launch, which has amassed over $140,000 in just two days.</p>
<p>Early investors can buy $THUG tokens for just $0.0007, presenting an appealing opportunity for those seeking the next meme coin sensation.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257941" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="357" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11-300x178.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Importantly, the Thug Life team has already pledged to lock liquidity for three months once the token makes its DEX debut – protecting investors from rug pull scenarios.</p>
<p>Also, 70% of the total $THUG supply has been set aside for presale investors, demonstrating the team&#8217;s commitment to fostering a strong community.</p>
<p>This setup seems to be bearing fruit, with over 2,400 people following the Thug Life <a href="https://twitter.com/thug_life_token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter account</a> already.</p>
<p>In addition, crypto influencer Jacob Bury uploaded a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mVtbCRWEmgA&amp;t=1s&amp;pp=ygUQdGh1ZyBsaWZlIGNyeXB0bw%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> discussing $THUG, stating that he thinks the token’s price could 10x after its DEX listing.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the future looks exceedingly bright for Thug Life – setting the stage for a solid second half of 2023.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-early-investment-in-dogecoin-made-this-investor-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-could-be-next/" rel="nofollow">How An Early Investment in Dogecoin Made This Investor a Millionaire: Which New Meme Coins Could Be Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/twt_101_1_1688059768gfAiBu9ZOa.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/twt_101_1_1688059768gfAiBu9ZOa.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, June 30th, 2023] Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign. Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, June 30th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign.</p>
<p>Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its token holders. While the MOOKY token draws its cues from other successful memecoins, the project has a more ambitious mandate. Mooky was conceived to increase awareness of global environmental challenges and to provide real-world solutions.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1_1688110387jD2jn6a98F.jpg" /></p>
<p>The project aims to raise enough funds to sustain an extensive reforestation initiative in key locations around the world. As part of its commitment to nature, Mooky has earmarked donations to charities working on sustainable environmental causes.</p>
<p>From a crypto-economic perspective, the MOOKY token features zero tax and low slippage, providing ample incentives for traders to get involved. Underpinning the project is a deep lore that aligns with Mooky’s core goals.</p>
<p>Mooky is based on the concept of a mythical land called Pygmy. This fantastical realm has stunning landscapes, abundant vegetation, and wildlife. As settlers came to the island, they destroyed the vegetation and polluted the air. The monkeys of Pygmy decide to fight back peacefully, teaching the settlers how to respect nature and live harmoniously. Under the leadership of Mooky, they become united and restore nature.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IiPyd5VoQIg"></iframe></div></p>
<p>To support the project’s development while providing greater opportunities for community participation, Mooky has created a collection of 1,000 NFTs. Each NFT is linked to a tree planted in the real world. Holders can access the Ventures Club, which grants access to exclusive rewards and events.</p>
<p>With five days left in the <a href="blank" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$MOOKY token presale</a>, there is still ample opportunity for crypto holders to get involved and capture the upside to a project that combines memes and nature to great effect.</p>
<h2>About MOOKY</h2>
<p>MOOKY is a community-driven initiative launched in 2023 that embraces the spirit of digital innovation to make a positive impact on the environment. More than just a meme token, MOOKY represents a global community united by a common goal: to inspire change and contribute to global tree-planting efforts.</p>
<p>MOOKY also stands as a symbol of creativity in the digital space, offering unique 3D NFTs that are each linked to real-world tree-planting initiatives. These NFTs serve not only as digital collectibles but also as an entry ticket to the exclusive Mooky Ventures Club, a vibrant community of environmentally conscious enthusiasts.</p>
<p>MOOKY is more than a digital token; it&#8217;s a movement aiming to better our environment while fostering a unique and engaging digital ecosystem. Join MOOKY in its journey to make a difference and follow the community on various social channels to stay updated.</p>
<p>Users can purchase MOOKY <a href="https://buy.mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">here</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/" rel="nofollow">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Files Request for Dismissal of Charges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257886</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coinbase_sec_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coinbase_sec_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to Coinbase, the lawsuit is at best government overreach and at worst an abuse of due process.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Merely a few weeks after the SEC sued the platform for facilitating unregistered trading with 12 tokens that the agency considers to be securities, Coinbase’s legal representatives have filed for a complete dismissal of the lawsuit, citing concerns regarding the legal authority of the regulator.</p>
<h2>Prior Approval Disregarded</h2>
<p>One of the principal arguments laid out by Coinbase’s legal team is that six of the twelve cryptocurrencies at the heart of the lawsuit had already been <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/4oVJN5EioULD0QnSyg01b8/2b1f34594a800c727fb61a384f37e74a/SEC_v._Coinbase__Coinbase_Answer_to_Complaint__As-Filed_.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">greenlit</a> by the SEC back in 2021. At the time, the six cryptocurrencies in question had been confirmed to not be securities by the SEC, which reviewed 240 digital assets that were listed on the exchange shortly after.</p>
<p>Since the SEC had already confirmed that the tokens in question were not considered securities, Coinbase argued that the current lawsuit is merely the result of internal policy changes that were not communicated to the companies the watchdog wishes to regulate.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The SEC’s about-face is not a product of material changes to Coinbase’s business since 2021; none are alleged. Nor is it due to new information. Nowhere in its Complaint does the SEC suggest that Coinbase hid anything in the many years of cooperative discussion that preceded it becoming a public company. Nor is the reversal a product of legislative change. […] The only change is in the SEC’s position regarding its powers.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Out of Scope</h2>
<p>Not only are the charges brought against Coinbase possibly unfounded, but they are also outside of the scope of existing law and regulatory precedent, argued Coinbase representatives.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@coinbase</a> filed our answer and notice of intent to file a motion to dismiss the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SECGov</a> case against us. You can read our response for yourself – our arguments speak for themselves. 1/2 <a href="https://t.co/Ld2ZEejhyM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/Ld2ZEejhyM</a></p>
<p>— paulgrewal.eth (@iampaulgrewal) <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1674271484263661569?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Coinbase’s leadership has repeatedly stressed that they are more than willing to entertain dialogue with regulatory bodies and stay well within the legal framework imposed upon them – so long as the given framework is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-responds-to-coinbase-request-for-crypto-clarity-wants-more-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">clearly</a> laid out.</p>
<p>In this case, however, Coinbase believes the tokens in question are outside of the SEC’s scope owing to them not being considered securities by the agency&#8217;s own admission. Even if the tokens were to come under the purview of the SEC, the current lawsuit represents a violation of Coinbase’s rights and an abuse of process.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Even if the SEC were correct that the assets and services it identifies are within the scope of its existing regulatory authority, this [legal] action must be dismissed on independent grounds that it violates Coinbase’s due process rights and constitutes an extraordinary abuse of process.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The request to dismiss charges is now pending with the judge, who will respond as he sees fit. Meanwhile, Coinbase’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-shares-have-jumped-nearly-40-since-the-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">stock</a> seems to be slowly recovering following the initial shock that sent it plunging to the depths.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Files Request for Dismissal of Charges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
