<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:45:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Platform Advises Users to Withdraw Funds Amid Custody Issues</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-platform-advises-users-to-withdraw-funds-amid-custody-issues/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Custody]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231807</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Juno.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Juno.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Juno cautioned users to employ self-custody methods due to "uncertainty" with its custodian partner.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency firm &#8211; Juno &#8211; advised its users to withdraw their assets and store them in self-custody wallets or sell their holdings for cash because of &#8220;uncertainty&#8221; with its partner.</p>
<p>The company plans to solve the issues by finding a new associate.</p>
<h2>A Warning Before the Storm?</h2>
<p>In a recent Twitter thread, Juno revealed that its custody partner has been experiencing certain problems. As such, the entity temporarily halted cryptocurrency purchases on its platform and auto-converted the stablecoins &#8211; USDC, USDT, mUSDC &#8211; to USD.</p>
<p>It also encouraged customers to withdraw their ownings and transfer them into self-custody wallets as a protection measure. The firm added that clients could sell their stash for fiat in case they don&#8217;t want to rely on non-custodial wallets.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">2/ Juno as a platform doesn’t custody crypto assets &amp; relies on our crypto partner for these services.</p>
<p>Due to uncertainty with our crypto partner, we have taken preemptive action in the interest of our customers.</p>
<p>— Juno (@JunoFinanceHQ) <a href="https://twitter.com/JunoFinanceHQ/status/1610639361263140865?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Juno has increased daily cryptocurrency withdrawal limits by five times for all &#8220;metal users&#8221; to cope with the potential surge of transactions and asserted that all banking and card-related services continue to function effortlessly.</p>
<p>The valuation of crypto assets stored on the platform has shrunk to $1.25 million after the firm shared its recommendation with customers.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are actively reaching out to customers and asking them to self-custody,&#8221; Juno stated.</p></blockquote>
<p>The organization seeks to restore all operations as soon as possible and is looking to collaborate with a new custody partner. It also vowed to stay on its crypto course, continuing to &#8220;build and ship like we always have.&#8221;</p>
<h2>JUNO&#8217;s Crash in the Past Several Months</h2>
<p>The price of the native token of the platform &#8211; JUNO &#8211; performed quite well during the first quarter of 2022, reaching an all-time high of over $45 in March. The intensifying bear market, though, took its role, and the asset started nosediving.</p>
<p>It lost nearly 90% of its USD valuation in a matter of two months and continued its downtrend until the end of last year.</p>
<p>The troubling news about the company&#8217;s custody partner and the disabled crypto purchases have also negatively affected JUNO, which currently <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/juno/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">trades</a> at around $1.13 (a 97% decline compared to the peak level).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-platform-advises-users-to-withdraw-funds-amid-custody-issues/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Platform Advises Users to Withdraw Funds Amid Custody Issues</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animoca Brands Seeks to Raise $1 Billion in Q1 2023 to Invest in Web3</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-seeks-to-raise-1-billion-in-q1-2023-to-invest-in-web3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 22:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231745</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Animoca.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Animoca.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Hong Kong-based Animoca Brands could roll out a $1 billion Web3 and Metaverse investment fund.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The blockchain gaming platform Animoca Brands seeks to raise around $1 billion for its latest Web3 and Metaverse investment fund during the year&#8217;s first quarter.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The initiative comes in spite of the market decline and the FTX crash, which have vaporized much of the interest in cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Special Attention on Web3</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Hong Kong-based Animoca Brands seeks to double down on its Web3 endeavors by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hong-kong-crypto-mogul-aims-to-raise-1-billion-for-web3-fund-1.1865955" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">raising</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $1 billion to support blockchain and Metaverse startups. Chairman and Co-Founder &#8211; Yat Siu &#8211; said the firm aims at completing the fundraisiер during the first three months of 2023:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Q1 is the goal, and then let&#8217;s see what happens. It is fair to say it&#8217;s a challenging market. But we have quite a bit of interest.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company&#8217;s intentions come nearly two months after the gigantic crash of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. The collapse affected several of Animoca&#8217;s portfolio firms negatively. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Hong Kong entity </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-unveils-2b-metaverse-fund/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to roll out a $2 billion fund (called &#8220;Animoca Capital&#8221;) to invest in Metaverse businesses across the globe in partnership with former Morgan Stanley exec Homer Sun at the end of 2022. Siu commented on the move:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The long-term goal for us, and frankly for myself, is creating a way where we all have digital property rights. I&#8217;m hoping that this will also drive a scenario where the digital property will be recognized like physical property in the legal system.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Siu outlined that fundraisers have become quite difficult after the demise of FTX, he revealed that some subsidiaries of his company continue to raise capital. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Chairman said Animoca has no plans for personal funding rounds after </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-temasek-to-lead-animocas-100m-funding-round/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">obtaining</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Temasek&#8217;s $100 million investment last year. The primary goal of the firm will be to develop an ecosystem of cryptocurrency organizations that work for the advancement of Web3.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the Bear Market, Valuation Goes up</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Animoca Brands carried out several fundraisers during 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-valuation-surges-to-5-5-billion-with-fresh-360-million-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">completed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a $360 million financing round nearly a year ago and another one worth $75 million in July. The company </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-valuation-nears-6-billion-after-a-fresh-fundraiser-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it will use the capital to hire more people, receive licenses for intellectual properties, and upgrade its products. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Animoca&#8217;s Japanese subsidiary &#8211; Animoca Brands KK &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-tightens-the-reigns-in-japan-with-45m-web-3-focused-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">raised</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $45 million in August, strengthening the organization&#8217;s presence in the Land of the Rising Sun.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/animoca-brands-seeks-to-raise-1-billion-in-q1-2023-to-invest-in-web3/" rel="nofollow">Animoca Brands Seeks to Raise $1 Billion in Q1 2023 to Invest in Web3</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic Eden to Reimburse Users Tricked into Buying Counterfeit NFTs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/magic-eden-to-reimburse-users-tricked-into-buying-counterfeit-nfts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 21:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231823</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Magic_Eden.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Magic_Eden.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The marketplace confirmed that the issue was resolved. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Magic Eden revealed that it will refund all the users who mistakenly bought unverified NFTs that showed up on the collection pages as a result of a recent breach.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://help.magiceden.io/en/articles/6868809-magic-eden-response-to-unverified-nfts-reports" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, the Solana-based NFT marketplace said that a bug was deployed in an update to two of its features &#8211; Snappy Marketplace and Pro Trade tools. As a result, unverified NFTs were listed in these two tools.</p>
<ul>
<li>More technically, the newly deployed &#8220;activity indexer&#8221; failed to detect dupe NFTs. Instead, the bug allowed these tokens to evade verification and get listed alongside genuine collections.</li>
<li>The development comes days after some Magic Eden users <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/magic-eden-blames-unsavory-pics-on-third-party-breach/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> seeing strange images on the platform instead of the NFTs, including pornographic images and stills from the TV series &#8220;The Big Bang Theory.&#8221;</li>
<li>On January 4th, however, the platform confirmed that its smart contract remains secure and added that the incident was an isolated UI issue.</li>
<li>According to the update, the breach led to 25 fraudulent NFTs being sold across four collections in the past day. The marketplace is now looking if additional NFTs were affected.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have identified in the last 24 hours, the impact was contained to 25 unverified NFTs sold across 4 collections. These unverified NFTs showed up on the collection pages and transactions of unverified NFTs showed up in the activity tabs of the collections. The issue has been resolved as of this morning.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Counterfeit NFTs were also added to high-priced and prominent Solana-based collections ABC and y00ts.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/magic-eden-to-reimburse-users-tricked-into-buying-counterfeit-nfts/" rel="nofollow">Magic Eden to Reimburse Users Tricked into Buying Counterfeit NFTs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New York AG Sues Celsius Co-Founder Alex Mashinsky for Alleged Fraud</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-ag-sues-celsius-co-founder-alex-mashinsky-for-alleged-fraud/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231840</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Alex_Mashinsky.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The lawsuit seeks disgorgement of any proceeds derived from Mashinsky's unlawful practices as well as restitution for investors.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Alex Mashinsky, the co-founder and former CEO of bankrupt cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network has been sued by New York Attorney General Letitia James for allegedly defrauding investors, including more than 26,000 New Yorkers, out of billions of dollars worth of digital assets.</p>
<p class="p2">In an official <a href="https://ag.ny.gov/press-release/2023/attorney-general-james-sues-former-ceo-celsius-cryptocurrency-platform-defrauding" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">press release</span></a>, the AG alleged that before Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy, Mashinsky repeatedly made false and misleading statements about the company&#8217;s safety to persuade investors to deposit billions of dollars worth of crypto on the platform.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Failure to Register as a Salesperson for Celsius</b></h2>
<p class="p2">James also stated that the Celsius co-founder failed to register as a salesperson for the lending platform and as a securities and commodities dealer.</p>
<p class="p2">According to the AG, these actions taken by Mashinsky before <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" data-wpel-link="internal">Celsius&#8217; bankruptcy</a> led to investors losing their investments on the platform.</p>
<p class="p2">James added that Mashinsky claimed that Celsius made &#8220;safe, low-risk investments&#8221; and only lent assets to &#8220;credible and reputable entities,&#8221; while in reality exposing investors&#8217; assets to high-risk counterparties and strategies with many leading to losses, which the former CEO kept from investors.</p>
<p class="p2">The AG also mentioned some of the residents who were left in ruins due to Mashinsky&#8217;s actions. She said one resident mortgaged two properties to invest with Celsius while a disabled veteran lost $36,000 of his life savings to Celsius.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Lawsuit Seeks Restitution for New York Investors</b></h2>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;The law is clear that making false and unsubstantiated promises and misleading investors is illegal. Today, we are taking action on behalf of thousands of New Yorkers who were defrauded by Mr. Mashinsky to recoup their losses,&#8221; Attorney General James said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">The lawsuit seeks to ban Mashinsky from doing business or serving as a director or officer of any entity operating in New York. The complaint also seeks to &#8220;secure disgorgement of any proceeds derived from Mashinsky&#8217;s unlawful conduct, as well as damages and restitution for investors.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p2">The lawsuit is part of the AG&#8217;s effort to enforce New York laws in the crypto sector. James had previously filed lawsuits against crypto lenders, including Nexo and the now-bankrupt BlockFi.</p>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, an earlier report <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/verdict-out-celsius-earn-assets-belong-to-bankrupt-firm-not-users/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that Celsius had won claims over $4.2 billion worth of assets deposited in its Earn accounts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-ag-sues-celsius-co-founder-alex-mashinsky-for-alleged-fraud/" rel="nofollow">New York AG Sues Celsius Co-Founder Alex Mashinsky for Alleged Fraud</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Logan Paul Plans to Sue Coffeezilla Over CryptoZoo Allegations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/logan-paul-plans-to-sue-coffeezilla-over-cryptozoo-allegations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 16:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231774</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Logan_Paul.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Logan_Paul.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, Paul has threatened to sue the blockchain investigator.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Logan Paul has been at the receiving end of seemingly endless controversies since his career took off as a media star. His two-year-old NFT venture &#8211; Crypto Zoo &#8211; is now under intense scrutiny.</p>
<p>The latest development has ruffled a lot of feathers in the space. The crypto scam allegations are yet to fizzle out, but the investigative journalist who interviewed purported investors of the project has dropped bombshell allegations about Paul and his team members.</p>
<h2>Accusation</h2>
<p>In a three-part series <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=386p68_lDHA" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">created</a> by a viewer-supported Youtube channel, Coffeezilla accused Paul of engaging in fraudulent activities with his NFT game.</p>
<p>Crypto Zoo was launched in 2021 on Binance Smart Chain. To play the game, all users had to do was buy &#8220;eggs&#8221; that hatch into hybrid animals. People reportedly purchased nearly $2.5 million worth of eggs even before it was launched. In fact, its native ZOO token skyrocketed in value, reaching over a $2 billion market cap pre-launch.</p>
<p>However, its social media channels have not been active over the past eight to nine months, brewing concerns of abandonment by Paul. Coffeezilla, whose real name is Stephen Findeisen, accused the 27-year-old Podcaster of allegedly stealing millions of dollars through the business.</p>
<p>The main idea of the game was to clock in a passive income, letting players cash out their ZOO tokens for real-world money. However, Findeisen investigations revealed that Crypto Zoo ended up burning investor pockets.</p>
<p>Findeisen alleged that the founding team, including Paul, did not spend $1 million in developing the game but instead copy-pasted a code from FlokiShibX and claimed it as their own.</p>
<p>One player who spoke on Coffeezilla&#8217;s series said Crypto Zoo was never been &#8220;fully playable.&#8221; A few others have claimed that could never even breed their hatched animals on cash-out. Another player added that while the passive income mechanic was the selling point of Paul&#8217;s venture, the game &#8220;never did (work) from the beginning,&#8221; and &#8220;there was no way to claim your yield (and) there never was.&#8221;</p>
<p>CryptoZoo investors also claimed having failed to hatch the eggs they had purchased and described them as &#8220;just a picture&#8221; that is &#8220;basically worth nothing whatsoever.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Logan Paul Hits Back</h2>
<p>The credibility of the entire series has been plucked and debated by the community members. But, for the most part, Paul himself opted to remain silent. Earlier this week, the American media personality finally broke his silence and uploaded his response to the investigation, saying he would &#8220;defend himself with facts.&#8221;</p>
<p>He also hurled insults at Findeisen and accused him of morphing &#8220;from an investigator to a gossip channel.&#8221;</p>
<p>Paul did admit to having worked with individuals who are currently embroiled in criminal cases, such as former CryptoZoo lead developer Eddie Ibanez as well as dev Zach Kelling. They were, however, removed from the project, and Paul assured that he and his manager Jeff &#8220;made no money&#8221; in the process.</p>
<p>He went on to say that he suffered significant losses in his latest <a href="https://twitter.com/LoganPaul/status/1610719291460190210?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">video</a> but will &#8220;continue to build CryptoZoo&#8221; and even shared a teaser stating that it was coming in 2023/2024.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Trust me, CryptoZoo is coming, I will make damn sure of it.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/logan-paul-plans-to-sue-coffeezilla-over-cryptozoo-allegations/" rel="nofollow">Logan Paul Plans to Sue Coffeezilla Over CryptoZoo Allegations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>3 Reasons Solana Regained its December Losses in a New Year Rally</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-reasons-solana-regained-its-december-losses-in-a-new-year-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231680</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana_RIse.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Solana_RIse.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After several really bad days, SOL went on the offensive with massive gains. Here are some of the possible reasons.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana has rallied for the week as the network continues to gain more users. Excitement over the new memecoin, Bonk Inu (BONK), coincided with the cryptocurrency&#8217;s rally. The asset is moving in stride, brushing off recent losses in connection with the FTX&#8217;s collapse.</p>
<p>Solana is pulling through tough times. It&#8217;s rough for the Ethereum competitor, the DeFi ecosystem especially, as it is tough for the entire industry out there in this biting crypto winter.</p>
<p>The gains for Solana have pushed the coin up to $13.50, meaning a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-taps-8-day-high-solana-jumps-40-weekly-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">40+% weekly surge</a>. It had been trading below double digits by the end of December. So that&#8217;s a rally for Solana on the 5-day pane after a long, drawn-out tumble over the 30-day, 6-month, and 1-year view.</p>
<h2>1. How Solana Is Weathering Its FTX Connections</h2>
<p>Bonk Inu (BONK) has been taking the Solana blockchain by storm since its launch. In the one-page brief on the project, the founders say they eschew &#8220;Alameda-style&#8221; tokenomics in favor of a coin that&#8217;s fun and gives everyone in the community a fair shot. That&#8217;s good news after all the fallout from <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-alameda-ftx-crisis-started-years-before-bankruptcy-wsj-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">the Alameda-FTX scandal</a>.</p>
<p>The platform also got a really <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1608591727316684804" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">nice note</a> from a crypto competitor, Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin. He tweeted over the New Year holiday week that &#8220;smart people&#8221; he trusts have told him about the &#8220;earnest smart developer community in Solana.&#8221;</p>
<p>He said the chain has &#8220;a bright future&#8221; and seemed assured that &#8220;the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out.&#8221; He even added that he hopes that Solana &#8220;gets its fair chance to thrive.&#8221;</p>
<p>That&#8217;s a better turn of the week for Solana <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/" data-wpel-link="internal">than for crypto lending partners Gemini and Genesis</a>. They roiled in a public spat over the damage to their customers in the solvency crunch that took down the FTX exchange.</p>
<h2>2. Solana Defi Platform Is Still Growing</h2>
<p>So Solana seems to be weathering the damage from FTX very well. That is if you consider how much its price fell over the last six months and over the month of December.</p>
<p>A crypto column on the Motley Fool <a href="https://www.fool.com/investing/2023/01/04/is-it-finally-time-to-give-up-on-solana/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">suggests there</a> isn&#8217;t really any lower to go over FTX, &#8220;The market had seemingly priced in all the potential bad news scenarios and driven Solana down to a bargain-basement level.&#8221;</p>
<p>On-chain <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/on-chain-metrics/solana" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data shows</a> that growth in new monthly addresses for Solana continued to swell throughout 2022, despite the deep freeze on crypto prices.</p>
<p>New monthly addresses and active monthly addresses slowed in growth in Q4 of 2022, but the network continues to generate new addresses and active monthly users.</p>
<h2>3. New Meme Coin Explodes Over New Year Holiday</h2>
<p>Enthusiasts are hailing it as the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-bonk-inu-bonk-the-dogecoin-of-solana/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dogecoin (DOGE) of Solana</a>. To be fair to Dogecoin, it is a proof-of-work accounting blockchain fork of Bitcoin (BTC). It&#8217;s not an ERC-20 or BEP-20 token that lives in Ethereum or Binance, but a Layer 1 PoW coin as well as a meme token.</p>
<p>(<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dogecoin-foundation-introduces-a-new-core-devlopment-fund/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dogecoin recently introduced a new 5 million DOGE Core Development Fund. You can read more about it here.</a>)</p>
<p>But Bonk Inu is certainly running for the title of Solana platform DOGE.</p>
<p>What&#8217;s been pushing the price of Bonk Inu crazy over the holiday week has been a spate of token burnings. It&#8217;s a page out of the marketing incentive playbook of Binance (BNB).</p>
<p>The team has gone on a public campaign of burning a large number of tokens, cryptographically locking them up forever. That results in giving value to the remaining coins in the token supply. So that&#8217;s generated a lot of excitement from traders. Like when the Bonk team just burned 500 billion BONK tokens up on Dec 4.</p>
<p>Liquidity providers are also yielding enormous yields for BONK tokens at the moment because of the rising volume and the huge demand for trades. It grew in fair market price by around 3,000% in about a week.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-reasons-solana-regained-its-december-losses-in-a-new-year-rally/" rel="nofollow">3 Reasons Solana Regained its December Losses in a New Year Rally</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Verdict Out: Celsius Earn Assets Belong to Bankrupt Firm, Not Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/verdict-out-celsius-earn-assets-belong-to-bankrupt-firm-not-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 13:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231726</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The court order is a blow to some users hoping to recover their funds from the company. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A federal bankruptcy judge has ruled that crypto-assets deposited in Celsius Network&#8217;s &#8220;Earn&#8221; accounts do not belong to the customers. Instead, the funds in the interest-bearing accounts belong to the bankrupt cryptocurrency lending platform.</p>
<p>In a 45-page written <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174901042380000000067.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">decision</a>, Martin Glenn, the chief US bankruptcy judge in the Southern District of New York, determined that Celsius is the owner of the $4.2 billion in crypto-assets. The verdict has set an important precedent that the platform&#8217;s users do not own their coins when using certain products and services.</p>
<h2>Estate&#8217;s Ownership of Funds</h2>
<p>Celsius&#8217; Earn program allowed users to deposit crypto-assets such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tether and get paid weekly with interest earned on them. Customers who parked their assets in Celsius&#8217; lending service lost access to those funds in June when the company froze withdrawals, citing extreme market conditions.</p>
<p>Celsius had 600,000 accounts in its Earn program when it filed for Chapter 11 last summer, which brings the assets worth $4.2 billion in assets as of July 2022. Stablecoins accounted for nearly $23 million of the total as of September last year. The entire fund in question has now been declared the property of the estate.</p>
<p>Glenn wrote,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Court concludes, based on Celsius’s unambiguous Terms of Use, and subject to any reserved defenses, that when the cryptocurrency assets (including stablecoins, discussed in detail below) were deposited in Earn Accounts, the cryptocurrency assets became Celsius’s property; and the cryptocurrency assets remaining in the Earn Accounts on the Petition Date became property of the Debtors’ bankruptcy estates (the “Estates”).&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Last month, Celsius and its customers locked horns with customers in court over ownership of the deposited crypto assets as it wanted to sell about $18 million worth of stablecoins, the proceeds of which will be used to fund administrative costs for the next several months.</p>
<p>The latest court order claimed that Celsius &#8220;established a good business reason to permit the sale, thereby permitting the sale.&#8221; This move was, however, opposed by the state regulators and the US Trustee&#8217;s office.</p>
<h2>Objection</h2>
<p>While objecting to Celsius&#8217;s arguments, account holders of the Earn program argued that the terms of service for the accounts were &#8220;ambiguous&#8221; and that the ownership of the assets could not be demonstrated without considering additional evidence. This included numerous statements made by the former CEO of the company, Alex Mashinksy.</p>
<p>Judge Glenn, on the other hand, maintained that the sale of stablecoins will help Celsius fund its bankruptcy proceedings while adding that the company is quickly exhausting its available funds.</p>
<p>The ownership ruling comes almost a month after the bankruptcy judge <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-ordered-to-return-44m-of-customers-custodied-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the embattled firm to return funds worth $44 million, which were not part of its yield-bearing accounts, to its customers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/verdict-out-celsius-earn-assets-belong-to-bankrupt-firm-not-users/" rel="nofollow">Verdict Out: Celsius Earn Assets Belong to Bankrupt Firm, Not Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX Lawyer Cooperates With US Authorities in SBF Case (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-lawyer-cooperates-with-us-authorities-in-sbf-case-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 11:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231767</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Daniel Friedberg supposedly met with two dozen US investigators to provide them with information regarding SBF's actions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Daniel Friedberg &#8211; the former leading lawyer of crypto exchange FTX &#8211; has reportedly given vital information to American prosecutors that could help the authorities during the lawsuit against Sam Bankman-Fried.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The attorney is expected to appear in SBF&#8217;s trial in October to shed more light on the actions of the 30-year-old while being in charge of the bankrupt platform.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a recent Reuters </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/ftxs-former-top-lawyer-aided-us-authorities-bankman-fried-case-2023-01-05/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">report</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Friedberg met with over 20 US investigators (officials part of the Justice Department, the Federal Bureau of Investigation, and the SEC) at the end of November last year.</span></li>
<li>He told them that Bankman-Fried used clients&#8217; funds to finance his business conglomerate and explained how the sister company Alameda Research operated.</li>
<li>Freidberg is not under criminal investigation regarding playing a role in the demise of FTX and the consecutive multi-billion investor losses.</li>
<li>He expects to participate in SBF&#8217;s trial in October this year, where he could provide further information as a government witness.</li>
<li>Bankman-Fried spent a week in the Bahamian Fox Hill Prison before being deported to the United States. A New York federal judge <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">allowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his release after a record $250 million bond, which is significantly more than the $100,000 he previously claimed he had in his bank account.</span></li>
<li>SBF recently pleaded not guilty to several accusations, including wire fraud and money laundering conspiracy, and now lives at his parents&#8217; house, constantly having to a monitoring bracelet.</li>
<li>His trial date is <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">set</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for October 2, 2023.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-lawyer-cooperates-with-us-authorities-in-sbf-case-report/" rel="nofollow">Former FTX Lawyer Cooperates With US Authorities in SBF Case (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alaska Gold Rush Announces GameSwift as a Strategic Partner</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alaska-gold-rush-announces-gameswift-as-a-strategic-partner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Danish Yasin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231782</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Online gaming is undoubtedly catching speed as more and more people get on board. With multi-million dollar tournaments and millions of people playing various games across the world, it’s no longer a niche field. In fact, some estimations have the global gaming market reaching a value of a whopping $268 billion by 2025. Interestingly enough, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Online gaming is undoubtedly catching speed as more and more people get on board. With multi-million dollar tournaments and millions of people playing various games across the world, it’s no longer a niche field.</p>
<p>In fact, some estimations have the global gaming market reaching a value of a whopping $268 billion by 2025.</p>
<p>Interestingly enough, online gaming is also commonly touted as one of the best applications for blockchain-based technology. In 2021 and 2022, we saw a massive boom of crypto-based games in the form of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-play-to-earn/" data-wpel-link="internal">play-to-earn</a>.</p>
<p>One Web3 game that’s well-established within relevant gaming communities with a lot of various collaborations is Alaska Gold Rush. Now, the team has announced a new strategic partnership.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-231789" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1.jpg" alt="alaska_gold_rush_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/alaska_gold_rush_cover-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Alaska Gold Rush: A Web3 Gaming Experience</h2>
<p><a href="https://alaskagoldrush.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Alaska Gold Rush</a> brings forth a Web3 native game with an open world and exciting plot that presents multiple adventures to the player.</p>
<p>The team acknowledges that to design an inspiring Web3 game, there needs to be a well-done economy. However, the cryptocurrency gaming space is suffering from massive inflation, limited demand for tokens, as well as a very highly-competitive NFT market.</p>
<p>At Alaska Gold Rush, the team consists of gamers and financial experts who have gathered to create a vibrant in-game economy and long-lasting incentives.</p>
<h2>Alaska Gold Rush Teams Up With GameSwift</h2>
<p>In short, GameSwift is a Web3 gaming ecosystem that’s backed by Polygon. It has an extensive product suite that consists, among other things, of a dedicated gaming-optimized chain, a gaming studio, a platform, as well as dedicated technology solutions.</p>
<p>GameSwift enables signing into games and applications through a single account (much like with a Google account) called GameSwift ID. It also allows for the optimization of the chain specifically for gaming purposes with interoperability in mind and also using a platform that will be like a decentralized version of Steam or GOG with easy access to a broad library of games.</p>
<p>The goal of this collaboration is for Alaska Gold Rush to use GameSwift’s technology, leveraging the tools created by the project. The idea is to bring a seamless experience to the players, as well as AAA+ fun in the Web3 gaming field.</p>
<p>In addition, because of GameSwift, Alaska Gold Rush can also expand its network of interesting Web3 projects, KOLs, investors, and developers, which shows the team’s great confidence in the future of the game.</p>
<h2>What’s Next?</h2>
<p>The new strategic partnership doesn’t just end here. The team is happy to announce that the GameSwift community will also have a unique opportunity to participate in the Alaska Gold Rush token distribution.</p>
<p>The team believes that launching on GameSwift will be a great opportunity for the game and its community.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alaska-gold-rush-announces-gameswift-as-a-strategic-partner/" rel="nofollow">Alaska Gold Rush Announces GameSwift as a Strategic Partner</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Surges 34% Weekly But is the New Year Rally Running out of Steam? (SOL Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-surges-34-weekly-but-is-the-new-year-rally-running-out-of-steam-sol-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231753</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In a somewhat surprising move, Solana&#8217;s price exploded this past week, putting bears on the defensive. Key Support levels: $9.5 Key Resistance levels: $15 After falling to the single-digit territory (almost $8), Solana seemed destined to continue on the bearish footing. However, this was interrupted on Monday when the price suddenly spiked higher after finding [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">In a somewhat surprising move, Solana&#8217;s price exploded this past week, putting bears on the defensive.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $9.5</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $15</strong></p>
<p>After falling to the single-digit territory (almost $8), Solana seemed destined to continue on the bearish footing. However, this was interrupted on Monday when the price suddenly spiked higher after finding good support at $9.5. This led SOL to close the past seven days with a 34% price increase. The resistance is at $15, and SOL&#8217;s price reached $14 during this most recent rally.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231756" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231756" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231756" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-06-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231756" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Trading Volume:</strong> The volume exploded on Monday and remained high until Wednesday. Today the volume opened in red, and the price is falling, which could mean a pullback is likely.</p>
<p><strong>RSI</strong>: The daily RSI moved above 50 points quickly and reached almost 60 points. If bulls manage to keep it above 50, then the bias could turn bullish.</p>
<p><strong>MACD</strong>: The daily MACD completed a bullish cross on Monday, and the histogram continues to make higher highs. So long as this continues, the outlook will remain positive.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231755" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231755" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231755" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/SOLUSDT_2023-01-05_16-11-22-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231755" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SOL is slightly bullish right now, but buyers have to break above $15 to confirm it.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SOL Price</h2>
<p>At this time, the biggest challenge for Solana is to break above the $15 resistance level. That would confirm a change in the trend and turn the chart bullish. However, even if SOL does not manage to do that, as long as buyers maintain the price at two digits, that can still be considered a significant victory for them.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-surges-34-weekly-but-is-the-new-year-rally-running-out-of-steam-sol-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Solana Surges 34% Weekly But is the New Year Rally Running out of Steam? (SOL Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
