<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:36:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Presidential Candidate Francis Suarez to Accept Donations in BTC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/presidential-candidate-francis-suarez-to-accept-donations-in-btc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/miami-mayer-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/miami-mayer-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/miami-mayer-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/presidential-candidate-francis-suarez-to-accept-donations-in-btc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Miami Mayor Francis Suarez announced that he is officially accepting Bitcoin for his presidential campaign donations.</p>
Crypto-Friendly Mayer from Miami&nbsp;
<p>On Friday, August 4, Miami Mayer and Republican candidate for the 2024 Presidential Election, Francis Suarez, confirmed that his campaign would be accepting donations in Bitcoin. He clarified that his supporters can donate as little as 0.00034 BTC, equivalent to $1, at his website.</p>

<p>"Officially, my campaign is accepting Bitcoin," Suarez announced. "This is a process of developing technologies that are going to create democratizing opportunities for wealth creation and are not manipulated by a human being's ulterior motives, political goals, etc."&nbsp;</p>

<p>Suarez heavily criticized the Biden administration for its approach towards cryptocurrencies which involves regulation through enforcement, without understanding the mechanisms of digital assets or setting clear rules.</p>

<p>"The biggest mistake that this administration has made is they don't understand crypto so they have gone to a regulated-by-enforcement mechanism as opposed to set the ground rules," Suarez explained. "You have to be able to classify certain digital products, you have to be able to have certain guidelines and rules that are clear with respect to the custody of assets."</p>

<p>The candidate also declared that, if elected the President, he would ban the use of central bank digital currencies (CBDC):</p>

<p>"Nobody wants the federal government knowing where you have your money and how much money you have ... I don't think that there's anything particularly innovative about that."</p>

<p>Francis Suarez announced his candidacy for the upcoming presidential race in June 2023. He argued that the country needs a president who understands how cryptocurrency and artificial intelligence (AI) technologies work.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Miami Mayer has long been a supporter of Bitcoin and digital assets in general. He already launched his own cryptocurrency MiamiCoin (MIA) in 2021, and promised to make Miami a Bitcoin hub.</p>
Presidential Candidates Against CBDC
<p>Francis Suarez is not the only presidential hopeful who spoke out against CBDCs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The governor of Florida and presidential candidate for the Republican party, Ron DeSantis, criticized the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s new payments system, FedNow, and said that the Biden administration&rsquo;s efforts towards launching a CBDC are &ldquo;about surveillance and control&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Both Ron DeSantis and another presidential hopeful of the Democratic party, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., implied they would not support the launch and use of a CBDC in the country. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has recently confirmed the purchase of BTC for his children, even though he had earlier denied investment in the digital currency.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bernie Sanders and Democratic Senators, including Elizabeth Warren, Bob Casey, and Richard Blumenthal, are urging the Biden administration to initiate a crackdown on &ldquo;crypto tax evaders&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami Mayor Francis Suarez announced that he is officially accepting Bitcoin for his presidential campaign donations.</p>
Crypto-Friendly Mayer from Miami&nbsp;
<p>On Friday, August 4, Miami Mayer and Republican candidate for the 2024 Presidential Election, Francis Suarez, confirmed that his campaign would be accepting donations in Bitcoin. He clarified that his supporters can donate as little as 0.00034 BTC, equivalent to $1, at his website.</p>

<p>"Officially, my campaign is accepting Bitcoin," Suarez announced. "This is a process of developing technologies that are going to create democratizing opportunities for wealth creation and are not manipulated by a human being's ulterior motives, political goals, etc."&nbsp;</p>

<p>Suarez heavily criticized the Biden administration for its approach towards cryptocurrencies which involves regulation through enforcement, without understanding the mechanisms of digital assets or setting clear rules.</p>

<p>"The biggest mistake that this administration has made is they don't understand crypto so they have gone to a regulated-by-enforcement mechanism as opposed to set the ground rules," Suarez explained. "You have to be able to classify certain digital products, you have to be able to have certain guidelines and rules that are clear with respect to the custody of assets."</p>

<p>The candidate also declared that, if elected the President, he would ban the use of central bank digital currencies (CBDC):</p>

<p>"Nobody wants the federal government knowing where you have your money and how much money you have ... I don't think that there's anything particularly innovative about that."</p>

<p>Francis Suarez announced his candidacy for the upcoming presidential race in June 2023. He argued that the country needs a president who understands how cryptocurrency and artificial intelligence (AI) technologies work.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Miami Mayer has long been a supporter of Bitcoin and digital assets in general. He already launched his own cryptocurrency MiamiCoin (MIA) in 2021, and promised to make Miami a Bitcoin hub.</p>
Presidential Candidates Against CBDC
<p>Francis Suarez is not the only presidential hopeful who spoke out against CBDCs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The governor of Florida and presidential candidate for the Republican party, Ron DeSantis, criticized the Federal Reserve&rsquo;s new payments system, FedNow, and said that the Biden administration&rsquo;s efforts towards launching a CBDC are &ldquo;about surveillance and control&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Both Ron DeSantis and another presidential hopeful of the Democratic party, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., implied they would not support the launch and use of a CBDC in the country. Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has recently confirmed the purchase of BTC for his children, even though he had earlier denied investment in the digital currency.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Bernie Sanders and Democratic Senators, including Elizabeth Warren, Bob Casey, and Richard Blumenthal, are urging the Biden administration to initiate a crackdown on &ldquo;crypto tax evaders&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Proceeds with Filing for SEC Lawsuit Dismissal]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coinbase-proceeds-with-filing-for-sec-lawsuit-dismissal</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-v.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-v.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-v.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/coinbase-proceeds-with-filing-for-sec-lawsuit-dismissal</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase filed a motion to dismiss the SEC lawsuit in its entirety, seeking clarity in crypto regulation.</p>
Coinbase Makes a Major Move in SEC Lawsuit
<p>On Friday, July 4, Coinbase filed a new motion seeking to dismiss the lawsuit started by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) entirely, after hinting at the major move in yesterday&rsquo;s Shareholder letter on the platform&rsquo;s Q2 earnings.</p>
<p>In the filing, Coinbase claims that the regular is exceeding its authority by suing the cryptocurrency exchange because the platform does not offer &ldquo;investment contracts&rdquo;.</p>

<p>"The transactions over Coinbase&rsquo;s platform and Prime are not, and do not involve, contractual undertakings to deliver future value reflecting the income, profits, or assets of a business. They are commodity sales, with the obligations on both sides discharged entirely the moment the digital token is delivered in exchange for payment," the filing stated.</p>

<p>The crypto exchange also referred to the recent ruling partially in favor of Ripple in a similar case against the SEC, saying that the core facts were "substantially identical to those alleged here." However, there&rsquo;s no guarantee that the court will consider this argument, because another crypto company Terraform Labs also recently tried to cite the Ripple&rsquo;s case but was rejected by Judge Rakoff.</p>
Ongoing Legal Battle Against SEC
<p>As it was recently revealed, before suing the exchange, the SEC first asked Coinbase to halt all crypto trading except that of Bitcoin, arguing that all other digital assets are viewed as securities. Coinbase decided to decline the SEC&rsquo;s request. The company&rsquo;s CEO Brian Armostrong explained why:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We really didn&rsquo;t [did not] have a choice at that point; delisting every asset other than Bitcoin, which by the way, is not what the law says, would have essentially meant the end of the crypto industry in the US. It kind of made it an easy choice&hellip; let&rsquo;s [let us] go to court and find out what the court says.&rdquo; </p>

<p>In June, the regulator filed suit against Coinbase alleging the platform failed to register as a broker, clearing agency, or national securities exchange and traded at least 13 cryptocurrencies that could be considered securities.&nbsp;</p>
Seeking Regulatory Clarity
<p>Coinbase has repeatedly asked for more clarity regarding crypto regulation from the SEC but still hasn&rsquo;t responded. The regulator requested four more months to provide a response to the platform&rsquo;s call.</p>
<p>In its latest Shareholder letter, Coinbase highlighted:</p>

<p>&ldquo;&hellip;despite our good faith efforts and transparency of our business to the SEC for years now, we were deeply disappointed that the SEC brought an unwarranted enforcement against us in June, and that ten states initiated proceedings about our staking services. We are confident in the work we have done to abide by all federal and state securities laws, and as we vigorously defend that work, we plan to use these proceedings as an opportunity to bring more clarity to our industry as a whole.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal expressed optimism regarding the case:</p>

<p>&ldquo;With respect to the litigation with the SEC, I want to be very clear. We do think we can win. We expect to win.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase filed a motion to dismiss the SEC lawsuit in its entirety, seeking clarity in crypto regulation.</p>
Coinbase Makes a Major Move in SEC Lawsuit
<p>On Friday, July 4, Coinbase filed a new motion seeking to dismiss the lawsuit started by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) entirely, after hinting at the major move in yesterday&rsquo;s Shareholder letter on the platform&rsquo;s Q2 earnings.</p>
<p>In the filing, Coinbase claims that the regular is exceeding its authority by suing the cryptocurrency exchange because the platform does not offer &ldquo;investment contracts&rdquo;.</p>

<p>"The transactions over Coinbase&rsquo;s platform and Prime are not, and do not involve, contractual undertakings to deliver future value reflecting the income, profits, or assets of a business. They are commodity sales, with the obligations on both sides discharged entirely the moment the digital token is delivered in exchange for payment," the filing stated.</p>

<p>The crypto exchange also referred to the recent ruling partially in favor of Ripple in a similar case against the SEC, saying that the core facts were "substantially identical to those alleged here." However, there&rsquo;s no guarantee that the court will consider this argument, because another crypto company Terraform Labs also recently tried to cite the Ripple&rsquo;s case but was rejected by Judge Rakoff.</p>
Ongoing Legal Battle Against SEC
<p>As it was recently revealed, before suing the exchange, the SEC first asked Coinbase to halt all crypto trading except that of Bitcoin, arguing that all other digital assets are viewed as securities. Coinbase decided to decline the SEC&rsquo;s request. The company&rsquo;s CEO Brian Armostrong explained why:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We really didn&rsquo;t [did not] have a choice at that point; delisting every asset other than Bitcoin, which by the way, is not what the law says, would have essentially meant the end of the crypto industry in the US. It kind of made it an easy choice&hellip; let&rsquo;s [let us] go to court and find out what the court says.&rdquo; </p>

<p>In June, the regulator filed suit against Coinbase alleging the platform failed to register as a broker, clearing agency, or national securities exchange and traded at least 13 cryptocurrencies that could be considered securities.&nbsp;</p>
Seeking Regulatory Clarity
<p>Coinbase has repeatedly asked for more clarity regarding crypto regulation from the SEC but still hasn&rsquo;t responded. The regulator requested four more months to provide a response to the platform&rsquo;s call.</p>
<p>In its latest Shareholder letter, Coinbase highlighted:</p>

<p>&ldquo;&hellip;despite our good faith efforts and transparency of our business to the SEC for years now, we were deeply disappointed that the SEC brought an unwarranted enforcement against us in June, and that ten states initiated proceedings about our staking services. We are confident in the work we have done to abide by all federal and state securities laws, and as we vigorously defend that work, we plan to use these proceedings as an opportunity to bring more clarity to our industry as a whole.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal expressed optimism regarding the case:</p>

<p>&ldquo;With respect to the litigation with the SEC, I want to be very clear. We do think we can win. We expect to win.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[First of its kind: Dash x Maya Protocol Unlocks Multichain Trading]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/first-of-its-kind-dash-x-maya-protocol-unlocks-multichain-trading</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-20230804-074816-511.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-20230804-074816-511.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/img-20230804-074816-511.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/first-of-its-kind-dash-x-maya-protocol-unlocks-multichain-trading</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Today, the DeFi space witnessed a groundbreaking moment as Maya Protocol announced its integration with the Dash blockchain. This milestone marks the first-ever opportunity for Dash users to engage in decentralized and permissionless trading, unlocking a new era of possibilities.</p>
<p>Maya Protocol, a decentralized liquidity platform, empowers users to exchange cryptocurrency assets across multiple networks while retaining complete control of their tokens in a permissionless manner.</p>
<p>Dash, renowned for its focus on speed, privacy, and self-governance, is among the oldest cryptocurrencies still in circulation. Its continuous technological advancements and growing adoption as a digital payment method make it a highly usable cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>By integrating Dash into Maya, a seamless connection is established, enabling frictionless exchange between Dash and other crypto assets without relying on centralized intermediaries. The synergy between Dash's attributes and Maya's mission of facilitating fluid cross-chain liquidity amplifies the benefits of both protocols.</p>
<p>Maya's ability to handle Dash transactions sets it apart from others, demonstrating its expertise in the decentralized ecosystem, particularly in terms of interoperability and composability. Dash represents the first unique integration for Maya, compared to Thorchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result of this collaboration, Maya gains exposure to Dash's extensive user base, loyal community, and real-world use cases as digital cash.</p>
<p>Retail users stand to benefit from increased trading opportunities (Maya supports BTC, ETH, RUNE, USDT, and USDC) and yield generation with their Dash tokens by becoming liquidity providers.</p>
<p>Beyond individual growth, this integration reflects the evolution and progress of the decentralized finance ecosystem. It showcases the potential of DeFi in driving innovation and disrupting traditional financial models.</p>
<p>Maya and Dash exemplify their commitment to pioneering decentralized systems and reshaping the financial landscape. To delve deeper into this game-changing integration, visit the official web resources of both protocols.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Today, the DeFi space witnessed a groundbreaking moment as Maya Protocol announced its integration with the Dash blockchain. This milestone marks the first-ever opportunity for Dash users to engage in decentralized and permissionless trading, unlocking a new era of possibilities.</p>
<p>Maya Protocol, a decentralized liquidity platform, empowers users to exchange cryptocurrency assets across multiple networks while retaining complete control of their tokens in a permissionless manner.</p>
<p>Dash, renowned for its focus on speed, privacy, and self-governance, is among the oldest cryptocurrencies still in circulation. Its continuous technological advancements and growing adoption as a digital payment method make it a highly usable cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>By integrating Dash into Maya, a seamless connection is established, enabling frictionless exchange between Dash and other crypto assets without relying on centralized intermediaries. The synergy between Dash's attributes and Maya's mission of facilitating fluid cross-chain liquidity amplifies the benefits of both protocols.</p>
<p>Maya's ability to handle Dash transactions sets it apart from others, demonstrating its expertise in the decentralized ecosystem, particularly in terms of interoperability and composability. Dash represents the first unique integration for Maya, compared to Thorchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result of this collaboration, Maya gains exposure to Dash's extensive user base, loyal community, and real-world use cases as digital cash.</p>
<p>Retail users stand to benefit from increased trading opportunities (Maya supports BTC, ETH, RUNE, USDT, and USDC) and yield generation with their Dash tokens by becoming liquidity providers.</p>
<p>Beyond individual growth, this integration reflects the evolution and progress of the decentralized finance ecosystem. It showcases the potential of DeFi in driving innovation and disrupting traditional financial models.</p>
<p>Maya and Dash exemplify their commitment to pioneering decentralized systems and reshaping the financial landscape. To delve deeper into this game-changing integration, visit the official web resources of both protocols.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Jump as Tradecurve Revives Bullish Market Sentiments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-and-ethereum-jump-as-tradecurve-revives-bullish-market-sentiments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161434.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161434.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161434.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-and-ethereum-jump-as-tradecurve-revives-bullish-market-sentiments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">The presale of Tradecurve has rejuvenated the crypto market, and bulls have become active too. According to analysts, this new project has massive growth potential, and can become a new market king soon.</p>
<p class="s6">It has emerged as a serious challenger to well-established titans like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), which are facing sluggishness.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) Miners Suffer A Drop In Revenue
<p class="s6">A couple of months ago, Bitcoin (BTC) miners were raking in big revenues, due to the mania around the Ordinals protocol. However, as the hype around Ordinals wanes, transaction activity on the Bitcoin (BTC) network has returned to normal.</p>
<p class="s6">This has caused a slump in the revenue of Bitcoin (BTC) miners. As per the data from IntoTheBlock, transaction fees on the Bitcoin (BTC) network have plummeted by 38% since March. However, Bitcoin miners are holding onto their tokens as they hope for a further increase in the price of BTC.</p>
<p class="s6">Meanwhile, the market value of Bitcoin (BTC) has seen a surge of 14% in the past 30 days. As a result, Bitcoin (BTC) currently changes hands at $30,195.15.</p>
Ethereum (ETH) Whales Sell Their Tokens
<p class="s6">The latest on-chain data has revealed that Ethereum (ETH) whales have aggressively sold off their tokens. For instance, an Ethereum whale recently sold 4,549 ETH tokens worth about $8.78 million.</p>
<p class="s6">The whale bought Ethereum (ETH) tokens on January 9 at a price of $1,319. According to market experts, the sell-off pattern indicates that Ethereum (ETH) whales want to cash out the benefits before any unforeseen market downfall in future. Interestingly, after the court&rsquo;s verdict in the SEC-XRP case, Ethereum (ETH) surged to approximately $2030. But since then, Ethereum&rsquo;s (ETH) value has suffered a drop of more than 5%.</p>
<p class="s6">At the time of writing, Ethereum (ETH) trades at $1,910.38.</p>
Tradecurve's Momentum Aligns with Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH): A Triumvirate Fueling Market Revival
<p class="s6">In a remarkable synergy with the established giants Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), Tradecurve is infusing a fresh dynamism into the market, showcasing its potential to stand alongside the titans.</p>
<p class="s6">Crypto aficionados have long been looking for an exchange that could help them trade several assets with one account. To meet this growing demand, Tradecurve has entered the crypto arena. It is a comprehensive decentralized exchange that allows the trading of several assets on a single user interface. The asset classes available here include cryptocurrencies, stocks, Forex, bonds, and more.</p>
<p class="s6">Since the demand for decentralized exchange has surged to a new high, this new platform can soon become a market leader. CoinGecko&rsquo;s data showed that the growth rate of decentralized exchanges in Q1 2023 was more than 33%.</p>
<p class="s6">The platform enables people to trade a wide range of assets without relying on fiat payments. The platform ensures that the identities of its users are never revealed as traders need not go through any KYC verification process. This feature makes it more privacy-focused than existing exchanges, such as Bakkt and Revolut, where traders must submit their private details.</p>
<p class="s6">The platform will give exclusive deposit and level-up bonuses, among other perks. It also offers a VIP account service and high-leverage trading that starts from 500:1. Besides, it is equipped with a mechanism that ensures negative balance protection. The presale of the platform&rsquo;s native token, TCRV, is currently running at a price tag of $0.025.</p>
<p class="s6">TCRV tokens have been built on the Ethereum blockchain. As per market forecast, the tokens&rsquo; value will increase by 50x during the presale, and 100x after launch on multiple CEXs and Uniswap. The platform has already more than 17,000 registered users to its presale.</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale:
<p class="s11">Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">The presale of Tradecurve has rejuvenated the crypto market, and bulls have become active too. According to analysts, this new project has massive growth potential, and can become a new market king soon.</p>
<p class="s6">It has emerged as a serious challenger to well-established titans like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), which are facing sluggishness.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) Miners Suffer A Drop In Revenue
<p class="s6">A couple of months ago, Bitcoin (BTC) miners were raking in big revenues, due to the mania around the Ordinals protocol. However, as the hype around Ordinals wanes, transaction activity on the Bitcoin (BTC) network has returned to normal.</p>
<p class="s6">This has caused a slump in the revenue of Bitcoin (BTC) miners. As per the data from IntoTheBlock, transaction fees on the Bitcoin (BTC) network have plummeted by 38% since March. However, Bitcoin miners are holding onto their tokens as they hope for a further increase in the price of BTC.</p>
<p class="s6">Meanwhile, the market value of Bitcoin (BTC) has seen a surge of 14% in the past 30 days. As a result, Bitcoin (BTC) currently changes hands at $30,195.15.</p>
Ethereum (ETH) Whales Sell Their Tokens
<p class="s6">The latest on-chain data has revealed that Ethereum (ETH) whales have aggressively sold off their tokens. For instance, an Ethereum whale recently sold 4,549 ETH tokens worth about $8.78 million.</p>
<p class="s6">The whale bought Ethereum (ETH) tokens on January 9 at a price of $1,319. According to market experts, the sell-off pattern indicates that Ethereum (ETH) whales want to cash out the benefits before any unforeseen market downfall in future. Interestingly, after the court&rsquo;s verdict in the SEC-XRP case, Ethereum (ETH) surged to approximately $2030. But since then, Ethereum&rsquo;s (ETH) value has suffered a drop of more than 5%.</p>
<p class="s6">At the time of writing, Ethereum (ETH) trades at $1,910.38.</p>
Tradecurve's Momentum Aligns with Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH): A Triumvirate Fueling Market Revival
<p class="s6">In a remarkable synergy with the established giants Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH), Tradecurve is infusing a fresh dynamism into the market, showcasing its potential to stand alongside the titans.</p>
<p class="s6">Crypto aficionados have long been looking for an exchange that could help them trade several assets with one account. To meet this growing demand, Tradecurve has entered the crypto arena. It is a comprehensive decentralized exchange that allows the trading of several assets on a single user interface. The asset classes available here include cryptocurrencies, stocks, Forex, bonds, and more.</p>
<p class="s6">Since the demand for decentralized exchange has surged to a new high, this new platform can soon become a market leader. CoinGecko&rsquo;s data showed that the growth rate of decentralized exchanges in Q1 2023 was more than 33%.</p>
<p class="s6">The platform enables people to trade a wide range of assets without relying on fiat payments. The platform ensures that the identities of its users are never revealed as traders need not go through any KYC verification process. This feature makes it more privacy-focused than existing exchanges, such as Bakkt and Revolut, where traders must submit their private details.</p>
<p class="s6">The platform will give exclusive deposit and level-up bonuses, among other perks. It also offers a VIP account service and high-leverage trading that starts from 500:1. Besides, it is equipped with a mechanism that ensures negative balance protection. The presale of the platform&rsquo;s native token, TCRV, is currently running at a price tag of $0.025.</p>
<p class="s6">TCRV tokens have been built on the Ethereum blockchain. As per market forecast, the tokens&rsquo; value will increase by 50x during the presale, and 100x after launch on multiple CEXs and Uniswap. The platform has already more than 17,000 registered users to its presale.</p>
For more information about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale:
<p class="s11">Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s11">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p class="s6">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="s6">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Price Prediction – Chainlink, Uniswap, and Pomerdoge]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/price-prediction-chainlink-uniswap-and-pomerdoge</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161704.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161704.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-08-04-at-161704.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/price-prediction-chainlink-uniswap-and-pomerdoge</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Traders and investors are always on the lookout for changes in market trends to capture maximum profits. Three top cryptos, Chainlink (LINK), Uniswap (UNI), and Pomerdoe (POMD)have captured the interest of many investors with their recent price actions. What are crypto market experts saying about future targets for these three cryptos?</p>
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Chainlink (LINK) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Chainlink (LINK) caught the attention of many investors and traders for its major rally during the bear market of June. From June 20 to July 20, the price of Chainlink spiked by almost 70%. Starting at $5.1, Chainlink traded as high as $8.4 in July.</p>
<p class="s6">Chainlink now appears to have broken market structure, entering a bear market. Over the last two weeks, the price of Chainlink has tumbled by 15%. In addition, the number of whale transactions on Chainlink is now 78% fewer than they were two weeks ago.</p>
<p class="s6">The price of Chainlink now stands at $7.3, but data from Global In/Out of Money Around Price (GIOM) remains bearish. According to the firm, the price of Chainlink could continue its decline in the coming weeks and drop to the $6.5 support.</p>
Uniswap (UNI) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Uniswap also enjoyed a massive rally from June to July, increasing by 60%. Following its peak at $6.7, the price of Uniswap has tumbled down to $6.22. Despite growing bearish pressure, the price outlook of Uniswap remains fairly bullish.</p>
<p class="s6">With support at $6.0, the number of buyers are overtaking the number of sellers. If buyers successfully hold this price at the 200-day SMA, Uniswap could see a price increase in the coming days. However, the overall outlook of the crypto market could contribute to this.</p>
<p class="s6">Crypto analysts at Changelly have predicted that the price of Uniswap could top $7 in August. For 2023, the analysts have forecasted a maximum price of $8.44 for Uniswap.</p>
Pomerdoge (POMD) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Unlike Uniswap, crypto experts are more bullish about the prospects of Pomerdoge (POMD) in the coming weeks. Creating a revolutionary P2E game, crypto experts have given very bullish predictions for Pomerdoge.</p>
<p class="s6">In the Pomergame, players will create unique characters known as Pomerdoges. With their Pomerdoges, they will enter into competitions and challenges for amazing rewards. Pomerdogecombines the thrilling gameplay of the Pomergame with a social infrastructure allowing gamers from around the world to communicate.</p>
<p class="s6">With the prospects of combining the best features of top P2E games, the Pomerdoge utility token has been given very bullish ratings. Now in its first presale stage, you can buy a POMD token for as low as $0.007. However, crypto experts have predicted a 280% price surge over the next few weeks as the project prepares for launch.</p>
<p class="s6">One feature that has caught the attention of investors is the shared earnings of Pomerdoge. The team recently announced that early presale investors will receive a share of the game's earnings depending on their token holdings. This innovative model effectively aligns the interests of investors, leading to the growth of the Pomerdoge ecosystem.</p>
Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today:
<p class="s6">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s6">Traders and investors are always on the lookout for changes in market trends to capture maximum profits. Three top cryptos, Chainlink (LINK), Uniswap (UNI), and Pomerdoe (POMD)have captured the interest of many investors with their recent price actions. What are crypto market experts saying about future targets for these three cryptos?</p>
<p>Click Here To Find Out More About The Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale</p>
Chainlink (LINK) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Chainlink (LINK) caught the attention of many investors and traders for its major rally during the bear market of June. From June 20 to July 20, the price of Chainlink spiked by almost 70%. Starting at $5.1, Chainlink traded as high as $8.4 in July.</p>
<p class="s6">Chainlink now appears to have broken market structure, entering a bear market. Over the last two weeks, the price of Chainlink has tumbled by 15%. In addition, the number of whale transactions on Chainlink is now 78% fewer than they were two weeks ago.</p>
<p class="s6">The price of Chainlink now stands at $7.3, but data from Global In/Out of Money Around Price (GIOM) remains bearish. According to the firm, the price of Chainlink could continue its decline in the coming weeks and drop to the $6.5 support.</p>
Uniswap (UNI) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Uniswap also enjoyed a massive rally from June to July, increasing by 60%. Following its peak at $6.7, the price of Uniswap has tumbled down to $6.22. Despite growing bearish pressure, the price outlook of Uniswap remains fairly bullish.</p>
<p class="s6">With support at $6.0, the number of buyers are overtaking the number of sellers. If buyers successfully hold this price at the 200-day SMA, Uniswap could see a price increase in the coming days. However, the overall outlook of the crypto market could contribute to this.</p>
<p class="s6">Crypto analysts at Changelly have predicted that the price of Uniswap could top $7 in August. For 2023, the analysts have forecasted a maximum price of $8.44 for Uniswap.</p>
Pomerdoge (POMD) Price Prediction
<p class="s6">Unlike Uniswap, crypto experts are more bullish about the prospects of Pomerdoge (POMD) in the coming weeks. Creating a revolutionary P2E game, crypto experts have given very bullish predictions for Pomerdoge.</p>
<p class="s6">In the Pomergame, players will create unique characters known as Pomerdoges. With their Pomerdoges, they will enter into competitions and challenges for amazing rewards. Pomerdogecombines the thrilling gameplay of the Pomergame with a social infrastructure allowing gamers from around the world to communicate.</p>
<p class="s6">With the prospects of combining the best features of top P2E games, the Pomerdoge utility token has been given very bullish ratings. Now in its first presale stage, you can buy a POMD token for as low as $0.007. However, crypto experts have predicted a 280% price surge over the next few weeks as the project prepares for launch.</p>
<p class="s6">One feature that has caught the attention of investors is the shared earnings of Pomerdoge. The team recently announced that early presale investors will receive a share of the game's earnings depending on their token holdings. This innovative model effectively aligns the interests of investors, leading to the growth of the Pomerdoge ecosystem.</p>
Find out more about the Pomerdoge (POMD) Presale Today:
<p class="s6">Website: https://pomerdoge.com/</p>
<p class="s6">Telegram Community: https://t.me/pomerdoge</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis: Narrow Range After 29399 - 5 August 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-after-29399-sally-ho-technical-analysis-5-august-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-4-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-4-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-4-august-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/bitcoin-price-analysis-after-29399-sally-ho-technical-analysis-5-august-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Narrow Range After 29399:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 5 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained in a narrow range early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 29164 area, a downside price objective related to recent selling pressure around the 30350.70 and 29686.41 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Bears kept BTC/USD below the 29399.97 area during a move higher that represented a test of a previous downside price objective related to selling pressure around the 30421 and 29851 levels.&nbsp; Minor buying pressure emerged around the 29083.19 area, right around a previous upside price objective associated with buying pressure around the 28850 area.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 27979, 27409, 27246, and 26501 levels.&nbsp; Below the market, additional downside price objectives include the 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Traders are monitoring the recent depreciating range from 31862.21 to 28850 with upside retracement levels around the 30356, 30711, 31151, and 31217 areas.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29260.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29199.93.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Narrow Range After 29399:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 5 August 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained in a narrow range early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 29164 area, a downside price objective related to recent selling pressure around the 30350.70 and 29686.41 areas.&nbsp; &nbsp;Bears kept BTC/USD below the 29399.97 area during a move higher that represented a test of a previous downside price objective related to selling pressure around the 30421 and 29851 levels.&nbsp; Minor buying pressure emerged around the 29083.19 area, right around a previous upside price objective associated with buying pressure around the 28850 area.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure include the 28432, 27979, 27409, 27246, and 26501 levels.&nbsp; Below the market, additional downside price objectives include the 28213, 28137, 27757, 27430, 27338, 27312, 26348, and 26199 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Also, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historic depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent upside activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28306, 27466, 26428, and 26272 levels.&nbsp; Traders are monitoring the recent depreciating range from 31862.21 to 28850 with upside retracement levels around the 30356, 30711, 31151, and 31217 areas.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30526, 30611, 30762, and 31145 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives related to other levels of buying pressure include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 29260.19 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 29199.93.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ProShares Becomes 11th In Flood Of ETH ETF Applications]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/proshares-becomes-11th-in-flood-of-eth-etf-applications</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ethereum-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/proshares-becomes-11th-in-flood-of-eth-etf-applications</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>ProShares has become the eleventh to apply to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to register an Ether exchange-traded fund (ETF).</p>
Multiple Filings By ProShares
<p>ProShares has joined the ranks of other asset managers seeking to register an Ether exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A total of 11 applications for Ether futures ETFs were submitted to the SEC within a week, with ProShares filing for four separate applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Among them is an equal-weight Bitcoin and Ether ETF that will track the performance of holding long positions in the nearest maturing monthly Bitcoin and Ether futures contracts. The asset manager has also filed for two other Ethereum-focused ETFs: Short Ether Strategy ETF and ProShares Ether Strategy ETF.</p>
Wave Of Ether-Based ETF Applications
<p>ProShares was not alone in the race for Ether ETFs. The surge in applications began when Volatility Shares filed for the Volatility Shares Ether Strategy ETF on July 28. Subsequently, Bitwise Asset Management, Roundhill Financial, Van Eck, ProShares, Grayscale Investments, Direxion, and Valkyrie Investments followed suit, all proposing new Ether futures ETFs.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the SEC has not yet approved any ETF that tracks Ether futures contracts, though Bitcoin futures ETFs have been around since October 2021.</p>
Volatility Could Be First Ether ETF
<p>If the applications go uncontested, the Ether ETFs are set to launch 75 days from their respective filing dates, with Volatility Shares ETF expected to be the first, launching on Oct. 12.</p>
<p>With $173.5 million managed across four exchange-traded funds, the investment firm has the potential to be the first to issue an ETF focused on Ether. Its proposed Ether Strategy ETF (ETHU) aims to invest up to 25% of its assets in cash-settled Ether futures contracts traded on the CFTC-regulated Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME).&nbsp;</p>
Spot BTC ETFs Coming Soon
<p>This surge in Ether-focused ETF applications comes alongside a flurry of filings from major asset management firms looking to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs. BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, is among those seeking to offer the first spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States.</p>
<p>As the SEC reviews these applications, the crypto market eagerly awaits the possibility of new investment opportunities through Ether and Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ProShares has become the eleventh to apply to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to register an Ether exchange-traded fund (ETF).</p>
Multiple Filings By ProShares
<p>ProShares has joined the ranks of other asset managers seeking to register an Ether exchange-traded fund (ETF) with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). A total of 11 applications for Ether futures ETFs were submitted to the SEC within a week, with ProShares filing for four separate applications.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Among them is an equal-weight Bitcoin and Ether ETF that will track the performance of holding long positions in the nearest maturing monthly Bitcoin and Ether futures contracts. The asset manager has also filed for two other Ethereum-focused ETFs: Short Ether Strategy ETF and ProShares Ether Strategy ETF.</p>
Wave Of Ether-Based ETF Applications
<p>ProShares was not alone in the race for Ether ETFs. The surge in applications began when Volatility Shares filed for the Volatility Shares Ether Strategy ETF on July 28. Subsequently, Bitwise Asset Management, Roundhill Financial, Van Eck, ProShares, Grayscale Investments, Direxion, and Valkyrie Investments followed suit, all proposing new Ether futures ETFs.</p>
<p>It is worth noting that the SEC has not yet approved any ETF that tracks Ether futures contracts, though Bitcoin futures ETFs have been around since October 2021.</p>
Volatility Could Be First Ether ETF
<p>If the applications go uncontested, the Ether ETFs are set to launch 75 days from their respective filing dates, with Volatility Shares ETF expected to be the first, launching on Oct. 12.</p>
<p>With $173.5 million managed across four exchange-traded funds, the investment firm has the potential to be the first to issue an ETF focused on Ether. Its proposed Ether Strategy ETF (ETHU) aims to invest up to 25% of its assets in cash-settled Ether futures contracts traded on the CFTC-regulated Chicago Mercantile Exchange (CME).&nbsp;</p>
Spot BTC ETFs Coming Soon
<p>This surge in Ether-focused ETF applications comes alongside a flurry of filings from major asset management firms looking to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs. BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, is among those seeking to offer the first spot Bitcoin ETF in the United States.</p>
<p>As the SEC reviews these applications, the crypto market eagerly awaits the possibility of new investment opportunities through Ether and Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Backs $1.5M Institutional DEX D8X Deal, Betting on Rise From CeFi To DeFi]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/polygon-backs-15m-institutional-dex-d8x-deal-betting-on-rise-from-cefi-to-defi</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d8x-derivatives-v2_16909207660c9bFxutIx.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d8x-derivatives-v2_16909207660c9bFxutIx.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d8x-derivatives-v2_16909207660c9bFxutIx.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:00:46 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/polygon-backs-15m-institutional-dex-d8x-deal-betting-on-rise-from-cefi-to-defi</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Zug, Switzerland, August 4th, 2023, Chainwire</p>D8X's pre-seed round features Polygon Ventures, Axelar Network, Swissborg Ventures and others&nbsp;<p>&nbsp;D8X, an institutional-grade decentralized exchange (DEX) for derivatives on Polygon zkEVM, announced a $1.5 million pre-seed round with support from Polygon Ventures and other notable investors. The capital will help D8X launch a decentralized derivatives trading platform in the second half of 2023 that provides a white-labeling solution to trading partners seeking access to powerful derivatives products.&nbsp;</p><p>The pre-seed round for D8X includes additional participation from Axelar Network, Swissborg Ventures, Cogitent Ventures, Veris Ventures, G1 Ventures, Pragma Ventures, CryptoDiscover and others.</p>&ldquo;DeFi is reshaping the future of finance. Projects like D8X are building the infrastructure that will help legacy finance to leap into web3,&rdquo; said Polygon Co-Founder Sandeep Nailwal.<p>Bridging CeFi to DeFi</p><p>D8X's founders bet on centralized players wanting to offer decentralized crypto derivatives to their clients without having to hire experts to develop in-house market-making and trading engines. D8X provides a white-label solution to partners who act as brokers and earn fees by running their own front ends powered by the D8X trade engine and shared liquidity.</p><p>Financial Engineering On Chain</p><p>D8X&rsquo;s sophisticated on-chain solutions curb costs and offer products that are competitive with centralized exchanges, such as cost-efficient hedging, a prerequisite for building a highly functional derivative trading space. Contract trading allows other DeFi protocols to efficiently hedge on-chain. Their perpetuals can be calibrated for a wide range of assets and support&mdash;as a first in DeFi&mdash;linear, inverse and quanto perpetuals. At launch, a liquidity pool in Lido's staked ETH (stETH) will enable liquidity providers to earn the Lido yield while simultaneously participating in the DEX&rsquo;s earnings.&nbsp;</p><p>D8X is the first business-to-business (B2B) DEX built on Polygon&rsquo;s zkEVM, harnessing the power of zero-knowledge proofs to cut transaction fees, increase security and scale operations across the Polygon and Ethereum networks.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;D8X is part of a driving force of innovation and community in Polygon&rsquo;s 2.0 zero-knowledge space,&rdquo; said Polygon Director of Growth Hamzah Khan.<p>D8X is a fully decentralized DEX following regulatory guidance from Switzerland&rsquo;s financial market regulator FINMA.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;We thank all our investors for believing in D8X's vision to bring truly decentralized derivatives as white-labeling solutions to institutions. With best-in-class financial engineering and risk management, D8X is changing the way decentralized derivatives are traded,&rdquo; said D8X co-founder Caspar Sauter.<p>The production codebase of D8X was audited by PeckShield and an earlier version was audited by Hacken.&nbsp;</p><p>About D8X</p><p>D8X is a Polygon Ventures-supported institutional-grade perpetual futures DEX with a financial engineering approach that elevates the way perpetual futures can be traded on-chain. Think of a powerful and decentralized trading platform on Polygon zkEVM that offers white-labeling to institutions. D8X&rsquo;s pricing mechanism adapts to changing market conditions protecting liquidity providers and profitable traders in volatile periods, resulting in superior DeFi trading conditions.</p><p>D8X | Twitter | GitHub | Docs</p>ContactPR DirectorPatrick BrendelScrib3patrick@scrib3.co]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Zug, Switzerland, August 4th, 2023, Chainwire</p>D8X's pre-seed round features Polygon Ventures, Axelar Network, Swissborg Ventures and others&nbsp;<p>&nbsp;D8X, an institutional-grade decentralized exchange (DEX) for derivatives on Polygon zkEVM, announced a $1.5 million pre-seed round with support from Polygon Ventures and other notable investors. The capital will help D8X launch a decentralized derivatives trading platform in the second half of 2023 that provides a white-labeling solution to trading partners seeking access to powerful derivatives products.&nbsp;</p><p>The pre-seed round for D8X includes additional participation from Axelar Network, Swissborg Ventures, Cogitent Ventures, Veris Ventures, G1 Ventures, Pragma Ventures, CryptoDiscover and others.</p>&ldquo;DeFi is reshaping the future of finance. Projects like D8X are building the infrastructure that will help legacy finance to leap into web3,&rdquo; said Polygon Co-Founder Sandeep Nailwal.<p>Bridging CeFi to DeFi</p><p>D8X's founders bet on centralized players wanting to offer decentralized crypto derivatives to their clients without having to hire experts to develop in-house market-making and trading engines. D8X provides a white-label solution to partners who act as brokers and earn fees by running their own front ends powered by the D8X trade engine and shared liquidity.</p><p>Financial Engineering On Chain</p><p>D8X&rsquo;s sophisticated on-chain solutions curb costs and offer products that are competitive with centralized exchanges, such as cost-efficient hedging, a prerequisite for building a highly functional derivative trading space. Contract trading allows other DeFi protocols to efficiently hedge on-chain. Their perpetuals can be calibrated for a wide range of assets and support&mdash;as a first in DeFi&mdash;linear, inverse and quanto perpetuals. At launch, a liquidity pool in Lido's staked ETH (stETH) will enable liquidity providers to earn the Lido yield while simultaneously participating in the DEX&rsquo;s earnings.&nbsp;</p><p>D8X is the first business-to-business (B2B) DEX built on Polygon&rsquo;s zkEVM, harnessing the power of zero-knowledge proofs to cut transaction fees, increase security and scale operations across the Polygon and Ethereum networks.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;D8X is part of a driving force of innovation and community in Polygon&rsquo;s 2.0 zero-knowledge space,&rdquo; said Polygon Director of Growth Hamzah Khan.<p>D8X is a fully decentralized DEX following regulatory guidance from Switzerland&rsquo;s financial market regulator FINMA.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;We thank all our investors for believing in D8X's vision to bring truly decentralized derivatives as white-labeling solutions to institutions. With best-in-class financial engineering and risk management, D8X is changing the way decentralized derivatives are traded,&rdquo; said D8X co-founder Caspar Sauter.<p>The production codebase of D8X was audited by PeckShield and an earlier version was audited by Hacken.&nbsp;</p><p>About D8X</p><p>D8X is a Polygon Ventures-supported institutional-grade perpetual futures DEX with a financial engineering approach that elevates the way perpetual futures can be traded on-chain. Think of a powerful and decentralized trading platform on Polygon zkEVM that offers white-labeling to institutions. D8X&rsquo;s pricing mechanism adapts to changing market conditions protecting liquidity providers and profitable traders in volatile periods, resulting in superior DeFi trading conditions.</p><p>D8X | Twitter | GitHub | Docs</p>ContactPR DirectorPatrick BrendelScrib3patrick@scrib3.co]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Chair Pivots From Crypto Manhunt To AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-chair-pivots-from-crypto-manhunt-to-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 13:42:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-chair-pivots-from-crypto-manhunt-to-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Gensler, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairperson, has expressed serious concern for AI technology, calling it a serious threat to financial markets.&nbsp;</p>
Gensler Pivoting Regulatory Eye To AI
<p>Under the leadership of its chairperson, the SEC has shifted its focus from cryptocurrency to artificial intelligence (AI), recognizing it as a technology that "warrants the hype." Gensler, who previously dealt with crypto industry scams and fraud, now views AI as the most transformative technology of this generation and warns of the risks it may pose if not properly regulated.</p>
<p>Gensler emphasizes that mass automation driven by AI can have far-reaching implications for the trillions of dollars in assets traded on SEC-regulated markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While AI's predictive capabilities can benefit firms in better serving their clients, there's a concern that it might also be used to obscure responsibility when things go wrong, potentially leading to significant market risks.</p>
A Long-Standing Interest In AI Technology
<p>Gary Gensler has a well-established history with AI, dating back to 1997 when he first delved into it after witnessing Russian chess grandmaster Garry Kasparov's defeat against IBM's supercomputer, Deep Blue. His involvement with AI deepened during his tenure as an MIT professor, leading to his co-authoring a 2020 paper, &ldquo;Deep Learning and Financial Stability,&rdquo; that examined the risks posed by deep learning to the financial system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He claimed that existing financial laws do not have the capacity to address the dangers of algorithmic deep learning. He believes that developers can create AI functions without any limits, and these functions might work against fair market ethics.</p>
Calls for Better Regulation
<p>Gensler asserts that existing regulatory frameworks are ill-equipped to manage the risks associated with AI. He highlights the potential challenges of coordinating AI models among major trading houses, which could lead to increased market volatility and instability. To address the conflict, Gensler has proposed one of the first regulatory frameworks for AI, urging trading houses and money managers to assess whether their use of AI or predictive data could create conflicts of interest.</p>
No Loosening of Crypto Enforcement
<p>Despite pivoting the SEC's attention to AI, Gensler's focus on crypto enforcement remains strong. Numerous lawsuits involving major cryptocurrency firms, such as Ripple, Binance, and Coinbase, are currently pending.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He has also faced severe criticism from leading market experts like Tim Draper and lawmakers like Ritchie Torres for his stance against crypto, calling it detrimental to the industry and the economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the landscape of both AI and crypto continues to evolve, market participants will be closely watching the SEC's actions and decisions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gary Gensler, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairperson, has expressed serious concern for AI technology, calling it a serious threat to financial markets.&nbsp;</p>
Gensler Pivoting Regulatory Eye To AI
<p>Under the leadership of its chairperson, the SEC has shifted its focus from cryptocurrency to artificial intelligence (AI), recognizing it as a technology that "warrants the hype." Gensler, who previously dealt with crypto industry scams and fraud, now views AI as the most transformative technology of this generation and warns of the risks it may pose if not properly regulated.</p>
<p>Gensler emphasizes that mass automation driven by AI can have far-reaching implications for the trillions of dollars in assets traded on SEC-regulated markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While AI's predictive capabilities can benefit firms in better serving their clients, there's a concern that it might also be used to obscure responsibility when things go wrong, potentially leading to significant market risks.</p>
A Long-Standing Interest In AI Technology
<p>Gary Gensler has a well-established history with AI, dating back to 1997 when he first delved into it after witnessing Russian chess grandmaster Garry Kasparov's defeat against IBM's supercomputer, Deep Blue. His involvement with AI deepened during his tenure as an MIT professor, leading to his co-authoring a 2020 paper, &ldquo;Deep Learning and Financial Stability,&rdquo; that examined the risks posed by deep learning to the financial system.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He claimed that existing financial laws do not have the capacity to address the dangers of algorithmic deep learning. He believes that developers can create AI functions without any limits, and these functions might work against fair market ethics.</p>
Calls for Better Regulation
<p>Gensler asserts that existing regulatory frameworks are ill-equipped to manage the risks associated with AI. He highlights the potential challenges of coordinating AI models among major trading houses, which could lead to increased market volatility and instability. To address the conflict, Gensler has proposed one of the first regulatory frameworks for AI, urging trading houses and money managers to assess whether their use of AI or predictive data could create conflicts of interest.</p>
No Loosening of Crypto Enforcement
<p>Despite pivoting the SEC's attention to AI, Gensler's focus on crypto enforcement remains strong. Numerous lawsuits involving major cryptocurrency firms, such as Ripple, Binance, and Coinbase, are currently pending.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He has also faced severe criticism from leading market experts like Tim Draper and lawmakers like Ritchie Torres for his stance against crypto, calling it detrimental to the industry and the economy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the landscape of both AI and crypto continues to evolve, market participants will be closely watching the SEC's actions and decisions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BlackBerry Identifies Notorious Malware Targeting Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/blackberry-identifies-notorious-malware-targeting-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blackberry-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blackberry-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blackberry-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:43:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/blackberry-identifies-notorious-malware-targeting-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Former smartphone giant BlackBerry&rsquo;s cybersecurity division has identified notorious malware families that are exclusively targeting cryptocurrencies and the crypto ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prominent malware includes the likes of RaccoonStealer, SmokeLoader, and Vidar, which hijack computers belonging to unsuspecting users for crypto mining or theft.&nbsp;</p>
BlackBerry Identifies Significant Threats&nbsp;
<p>The findings were published in a &ldquo;Global Threat Intelligence Report&rdquo; published on Thursday. In the report, the former smartphone giant states that they successfully averted over 1.5 million cyberattacks between the months of March and May. The company added that the primary target of these attacks was the healthcare, financial, and government sectors. BlackBerry published the report on X, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Think only enterprises get hacked? If you&rsquo;re a mid-market or small business, you still have a big target on your small or mid-size back. BlackBerry&rsquo;s@aboutsecurity shares why cybercriminals select targets based on impact &amp; how much they&rsquo;re willing to pay.&rdquo;</p>

<p>One of the most significant threats identified during this period was RedLine, a commodity malware that can harvest information such as saved credentials, crypto, and credit card information. RedLine was used to breach Hatch Bank, a fintech banking platform, leading to the loss of significant banking data and crypto. BlackBerry noted in its report,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;During this reporting period, BlackBerry telemetry observed a continuous trend in the use of commodity malware such as RedLine, which can harvest information including saved credentials, credit card information, and cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>

Malware Targeting Crypto&nbsp;
<p>The company also identified several other malware families specifically designed to hijack and use computers for mining purposes. These include RaccoonStealer, Vidar, and SmokeLoader. SmokeLoader, a rogue financial tool, is of particular concern and has been used by Russian hackers and threat actors for rogue crypto mining. RaccoonStealer, a malware that can be sourced from the dark web, has been designed to specifically target crypto wallets and steal information. The malware is capable of obtaining passwords, cookies, web browser data, and cryptocurrency wallet data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another malware, Vidar, targets Linux users and extracts information from crypto wallets and exchanges. Hackers routinely target Linux systems because they are vulnerable to mining attacks. BlackBerry has advised companies to apply security patches to secure themselves from attacks orchestrated by the malware families in question.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Vidar harvests banking information, browser credentials, and cryptocurrency wallets, as well as standard files.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The report also highlighted the Clop ransomware, which was used to target banking and financial institutions. This particular ransomware was also responsible for a data breach at Hatch Bank. The report also highlighted the growing threat to critical sectors from hackers and such malware, emphasizing the importance and urgency for companies to bolster their cybersecurity practices to counter these threats.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hackers have also introduced the Promotei botnet to target Linux-based servers to mine cryptocurrencies such as Monero. Given the botnet&rsquo;s advanced features, tracing and stopping it has been notoriously difficult.</p>
The Crypto Space And Cybersecurity&nbsp;
<p>SonicWall, a cybersecurity firm, has, in a recent report, stated that crypto-jacking incidents have risen a staggering 399% year-on-year. Most of the entities behind these attempts are based in regions where mining bans and sanctions are in force. An estimate by Statista projects the cybersecurity market to reach $162 billion in 2023 on the back of increasing threats to the crypto ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The most recent hack targeting an exchange occurred on the 22nd of July when North Korean hackers from the notorious Lazarus Group targeted the Coinspaid exchange and stole around $37 million.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former smartphone giant BlackBerry&rsquo;s cybersecurity division has identified notorious malware families that are exclusively targeting cryptocurrencies and the crypto ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Prominent malware includes the likes of RaccoonStealer, SmokeLoader, and Vidar, which hijack computers belonging to unsuspecting users for crypto mining or theft.&nbsp;</p>
BlackBerry Identifies Significant Threats&nbsp;
<p>The findings were published in a &ldquo;Global Threat Intelligence Report&rdquo; published on Thursday. In the report, the former smartphone giant states that they successfully averted over 1.5 million cyberattacks between the months of March and May. The company added that the primary target of these attacks was the healthcare, financial, and government sectors. BlackBerry published the report on X, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Think only enterprises get hacked? If you&rsquo;re a mid-market or small business, you still have a big target on your small or mid-size back. BlackBerry&rsquo;s@aboutsecurity shares why cybercriminals select targets based on impact &amp; how much they&rsquo;re willing to pay.&rdquo;</p>

<p>One of the most significant threats identified during this period was RedLine, a commodity malware that can harvest information such as saved credentials, crypto, and credit card information. RedLine was used to breach Hatch Bank, a fintech banking platform, leading to the loss of significant banking data and crypto. BlackBerry noted in its report,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;During this reporting period, BlackBerry telemetry observed a continuous trend in the use of commodity malware such as RedLine, which can harvest information including saved credentials, credit card information, and cryptocurrency.&rdquo;</p>

Malware Targeting Crypto&nbsp;
<p>The company also identified several other malware families specifically designed to hijack and use computers for mining purposes. These include RaccoonStealer, Vidar, and SmokeLoader. SmokeLoader, a rogue financial tool, is of particular concern and has been used by Russian hackers and threat actors for rogue crypto mining. RaccoonStealer, a malware that can be sourced from the dark web, has been designed to specifically target crypto wallets and steal information. The malware is capable of obtaining passwords, cookies, web browser data, and cryptocurrency wallet data.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Another malware, Vidar, targets Linux users and extracts information from crypto wallets and exchanges. Hackers routinely target Linux systems because they are vulnerable to mining attacks. BlackBerry has advised companies to apply security patches to secure themselves from attacks orchestrated by the malware families in question.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Vidar harvests banking information, browser credentials, and cryptocurrency wallets, as well as standard files.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The report also highlighted the Clop ransomware, which was used to target banking and financial institutions. This particular ransomware was also responsible for a data breach at Hatch Bank. The report also highlighted the growing threat to critical sectors from hackers and such malware, emphasizing the importance and urgency for companies to bolster their cybersecurity practices to counter these threats.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Hackers have also introduced the Promotei botnet to target Linux-based servers to mine cryptocurrencies such as Monero. Given the botnet&rsquo;s advanced features, tracing and stopping it has been notoriously difficult.</p>
The Crypto Space And Cybersecurity&nbsp;
<p>SonicWall, a cybersecurity firm, has, in a recent report, stated that crypto-jacking incidents have risen a staggering 399% year-on-year. Most of the entities behind these attempts are based in regions where mining bans and sanctions are in force. An estimate by Statista projects the cybersecurity market to reach $162 billion in 2023 on the back of increasing threats to the crypto ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The most recent hack targeting an exchange occurred on the 22nd of July when North Korean hackers from the notorious Lazarus Group targeted the Coinspaid exchange and stole around $37 million.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Revolut the latest fintech to shutter operations in US]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/revolut-the-latest-fintech-to-shutter-operations-in-us</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/rev.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/rev.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/rev.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:52:30 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/revolut-the-latest-fintech-to-shutter-operations-in-us</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In light of the evolving regulatory landscape surrounding digital currencies in the US, Revolut has decided to shut down its crypto offerings in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By October 3, 2023, US-based users of Revolut will experience a halt in their crypto services, preventing any further transactions on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the broader crypto industry grapples with the SEC's viewpoint, which leans towards classifying a significant portion of digital currencies as securities, Revolut has taken proactive steps. The company has already delisted Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC) given that the SEC had opined that they were securities. Their removal is set to be finalised by September 18.&nbsp;</p>
<p>First published in an article earlier today by Decrypt, a spokesperson for Revolut told the news platform:</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of the evolving regulatory environment and the uncertainties around the crypto market in the US, we&rsquo;ve taken the difficult decision, together with our US banking partner, to suspend access to cryptocurrencies through Revolut in the U.S. This decision has not been taken lightly, and we understand the disappointment this may cause.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Regulatory action began ramping up when the SEC moved against major players in the crypto industry. The allegations, made by the SEC, centred around registration discrepancies, and have been met with counter arguments by the implicated platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite the challenges in the US, Revolut's global crypto initiatives are on a steady course. The company has been continuing to expand in regions such as Europe. A popular staking program, available to users in the UK and several European countries, offered the opportunity to earn cryptocurrency rewards, and was well received.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision to shutter its crypto services in the US, set to commence on September 2, 2023, highlights the issues between innovation in the crypto space and the ever-evolving regulatory frameworks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the US continues to provide what is seen as a muddy and opaque framework for cryptocurrencies going forward, it is likely to lose far more companies of the calibre of Revolut, as Asia and Europe step up in an effort to capture the markets that such an innovative technology provides.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In light of the evolving regulatory landscape surrounding digital currencies in the US, Revolut has decided to shut down its crypto offerings in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By October 3, 2023, US-based users of Revolut will experience a halt in their crypto services, preventing any further transactions on the platform.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the broader crypto industry grapples with the SEC's viewpoint, which leans towards classifying a significant portion of digital currencies as securities, Revolut has taken proactive steps. The company has already delisted Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), and Polygon (MATIC) given that the SEC had opined that they were securities. Their removal is set to be finalised by September 18.&nbsp;</p>
<p>First published in an article earlier today by Decrypt, a spokesperson for Revolut told the news platform:</p>

<p>&ldquo;As a result of the evolving regulatory environment and the uncertainties around the crypto market in the US, we&rsquo;ve taken the difficult decision, together with our US banking partner, to suspend access to cryptocurrencies through Revolut in the U.S. This decision has not been taken lightly, and we understand the disappointment this may cause.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Regulatory action began ramping up when the SEC moved against major players in the crypto industry. The allegations, made by the SEC, centred around registration discrepancies, and have been met with counter arguments by the implicated platforms.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite the challenges in the US, Revolut's global crypto initiatives are on a steady course. The company has been continuing to expand in regions such as Europe. A popular staking program, available to users in the UK and several European countries, offered the opportunity to earn cryptocurrency rewards, and was well received.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The decision to shutter its crypto services in the US, set to commence on September 2, 2023, highlights the issues between innovation in the crypto space and the ever-evolving regulatory frameworks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the US continues to provide what is seen as a muddy and opaque framework for cryptocurrencies going forward, it is likely to lose far more companies of the calibre of Revolut, as Asia and Europe step up in an effort to capture the markets that such an innovative technology provides.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[China is far more important than US for crypto sector]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/china-is-far-more-important-than-us-for-crypto-sector</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uschin.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uschin.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uschin.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:57:20 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/china-is-far-more-important-than-us-for-crypto-sector</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the West far more attention is paid to the US as regards crypto, but China and Asia in general are the ones buying.</p>
A US in turmoil not good for crypto
<p>With the US debt pile increasing rapidly from its current impossibly sized $32 trillion on which $1 trillion interest needs to be paid annually, and a government and its financial watchdogs trying their best to suppress and close down crypto companies, this cannot be the best jurisdiction to support the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The US debt cannot be funded, and the Federal Reserve pushing up interest rates will only serve to close smaller businesses and put American people out of work. The crypto industry would create jobs, but it appears that this US administration does not want them.</p>
<p>A recent downgrade of the US by the Fitch ratings agency would suggest that the cat is out of the bag and the craziness of US economic policy, and the ineptness of its government is being called to account.</p>
<p>Jamie Dimon, CEO of JP Morgan, and obviously a staunch supporter of the US banking system, said of the downgrade:</p>

<p>&ldquo;It doesn&rsquo;t really matter that much. The markets decide, not the rating agencies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Mr Dimon might want to hope and pray that the markets carry on turning a blind eye to the house of cards that the US has become. Buying its own debt, and just being able to print more money doesn&rsquo;t provide the solid base that its economy needs.</p>
Crypto exchanges worldwide tell an interesting story
<p>So where does this leave crypto?</p>
<p>As per data from The Block, on North American exchanges for the month of July, a total of $42 billion in exchange volume was achieved. For exchanges based in Europe for the same month, the volume was $18 billion, and for those based in Asia it was a whopping $340 billion, which dwarfs that of both North America and Europe combined.</p>
<p>These figures mean that the crypto trading market is only really happening in Asia, with around 8 times the volume of that taking place in North America.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But what of China? Crypto trading has been banned here. So why, according to the Wall Street Journal, did Binance just do a monthly crypto trading volume of $90 billion in China? This volume also makes China the biggest contributor of trading volume to Binance worldwide.</p>
<p>Either China has had a major rethink on crypto, or it just cannot suppress crypto within its own borders. But then if one looks to its overseas territory of Hong Kong, and how it is starting to give out licences to crypto companies and is setting itself up to be one of the major crypto hubs for Asia, it gives a bit more insight into the Chinese new thinking on crypto.</p>
<p>The US is tearing itself apart with poor government and internal division, and is in the process of excluding a new and innovative technology from its shores. China could certainly be the major beneficiary of this poorly thought out US policy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the West far more attention is paid to the US as regards crypto, but China and Asia in general are the ones buying.</p>
A US in turmoil not good for crypto
<p>With the US debt pile increasing rapidly from its current impossibly sized $32 trillion on which $1 trillion interest needs to be paid annually, and a government and its financial watchdogs trying their best to suppress and close down crypto companies, this cannot be the best jurisdiction to support the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The US debt cannot be funded, and the Federal Reserve pushing up interest rates will only serve to close smaller businesses and put American people out of work. The crypto industry would create jobs, but it appears that this US administration does not want them.</p>
<p>A recent downgrade of the US by the Fitch ratings agency would suggest that the cat is out of the bag and the craziness of US economic policy, and the ineptness of its government is being called to account.</p>
<p>Jamie Dimon, CEO of JP Morgan, and obviously a staunch supporter of the US banking system, said of the downgrade:</p>

<p>&ldquo;It doesn&rsquo;t really matter that much. The markets decide, not the rating agencies.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Mr Dimon might want to hope and pray that the markets carry on turning a blind eye to the house of cards that the US has become. Buying its own debt, and just being able to print more money doesn&rsquo;t provide the solid base that its economy needs.</p>
Crypto exchanges worldwide tell an interesting story
<p>So where does this leave crypto?</p>
<p>As per data from The Block, on North American exchanges for the month of July, a total of $42 billion in exchange volume was achieved. For exchanges based in Europe for the same month, the volume was $18 billion, and for those based in Asia it was a whopping $340 billion, which dwarfs that of both North America and Europe combined.</p>
<p>These figures mean that the crypto trading market is only really happening in Asia, with around 8 times the volume of that taking place in North America.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But what of China? Crypto trading has been banned here. So why, according to the Wall Street Journal, did Binance just do a monthly crypto trading volume of $90 billion in China? This volume also makes China the biggest contributor of trading volume to Binance worldwide.</p>
<p>Either China has had a major rethink on crypto, or it just cannot suppress crypto within its own borders. But then if one looks to its overseas territory of Hong Kong, and how it is starting to give out licences to crypto companies and is setting itself up to be one of the major crypto hubs for Asia, it gives a bit more insight into the Chinese new thinking on crypto.</p>
<p>The US is tearing itself apart with poor government and internal division, and is in the process of excluding a new and innovative technology from its shores. China could certainly be the major beneficiary of this poorly thought out US policy.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Charges 18 Defendants in DEBT Box, Freezes Its Assets]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-charges-18-defendants-in-debt-box-freezes-its-assets</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 10:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/sec-charges-18-defendants-in-debt-box-freezes-its-assets</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC on Thursday secured a temporary asset freeze, restraining order and further emergency relief against Digital Licensing, a Draper, Utah-based entity operating as DEBT Box. </p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced it had obtained emergency relief against DEBT Box and four of the company&rsquo;s principals.</p>
<p>In its continued crackdown on crypto fraud, the SEC obtained a temporary asset freeze, restraining order, and other emergency relief against Digital Licensing Inc., a Draper, Utah-based entity operating as &ldquo;DEBT Box.&rdquo; The agency also acted against four of the company&rsquo;s principals, Jason Anderson, his brother Jacob Anderson, Schad Brannon, and Roydon Nelson, along with 13 other defendants for their connecting to a scheme to sell crypto asset securities to US investors which raised around $50 million and an undisclosed amount of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH).</p>
<p>According to the securities agency, the defendant sold unregistered securities called &ldquo;node licenses&rdquo; to unsuspecting victims. In the scheme, which started operating in March 2021, the defendants said to investors that the licenses would mine crypto and, in turn, increase in value when the defendants actually created the crypto using code on a blockchain.</p>
<p>Tracy S. Combs, Director of the SEC&rsquo;s Salt Lake Regional Office, said in a press release:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We allege that DEBT Box and its principals lied to investors about virtually every material aspect of their unregistered offering of securities, including by falsely stating that they were engaged in crypto asset mining.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Adding,</p>

<p>&ldquo;We filed this emergency action to protect the victims of the defendants&rsquo; unlawful actions and stop further harm.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The SEC charged the 18 defendants, including the four principals mentioned above, with engaging in unregistered securities offerings.</p>

<p>&ldquo;DEBT Box, Jason Anderson, Jacob Anderson, Brannon, Nelson, Franklin, Western Oil, and Bowen were also charged with violations of the antifraud provisions of the federal securities laws. Jason Anderson, Jacob Anderson, Brannon, Nelson, Bowen, Mark Schuler, Benjamin Daniels, Joseph Martinez, Travis Flaherty, Brendon Stangis, Matthew Fritzsche, B &amp; B Investment Group, LLC, and iX Global, LLC were charged with acting as unregistered brokers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The SEC charges seek permanent injunctive relief, the return of the ill-gotten gains, and further civil penalties.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US SEC on Thursday secured a temporary asset freeze, restraining order and further emergency relief against Digital Licensing, a Draper, Utah-based entity operating as DEBT Box. </p>
<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced it had obtained emergency relief against DEBT Box and four of the company&rsquo;s principals.</p>
<p>In its continued crackdown on crypto fraud, the SEC obtained a temporary asset freeze, restraining order, and other emergency relief against Digital Licensing Inc., a Draper, Utah-based entity operating as &ldquo;DEBT Box.&rdquo; The agency also acted against four of the company&rsquo;s principals, Jason Anderson, his brother Jacob Anderson, Schad Brannon, and Roydon Nelson, along with 13 other defendants for their connecting to a scheme to sell crypto asset securities to US investors which raised around $50 million and an undisclosed amount of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH).</p>
<p>According to the securities agency, the defendant sold unregistered securities called &ldquo;node licenses&rdquo; to unsuspecting victims. In the scheme, which started operating in March 2021, the defendants said to investors that the licenses would mine crypto and, in turn, increase in value when the defendants actually created the crypto using code on a blockchain.</p>
<p>Tracy S. Combs, Director of the SEC&rsquo;s Salt Lake Regional Office, said in a press release:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We allege that DEBT Box and its principals lied to investors about virtually every material aspect of their unregistered offering of securities, including by falsely stating that they were engaged in crypto asset mining.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Adding,</p>

<p>&ldquo;We filed this emergency action to protect the victims of the defendants&rsquo; unlawful actions and stop further harm.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The SEC charged the 18 defendants, including the four principals mentioned above, with engaging in unregistered securities offerings.</p>

<p>&ldquo;DEBT Box, Jason Anderson, Jacob Anderson, Brannon, Nelson, Franklin, Western Oil, and Bowen were also charged with violations of the antifraud provisions of the federal securities laws. Jason Anderson, Jacob Anderson, Brannon, Nelson, Bowen, Mark Schuler, Benjamin Daniels, Joseph Martinez, Travis Flaherty, Brendon Stangis, Matthew Fritzsche, B &amp; B Investment Group, LLC, and iX Global, LLC were charged with acting as unregistered brokers.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The SEC charges seek permanent injunctive relief, the return of the ill-gotten gains, and further civil penalties.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Shiba Memu Announces BitMart Listing As Presale Soars Past $1.5M Milestone]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/shiba-memu-announces-bitmart-listing-as-presale-soars-past-15m-milestone</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/prshib_1691061164UclWT8Q2sT.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/prshib_1691061164UclWT8Q2sT.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/prshib_1691061164UclWT8Q2sT.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 09:59:35 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/shiba-memu-announces-bitmart-listing-as-presale-soars-past-15m-milestone</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, UK, August 4th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Shiba Memu, a buzzing new AI-backed crypto meme coin, is creating more stir as it surges past the $1.5 million fundraising milestone and makes its exchange announcement debut with a BitMart listing &ndash; all within just one month of its presale starting.</p><p>Getting listed on an established exchange like Bitmart, a significant player since 2017 that showcases an impressive roster of over 1500 cryptocurrency pairs, underscores a smart strategic play for the project.</p><p>The main idea behind Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI was born out of the team's experiences with excessive marketing agency fees in previous business endeavors. This motivated them to take the initiative, developing a self-promoting AI that can scale into a variety of practical applications.</p><p>The tangible concept, combined with the appealing Shiba Memu mascot, has fueled a wave of interest from investors and crypto enthusiasts who recognize the long-term potential of the project.</p><p>Shiba Memu is currently priced at $0.0181, with a scheduled price increase every 24 hours, courtesy of the team's expertly programmed smart contract. This enticing mechanism is especially appealing to presale fans, as it guarantees the token purchase price will always be lower than the eventual exchange listing price. For example, if you bought today at $0.0181 the increase by the end of the presale on day 60 would be 35%.</p><p>SHMU tokens are available to purchase on the official Shiba Memu website here.</p>Why is Shiba Memu Trending?&nbsp;<p>Shiba Memu's notable success can be attributed to the untapped potential of its AI. Still in its early stages, the AI employs Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Sentiment Analysis to scan the web, primarily focusing on social platforms, for Shiba Memu mentions and tailors its promotions accordingly.</p><p>This has transformed the brand image from a simple cute dog meme to a funny and engaging dog meme with a sharp sense of humor! The glimpse into the project's future, and the forthcoming AI dashboards scheduled for Q4, are whetting investor appetite for meme coins with tangible utility.</p><p>The project boasts a healthy outlook in its tokenomics, with 85% of tokens being dedicated to its presale, 10% to exchange listing liquidity and 5% to development - putting real power in the hands of SHMU owners in the future development of the dApp.</p>Crypto Community Backing Is Driving Shiba Memu Engagement Through the Roof<p>With more and more hard-hitting YouTubers getting involved with the project, it&rsquo;s no wonder that global enthusiasm for the project is growing by the day.</p><p>Prominent Youtuber NFTsGuide, with over 700K followers recently described the project as a &lsquo;AI Marketing Powerhouse&rsquo;, which again goes to show how the developers premise of building self-marketing tech is relatable to not only investors but crypto enthusiasts.</p><p>Some have even speculated that Shiba Memu is in the running to dominate other memes, with Crypto Moonlight&rsquo;s channel suggesting this could be an interesting opportunity for those who missed out on PEPE and others like Austin Hilton making some bold price predictions and calculations about how much SHMU investors would need to hold to hit significant ROI.</p><p>The rapidity with which word has spread and the interest it&rsquo;s gauged from seasoned hands like those above goes to show that the marketing tactics implemented so far are gaining serious traction - it will be interesting indeed to see how this one plays out.</p><p>Now on day 32 of the presale which is scheduled to run for 60 days, at which time the price will have increased 119% from $0.011125 to $0.024400, Shiba Memu is truly racing ahead &ndash; time is running out for investors looking to get involved.&nbsp;</p>About Shiba Memu<p>Shiba Memu (SHMU) is a fresh dog-themed crypto meme coin that supports a platform utilizing AI to promote itself and generate buzz in online communities. This technology is poised to gain traction within the blockchain industry in the coming years, establishing Shiba Memu's position as an industry innovator. The innovative AI technology behind the project demonstrates true innovation in the meme coin sector, offering small and medium-sized businesses access to effective marketing solutions that could significantly cut costs and provide competitive advantage.</p><p>Learn more about this innovative AI-powered dog meme on the official website.</p><p>For more information: Website | Whitepaper | Socials</p>ContactShiba Memu PressShiba Memupr@shibamemu.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, UK, August 4th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Shiba Memu, a buzzing new AI-backed crypto meme coin, is creating more stir as it surges past the $1.5 million fundraising milestone and makes its exchange announcement debut with a BitMart listing &ndash; all within just one month of its presale starting.</p><p>Getting listed on an established exchange like Bitmart, a significant player since 2017 that showcases an impressive roster of over 1500 cryptocurrency pairs, underscores a smart strategic play for the project.</p><p>The main idea behind Shiba Memu&rsquo;s AI was born out of the team's experiences with excessive marketing agency fees in previous business endeavors. This motivated them to take the initiative, developing a self-promoting AI that can scale into a variety of practical applications.</p><p>The tangible concept, combined with the appealing Shiba Memu mascot, has fueled a wave of interest from investors and crypto enthusiasts who recognize the long-term potential of the project.</p><p>Shiba Memu is currently priced at $0.0181, with a scheduled price increase every 24 hours, courtesy of the team's expertly programmed smart contract. This enticing mechanism is especially appealing to presale fans, as it guarantees the token purchase price will always be lower than the eventual exchange listing price. For example, if you bought today at $0.0181 the increase by the end of the presale on day 60 would be 35%.</p><p>SHMU tokens are available to purchase on the official Shiba Memu website here.</p>Why is Shiba Memu Trending?&nbsp;<p>Shiba Memu's notable success can be attributed to the untapped potential of its AI. Still in its early stages, the AI employs Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Sentiment Analysis to scan the web, primarily focusing on social platforms, for Shiba Memu mentions and tailors its promotions accordingly.</p><p>This has transformed the brand image from a simple cute dog meme to a funny and engaging dog meme with a sharp sense of humor! The glimpse into the project's future, and the forthcoming AI dashboards scheduled for Q4, are whetting investor appetite for meme coins with tangible utility.</p><p>The project boasts a healthy outlook in its tokenomics, with 85% of tokens being dedicated to its presale, 10% to exchange listing liquidity and 5% to development - putting real power in the hands of SHMU owners in the future development of the dApp.</p>Crypto Community Backing Is Driving Shiba Memu Engagement Through the Roof<p>With more and more hard-hitting YouTubers getting involved with the project, it&rsquo;s no wonder that global enthusiasm for the project is growing by the day.</p><p>Prominent Youtuber NFTsGuide, with over 700K followers recently described the project as a &lsquo;AI Marketing Powerhouse&rsquo;, which again goes to show how the developers premise of building self-marketing tech is relatable to not only investors but crypto enthusiasts.</p><p>Some have even speculated that Shiba Memu is in the running to dominate other memes, with Crypto Moonlight&rsquo;s channel suggesting this could be an interesting opportunity for those who missed out on PEPE and others like Austin Hilton making some bold price predictions and calculations about how much SHMU investors would need to hold to hit significant ROI.</p><p>The rapidity with which word has spread and the interest it&rsquo;s gauged from seasoned hands like those above goes to show that the marketing tactics implemented so far are gaining serious traction - it will be interesting indeed to see how this one plays out.</p><p>Now on day 32 of the presale which is scheduled to run for 60 days, at which time the price will have increased 119% from $0.011125 to $0.024400, Shiba Memu is truly racing ahead &ndash; time is running out for investors looking to get involved.&nbsp;</p>About Shiba Memu<p>Shiba Memu (SHMU) is a fresh dog-themed crypto meme coin that supports a platform utilizing AI to promote itself and generate buzz in online communities. This technology is poised to gain traction within the blockchain industry in the coming years, establishing Shiba Memu's position as an industry innovator. The innovative AI technology behind the project demonstrates true innovation in the meme coin sector, offering small and medium-sized businesses access to effective marketing solutions that could significantly cut costs and provide competitive advantage.</p><p>Learn more about this innovative AI-powered dog meme on the official website.</p><p>For more information: Website | Whitepaper | Socials</p>ContactShiba Memu PressShiba Memupr@shibamemu.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[What Price Could XRP Eventually Reach?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/what-price-could-xrp-eventually-reach</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xrp-6.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xrp-6.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xrp-6.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:53:27 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/what-price-could-xrp-eventually-reach</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Following Ripple's partial victory over the SEC, it was ruled XRP does not constitute a security concerning programmatic sales. What is a realistic price prediction following this decision, and what is it based on? </p>
<p>Popular Twitter personality Shannon Thorp was recently asked to give a price prediction for XRP with no time frame or a set idea of circulating supply or the dollar amount it equates to. Thorp has noticed a trend among the XRP followers (the #XRPArmy as they are better known on Twitter) and found the camp to be divided. One side bases their future views and prediction based solely on charts, taking guidance from past price action and trends that Bitcoin &ndash; the biggest crypto by market cap, follows to determine short-term price predictions. The other side bases their views on Ripple and XRP's utility. This camp of XRP supporters is of the opinion that partnerships and the replacement of "antiquated systems" will determine XRP's price.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">People have long asked what will be the price of $XRP, when will this &ldquo;utility&rdquo; come? In my opinion, now more than ever I see a divided #XRPArmy! One side looking at only charts, taking cues from the past and trends that follow Bitcoin to draw short term price predictions. Whilst&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Shannon Thorp (@thorpshannon87) July 29, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Thorp believes no side is correct since XRP does not constitute a security. In Ms Thorp's view, it is wrong to continue making price predictions for XRP as a "security."</p>
<p>After the XRP ruling, the FedNow announcement and the US Congress passing its proposed crypto regulation bill to Senate, estimates of XRP's future price have come under question.</p>
<p>Vahil Capital released a white paper on XRP's price, which indicates XRP's price could reach anywhere between $3,500 and $21,900. Vahil based its predictions on two years of research and six distinct quantitative models. The VC firm's prediction has been met with shock and scepticism, to say the least, and this apprehension is based on chart analysts stating the chart does not allow for such a prediction.</p>
Ms Thorp was quick to call out an issue with the charts:
<p>She argues that if a range for XRP is set at $1.00 - $5.00, what it ultimately means is that if one company owned all the XRP tokens in circulation, then yes, it would mean that that company in possession of all 100 billion tokens would have a Liquidity Strength of (LS) anywhere between $100B - $500B - bear in mind that is a burn rate for every transaction regardless of the amount. An LS such as this does not factor for economic growth, messaging and settling and does not account for the benefits of using XRP.</p>
<p>Thorp explains the situation concerning SWIFT &ndash; SWIFT is one of the systems Ripple aims to improve on. As it stands, SWIFT handles 44.8 million messages in a day, does not include settlements, and at this point, is only half of what Ripple can do. Based on a $7 trillion value for SWIFT in a day (not 24/7 or 365). She suggests that if Ripple, in its ten years of innovation and partnerships, has only gained 30% of SWIFTs value, it would put XRP's daily value at $2.1 trillion (about 13.2 million messages). XRP settles in 1 -5 seconds, and the liquidity would be there. However, settlements are fast, but if a user were to send a $750 million transaction with an LS of $1.00, for argument's sake, it equates to 10% of all that bank's XRP.</p>
To determine a price prediction, Thorp follows the following logic:
<p>Considering all banks globally, all the XRP that has been burnt through other transactions, all the XRP tokens all its holder own, and all the XRP given to other large banks and the XRP tokens awarded to its creators. Then account for the XRP on liquidity hubs and exchanges and present an amount representing a range, using 50B-75B XRP at any one-time support LS. Then spread that across 300 -1000 banks, liquidity providers and governments.</p>
The math follows:
<p>75 billion XRP at $1.00 amounts to $75 billion. Take $75B and divide by 1,000 banks equals $75 million XRP/dollars for each bank or liquidity provider. Further, assume big banks hold more XRP than small banks, and small banks would use liquidity providers. Then consider that Ripple has released all the XRP tokens to reach a circulating supply of 75 billion.</p>
<p>LS would be $75M per bank, and a top-tier bank such as J.P. Morgan moves more than $8 trillion a day and considers service overlaps with SWIFT and the assumption that Ripple only has 10% of the market ($800 billion). This movement only accounts for cross-border transactions, not CBDCs, derivatives, real estate, NFTs and technical parallels. Vahil Capital's price prediction and logic do not seem so outrageous anymore.</p>
<p>Thorp finally comes to her own price prediction. The Twitter personality has placed her prediction anywhere from $100 - $500 in the short term of four to seven months. She argues that it all comes down to LS if XRP is $100 at a supply of only 50 billion, which equates to an LS of $5 trillion and at $500 makes an LS of $25 trillion. The logic is that this gives the market room to grow and breathe and ensures that no one company needs to own billions of XRP tokens for day-to-day operation.</p>
XRP Is On the Rise But Has Not Even Reached $1
<p>While the ruling was highly bullish for XRP, and the price soared over 100% following Judge Torres's order, it has not continued its momentum. XRP reached a high of $0.84 on July 19 but currently trades at $0.66.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following Ripple's partial victory over the SEC, it was ruled XRP does not constitute a security concerning programmatic sales. What is a realistic price prediction following this decision, and what is it based on? </p>
<p>Popular Twitter personality Shannon Thorp was recently asked to give a price prediction for XRP with no time frame or a set idea of circulating supply or the dollar amount it equates to. Thorp has noticed a trend among the XRP followers (the #XRPArmy as they are better known on Twitter) and found the camp to be divided. One side bases their future views and prediction based solely on charts, taking guidance from past price action and trends that Bitcoin &ndash; the biggest crypto by market cap, follows to determine short-term price predictions. The other side bases their views on Ripple and XRP's utility. This camp of XRP supporters is of the opinion that partnerships and the replacement of "antiquated systems" will determine XRP's price.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">People have long asked what will be the price of $XRP, when will this &ldquo;utility&rdquo; come? In my opinion, now more than ever I see a divided #XRPArmy! One side looking at only charts, taking cues from the past and trends that follow Bitcoin to draw short term price predictions. Whilst&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Shannon Thorp (@thorpshannon87) July 29, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Thorp believes no side is correct since XRP does not constitute a security. In Ms Thorp's view, it is wrong to continue making price predictions for XRP as a "security."</p>
<p>After the XRP ruling, the FedNow announcement and the US Congress passing its proposed crypto regulation bill to Senate, estimates of XRP's future price have come under question.</p>
<p>Vahil Capital released a white paper on XRP's price, which indicates XRP's price could reach anywhere between $3,500 and $21,900. Vahil based its predictions on two years of research and six distinct quantitative models. The VC firm's prediction has been met with shock and scepticism, to say the least, and this apprehension is based on chart analysts stating the chart does not allow for such a prediction.</p>
Ms Thorp was quick to call out an issue with the charts:
<p>She argues that if a range for XRP is set at $1.00 - $5.00, what it ultimately means is that if one company owned all the XRP tokens in circulation, then yes, it would mean that that company in possession of all 100 billion tokens would have a Liquidity Strength of (LS) anywhere between $100B - $500B - bear in mind that is a burn rate for every transaction regardless of the amount. An LS such as this does not factor for economic growth, messaging and settling and does not account for the benefits of using XRP.</p>
<p>Thorp explains the situation concerning SWIFT &ndash; SWIFT is one of the systems Ripple aims to improve on. As it stands, SWIFT handles 44.8 million messages in a day, does not include settlements, and at this point, is only half of what Ripple can do. Based on a $7 trillion value for SWIFT in a day (not 24/7 or 365). She suggests that if Ripple, in its ten years of innovation and partnerships, has only gained 30% of SWIFTs value, it would put XRP's daily value at $2.1 trillion (about 13.2 million messages). XRP settles in 1 -5 seconds, and the liquidity would be there. However, settlements are fast, but if a user were to send a $750 million transaction with an LS of $1.00, for argument's sake, it equates to 10% of all that bank's XRP.</p>
To determine a price prediction, Thorp follows the following logic:
<p>Considering all banks globally, all the XRP that has been burnt through other transactions, all the XRP tokens all its holder own, and all the XRP given to other large banks and the XRP tokens awarded to its creators. Then account for the XRP on liquidity hubs and exchanges and present an amount representing a range, using 50B-75B XRP at any one-time support LS. Then spread that across 300 -1000 banks, liquidity providers and governments.</p>
The math follows:
<p>75 billion XRP at $1.00 amounts to $75 billion. Take $75B and divide by 1,000 banks equals $75 million XRP/dollars for each bank or liquidity provider. Further, assume big banks hold more XRP than small banks, and small banks would use liquidity providers. Then consider that Ripple has released all the XRP tokens to reach a circulating supply of 75 billion.</p>
<p>LS would be $75M per bank, and a top-tier bank such as J.P. Morgan moves more than $8 trillion a day and considers service overlaps with SWIFT and the assumption that Ripple only has 10% of the market ($800 billion). This movement only accounts for cross-border transactions, not CBDCs, derivatives, real estate, NFTs and technical parallels. Vahil Capital's price prediction and logic do not seem so outrageous anymore.</p>
<p>Thorp finally comes to her own price prediction. The Twitter personality has placed her prediction anywhere from $100 - $500 in the short term of four to seven months. She argues that it all comes down to LS if XRP is $100 at a supply of only 50 billion, which equates to an LS of $5 trillion and at $500 makes an LS of $25 trillion. The logic is that this gives the market room to grow and breathe and ensures that no one company needs to own billions of XRP tokens for day-to-day operation.</p>
XRP Is On the Rise But Has Not Even Reached $1
<p>While the ruling was highly bullish for XRP, and the price soared over 100% following Judge Torres's order, it has not continued its momentum. XRP reached a high of $0.84 on July 19 but currently trades at $0.66.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Curve Extends Olive Branch, Offers 10% Bug Bounty To Hackers]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/curve-extends-olive-branch-offers-10-bug-bounty-to-hackers</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/curve-728x350.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/curve-extends-olive-branch-offers-10-bug-bounty-to-hackers</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Finance platforms Curve Finance, Alchemix, and Metronome have announced a joint initiative to recover the stolen funds in the wake of the recent exploits that hit Curve&rsquo;s pools.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exploit resulted in a loss of around $70 million worth of crypto assets, meaning the bounty offered is around $7 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Resolution In Sight?&nbsp;
<p>The DeFi platforms impacted by the Curve heist are doing everything they can to recover the stolen funds. According to on-chain data, Curve, Alchemix, and Metronome have offered the hackers a 10% bounty as a reward, urging the hackers to return the remaining 90% of the stolen funds. Curve Finance updated users about their offer to the hackers via X, stressing that they would face no further legal or law enforcement actions if they chose to return the funds. Curve stated in the joint message sent via Etherscan,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The offer comes with a guarantee of no further legal actions or involvement of law enforcement. We want to resolve this in a civilized manner. You will have no risk of us pursuing this further, no risk of law enforcement issues.&rdquo;</p>

Final Warning
<p>The three protocols gave the hackers a deadline of 6th August to accept their offer. They added that should the hackers refuse the offer; the protocols would expand the bounty to the public and offer the 10% to anyone who would be able to identify them in a way that leads to their conviction. The stark warning read,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you choose not to partake in the voluntary return and complete the process by 6th August at 0800 UTC, we will expand the bounty to the public and offer the full 10% to the person who is able to identify you in a way that leads to your conviction in the courts. We will pursue you from all angles with the full extent of the law.&rdquo;</p>

<p>All three protocols have opened a direct line of communication with the hackers through curvenegotiation@protonmail.com and urged the hackers to respond and take the offer to avoid legal action. The protocols also stressed that any individuals responding for negotiations would need to verify their credentials and ownership of their email address on-chain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Curve and the other protocol&rsquo;s outreach is similar to the strategy adopted by DeFi protocol Euler Finance, which fell victim to a crippling hack earlier in the year. However, the protocol was able to negotiate with the hackers and retrieve the stolen funds successfully.&nbsp;</p>
The Curve Hack&nbsp;
<p>The Curve exploit saw around $70 million worth of crypto stolen by hackers. This figure included CRV tokens worth around $4.52 million, which led to a significant drop in the price of the token. At the heart of the exploit was a vulnerability in Vyper called a reentrancy bug. This vulnerability allowed hackers to drain several stablecoin pools on Curve, leading to considerable chaos in the DeFi ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi markets were further spooked after reports emerged that Curve Finance founder Michael Egorov had allegedly taken several loans using around 47% of CRV&rsquo;s circulating supply. Several DeFi protocols, such as Aave, Abracadabra, and several others, faced major implications following the drop in CRV&rsquo;s value. This is because the decline put Egorov&rsquo;s $168 million lending position at risk of liquidation, potentially unleashing a domino effect on DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Curve and Egorov found support from prominent names in the crypto and DeFi space, such as Power DeFi user DCF God, Tron Foundation CEO Justin Sun, and Jeffrey Huang, also known as Machi Big Brother. Sun, DCF God, and Huang purchased large quantities of CRV from Egorov, helping reduce the principal value of Egorov&rsquo;s loan from $63 million to $54 million. Other players who assisted Egorov were Cream Finance, which sent Egorov $1 million worth of USDT and USDC, and Huang, who sent Egorov $1.5 million worth of USDT.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Finance platforms Curve Finance, Alchemix, and Metronome have announced a joint initiative to recover the stolen funds in the wake of the recent exploits that hit Curve&rsquo;s pools.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The exploit resulted in a loss of around $70 million worth of crypto assets, meaning the bounty offered is around $7 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Resolution In Sight?&nbsp;
<p>The DeFi platforms impacted by the Curve heist are doing everything they can to recover the stolen funds. According to on-chain data, Curve, Alchemix, and Metronome have offered the hackers a 10% bounty as a reward, urging the hackers to return the remaining 90% of the stolen funds. Curve Finance updated users about their offer to the hackers via X, stressing that they would face no further legal or law enforcement actions if they chose to return the funds. Curve stated in the joint message sent via Etherscan,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The offer comes with a guarantee of no further legal actions or involvement of law enforcement. We want to resolve this in a civilized manner. You will have no risk of us pursuing this further, no risk of law enforcement issues.&rdquo;</p>

Final Warning
<p>The three protocols gave the hackers a deadline of 6th August to accept their offer. They added that should the hackers refuse the offer; the protocols would expand the bounty to the public and offer the 10% to anyone who would be able to identify them in a way that leads to their conviction. The stark warning read,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;If you choose not to partake in the voluntary return and complete the process by 6th August at 0800 UTC, we will expand the bounty to the public and offer the full 10% to the person who is able to identify you in a way that leads to your conviction in the courts. We will pursue you from all angles with the full extent of the law.&rdquo;</p>

<p>All three protocols have opened a direct line of communication with the hackers through curvenegotiation@protonmail.com and urged the hackers to respond and take the offer to avoid legal action. The protocols also stressed that any individuals responding for negotiations would need to verify their credentials and ownership of their email address on-chain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Curve and the other protocol&rsquo;s outreach is similar to the strategy adopted by DeFi protocol Euler Finance, which fell victim to a crippling hack earlier in the year. However, the protocol was able to negotiate with the hackers and retrieve the stolen funds successfully.&nbsp;</p>
The Curve Hack&nbsp;
<p>The Curve exploit saw around $70 million worth of crypto stolen by hackers. This figure included CRV tokens worth around $4.52 million, which led to a significant drop in the price of the token. At the heart of the exploit was a vulnerability in Vyper called a reentrancy bug. This vulnerability allowed hackers to drain several stablecoin pools on Curve, leading to considerable chaos in the DeFi ecosystem.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi markets were further spooked after reports emerged that Curve Finance founder Michael Egorov had allegedly taken several loans using around 47% of CRV&rsquo;s circulating supply. Several DeFi protocols, such as Aave, Abracadabra, and several others, faced major implications following the drop in CRV&rsquo;s value. This is because the decline put Egorov&rsquo;s $168 million lending position at risk of liquidation, potentially unleashing a domino effect on DeFi.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Curve and Egorov found support from prominent names in the crypto and DeFi space, such as Power DeFi user DCF God, Tron Foundation CEO Justin Sun, and Jeffrey Huang, also known as Machi Big Brother. Sun, DCF God, and Huang purchased large quantities of CRV from Egorov, helping reduce the principal value of Egorov&rsquo;s loan from $63 million to $54 million. Other players who assisted Egorov were Cream Finance, which sent Egorov $1 million worth of USDT and USDC, and Huang, who sent Egorov $1.5 million worth of USDT.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LET'S GET READY FOR THE NEXT BULL RUN TOGETHER - JOIN US IN OCTOBER]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/lets-get-ready-for-the-next-bull-run-together-join-us-in-october</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image2-96.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image2-96.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image2-96.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/lets-get-ready-for-the-next-bull-run-together-join-us-in-october</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Are you constantly in search of the finest web3 events to participate in? It feels like every event you come across is either too large, too small, overly pricey, or inconveniently distant. If that sounds familiar, then you probably haven't heard about the DEGAMEFI WEB3 CONFERENCE 2023 just yet!</p>
Save the dates, because this will be one of the most fruitful experiences that you have had.&nbsp;
<p>The Degamefi Web3 Conference stands as the largest event in the Caucasus region, acting as a gathering ground for blockchain and Web3 experts, thought leaders, and innovators. It draws a diverse audience comprising developers, investors, entrepreneurs, and enthusiasts, all driven by their eagerness to stay informed about the latest trends, technologies, and applications in this rapidly-evolving field.</p>
🎉 The conference's main sponsor is TETHER.
<p>By collaborating with the DEGAMEFI 2023, Tether reaffirms its commitment to fostering innovation, collaboration, and the advancement of Bitcoin, Peer-to-Peer and blockchain-based solutions worldwide and in Georgia.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;By sponsoring this event in Georgia, we want to be an active player and further commit to fostering and nurturing this growing ecosystem. We believe that by empowering the local community with blockchain expertise, we can drive adoption and foster economic growth in the region. By demonstrating our commitment to Georgia&rsquo;s blockchain ecosystem, we aim to build valuable relationships, foster Bitcoin and p2p technologies adoption, and explore new business opportunities.&rdquo; &ndash; Marco Dal Lago, Head of Expansion in Tether and Bitfinex.</p>

<p>The event will feature keynote speeches, panel discussions, start-up competition, dedicated area spaces, and networking opportunities, providing attendees with valuable and the most up-to-date insights and real-time opportunities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The conference will include keynote speeches, panel discussions, a startup competition, dedicated areas for various topics, and ample networking opportunities. This will provide attendees with valuable insights and real-time opportunities related to decentralized finance, non-fungible tokens, governance, identity, privacy, cybersecurity, law adoption, AI, and more. Some notable industry professionals, such as TOBIAS (TOBI) BAUER, MARCO DAL LAGO, DR. VILMA MATTILA, LAURA INAMEDINOVA, CAL EVANS, will be among the speakers. Check the rest here.</p>
🚀 Key Highlights:
<ul>
<li>Expected Attendance: 1500 attendees</li>
<li>Panel discussions and solo speeches</li>
<li>Dedicated sessions</li>
<li>Gaming Area</li>
<li>Startup competition</li>
<li>VIP Space</li>
<li>Official side events</li>
<li>And more...</li>
</ul>
<p>📌Venue: Sheraton Grand Tbilisi Metechi Palace Hotel&nbsp;</p>
<p>🗓 Date: 7-8 Oct. 2023&nbsp;</p>
<p>🚀 To seize new opportunities, secure your passes here.</p>
<p>FOR FURTHER ASSISTANCE CONTACT - info@degamefi.io or ani@degamefi.io</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you constantly in search of the finest web3 events to participate in? It feels like every event you come across is either too large, too small, overly pricey, or inconveniently distant. If that sounds familiar, then you probably haven't heard about the DEGAMEFI WEB3 CONFERENCE 2023 just yet!</p>
Save the dates, because this will be one of the most fruitful experiences that you have had.&nbsp;
<p>The Degamefi Web3 Conference stands as the largest event in the Caucasus region, acting as a gathering ground for blockchain and Web3 experts, thought leaders, and innovators. It draws a diverse audience comprising developers, investors, entrepreneurs, and enthusiasts, all driven by their eagerness to stay informed about the latest trends, technologies, and applications in this rapidly-evolving field.</p>
🎉 The conference's main sponsor is TETHER.
<p>By collaborating with the DEGAMEFI 2023, Tether reaffirms its commitment to fostering innovation, collaboration, and the advancement of Bitcoin, Peer-to-Peer and blockchain-based solutions worldwide and in Georgia.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;By sponsoring this event in Georgia, we want to be an active player and further commit to fostering and nurturing this growing ecosystem. We believe that by empowering the local community with blockchain expertise, we can drive adoption and foster economic growth in the region. By demonstrating our commitment to Georgia&rsquo;s blockchain ecosystem, we aim to build valuable relationships, foster Bitcoin and p2p technologies adoption, and explore new business opportunities.&rdquo; &ndash; Marco Dal Lago, Head of Expansion in Tether and Bitfinex.</p>

<p>The event will feature keynote speeches, panel discussions, start-up competition, dedicated area spaces, and networking opportunities, providing attendees with valuable and the most up-to-date insights and real-time opportunities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The conference will include keynote speeches, panel discussions, a startup competition, dedicated areas for various topics, and ample networking opportunities. This will provide attendees with valuable insights and real-time opportunities related to decentralized finance, non-fungible tokens, governance, identity, privacy, cybersecurity, law adoption, AI, and more. Some notable industry professionals, such as TOBIAS (TOBI) BAUER, MARCO DAL LAGO, DR. VILMA MATTILA, LAURA INAMEDINOVA, CAL EVANS, will be among the speakers. Check the rest here.</p>
🚀 Key Highlights:
<ul>
<li>Expected Attendance: 1500 attendees</li>
<li>Panel discussions and solo speeches</li>
<li>Dedicated sessions</li>
<li>Gaming Area</li>
<li>Startup competition</li>
<li>VIP Space</li>
<li>Official side events</li>
<li>And more...</li>
</ul>
<p>📌Venue: Sheraton Grand Tbilisi Metechi Palace Hotel&nbsp;</p>
<p>🗓 Date: 7-8 Oct. 2023&nbsp;</p>
<p>🚀 To seize new opportunities, secure your passes here.</p>
<p>FOR FURTHER ASSISTANCE CONTACT - info@degamefi.io or ani@degamefi.io</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Hacker Behind 2016 Bitfinex Attack Pleads Guilty at Court]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/hacker-behind-2016-bitfinex-attack-pleads-guilty-at-court</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitfinex-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Olga Krasilnikova]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/hacker-behind-2016-bitfinex-attack-pleads-guilty-at-court</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Ilya Lichtenstein admitted to laundering the $4.5B worth of Bitcoin stolen during the 2016 Bitfinex attack; his wife Heather Morgan also pleaded guilty.</p>
Seven-year-long Investigation Comes to an End
<p>According to the CNBC report, resident of New York City Ilya Lichtenstein admitted to being the original hacker behind the 2016 Bitfinex attack in a federal court in Washington, D.C on July 3. On the same day, his wife Heather Morgan also pleaded guilty to the counts of money laundering and conspiracy related to the hack.</p>
<p>The cyberattack deprived Bitfinext of almost 120 BTC, which was worth $70 million at the time and has since risen to the price of $4.5 billion. It took the US Department of Justice (DOJ) seven years to seize the stolen funds and the person responsible for the hack.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitfinex diligently worked with the U.S. Department of Justice to identify the perpetrators of the hack, recover the stolen bitcoin, and bring the hackers to justice," said an external spokesperson for Bitfinex. "After seven years, those efforts have come to fruition.&rdquo;</p>

The Bizarre Couple Caught for Money Laundering
<p>Ilya Lichtenstein and his wife Heather Morgan, also known as &ldquo;Razzlekhan&rdquo; (the name she uses to publish her comedy rap videos) were arrested on charges of money laundering and theft in connection to the 2016 Bitfinex hack in February 2022. However, the Department of Justice didn&rsquo;t accuse the couple of being the original hackers behind the attack at that time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Morgan proclaimed to be a cybercrime expert specializing in social engineering on her LinkedIn, while Lichtenstein had technical background in coding and data analysis. These facts suggested that the couple had enough expertise to pull off the hack, even though many didn&rsquo;t believe it due to the image of eccentric personas the two projected on the Internet.</p>
Most of the Bitfinex Funds Recovered
<p>At the time of Lichtenstein's and Morgan&rsquo;s arrest, the DOJ was able to recover 94,000 BTC linked to the hack, the sum now equivalent to around $3.6 billion. It was discovered that in early 2017, Lichtenstein &ldquo;began to move a portion of the Bitcoin&rdquo; stolen during the Bitfinex attack &ldquo;in a series of small, complex transactions across multiple accounts and platforms.&rdquo; The shuffling process, which involved a large number of transactions, was aimed at obscuring the path of the stolen money.</p>
<p>Last month, the crypto exchange recovered another part of its lost funds: $312,219 in cash and 6.9 in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) worth around $1951 today. Apparently, the United States Department of Homeland Security got control of the sum in 2022 after the culprit&rsquo;s arrest.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The couple is now facing up to 25 years in prison. Following their arrest in 2022, Netflix announced it might create a series about the case.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ilya Lichtenstein admitted to laundering the $4.5B worth of Bitcoin stolen during the 2016 Bitfinex attack; his wife Heather Morgan also pleaded guilty.</p>
Seven-year-long Investigation Comes to an End
<p>According to the CNBC report, resident of New York City Ilya Lichtenstein admitted to being the original hacker behind the 2016 Bitfinex attack in a federal court in Washington, D.C on July 3. On the same day, his wife Heather Morgan also pleaded guilty to the counts of money laundering and conspiracy related to the hack.</p>
<p>The cyberattack deprived Bitfinext of almost 120 BTC, which was worth $70 million at the time and has since risen to the price of $4.5 billion. It took the US Department of Justice (DOJ) seven years to seize the stolen funds and the person responsible for the hack.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Bitfinex diligently worked with the U.S. Department of Justice to identify the perpetrators of the hack, recover the stolen bitcoin, and bring the hackers to justice," said an external spokesperson for Bitfinex. "After seven years, those efforts have come to fruition.&rdquo;</p>

The Bizarre Couple Caught for Money Laundering
<p>Ilya Lichtenstein and his wife Heather Morgan, also known as &ldquo;Razzlekhan&rdquo; (the name she uses to publish her comedy rap videos) were arrested on charges of money laundering and theft in connection to the 2016 Bitfinex hack in February 2022. However, the Department of Justice didn&rsquo;t accuse the couple of being the original hackers behind the attack at that time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Morgan proclaimed to be a cybercrime expert specializing in social engineering on her LinkedIn, while Lichtenstein had technical background in coding and data analysis. These facts suggested that the couple had enough expertise to pull off the hack, even though many didn&rsquo;t believe it due to the image of eccentric personas the two projected on the Internet.</p>
Most of the Bitfinex Funds Recovered
<p>At the time of Lichtenstein's and Morgan&rsquo;s arrest, the DOJ was able to recover 94,000 BTC linked to the hack, the sum now equivalent to around $3.6 billion. It was discovered that in early 2017, Lichtenstein &ldquo;began to move a portion of the Bitcoin&rdquo; stolen during the Bitfinex attack &ldquo;in a series of small, complex transactions across multiple accounts and platforms.&rdquo; The shuffling process, which involved a large number of transactions, was aimed at obscuring the path of the stolen money.</p>
<p>Last month, the crypto exchange recovered another part of its lost funds: $312,219 in cash and 6.9 in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) worth around $1951 today. Apparently, the United States Department of Homeland Security got control of the sum in 2022 after the culprit&rsquo;s arrest.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The couple is now facing up to 25 years in prison. Following their arrest in 2022, Netflix announced it might create a series about the case.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[‘Miners should maximize their returns’: Top-5 solutions from Leading Mining Pool emcd.]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/miners-should-maximize-their-returns-top-5-solutions-from-leading-mining-pool-emcd</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/788-443.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/788-443.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/788-443.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/miners-should-maximize-their-returns-top-5-solutions-from-leading-mining-pool-emcd</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>One of the top-10 mining pools offers a comprehensive solution to crises that cryptocurrency miners face in 2023: emcd. Cyberbank &mdash; a cyberbank with a package of services that help miners make more without &lsquo;additional costs&rsquo;.</p>
<p>Mining in 2023, with operational costs&rsquo; growth and a long cryptowinter, is becoming less and less profitable for miners. But one of the largest pools in the world has a solution: launching its own ecosystem aimed specifically at miners and other cryptocurrency users. The cyberbank from the leading pool offers users services from friendly commission-free withdrawal tools to investment tools with up to 12% per annum to raise mining profits.</p>

&lsquo;Miners should make more money, and we know how to make it happen. We&rsquo;re launching a neobank where miners will be able to fully manage their assets in a single app, without additional commissions and other costs.&rsquo;

<p>&nbsp;&mdash; emcd. team</p>
Top-5 Solutions from emcd.
<p>Mining on asics and videocards is no longer the &lsquo;wild west&rsquo; it was at the dawn of crypto. Without pools and growing ecosystems it&rsquo;s harder and harder for miners to manage assets and wait until investments and huge operational costs pay off.</p>
Who are emcd.?
<p>In 5 years, emcd. made the journey from a small startup to a major pool that made it to the top-10 BTC mining pools in the world. 270,000 miners from 120 countries already use the platform.</p>
<p>emcd. decided to choose a comprehensive approach to miners&rsquo; issues, with a whole set of services for digital asset management. And even though mining always involves costs nobody can single-handedly control, emcd. is cutting additional operational costs that hit miners with 5 easy solutions.</p>
One of the lowest comissions on the market
<p>How did a start-up make it to the top-10 BTC mining pools in the world? Easy &mdash; the service has a fixed commission rate of 5%. Hardly any pool in the world is ready to offer its miners to take away 98.5% of their rewards, but emcd. are playing the long game on the market (and so far, judging by volumes and users, they&rsquo;re making the right call).</p>
Secure and user-friendly wallet
<p>Everything a miner makes goes to an internal wallet that is actually easy to use. Without shelling out extra commissions for transfers, users can convert currencies and withdraw money directly to their cards directly in the emcd. app. Moreover, there&rsquo;s no minimal withdrawal amount, which is usually the case for platforms like this &mdash; if you want to withdraw each dollar one by one, nobody&rsquo;s stopping you.&nbsp;</p>
A native P2P platform
<p>One of the biggest headaches miners have is withdrawing their rewards to fiat. And P2P exchanges remain one of the most popular solutions &mdash; even people who still haven&rsquo;t heard of mining in 2023 know how to use them. emcd. Isn&rsquo;t asking miners to ditch their long-trusted tool in favor of the built-in withdrawal features in the wallet, instead, they offer their own P2P platform, once again helping miners bypass unnecessary transfer commissions.</p>
12% per annum on your balance
<p>Mining as a source of income is inevitably tied to issues in the rest of the economy, including unpredictable inflation, especially in regions where mining is an affordable additional income source. To make sure miners&rsquo; profits don&rsquo;t devalue because of economic fluctuations, emcd. offers its own investment tools with rates better than any bank &mdash; 12% per annum.&nbsp;</p>
Live support
<p>No bots &mdash; only actual humans who respond in approximately 15 minutes 24/7. Don&rsquo;t waste time searching for the code phrase that will finally get you to an operator, only to refresh the chat page for hours waiting for a response to urgent questions about your own assets.&nbsp;</p>
Will there be mining in 2023?
<p>And more importantly, is mining profitable in 2023, and what will happen with Bitcoin mining after Bitcoin halving? emcd. has answers for experts and newbies alike. The platform&rsquo;s official Telegram offers all the current updates and news, reviews, and even cryptocurrency mining guides for newbies. Following the project&rsquo;s progress!</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the top-10 mining pools offers a comprehensive solution to crises that cryptocurrency miners face in 2023: emcd. Cyberbank &mdash; a cyberbank with a package of services that help miners make more without &lsquo;additional costs&rsquo;.</p>
<p>Mining in 2023, with operational costs&rsquo; growth and a long cryptowinter, is becoming less and less profitable for miners. But one of the largest pools in the world has a solution: launching its own ecosystem aimed specifically at miners and other cryptocurrency users. The cyberbank from the leading pool offers users services from friendly commission-free withdrawal tools to investment tools with up to 12% per annum to raise mining profits.</p>

&lsquo;Miners should make more money, and we know how to make it happen. We&rsquo;re launching a neobank where miners will be able to fully manage their assets in a single app, without additional commissions and other costs.&rsquo;

<p>&nbsp;&mdash; emcd. team</p>
Top-5 Solutions from emcd.
<p>Mining on asics and videocards is no longer the &lsquo;wild west&rsquo; it was at the dawn of crypto. Without pools and growing ecosystems it&rsquo;s harder and harder for miners to manage assets and wait until investments and huge operational costs pay off.</p>
Who are emcd.?
<p>In 5 years, emcd. made the journey from a small startup to a major pool that made it to the top-10 BTC mining pools in the world. 270,000 miners from 120 countries already use the platform.</p>
<p>emcd. decided to choose a comprehensive approach to miners&rsquo; issues, with a whole set of services for digital asset management. And even though mining always involves costs nobody can single-handedly control, emcd. is cutting additional operational costs that hit miners with 5 easy solutions.</p>
One of the lowest comissions on the market
<p>How did a start-up make it to the top-10 BTC mining pools in the world? Easy &mdash; the service has a fixed commission rate of 5%. Hardly any pool in the world is ready to offer its miners to take away 98.5% of their rewards, but emcd. are playing the long game on the market (and so far, judging by volumes and users, they&rsquo;re making the right call).</p>
Secure and user-friendly wallet
<p>Everything a miner makes goes to an internal wallet that is actually easy to use. Without shelling out extra commissions for transfers, users can convert currencies and withdraw money directly to their cards directly in the emcd. app. Moreover, there&rsquo;s no minimal withdrawal amount, which is usually the case for platforms like this &mdash; if you want to withdraw each dollar one by one, nobody&rsquo;s stopping you.&nbsp;</p>
A native P2P platform
<p>One of the biggest headaches miners have is withdrawing their rewards to fiat. And P2P exchanges remain one of the most popular solutions &mdash; even people who still haven&rsquo;t heard of mining in 2023 know how to use them. emcd. Isn&rsquo;t asking miners to ditch their long-trusted tool in favor of the built-in withdrawal features in the wallet, instead, they offer their own P2P platform, once again helping miners bypass unnecessary transfer commissions.</p>
12% per annum on your balance
<p>Mining as a source of income is inevitably tied to issues in the rest of the economy, including unpredictable inflation, especially in regions where mining is an affordable additional income source. To make sure miners&rsquo; profits don&rsquo;t devalue because of economic fluctuations, emcd. offers its own investment tools with rates better than any bank &mdash; 12% per annum.&nbsp;</p>
Live support
<p>No bots &mdash; only actual humans who respond in approximately 15 minutes 24/7. Don&rsquo;t waste time searching for the code phrase that will finally get you to an operator, only to refresh the chat page for hours waiting for a response to urgent questions about your own assets.&nbsp;</p>
Will there be mining in 2023?
<p>And more importantly, is mining profitable in 2023, and what will happen with Bitcoin mining after Bitcoin halving? emcd. has answers for experts and newbies alike. The platform&rsquo;s official Telegram offers all the current updates and news, reviews, and even cryptocurrency mining guides for newbies. Following the project&rsquo;s progress!</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BlockFi Restructure Plan Nears Completion]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/blockfi-restructure-plan-nears-completion</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-restructure-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-restructure-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-restructure-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/08/blockfi-restructure-plan-nears-completion</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankrupt cryptocurrency lending platform BlockFi's restructuring plan has taken a step closer to fruition, as the firm announced that its disclosure statement has received conditional approval from the U.S. Bankruptcy Court in New Jersey.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development is a critical part of the company's mission to maximize recoveries for creditors and expedite the return of cryptocurrencies to clients, said Mark Renzi, BlockFi&rsquo;s chief restructuring officer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm's restructuring plan will allow BlockFi to direct efforts towards recouping funds from other failed businesses such as Alameda Research, FTX, Three Arrows Capital, Emergent, Marex, and Core Scientific. However, the proposed plan has not been devoid of criticism,.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Organizations like FTX, Three Arrows Capital, and the Securities and Exchange Commission have voiced concerns about the plan's fairness and its potential to absolve BlockFi and its management from legal responsibility, especially with disputed transactions worth over a billion dollars hanging in the balance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Under the new plan, BlockFi intends to refund non-wallet funds back to customers, while also creating a "convenience claim class" for customers with claims under $3,000, who would receive a lump sum payout equating to 50% of the total claim. The company will also refrain from clawing back amounts under $250,000 that clients properly transferred from BlockFi interest accounts or BlockFi private client accounts to wallets.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the progress, hurdles remain. FTX and Three Arrows Capital have contested the disclosure statement, citing failure to meet bankruptcy code requirements and provide adewquate information for creditors to evaluate the feasibility of BlockFi's strategy. Meanwhile, the SEC has requested more detailed information on the releases.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">BlockFi's restructuring process comes after allegations of fraud by the company's unsecured creditors and former CEO Zac Prince. The firm was accused of breaking promises to customers by liquidating nearly $240 million in customers' crypto, which forms part of the justification for the move to appoint a Chapter 11 trustee outside of its bankruptcy plan. The deadline for voting on BlockFi's proposed reorganization is slated for September 11.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankrupt cryptocurrency lending platform BlockFi's restructuring plan has taken a step closer to fruition, as the firm announced that its disclosure statement has received conditional approval from the U.S. Bankruptcy Court in New Jersey.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This development is a critical part of the company's mission to maximize recoveries for creditors and expedite the return of cryptocurrencies to clients, said Mark Renzi, BlockFi&rsquo;s chief restructuring officer.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm's restructuring plan will allow BlockFi to direct efforts towards recouping funds from other failed businesses such as Alameda Research, FTX, Three Arrows Capital, Emergent, Marex, and Core Scientific. However, the proposed plan has not been devoid of criticism,.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Organizations like FTX, Three Arrows Capital, and the Securities and Exchange Commission have voiced concerns about the plan's fairness and its potential to absolve BlockFi and its management from legal responsibility, especially with disputed transactions worth over a billion dollars hanging in the balance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Under the new plan, BlockFi intends to refund non-wallet funds back to customers, while also creating a "convenience claim class" for customers with claims under $3,000, who would receive a lump sum payout equating to 50% of the total claim. The company will also refrain from clawing back amounts under $250,000 that clients properly transferred from BlockFi interest accounts or BlockFi private client accounts to wallets.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the progress, hurdles remain. FTX and Three Arrows Capital have contested the disclosure statement, citing failure to meet bankruptcy code requirements and provide adewquate information for creditors to evaluate the feasibility of BlockFi's strategy. Meanwhile, the SEC has requested more detailed information on the releases.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">BlockFi's restructuring process comes after allegations of fraud by the company's unsecured creditors and former CEO Zac Prince. The firm was accused of breaking promises to customers by liquidating nearly $240 million in customers' crypto, which forms part of the justification for the move to appoint a Chapter 11 trustee outside of its bankruptcy plan. The deadline for voting on BlockFi's proposed reorganization is slated for September 11.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
