<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 04:44:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bank of England: Crypto Market Too Dangerous Not to Regulate]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bank-of-england-crypto-market-too-dangerous-not-to-regulate</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/uk-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 17:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bank-of-england-crypto-market-too-dangerous-not-to-regulate</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The deputy governor of the Bank of England (BoE) has warned that cryptocurrency trading is &ldquo;too dangerous&rdquo; to remain unregulated adding that it could pose &ldquo;a systemic problem&rdquo; if action is not taken. </p>
<p>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Sir Jon Cunliffe, deputy governor of the Bank of England, said that investors and the financial system need to be protected from the &ldquo;casino&rdquo; of cryptocurrency trading. Speaking for the first time since the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX, Cunliffe indicated that the BoE might soon regulate the industry to protect investors from the dangers of crypto trading, as well as the wider financial system against potential fallout associated with cryptocurrencies. Cunliffe said that the BoE&rsquo;s stance is that retail investors should be able to safely speculate on cryptocurrencies, as they do in traditional markets.</p>
<p>Cunliffe said:</p>

<p>I think for the majority of people if they do want to be involved in speculation in [crypto] ... for consumer protection and market integrity, they should have a place to do that where they get the protection they would get in a similar activity in the UK.</p>

Crypto is Becoming Increasingly Integrated into Traditional Financial Systems
<p>The deputy governor added that cryptocurrencies are becoming increasingly integrated into the traditional financial system and therefore should be regulated soon rather than later. He noted:</p>

<p>I do not know how that would [have] developed, but we had banks and investment funds and others who wanted to invest in it.</p>

<p>During his interview with Sky News, Cunliffe said the trading of crypto assets has not yet been sizeable enough to destabilise the financial system, &ldquo;but it was starting to develop links.&rdquo; On that note, and commenting on the BoE&rsquo;s future plans to manage digital assets, Cunliffe added:</p>

<p>I think we should think about regulation before it becomes integrated with the financial system and before we could have a potential systemic problem.</p>

UK&rsquo;s Regulatory Efforts
<p>According to the reports by Sky News, in the UK, regulators have attempted to, and failed, &ldquo;to impose their write on crypto exchanges domiciled offshore.&rdquo; When the now Prime Minister Rishi Sunak was chancellor of the exchequer, the government made it clear that its goal was to make the UK a &ldquo;global crypto asset hub&rdquo; &ndash; something which naturally will depend largely on an effective regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Cunliffe, in his role as being responsible for financial stability, said that the BoE&rsquo;s previous regulatory efforts were aimed at protecting individuals and maintaining financial stability &ndash; a common goal of central banks. He said:</p>

<p>There's a lot of activity that's developed over the last 10 years on the trading and sale of crypto assets, assets without any intrinsic value, so they're incredibly volatile. And all of that has grown up outside of regulation.</p>

<p>In an attempt to explain the absolute need for effective regulation, the deputy governor drew upon the collapse of FTX to highlight his point:</p>

<p>What we saw in FTX&hellip; is a number of activities which in the regulated financial sector, would have had certain protections. We saw things like clients' money appears to have gone missing, conflicts of interest between different operations, transparency, audit and accounting. All of the perhaps boring things that happened in the normal financial sector, didn't really happen in that set of activities. And as a result, I think a lot of people have lost a lot of money.</p>

BoE is in the Process of Developing its Own Digital Coin
<p>Cryptocurrencies aside, the BoE does see the value in blockchain technology. The Central Bank is currently consulting on plans to develop its own central bank digital coin, a digital version of its currency that would offer the same security as a pound coin, but with the added benefit of digital flexibility that could see it replace cash. Recognising the value of a digital currency, Sir Jon commented:</p>

<p>Physical cash will always be made available by the bank as long as people want it and many people depend on it. But it's not fully usable in the way we live now. So the question for the Bank of England is that as the way we as society changes, as we live our lives more digitally, should we continue to provide money to the public which is usable across a range of transactions?</p>

<p>He further said:</p>

<p>This would be a digital equivalent of the' I promise to pay the bearer' promise, which in the end underpins confidence in money in the UK. Whenever you want, you can turn that money you hold in the bank into basically Bank of England money backed by the state with that promise to pay the bearer.</p>

<p>Finally, realising that physical cash is becoming less feasible and practical, Sir Jon said:</p>

<p>We want to ensure that as physical cash becomes less usable in many parts of the economy, perhaps we need to offer something digitally to provide that underpinning.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The deputy governor of the Bank of England (BoE) has warned that cryptocurrency trading is &ldquo;too dangerous&rdquo; to remain unregulated adding that it could pose &ldquo;a systemic problem&rdquo; if action is not taken. </p>
<p>In an exclusive interview with Sky News, Sir Jon Cunliffe, deputy governor of the Bank of England, said that investors and the financial system need to be protected from the &ldquo;casino&rdquo; of cryptocurrency trading. Speaking for the first time since the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX, Cunliffe indicated that the BoE might soon regulate the industry to protect investors from the dangers of crypto trading, as well as the wider financial system against potential fallout associated with cryptocurrencies. Cunliffe said that the BoE&rsquo;s stance is that retail investors should be able to safely speculate on cryptocurrencies, as they do in traditional markets.</p>
<p>Cunliffe said:</p>

<p>I think for the majority of people if they do want to be involved in speculation in [crypto] ... for consumer protection and market integrity, they should have a place to do that where they get the protection they would get in a similar activity in the UK.</p>

Crypto is Becoming Increasingly Integrated into Traditional Financial Systems
<p>The deputy governor added that cryptocurrencies are becoming increasingly integrated into the traditional financial system and therefore should be regulated soon rather than later. He noted:</p>

<p>I do not know how that would [have] developed, but we had banks and investment funds and others who wanted to invest in it.</p>

<p>During his interview with Sky News, Cunliffe said the trading of crypto assets has not yet been sizeable enough to destabilise the financial system, &ldquo;but it was starting to develop links.&rdquo; On that note, and commenting on the BoE&rsquo;s future plans to manage digital assets, Cunliffe added:</p>

<p>I think we should think about regulation before it becomes integrated with the financial system and before we could have a potential systemic problem.</p>

UK&rsquo;s Regulatory Efforts
<p>According to the reports by Sky News, in the UK, regulators have attempted to, and failed, &ldquo;to impose their write on crypto exchanges domiciled offshore.&rdquo; When the now Prime Minister Rishi Sunak was chancellor of the exchequer, the government made it clear that its goal was to make the UK a &ldquo;global crypto asset hub&rdquo; &ndash; something which naturally will depend largely on an effective regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Cunliffe, in his role as being responsible for financial stability, said that the BoE&rsquo;s previous regulatory efforts were aimed at protecting individuals and maintaining financial stability &ndash; a common goal of central banks. He said:</p>

<p>There's a lot of activity that's developed over the last 10 years on the trading and sale of crypto assets, assets without any intrinsic value, so they're incredibly volatile. And all of that has grown up outside of regulation.</p>

<p>In an attempt to explain the absolute need for effective regulation, the deputy governor drew upon the collapse of FTX to highlight his point:</p>

<p>What we saw in FTX&hellip; is a number of activities which in the regulated financial sector, would have had certain protections. We saw things like clients' money appears to have gone missing, conflicts of interest between different operations, transparency, audit and accounting. All of the perhaps boring things that happened in the normal financial sector, didn't really happen in that set of activities. And as a result, I think a lot of people have lost a lot of money.</p>

BoE is in the Process of Developing its Own Digital Coin
<p>Cryptocurrencies aside, the BoE does see the value in blockchain technology. The Central Bank is currently consulting on plans to develop its own central bank digital coin, a digital version of its currency that would offer the same security as a pound coin, but with the added benefit of digital flexibility that could see it replace cash. Recognising the value of a digital currency, Sir Jon commented:</p>

<p>Physical cash will always be made available by the bank as long as people want it and many people depend on it. But it's not fully usable in the way we live now. So the question for the Bank of England is that as the way we as society changes, as we live our lives more digitally, should we continue to provide money to the public which is usable across a range of transactions?</p>

<p>He further said:</p>

<p>This would be a digital equivalent of the' I promise to pay the bearer' promise, which in the end underpins confidence in money in the UK. Whenever you want, you can turn that money you hold in the bank into basically Bank of England money backed by the state with that promise to pay the bearer.</p>

<p>Finally, realising that physical cash is becoming less feasible and practical, Sir Jon said:</p>

<p>We want to ensure that as physical cash becomes less usable in many parts of the economy, perhaps we need to offer something digitally to provide that underpinning.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[3 reasons why Bitcoin is better than CBDCs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-is-better-than-cbdcs</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btc-cbdc.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btc-cbdc.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btc-cbdc.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/3-reasons-why-bitcoin-is-better-than-cbdcs</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is a decentralised network that allows anyone to transact with anyone else. CBDCs are issued by a central bank and have controls built into them. Bitcoin offers freedom while CBDCs offer total control.</p>
<p>There is much at stake as world economies look for a way out of the desperate plight that a fiat-backed monetary system has driven them into. Central banks believe that their own digital currencies will put economies back on track. Here are 3 reasons why Bitcoin is eminently preferable.</p>
Decentralisation
<p>decentralised control is a key feature of Bitcoin and other decentralised digital currencies. In a decentralised system, control is distributed among multiple parties rather than being concentrated in a single entity. This means that no single entity has the power to make decisions or exert control over the system.</p>
<p>In the case of Bitcoin, the decentralised control is achieved through the use of a decentralised network of computers, known as nodes, which validate and record transactions on the blockchain. The blockchain is a decentralised, distributed ledger that records all transactions made on the Bitcoin network. Each transaction is recorded on the blockchain in a block, which is then added to the chain of blocks that make up the blockchain.</p>
<p>Because the blockchain is decentralised and distributed, it is not controlled by any single entity. Instead, it is maintained by a network of users who contribute their computing resources to the network. This decentralised structure makes it difficult for any single entity to manipulate the network or the information stored on the blockchain.</p>
<p>In contrast, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) are issued and controlled by central banks, which are typically government-controlled financial institutions. This means that CBDCs are subject to the policies and decisions of those central banks, and the central banks have the ability to exert control over the issuance and use of CBDCs.</p>
Limited Supply
<p>One of the key features of bitcoin is that it has a limited supply of 21 million coins. This limit is built into the bitcoin blockchain, which is the underlying technology that supports the bitcoin network. This means that no matter how much demand there is for bitcoin, the total number of bitcoins that will ever exist is fixed at 21 million.</p>
<p>The limited supply of bitcoin is intended to help protect the value of the currency. Inflation occurs when the supply of a currency increases faster than the demand for it, which can lead to a decline in its value. By limiting the supply of bitcoin, its creator hoped to reduce the risk of inflation and protect its value.</p>
<p>In contrast, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) are digital versions of traditional fiat currencies, such as the US dollar or the euro. These currencies are issued and backed by central banks, which have the power to create new units of the currency as needed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This means that the supply of CBDCs is not fixed, and the central bank has the ability to increase the supply of the currency if it sees fit. This introduces the risk of inflation if the central bank creates too much of the currency, leading to a decline in its value.</p>
High level of security
<p>Bitcoin uses a combination of advanced cryptographic techniques and a decentralised network to ensure the security of transactions and the integrity of the blockchain.</p>
<p>The blockchain is a decentralised ledger that records all bitcoin transactions. Each transaction is verified by a network of computers, called nodes, that work together to validate the transaction and add it to the blockchain.</p>
<p>These nodes use cryptographic techniques to ensure that the transaction is legitimate and cannot be altered or tampered with once it is added to the blockchain. This makes it extremely difficult for anyone to fraudulently alter the ledger or steal bitcoins.</p>
<p>While CBDCs may also be secure, there is a risk that they could be vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because CBDCs rely on a centralised system, which means that there is a single point of failure that could be targeted by hackers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is a decentralised network that allows anyone to transact with anyone else. CBDCs are issued by a central bank and have controls built into them. Bitcoin offers freedom while CBDCs offer total control.</p>
<p>There is much at stake as world economies look for a way out of the desperate plight that a fiat-backed monetary system has driven them into. Central banks believe that their own digital currencies will put economies back on track. Here are 3 reasons why Bitcoin is eminently preferable.</p>
Decentralisation
<p>decentralised control is a key feature of Bitcoin and other decentralised digital currencies. In a decentralised system, control is distributed among multiple parties rather than being concentrated in a single entity. This means that no single entity has the power to make decisions or exert control over the system.</p>
<p>In the case of Bitcoin, the decentralised control is achieved through the use of a decentralised network of computers, known as nodes, which validate and record transactions on the blockchain. The blockchain is a decentralised, distributed ledger that records all transactions made on the Bitcoin network. Each transaction is recorded on the blockchain in a block, which is then added to the chain of blocks that make up the blockchain.</p>
<p>Because the blockchain is decentralised and distributed, it is not controlled by any single entity. Instead, it is maintained by a network of users who contribute their computing resources to the network. This decentralised structure makes it difficult for any single entity to manipulate the network or the information stored on the blockchain.</p>
<p>In contrast, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) are issued and controlled by central banks, which are typically government-controlled financial institutions. This means that CBDCs are subject to the policies and decisions of those central banks, and the central banks have the ability to exert control over the issuance and use of CBDCs.</p>
Limited Supply
<p>One of the key features of bitcoin is that it has a limited supply of 21 million coins. This limit is built into the bitcoin blockchain, which is the underlying technology that supports the bitcoin network. This means that no matter how much demand there is for bitcoin, the total number of bitcoins that will ever exist is fixed at 21 million.</p>
<p>The limited supply of bitcoin is intended to help protect the value of the currency. Inflation occurs when the supply of a currency increases faster than the demand for it, which can lead to a decline in its value. By limiting the supply of bitcoin, its creator hoped to reduce the risk of inflation and protect its value.</p>
<p>In contrast, central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) are digital versions of traditional fiat currencies, such as the US dollar or the euro. These currencies are issued and backed by central banks, which have the power to create new units of the currency as needed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This means that the supply of CBDCs is not fixed, and the central bank has the ability to increase the supply of the currency if it sees fit. This introduces the risk of inflation if the central bank creates too much of the currency, leading to a decline in its value.</p>
High level of security
<p>Bitcoin uses a combination of advanced cryptographic techniques and a decentralised network to ensure the security of transactions and the integrity of the blockchain.</p>
<p>The blockchain is a decentralised ledger that records all bitcoin transactions. Each transaction is verified by a network of computers, called nodes, that work together to validate the transaction and add it to the blockchain.</p>
<p>These nodes use cryptographic techniques to ensure that the transaction is legitimate and cannot be altered or tampered with once it is added to the blockchain. This makes it extremely difficult for anyone to fraudulently alter the ledger or steal bitcoins.</p>
<p>While CBDCs may also be secure, there is a risk that they could be vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because CBDCs rely on a centralised system, which means that there is a single point of failure that could be targeted by hackers.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bears Dominating - 24 December 2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-dominating-24-december-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-22-december-2022-240-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-22-december-2022-240-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-22-december-2022-240-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/bitcoin-price-analysis-bears-dominating-24-december-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Dominating:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 24 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from downward pressure early in the Asian session as the pair has been unable to free itself from its orbit around key technical areas including the 16880.44 area, a level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; A recent rebound saw BTC/USD test the 18469.40 area, a level it could not sustain as elevated risk aversion resulted in more downward pressure.&nbsp;&nbsp; Selling pressure recently intensified around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels and BTC/USD tested downside price objectives related to these levels, including the 16375.18 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD has depreciated approximately 63% year-to-date, and is off more than 1% month-to-date.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16838.41 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16789.03.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Dominating:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 24 December 2022</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continued to suffer from downward pressure early in the Asian session as the pair has been unable to free itself from its orbit around key technical areas including the 16880.44 area, a level that represents the 23.6% retracement of the depreciating range from 21478.80 to 15460.&nbsp;&nbsp; A recent rebound saw BTC/USD test the 18469.40 area, a level it could not sustain as elevated risk aversion resulted in more downward pressure.&nbsp;&nbsp; Selling pressure recently intensified around the 18385.36 and 17525 levels and BTC/USD tested downside price objectives related to these levels, including the 16375.18 area.&nbsp; &nbsp;Additional related downside price objectives related to these areas of selling pressure include the 15900, 15313, and 14364 levels.&nbsp; If BTC/USD reclaims some upside momentum, additional technically significant upside retracement levels include the 18495, 19199, 20070, and 20201 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>BTC/USD has depreciated approximately 63% year-to-date, and is off more than 1% month-to-date.&nbsp; Below current price activity, BTC/USD bears are eyeing a possible test of recent two-year lows around the 15460 area, established after Stops were elected below the 15512 area.&nbsp; Notably, the 15512 level represented an exact bearish price objective based on selling pressure that strengthened around the 21478.80 and 18495.50 areas.&nbsp; Below these areas, technically significant levels include the 14613, 14500.15, 13369, 10432.73, 10727, 9682, 8837, and 7538 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bullishly indicating above the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 16838.41 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 16789.03.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;14500.15/ 13369.11/ 10727.75 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;18495.40/ 19199.48/ 20070.64 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Legendary investor Bill Miller still bullish on Bitcoin]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/legendary-investor-bill-miller-still-bullish-on-bitcoin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-26.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-26.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-26.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/legendary-investor-bill-miller-still-bullish-on-bitcoin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Miller thinks that Bitcoin has held up well considering the upheavals in the crypto market.</p>
<p>With Bill Miller still planning to retire from investing at the end of this year, the legendary investor has sprinkled some last pieces of wisdom out there for anyone who might like to take notice of it.</p>
<p>In an interview with Barrons on Thursday he said that he was surprised at the performance of Bitcoin given that most of the crypto market was still correcting following the highly public collapse of Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s FTX empire.</p>
<p>Miller said that in his view it was &ldquo;remarkable&rdquo; that Bitcoin was still around $17,000 considering how the crypto market had imploded and how investors had &ldquo;fled the space&rdquo;. However, he thought that once the Fed started to pivot, &ldquo;Bitcoin would do quite well&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m surprised Bitcoin isn&rsquo;t at half of its current price, given the FTX implosion. People have fled the space, so the fact that it&rsquo;s still hanging in there at $17,000 is pretty remarkable. But inflation is being attacked, and real rates are rising rapidly. I would expect that if and when the Federal Reserve begins to pivot [toward easier monetary policy], Bitcoin would do quite well,&rdquo;</p>

<p>In the interview Miller was careful to differentiate Bitcoin from the rest of the cryptocurrency space. He saw the king of the cryptocurrencies as being a digital store of value along the same lines as gold, and suggested that investors might put at least 1% of their portfolio into the asset.</p>

<p>&ldquo;First, I want to differentiate between Bitcoin, which I see as a potential store of value like digital gold, and all the other cryptocurrencies, which can be lumped together in the category of venture speculation. Most of them, like most venture investments, will fail. But I&rsquo;ve never heard a good argument that you shouldn&rsquo;t put at least 1% of your net worth into Bitcoin. Anybody can afford to lose 1%,&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bill Miller thinks that Bitcoin has held up well considering the upheavals in the crypto market.</p>
<p>With Bill Miller still planning to retire from investing at the end of this year, the legendary investor has sprinkled some last pieces of wisdom out there for anyone who might like to take notice of it.</p>
<p>In an interview with Barrons on Thursday he said that he was surprised at the performance of Bitcoin given that most of the crypto market was still correcting following the highly public collapse of Sam Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s FTX empire.</p>
<p>Miller said that in his view it was &ldquo;remarkable&rdquo; that Bitcoin was still around $17,000 considering how the crypto market had imploded and how investors had &ldquo;fled the space&rdquo;. However, he thought that once the Fed started to pivot, &ldquo;Bitcoin would do quite well&rdquo;.</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m surprised Bitcoin isn&rsquo;t at half of its current price, given the FTX implosion. People have fled the space, so the fact that it&rsquo;s still hanging in there at $17,000 is pretty remarkable. But inflation is being attacked, and real rates are rising rapidly. I would expect that if and when the Federal Reserve begins to pivot [toward easier monetary policy], Bitcoin would do quite well,&rdquo;</p>

<p>In the interview Miller was careful to differentiate Bitcoin from the rest of the cryptocurrency space. He saw the king of the cryptocurrencies as being a digital store of value along the same lines as gold, and suggested that investors might put at least 1% of their portfolio into the asset.</p>

<p>&ldquo;First, I want to differentiate between Bitcoin, which I see as a potential store of value like digital gold, and all the other cryptocurrencies, which can be lumped together in the category of venture speculation. Most of them, like most venture investments, will fail. But I&rsquo;ve never heard a good argument that you shouldn&rsquo;t put at least 1% of your net worth into Bitcoin. Anybody can afford to lose 1%,&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Vs The Hideaways (HDWY): Which Could Pull A Bull Run In 2023?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/dogecoin-doge-vs-the-hideaways-hdwy-which-could-pull-a-bull-run-in-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/dogecoin-doge-vs-the-hideaways-hdwy-which-could-pull-a-bull-run-in-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s4">With the lack of news about the integration of Dogecoin (DOGE) into Twitter, investors quickly lost interest in the meme coin. DOGE holders have decided to drop most of their holdings as the price momentum continues to skid.</p>
<p class="s4">Upon learning what The Hideaways (HDWY) could offer, analysts are convinced that the project could be the next major token.</p>
<p class="s7">Dogecoin (DOGE) Bleeds As Crypto Flash Red</p>
<p class="s4">The profitability of Dogecoin (DOGE) has always been a question, as the high volatility of the token indicates a threat to the stability of holders&rsquo; portfolios.</p>
<p class="s4">At the time of writing, DOGE has slashed 10.20% to $0.077490 in the past 30 days as the crypto market sell-off worsens.</p>
<p class="s4">Accordingly, the descending movement of the token reflects the poor state of Dogecoin (DOGE) on the market, citing a lack of speculative interest from both bulls and bears toward the coin.</p>
<p class="s4">Market participants now rush to exit their DOGE holdings as the meme coin does not have a foreseeable future. Differently, The Hideaways (HDWY) guaranteed safety for investors thanks to its permanently locked liquidity, offering security and profitability.</p>
<p class="s7">Dogecoin (DOGE) Whale Withdraws $6.5M</p>
<p class="s4">A minor consolation for Dogecoin (DOGE) holders could be the recent massive transfer from the crypto exchange Binance. Reports revealed that a whale transferred out 81,396,088 DOGE, amounting to $6.50 million.</p>
<p class="s4">Nevertheless, DOGE's drawback persisted despite its explosive performance in November and October.</p>
<p class="s4">Notably, Dogecoin (DOGE) gained popularity after receiving support from celebrities and public figures like Tesla CEO Elon Musk. However, the lack of real use of the token remains its main weakness amid the dragging market factors.</p>
<p class="s4">Fortunately, The Hideaways (HDWY) offers profitable functionality to save investors from further woes in the crypto space.</p>
<p class="s9">The Hideaways (HDWY) Takes Off Far From Dogecoin (DOGE)</p>
<p class="s4">Crypto enthusiasts have projected that Dogecoin (DOGE) is set to play a dismal performance in 2023 compared with more rounded projects like The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p class="s4">Dog-themed meme coins are popular as they offer a fun and easy way to access the blockchain. Still, brand-new projects like HDWY are taking the new-generational investment to deliver bullish gains.</p>
<p class="s4">The Hideaways (HDWY) operates a platform set to mint non-fungible tokens underpinned by high-tier real estate properties that are hand-picked by experts.</p>
<p class="s4">The crypto-driven project will close its presale at the end of December with an offered price of $0.10 per token. There is still time to be part of The Hideaways (HDWY) and win amazing rewards of up to a 100% bonus and a prize draw of $100,000!</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io </p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s4">With the lack of news about the integration of Dogecoin (DOGE) into Twitter, investors quickly lost interest in the meme coin. DOGE holders have decided to drop most of their holdings as the price momentum continues to skid.</p>
<p class="s4">Upon learning what The Hideaways (HDWY) could offer, analysts are convinced that the project could be the next major token.</p>
<p class="s7">Dogecoin (DOGE) Bleeds As Crypto Flash Red</p>
<p class="s4">The profitability of Dogecoin (DOGE) has always been a question, as the high volatility of the token indicates a threat to the stability of holders&rsquo; portfolios.</p>
<p class="s4">At the time of writing, DOGE has slashed 10.20% to $0.077490 in the past 30 days as the crypto market sell-off worsens.</p>
<p class="s4">Accordingly, the descending movement of the token reflects the poor state of Dogecoin (DOGE) on the market, citing a lack of speculative interest from both bulls and bears toward the coin.</p>
<p class="s4">Market participants now rush to exit their DOGE holdings as the meme coin does not have a foreseeable future. Differently, The Hideaways (HDWY) guaranteed safety for investors thanks to its permanently locked liquidity, offering security and profitability.</p>
<p class="s7">Dogecoin (DOGE) Whale Withdraws $6.5M</p>
<p class="s4">A minor consolation for Dogecoin (DOGE) holders could be the recent massive transfer from the crypto exchange Binance. Reports revealed that a whale transferred out 81,396,088 DOGE, amounting to $6.50 million.</p>
<p class="s4">Nevertheless, DOGE's drawback persisted despite its explosive performance in November and October.</p>
<p class="s4">Notably, Dogecoin (DOGE) gained popularity after receiving support from celebrities and public figures like Tesla CEO Elon Musk. However, the lack of real use of the token remains its main weakness amid the dragging market factors.</p>
<p class="s4">Fortunately, The Hideaways (HDWY) offers profitable functionality to save investors from further woes in the crypto space.</p>
<p class="s9">The Hideaways (HDWY) Takes Off Far From Dogecoin (DOGE)</p>
<p class="s4">Crypto enthusiasts have projected that Dogecoin (DOGE) is set to play a dismal performance in 2023 compared with more rounded projects like The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p class="s4">Dog-themed meme coins are popular as they offer a fun and easy way to access the blockchain. Still, brand-new projects like HDWY are taking the new-generational investment to deliver bullish gains.</p>
<p class="s4">The Hideaways (HDWY) operates a platform set to mint non-fungible tokens underpinned by high-tier real estate properties that are hand-picked by experts.</p>
<p class="s4">The crypto-driven project will close its presale at the end of December with an offered price of $0.10 per token. There is still time to be part of The Hideaways (HDWY) and win amazing rewards of up to a 100% bonus and a prize draw of $100,000!</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io </p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Analysts: Focus On The Hideaways (HDWY) Instead Of Shiba Inu (SHIB) And Polygon (MATIC)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/analysts-focus-on-the-hideaways-hdwy-instead-of-shiba-inu-shib-and-polygon-matic</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/analysts-focus-on-the-hideaways-hdwy-instead-of-shiba-inu-shib-and-polygon-matic</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Finding a currency that can make investors money is becoming increasingly difficult as many coins are produced daily. You might be wondering right now if famous cryptocurrencies still generate earnings.</p>
<p>Various crypto analysts believe that the answer is no. After FTX and BlockFi fell, these cryptocurrencies could not sustain the strain and have fallen sharply. Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Polygon (MATIC) were some of those caught in the downtrend.</p>
<p>But a new presale for The Hideaways has created some hype behind it. Let's look at the factors that might cause this coin to rise in 2023! </p>
<p class="s8">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Down 22% In the Last Three Months</p>
<p>Cryptocurrencies with canine themes have been proliferating over the past year. Shiba Inu(SHIB) is one such canine coin. Shiba Inu (SHIB) has attracted significant internet followers because it is a "meme coin."</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this hype has not resulted in a significant price point for Shiba Inu (SHIB). It has a price of $0.000008714, a 22% loss in the past three months. Bears still have Shiba Inu (SHIB) in their palm, and an investment in it at this time is not a good idea. According to some analysts, The Hideaways will be a better alternative in 2023. </p>
<p class="s8">Polygon (MATIC) Still Stuck In A Bear Market </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) was developed as a scalable mechanism to address several issues with the blockchain network, notably trading costs. Many blockchain platforms like Avalanche and Polkadot have features that Polygon (MATIC) shares.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) has had a tough year, as its price dropped by 63% in the last 12 months. And with the 11% weekly fall that occurred, Polygon (MATIC) is a high-risk asset that you should avoid. And investors are also noticing that, putting their funds in The Hideaways. </p>
<p class="s8">The Hideaways (HDWY) Price Will Drastically Increase</p>
<p>What makes The Hideaways stop going down the road that Polygon (MATIC) and Shiba Inu(SHIB) are now going? Let's take a closer look: </p>
● The Hideaways will generate an NFT backed by a real property that provides rental income.
● The Hideaways will deliver passive income to investors through ETH and USDT. 
● All members will be a part of monthly prize drops. 
<p>Have you ever wanted to invest in real estate for just $100? Through The Hideaways, that dream will become a reality. It will create a one-of-a-kind alternative-investment platformallowing individuals to buy and trade fractionalized NFTs backed by luxurious penthouses and mansions. </p>
<p>The Hideaways price is currently only $0.10, and it is predicted to rise to $4 by mid-2023. This will give early investors a 4,000% profit! With an early investment, you will also gain access to the first five properties with 6 NFTs each. </p>
<p>It has completed an audit through Solid Proof and will freeze liquidity for 999 years to diminish any rug-pull or scam scares. The Hideaways currently has a $100,000 giveaway so buy into this future blue-chip token now! </p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io </p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Finding a currency that can make investors money is becoming increasingly difficult as many coins are produced daily. You might be wondering right now if famous cryptocurrencies still generate earnings.</p>
<p>Various crypto analysts believe that the answer is no. After FTX and BlockFi fell, these cryptocurrencies could not sustain the strain and have fallen sharply. Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Polygon (MATIC) were some of those caught in the downtrend.</p>
<p>But a new presale for The Hideaways has created some hype behind it. Let's look at the factors that might cause this coin to rise in 2023! </p>
<p class="s8">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Down 22% In the Last Three Months</p>
<p>Cryptocurrencies with canine themes have been proliferating over the past year. Shiba Inu(SHIB) is one such canine coin. Shiba Inu (SHIB) has attracted significant internet followers because it is a "meme coin."</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this hype has not resulted in a significant price point for Shiba Inu (SHIB). It has a price of $0.000008714, a 22% loss in the past three months. Bears still have Shiba Inu (SHIB) in their palm, and an investment in it at this time is not a good idea. According to some analysts, The Hideaways will be a better alternative in 2023. </p>
<p class="s8">Polygon (MATIC) Still Stuck In A Bear Market </p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) was developed as a scalable mechanism to address several issues with the blockchain network, notably trading costs. Many blockchain platforms like Avalanche and Polkadot have features that Polygon (MATIC) shares.</p>
<p>Polygon (MATIC) has had a tough year, as its price dropped by 63% in the last 12 months. And with the 11% weekly fall that occurred, Polygon (MATIC) is a high-risk asset that you should avoid. And investors are also noticing that, putting their funds in The Hideaways. </p>
<p class="s8">The Hideaways (HDWY) Price Will Drastically Increase</p>
<p>What makes The Hideaways stop going down the road that Polygon (MATIC) and Shiba Inu(SHIB) are now going? Let's take a closer look: </p>
● The Hideaways will generate an NFT backed by a real property that provides rental income.
● The Hideaways will deliver passive income to investors through ETH and USDT. 
● All members will be a part of monthly prize drops. 
<p>Have you ever wanted to invest in real estate for just $100? Through The Hideaways, that dream will become a reality. It will create a one-of-a-kind alternative-investment platformallowing individuals to buy and trade fractionalized NFTs backed by luxurious penthouses and mansions. </p>
<p>The Hideaways price is currently only $0.10, and it is predicted to rise to $4 by mid-2023. This will give early investors a 4,000% profit! With an early investment, you will also gain access to the first five properties with 6 NFTs each. </p>
<p>It has completed an audit through Solid Proof and will freeze liquidity for 999 years to diminish any rug-pull or scam scares. The Hideaways currently has a $100,000 giveaway so buy into this future blue-chip token now! </p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io </p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Gensler says further legislation for crypto not necessary]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sec-gensler-says-further-legislation-for-crypto-not-necessary</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/reg-6.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/reg-6.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/reg-6.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sec-gensler-says-further-legislation-for-crypto-not-necessary</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Amidst the ongoing debacle of the FTX collapse and SBF&rsquo;s arrest, there are increasing calls in Washington for legislation to regulate the digital asset industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Gary Gensler, the chair of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), has opposed these calls for new laws, stating that existing SEC rules and Supreme Court decisions are sufficient and that crypto issuers and exchanges simply need to follow them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After two FTX executives pleaded guilty to fraud charges on Wednesday, Gensler warned other unregistered crypto issuers and exchanges that they may soon face enforcement actions from the agency. In a report in the NY Times, he stated, "The roadway is getting shorter."</p>
<p>According to Gensler's estimate, only a small fraction (approximately 0.06%) of the cryptocurrency tokens in circulation are registered with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors in these tokens do not receive the same level of disclosures as they would with investments in stocks. As a result, the public should be cautious when considering the reported volumes traded and values of these tokens.</p>
<p>According to Gensler, many of the thousands of cryptocurrencies listed on exchanges and tracking websites have low levels of trading activity and are susceptible to manipulation, similar to micro-cap companies (small publicly traded companies with a market capitalization of around $50 million to $300 million).</p>
<p>Gensler suggested that insiders of these projects may try to "sell the public on an idea while they're potentially fraudulently pumping up the stock,"&nbsp;</p>
<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;This leads to distorted incentives and puts the public further at risk of the token not being properly registered and having proper disclosures and complying with the various provisions of the securities law about anti-fraud and anti-manipulation,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Gensler expressed support for regulating certain sectors of the cryptocurrency market, such as stablecoins, which are digital assets designed to maintain a stable value relative to a specific asset, like the dollar. These assets often act as a connection between traditional finance and the future of finance, and have gained investor interest and the attention of some traditional finance players. However, Gensler expressed caution towards legislation that could weaken the SEC&rsquo;s authority.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst the ongoing debacle of the FTX collapse and SBF&rsquo;s arrest, there are increasing calls in Washington for legislation to regulate the digital asset industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, Gary Gensler, the chair of the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), has opposed these calls for new laws, stating that existing SEC rules and Supreme Court decisions are sufficient and that crypto issuers and exchanges simply need to follow them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After two FTX executives pleaded guilty to fraud charges on Wednesday, Gensler warned other unregistered crypto issuers and exchanges that they may soon face enforcement actions from the agency. In a report in the NY Times, he stated, "The roadway is getting shorter."</p>
<p>According to Gensler's estimate, only a small fraction (approximately 0.06%) of the cryptocurrency tokens in circulation are registered with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Investors in these tokens do not receive the same level of disclosures as they would with investments in stocks. As a result, the public should be cautious when considering the reported volumes traded and values of these tokens.</p>
<p>According to Gensler, many of the thousands of cryptocurrencies listed on exchanges and tracking websites have low levels of trading activity and are susceptible to manipulation, similar to micro-cap companies (small publicly traded companies with a market capitalization of around $50 million to $300 million).</p>
<p>Gensler suggested that insiders of these projects may try to "sell the public on an idea while they're potentially fraudulently pumping up the stock,"&nbsp;</p>
<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;This leads to distorted incentives and puts the public further at risk of the token not being properly registered and having proper disclosures and complying with the various provisions of the securities law about anti-fraud and anti-manipulation,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>Gensler expressed support for regulating certain sectors of the cryptocurrency market, such as stablecoins, which are digital assets designed to maintain a stable value relative to a specific asset, like the dollar. These assets often act as a connection between traditional finance and the future of finance, and have gained investor interest and the attention of some traditional finance players. However, Gensler expressed caution towards legislation that could weaken the SEC&rsquo;s authority.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SBF Extradited to the U.S., Crypto Daily TV 23/12/2022]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sbf-extradited-to-the-us-crypto-daily-tv-23-12-2022</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cdtv-23.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cdtv-23.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/cdtv-23.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sbf-extradited-to-the-us-crypto-daily-tv-23-12-2022</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>DeFi protocol Ankr says ex-employee caused $5M exploit.</p>
<p>A former employee of De-Fi protocol Ankr maliciously caused a $5 million exploit earlier this month. The ex-employee inserted a malicious code package to conduct a supply chain attack, which allowed a user to mint 6 quadrillion aBNBc tokens.</p>
<p>XRP Ripple Price Prediction: 2022-2030</p>
<p>If you intend to take advantage of the low prices of this bear market to invest in cryptocurrency, you might be wondering how XRP coins may fare in the future.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried to be extradited to the US.</p>
<p>After less than a week in Bahamian custody, Bankman-Fried appeared at court to ask a new magistrate judge, Judge Shaka Serville, to be extradited to the U.S. The hearing appeared to come as a surprise to both Bankman-Fried's local counsel, Jerone Roberts, and Bahamian prosecutors, and he was sent back to Fox Hill.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal, which matches our overall technical analysis.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>Ethereum gained 0.3% against the Dollar in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 1.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.3% in the last session. The Stochastic indicator's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD rose 0.4% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair gained 0.4% in the last session. The RSI is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Durable Goods Orders</p>
<p>The Durable Goods Orders measure the cost of orders received by manufacturers for durable goods, which means goods that should last three years or more, excluding the transport sector.</p>
<p>The US Durable Goods Orders will be released at 13:30 GMT, the US Nondefense Capital Goods Orders at 13:30 GMT, and the Belgian Consumer Price Index at 10:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Nondefense Capital Goods Orders</p>
<p>The Nondefense Capital Goods Orders measures the cost of orders received by manufacturers for capital goods, which are durable goods used in the production of goods or services.</p>
<p>BE Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>NL Gross Domestic Product</p>
<p>The Gross Domestic Product is a measure of the total value of all goods and services produced by a country. The GDP is considered a broad measure of economic activity and health.</p>
<p>The Dutch Gross Domestic Product will be released at 05:30 GMT, Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT, and the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>DeFi protocol Ankr says ex-employee caused $5M exploit.</p>
<p>A former employee of De-Fi protocol Ankr maliciously caused a $5 million exploit earlier this month. The ex-employee inserted a malicious code package to conduct a supply chain attack, which allowed a user to mint 6 quadrillion aBNBc tokens.</p>
<p>XRP Ripple Price Prediction: 2022-2030</p>
<p>If you intend to take advantage of the low prices of this bear market to invest in cryptocurrency, you might be wondering how XRP coins may fare in the future.</p>
<p>Sam Bankman-Fried to be extradited to the US.</p>
<p>After less than a week in Bahamian custody, Bankman-Fried appeared at court to ask a new magistrate judge, Judge Shaka Serville, to be extradited to the U.S. The hearing appeared to come as a surprise to both Bankman-Fried's local counsel, Jerone Roberts, and Bahamian prosecutors, and he was sent back to Fox Hill.</p>
BTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal, which matches our overall technical analysis.</p>
<p>The MACD is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>Ethereum gained 0.3% against the Dollar in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD skyrocketed 1.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair skyrocketed 1.3% in the last session. The Stochastic indicator's negative signal is in line with the overall technical analysis.</p>
<p>The Stochastic indicator is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD rose 0.4% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair gained 0.4% in the last session. The RSI is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in negative territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Durable Goods Orders</p>
<p>The Durable Goods Orders measure the cost of orders received by manufacturers for durable goods, which means goods that should last three years or more, excluding the transport sector.</p>
<p>The US Durable Goods Orders will be released at 13:30 GMT, the US Nondefense Capital Goods Orders at 13:30 GMT, and the Belgian Consumer Price Index at 10:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Nondefense Capital Goods Orders</p>
<p>The Nondefense Capital Goods Orders measures the cost of orders received by manufacturers for capital goods, which are durable goods used in the production of goods or services.</p>
<p>BE Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>NL Gross Domestic Product</p>
<p>The Gross Domestic Product is a measure of the total value of all goods and services produced by a country. The GDP is considered a broad measure of economic activity and health.</p>
<p>The Dutch Gross Domestic Product will be released at 05:30 GMT, Japan's CFTC JPY NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT, and the UK's CFTC GBP NC Net Positions at 20:30 GMT.</p>
<p>JP CFTC JPY NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>UK CFTC GBP NC Net Positions</p>
<p>The weekly Commitments of Traders (COT) report provides information on the size and the direction of the positions taken. The report focuses on speculative positions.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Brazil Signs Crypto Regulations into Law]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/brazil-signs-crypto-regulations-into-law</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/brazil-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/brazil-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/brazil-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/brazil-signs-crypto-regulations-into-law</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Brazil&rsquo;s outgoing president, Jair Bolsonaro, has signed a bill that will legalize the use of cryptocurrencies as a payment method in the country. </p>
<p>Jair Bolsonaro, the president of Brazil who is set to leave office on December 31, on Thursday approved a crypto regulation bill that was recently passed by the country&rsquo;s Chamber of Deputies and the Senate. The new law establishes a crime of fraud involving virtual assets that will come with a penalty of anywhere between four and six years in prison and will further include a fine. The bill also created a &ldquo;virtual service provider&rdquo; license, which will be required by digital asset firms, including exchanges and trading intermediaries. The news was first reported by Bloomberg.</p>
<p>The bill&rsquo;s text explains that Brazilians will not be able to use crypto such as Bitcoin as legal tender like in El Salvador. The newly passed bill does however include various digital currencies under the definition of legal payment methods within the country. Bolsonaro&rsquo;s administration does also not indicate which deferral agency would oversee supervising cryptocurrency payments. Digital assets, like in the U.S., are deemed to be securities, and therefore fall under the purview of Brazil&rsquo;s Securities and Exchange Commission. The bill also includes provisions that have been developed in response to the collapse of FTX and requires crypto exchanges to clearly distinguish between user and company assets.</p>
<p>Following its approval on Thursday, companies have 180 days to adapt to the new rules put forward in the bill. Bolsonaro will not be in the office to see the new crypto law take effect and will be replaced by Luiz In&aacute;cio Lula da Silva who will take over as president as of January 1, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brazil&rsquo;s outgoing president, Jair Bolsonaro, has signed a bill that will legalize the use of cryptocurrencies as a payment method in the country. </p>
<p>Jair Bolsonaro, the president of Brazil who is set to leave office on December 31, on Thursday approved a crypto regulation bill that was recently passed by the country&rsquo;s Chamber of Deputies and the Senate. The new law establishes a crime of fraud involving virtual assets that will come with a penalty of anywhere between four and six years in prison and will further include a fine. The bill also created a &ldquo;virtual service provider&rdquo; license, which will be required by digital asset firms, including exchanges and trading intermediaries. The news was first reported by Bloomberg.</p>
<p>The bill&rsquo;s text explains that Brazilians will not be able to use crypto such as Bitcoin as legal tender like in El Salvador. The newly passed bill does however include various digital currencies under the definition of legal payment methods within the country. Bolsonaro&rsquo;s administration does also not indicate which deferral agency would oversee supervising cryptocurrency payments. Digital assets, like in the U.S., are deemed to be securities, and therefore fall under the purview of Brazil&rsquo;s Securities and Exchange Commission. The bill also includes provisions that have been developed in response to the collapse of FTX and requires crypto exchanges to clearly distinguish between user and company assets.</p>
<p>Following its approval on Thursday, companies have 180 days to adapt to the new rules put forward in the bill. Bolsonaro will not be in the office to see the new crypto law take effect and will be replaced by Luiz In&aacute;cio Lula da Silva who will take over as president as of January 1, 2023.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Astar Network Named ‘Product of the Year’ At the JBA  Annual Blockchain Award]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Sota_Watanbe_Astar_1671802255bO3lPYBkyA.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Sota_Watanbe_Astar_1671802255bO3lPYBkyA.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Sota_Watanbe_Astar_1671802255bO3lPYBkyA.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/astar-network-named-product-of-the-year-at-the-jba-annual-blockchain-award</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, has been awarded the Product of the Year at the 4th annual Blockchain Award by the Japan Blockchain Association. Astar Network&rsquo;s founder and CEO Sota Watanabe bagged the Person of the Year award for the second consecutive year at the same event.</p>
<p>Both Astar Network and Sota Watanabe emerged as the favorites of the Japanese Web3 community in a survey conducted by the Japan Blockchain Association (JBA). The JBA is the largest blockchain association in Japan, consisting of 171 companies including bitFlyer, Coincheck, Microsoft, GMO, EY, Deloitte, PwC, KPMG, Toyota, and ConsenSys.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sota Watanabe, the founder and CEO of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We are delighted to have been recognized by the Japanese Web3 community. As Japan&rsquo;s leading blockchain project, we remain committed to accelerating Web3 innovation through Astar. In 2023 and beyond, we will leverage our presence in Japan to unlock opportunities for entrepreneurs, developers, and users alike.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 chain in Japan. As a parachain of Polkadot, it enables developers to build interoperable dApps. It supports both EVM and WASM smart contracts with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine messaging (XVM).</p>
<p>As the Japanese government has made Web3 a part of its national strategy, Sota Watanabe is helping the government on the path forward. Sota has also been featured in the Forbes 30 Under 30 for both Asia and Japan. He has also been picked as one of the top entrepreneurs in Japan, and graces the cover of the latest edition of the Forbes Japan magazine.</p>

<p>Astar Network is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. It&rsquo;s also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p>
About Astar Network
<p>Astar Network supports the building of dApps with EVM and WASM smart contracts and offers developers true interoperability, with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine (XVM). We are made by developers and for developers. Astar&rsquo;s unique Build2Earn model empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the code they write and dApps they build.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Astar&rsquo;s vibrant ecosystem has become Polkadot&rsquo;s leading Parachain globally, supported by all major exchanges and tier 1 VCs. Astar offers the flexibility of all Ethereum and WASM toolings for developers to start building their dApps.</p>
<p>&nbsp;For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit</p>ContactMaarten Henskenspress@astar.network]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo, Japan, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Astar Network, the smart contract platform for multichain, has been awarded the Product of the Year at the 4th annual Blockchain Award by the Japan Blockchain Association. Astar Network&rsquo;s founder and CEO Sota Watanabe bagged the Person of the Year award for the second consecutive year at the same event.</p>
<p>Both Astar Network and Sota Watanabe emerged as the favorites of the Japanese Web3 community in a survey conducted by the Japan Blockchain Association (JBA). The JBA is the largest blockchain association in Japan, consisting of 171 companies including bitFlyer, Coincheck, Microsoft, GMO, EY, Deloitte, PwC, KPMG, Toyota, and ConsenSys.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sota Watanabe, the founder and CEO of Astar Network, said, &ldquo;We are delighted to have been recognized by the Japanese Web3 community. As Japan&rsquo;s leading blockchain project, we remain committed to accelerating Web3 innovation through Astar. In 2023 and beyond, we will leverage our presence in Japan to unlock opportunities for entrepreneurs, developers, and users alike.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Astar Network is the leading Layer-1 chain in Japan. As a parachain of Polkadot, it enables developers to build interoperable dApps. It supports both EVM and WASM smart contracts with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine messaging (XVM).</p>
<p>As the Japanese government has made Web3 a part of its national strategy, Sota Watanabe is helping the government on the path forward. Sota has also been featured in the Forbes 30 Under 30 for both Asia and Japan. He has also been picked as one of the top entrepreneurs in Japan, and graces the cover of the latest edition of the Forbes Japan magazine.</p>

<p>Astar Network is the go-to blockchain for developers and enterprises interested in exploring the Japanese Web3 space. It&rsquo;s also the first public blockchain from the country to be listed there despite Japan&rsquo;s strict listing regulations. Astar&rsquo;s native token ASTR is registered as a cryptocurrency, not a security, by the Japanese government.</p>
About Astar Network
<p>Astar Network supports the building of dApps with EVM and WASM smart contracts and offers developers true interoperability, with cross-consensus messaging (XCM) and cross-virtual machine (XVM). We are made by developers and for developers. Astar&rsquo;s unique Build2Earn model empowers developers to get paid through a dApp staking mechanism for the code they write and dApps they build.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Astar&rsquo;s vibrant ecosystem has become Polkadot&rsquo;s leading Parachain globally, supported by all major exchanges and tier 1 VCs. Astar offers the flexibility of all Ethereum and WASM toolings for developers to start building their dApps.</p>
<p>&nbsp;For more information, visit: Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram | GitHub | Reddit</p>ContactMaarten Henskenspress@astar.network]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[AAG Taps Coinbase Pay  As A Fiat On-ramping Solution For The MetaOne Wallet]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/aag-taps-coinbase-pay-as-a-fiat-on-ramping-solution-for-the-metaone-wallet</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-22_14-19-05_1671712852JS9mf34z6d.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-22_14-19-05_1671712852JS9mf34z6d.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-22_14-19-05_1671712852JS9mf34z6d.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/aag-taps-coinbase-pay-as-a-fiat-on-ramping-solution-for-the-metaone-wallet</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, SG, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>AAG, a web3 infrastructure company, has integrated Coinbase Pay to enhance the fiat on-ramping features of its new user focused MetaOne Wallet. The integration will make it easier for users, many who never previously owned cryptocurrencies, to acquire digital assets and NFTs as part of their web3 journey. </p>
<p>MetaOne Wallet is the flagship product under the AAG banner. It is a digital and unique crypto wallet that suits the needs of novices and experienced users. There is a substantial emphasis on security, safety, and efficiency, without compromising convenience. </p>
<p>MetaOne has integrated Coinbase Pay to make the onboarding process more straightforward. With the help of Coinbase Pay, MetaOne Wallet users can conveniently purchase non-fungible tokens and cryptocurrencies through convenient fiat currency payment methods.</p>
<p>&ldquo;With the recent situation with FTX, we believe that more and more users will be looking for an alternative option for self-custody. MetaOne, with its unique features, is perfect for those who might not be comfortable with a fully non-custodial wallet.&rdquo; - said Jack Vinijtrongjit, CEO of AAG
</p>
<p>Integrating convenient fiat currency payment support is an integral part of AAG's mission to make MetaOne Wallet the only necessary tool for Web3 and metaverse purposes. Therefore, it is easy enough for novice crypto users, but powerful enough when they become power users.</p>
<p>The MetaOne Wallet features an integrated decentralized application store where only safe applications are whitelisted and approved called the MetaOne dpp store. Accessing these applications is done within the wallet through a built-in browser. </p>
<p>Furthermore, users benefit from eliminating private keys and seed phrases, making the wallet more straightforward to use by mainstream users. Instead, MetaOne relies on n-factor authentication to provide a seamless user experience.</p>
<p>In addition, the MetaOne Wallet performs automatic asset discovery. User assets will automatically be identified and displayed on the balance screen without requiring manual intervention. With support for assets across multiple blockchains - more to be added soon - it is an all-in-one solution for storing and managing digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
 &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;###</p>
<p>About AAG</p>
<p>AAG is a web3 infrastructure company focusing on providing software that helps simplify interactions with blockchain applications and the Metaverse for mainstream users and traditional companies. AAG provides a secure and easy-to-use crypto wallet, as well as infrastructure software, such as a cross-chain search engine and GameFi SDK for enterprise companies. With the belief that education is the key to unlock the potential of web3, AAG is also exploring the concept of Learn-and-Earn with the mission of enabling economic opportunities worldwide via the Metaverse economy. AAG aims to bring 1 billion people into the Metaverse economy by 2030.</p>
<p>For more information about AAG, visit: AAG Linktree</p>ContactDan HorowitzPR@marketacross.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, SG, 23rd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>AAG, a web3 infrastructure company, has integrated Coinbase Pay to enhance the fiat on-ramping features of its new user focused MetaOne Wallet. The integration will make it easier for users, many who never previously owned cryptocurrencies, to acquire digital assets and NFTs as part of their web3 journey. </p>
<p>MetaOne Wallet is the flagship product under the AAG banner. It is a digital and unique crypto wallet that suits the needs of novices and experienced users. There is a substantial emphasis on security, safety, and efficiency, without compromising convenience. </p>
<p>MetaOne has integrated Coinbase Pay to make the onboarding process more straightforward. With the help of Coinbase Pay, MetaOne Wallet users can conveniently purchase non-fungible tokens and cryptocurrencies through convenient fiat currency payment methods.</p>
<p>&ldquo;With the recent situation with FTX, we believe that more and more users will be looking for an alternative option for self-custody. MetaOne, with its unique features, is perfect for those who might not be comfortable with a fully non-custodial wallet.&rdquo; - said Jack Vinijtrongjit, CEO of AAG
</p>
<p>Integrating convenient fiat currency payment support is an integral part of AAG's mission to make MetaOne Wallet the only necessary tool for Web3 and metaverse purposes. Therefore, it is easy enough for novice crypto users, but powerful enough when they become power users.</p>
<p>The MetaOne Wallet features an integrated decentralized application store where only safe applications are whitelisted and approved called the MetaOne dpp store. Accessing these applications is done within the wallet through a built-in browser. </p>
<p>Furthermore, users benefit from eliminating private keys and seed phrases, making the wallet more straightforward to use by mainstream users. Instead, MetaOne relies on n-factor authentication to provide a seamless user experience.</p>
<p>In addition, the MetaOne Wallet performs automatic asset discovery. User assets will automatically be identified and displayed on the balance screen without requiring manual intervention. With support for assets across multiple blockchains - more to be added soon - it is an all-in-one solution for storing and managing digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>
 &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;###</p>
<p>About AAG</p>
<p>AAG is a web3 infrastructure company focusing on providing software that helps simplify interactions with blockchain applications and the Metaverse for mainstream users and traditional companies. AAG provides a secure and easy-to-use crypto wallet, as well as infrastructure software, such as a cross-chain search engine and GameFi SDK for enterprise companies. With the belief that education is the key to unlock the potential of web3, AAG is also exploring the concept of Learn-and-Earn with the mission of enabling economic opportunities worldwide via the Metaverse economy. AAG aims to bring 1 billion people into the Metaverse economy by 2030.</p>
<p>For more information about AAG, visit: AAG Linktree</p>ContactDan HorowitzPR@marketacross.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Released on $250 Million Bail]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-250-million-bail</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sbf-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-250-million-bail</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Former CEO and founder of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, has been released on $250 million bail as he awaits trial for eight federal charges related to fraud. The 30-year-old crypto whizz is accused of mismanaging billions in customer funds at FTX. </p>
<p>A New York federal judge ruled on Thursday that FTX founder SBF will be released on a $250 million bond while he awaits trial for fraud related to his collapsed crypto empire. Per reports by CNBC and Reuters,&nbsp;SBF&rsquo;s bail was secured by his parents Joseph Bankman and Barbara Fried, who offered up their home in Palo Alto, California as collateral. This essentially means that since Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s parents signed the bond agreement, they would be liable for $250 million should their son decide to flee. Many have wondered how SBF, or his parents, in fact, could afford bail as Bankman-Fried said in late November that he now had &ldquo;close to nothing&rdquo; left and has one remaining credit card with &ldquo;maybe $100,000 in that bank account.&rdquo;</p>
Largest Bail in White Collar History
<p>It is no surprise that SBF received bail as he is accused of committing a white collar, or financial crime. New York federal prosecutors have indicated SBF&rsquo;s alleged crimes and the collapse of FTX as one of the largest financial frauds in the history of the United States, and his bond package understandably far exceeds some of the most notorious white-collar cases in that history. Reuters reports that one prominent New York bail bondsman who specializes in high-profile defendants said, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s the largest bond I&rsquo;ve ever heard of in my history of doing bonds.&rdquo;</p>
<p>One of the most prolific financial crimes in history &ndash; the $65 billion Ponzi scheme in which Bernard Madoff was at the helm, saw him released in 2008 on a $10 million bond. Madoff was ordered to surrender his passport and had to consent to strict monitoring conditions.</p>
<p>A more recent scandal saw Elizabeth Holmes, founder of blood testing startup Theranos, who was convicted of defrauding investors, released after her arrest in 2018 on a $500,000 bail bond after she was also required to surrender her passport.</p>
Bail Conditions See SBF Surrender His Passport
<p>As is common in accused crimes of this nature, defendants typically are required to surrender their passports and must wear monitoring devices. SBF&rsquo;s bail package is not different. Prosecutor Nicolas Roos told U.S. Magistrate Judge Gabriel Gorenstein that as part of the conditions of his bail, SBF would have to hand over his passport and will see him confined to his parent&rsquo;s home.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Former CEO and founder of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, has been released on $250 million bail as he awaits trial for eight federal charges related to fraud. The 30-year-old crypto whizz is accused of mismanaging billions in customer funds at FTX. </p>
<p>A New York federal judge ruled on Thursday that FTX founder SBF will be released on a $250 million bond while he awaits trial for fraud related to his collapsed crypto empire. Per reports by CNBC and Reuters,&nbsp;SBF&rsquo;s bail was secured by his parents Joseph Bankman and Barbara Fried, who offered up their home in Palo Alto, California as collateral. This essentially means that since Bankman-Fried&rsquo;s parents signed the bond agreement, they would be liable for $250 million should their son decide to flee. Many have wondered how SBF, or his parents, in fact, could afford bail as Bankman-Fried said in late November that he now had &ldquo;close to nothing&rdquo; left and has one remaining credit card with &ldquo;maybe $100,000 in that bank account.&rdquo;</p>
Largest Bail in White Collar History
<p>It is no surprise that SBF received bail as he is accused of committing a white collar, or financial crime. New York federal prosecutors have indicated SBF&rsquo;s alleged crimes and the collapse of FTX as one of the largest financial frauds in the history of the United States, and his bond package understandably far exceeds some of the most notorious white-collar cases in that history. Reuters reports that one prominent New York bail bondsman who specializes in high-profile defendants said, &ldquo;It&rsquo;s the largest bond I&rsquo;ve ever heard of in my history of doing bonds.&rdquo;</p>
<p>One of the most prolific financial crimes in history &ndash; the $65 billion Ponzi scheme in which Bernard Madoff was at the helm, saw him released in 2008 on a $10 million bond. Madoff was ordered to surrender his passport and had to consent to strict monitoring conditions.</p>
<p>A more recent scandal saw Elizabeth Holmes, founder of blood testing startup Theranos, who was convicted of defrauding investors, released after her arrest in 2018 on a $500,000 bail bond after she was also required to surrender her passport.</p>
Bail Conditions See SBF Surrender His Passport
<p>As is common in accused crimes of this nature, defendants typically are required to surrender their passports and must wear monitoring devices. SBF&rsquo;s bail package is not different. Prosecutor Nicolas Roos told U.S. Magistrate Judge Gabriel Gorenstein that as part of the conditions of his bail, SBF would have to hand over his passport and will see him confined to his parent&rsquo;s home.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The New NTO Collection Designed By Choise.com Launches On December 21st]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/the-new-nto-collection-designed-by-choisecom-launches-on-december-21st</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-21_131556_1671623113jk7Uukglko.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-21_131556_1671623113jk7Uukglko.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2022-12-21_131556_1671623113jk7Uukglko.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/the-new-nto-collection-designed-by-choisecom-launches-on-december-21st</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, UK, 22nd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Crypto firm and earn marketplace Choise.com is excited to announce the start of a new initiative, NFT Token Offering (NTO). By launching NTO Collection Choise.com sets out to introduce new mechanics that will fundamentally change the distribution market for tokens and NFTs.</p>
<p>NTO is a new type of token distribution that introduces a new asset class concept - overcollateralized NFTs. Each NFT offered via Choise.com NTO is backed by the company&rsquo;s native CHO tokens that are already actively traded on exchanges. This means that each NFT has actual value behind it. In addition to the tokens, a large number of gifts and prizes, whereby the prize pool is $5 million, are hidden in NFTs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choise.com is a leading earning marketplace that has been around since 2017. It offers a unified ecosystem where people can easily find and make use of various financial solutions to earn on their digital assets. This allows Choise.com clients the chance to select the most promising products and enjoy high returns from their investments without having to delve too deep into technical details.</p>
<p>Now Choise.com sets out to change the distribution market for tokens and NFTs. &nbsp;The Chobies NTO Collection is the first in the upcoming line of Choise.com NTO products. It embodies an interesting trend that might pick up in the crypto market over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choby NFTs come with a lot of features &ndash; almost a quarter of them come with perks. For example, users can win from 25 to 100,000 USDT in Choby NFTs or get cashback of up to 100%. Users also have a chance to get one of Choise.com's plastic and metal crypto cards inside a Choby NFT. Also, over 30 million CHO tokens have a 0-12 months lockup period, and vesting period is 0-36 months. However, you can mint a Choby NFT with a shorter or no period at all.</p>
<p>The NTO launch will be taking place in 6 stages, and the amount of offered NFTs will grow with each of them. Minting an NFT starts at $150 and grows at each stage by $50. Users can mint a Choby NFT, with thousands of CHO tokens inside. Notably, 1000 CHO cost $850 at the time of writing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Until now the value of NFTs was hard to assess, and their price could fluctuate wildly as a result. With Chobies, investors acquire NFTs that are backed by tokens with real value. Monitoring the rate of CHO allows them to estimate the viability of their investments. In the long term, this can become a great way for companies to expand their operations and grow their shareholder base.</p>
<p>NFTs represent a good tool for the tokenization of various creative and financial assets. And Choise.com NTO can help establish a new industry standard where companies with good tokenomics can raise the necessary funds to develop their own products while catering to the desires of market players. As a result, everyone stands to benefit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Visit the Choise.com website for more information on how to take part in this exciting opportunity here.</p>
<p>About Choise.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choise.com is a crypto firm that combines the best of the CeFi and DeFi worlds. Choise.com is the evolution of Crypterium, serving over 750,000 registered users and with a $1 billion 12-month turnover. With the recent rebrand, the company seeks to offer its clients the most profitable and exciting opportunities to earn on crypto via centralised and decentralised finance solutions alike.</p>
<p>Learn more: https://choise.com/ </p>ContactAlina SysoevaChoise.compr@choise.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, UK, 22nd December, 2022, Chainwire</p><p>Crypto firm and earn marketplace Choise.com is excited to announce the start of a new initiative, NFT Token Offering (NTO). By launching NTO Collection Choise.com sets out to introduce new mechanics that will fundamentally change the distribution market for tokens and NFTs.</p>
<p>NTO is a new type of token distribution that introduces a new asset class concept - overcollateralized NFTs. Each NFT offered via Choise.com NTO is backed by the company&rsquo;s native CHO tokens that are already actively traded on exchanges. This means that each NFT has actual value behind it. In addition to the tokens, a large number of gifts and prizes, whereby the prize pool is $5 million, are hidden in NFTs.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choise.com is a leading earning marketplace that has been around since 2017. It offers a unified ecosystem where people can easily find and make use of various financial solutions to earn on their digital assets. This allows Choise.com clients the chance to select the most promising products and enjoy high returns from their investments without having to delve too deep into technical details.</p>
<p>Now Choise.com sets out to change the distribution market for tokens and NFTs. &nbsp;The Chobies NTO Collection is the first in the upcoming line of Choise.com NTO products. It embodies an interesting trend that might pick up in the crypto market over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choby NFTs come with a lot of features &ndash; almost a quarter of them come with perks. For example, users can win from 25 to 100,000 USDT in Choby NFTs or get cashback of up to 100%. Users also have a chance to get one of Choise.com's plastic and metal crypto cards inside a Choby NFT. Also, over 30 million CHO tokens have a 0-12 months lockup period, and vesting period is 0-36 months. However, you can mint a Choby NFT with a shorter or no period at all.</p>
<p>The NTO launch will be taking place in 6 stages, and the amount of offered NFTs will grow with each of them. Minting an NFT starts at $150 and grows at each stage by $50. Users can mint a Choby NFT, with thousands of CHO tokens inside. Notably, 1000 CHO cost $850 at the time of writing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Until now the value of NFTs was hard to assess, and their price could fluctuate wildly as a result. With Chobies, investors acquire NFTs that are backed by tokens with real value. Monitoring the rate of CHO allows them to estimate the viability of their investments. In the long term, this can become a great way for companies to expand their operations and grow their shareholder base.</p>
<p>NFTs represent a good tool for the tokenization of various creative and financial assets. And Choise.com NTO can help establish a new industry standard where companies with good tokenomics can raise the necessary funds to develop their own products while catering to the desires of market players. As a result, everyone stands to benefit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Visit the Choise.com website for more information on how to take part in this exciting opportunity here.</p>
<p>About Choise.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Choise.com is a crypto firm that combines the best of the CeFi and DeFi worlds. Choise.com is the evolution of Crypterium, serving over 750,000 registered users and with a $1 billion 12-month turnover. With the recent rebrand, the company seeks to offer its clients the most profitable and exciting opportunities to earn on crypto via centralised and decentralised finance solutions alike.</p>
<p>Learn more: https://choise.com/ </p>ContactAlina SysoevaChoise.compr@choise.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance supplies answers to all the FUD]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/binance-supplies-answers-to-all-the-fud</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-9.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-9.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bin-9.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/binance-supplies-answers-to-all-the-fud</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Top crypto exchange Binance has been the target of much FUD over recent weeks. In a Chinese blog post, Binance answers all its critics.</p>
<p>Binance has been under huge scrutiny recently, in part due to many critics who want undeniable proof that the platform has the assets it says it has, and in perhaps in part due to some who would like to see the biggest crypto trading platform in the world brought down.</p>
<p>Binance has sought to answer all the accusations brought against it over recent weeks with a Chinese blog post (no English version available as yet). In the post it seeks to clear up 7 key issues.</p>
<p>Firstly, it tackles the issue of USDC. This stable coin was temporarily suspended earlier this month. Binance said that it wanted to consolidate its stablecoins into the most liquid ones - one of these being its own BUSD stablecoin.</p>
<p>Next it answered the accusation that there weren&rsquo;t sufficient liquid reserves for users to withdraw. Binance said that between the 12th to the 14th of December, net withdrawals had reached $6 billion, but that the exchange had withstood the test.</p>
<p>Even though blockchain auditor Mazars had distanced itself from its Binance audit, CryptoQuant, a data analytics platform, confirmed that the Binance reserves were at least 99% equal to what the platform said they were.</p>
<p>Also on the question of a suitable auditor, Binance said that it was in discussions with companies that could provide verification services. Binance maintains that even the big four auditors would not know how to audit the overall reserves of an encrypted company.</p>
<p>The fourth point of contention was why only BTC verification had been supplied, and why not other crypto assets? Binance said that it &ldquo;takes the most cautious attitude towards all work involving user assets&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It cited the many currencies, huge volumes, the amount of teams involved, and the money and time taken to carry out the verification process. It said that the second batch of asset verification would happen soon.</p>
<p>On how it had refused to disclose financial information, Binance said that by law it didn&rsquo;t have to, given that it was a private company, and that it was &ldquo;financially healthy, self-sufficient, no external financing needs, and no external investors, and no intention to go public at this stage.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The sixth point was the mainstream media coverage given to Binance. As an example the exchange cited a Reuters report which contained &ldquo;ambiguities&rdquo;, and that readers would only see the &ldquo;eye-catching headlines&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Binance commented that it had the most approvals/licences in the world, and that it spent the most on fighting crime. It was stated that Binance had responded to 47,000 law enforcement requests since 2021.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Finally, in response to the seventh accusation that Binance had &ldquo;destroyed FTX&rdquo;, the exchange CEO CZ stated that &ldquo;FTX destroyed itself&rdquo;. He said that it had misappropriated user assets and that no healthy company can be destroyed by a tweet.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top crypto exchange Binance has been the target of much FUD over recent weeks. In a Chinese blog post, Binance answers all its critics.</p>
<p>Binance has been under huge scrutiny recently, in part due to many critics who want undeniable proof that the platform has the assets it says it has, and in perhaps in part due to some who would like to see the biggest crypto trading platform in the world brought down.</p>
<p>Binance has sought to answer all the accusations brought against it over recent weeks with a Chinese blog post (no English version available as yet). In the post it seeks to clear up 7 key issues.</p>
<p>Firstly, it tackles the issue of USDC. This stable coin was temporarily suspended earlier this month. Binance said that it wanted to consolidate its stablecoins into the most liquid ones - one of these being its own BUSD stablecoin.</p>
<p>Next it answered the accusation that there weren&rsquo;t sufficient liquid reserves for users to withdraw. Binance said that between the 12th to the 14th of December, net withdrawals had reached $6 billion, but that the exchange had withstood the test.</p>
<p>Even though blockchain auditor Mazars had distanced itself from its Binance audit, CryptoQuant, a data analytics platform, confirmed that the Binance reserves were at least 99% equal to what the platform said they were.</p>
<p>Also on the question of a suitable auditor, Binance said that it was in discussions with companies that could provide verification services. Binance maintains that even the big four auditors would not know how to audit the overall reserves of an encrypted company.</p>
<p>The fourth point of contention was why only BTC verification had been supplied, and why not other crypto assets? Binance said that it &ldquo;takes the most cautious attitude towards all work involving user assets&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It cited the many currencies, huge volumes, the amount of teams involved, and the money and time taken to carry out the verification process. It said that the second batch of asset verification would happen soon.</p>
<p>On how it had refused to disclose financial information, Binance said that by law it didn&rsquo;t have to, given that it was a private company, and that it was &ldquo;financially healthy, self-sufficient, no external financing needs, and no external investors, and no intention to go public at this stage.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The sixth point was the mainstream media coverage given to Binance. As an example the exchange cited a Reuters report which contained &ldquo;ambiguities&rdquo;, and that readers would only see the &ldquo;eye-catching headlines&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Binance commented that it had the most approvals/licences in the world, and that it spent the most on fighting crime. It was stated that Binance had responded to 47,000 law enforcement requests since 2021.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Finally, in response to the seventh accusation that Binance had &ldquo;destroyed FTX&rdquo;, the exchange CEO CZ stated that &ldquo;FTX destroyed itself&rdquo;. He said that it had misappropriated user assets and that no healthy company can be destroyed by a tweet.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Jetshare_JETT$: The  Aviation Industry Saviour]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/jetshare-jett-the-aviation-industry-saviour</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-22-161939.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-22-161939.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-22-161939.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/jetshare-jett-the-aviation-industry-saviour</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>There are quite a handful of industries that produce the world&rsquo;s richest people. One such industry is the aviation industry. Entering the industry is reserved for the wealthy and powerful.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This goes to confirm the mantra, &ldquo;The rich keep getting richer." The average cost of a private aircraft is out of range for the average Joe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But this is completely changing, thanks to a new blockchain project - Jetshare. In this article, we'll talk about how the Jetshare protocol is saving the global airline industry one fractional NFT at a time.</p>
The Fractional NFT Protocol
<p>The fractional NFT protocol of Jetshare makes it possible for people to own private jets without having to spend millions of dollars. Instead, the company purchases private Jets through its SPV and stores them at high security, insured airport hangars across the world.</p>
<p>A digital version of these jets is minted and made available to native JETT$ token holders. Jet ownership is registered on international databases like the Civil Aviation Authority website and the tokens are visible on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Benefits &amp; Returns</p>
<p>It's safe to say that there are many reasons to invest in Jetshare, from its price to the community the project is building. Additionally, Jetshare's smart contract audit was completed and approved by renowned Canadian auditors Soken, making the platform a secure investment in the eyes of blockchain specialists. RJ Aleksandrs the founder has over 25 years experience buying/selling Jets and as a pilot.</p>
<p>Community members will have access to free sightseeing flights, discount private Jet charters, flying lesson, access to Aviator NFTs and many more benefits. The JETT$ token can be utilised in a number of ways including as payment for booking Jet charters from third party companies, access to worldwide private jet events and for payment of goods at airports around the world.</p>
<p>Shareowners receive capital growth through Jet sales or income from lease contracts as well as organic token price increases and trading of fractional NFTs. This industry has always been seen as private and luxury so it makes it even more timely that projects like Jetshare exist to decentralize and democratize ownership. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
How To Invest
<p>To invest in the Jetshare project, you&rsquo;ll need to follow the steps listed below:</p>
<ul>
<li> Visit the Jetshare website.</li>
<li> Click on &ldquo;Buy JETT$ Now&rdquo;</li>
<li> Fill in your name and basic info and create a password</li>
<li> Select the token you wish to invest with. (Eg. BTC, USDT)</li>
<li> Tick all boxes</li>
<li> Click on &lsquo;create account&rdquo;</li>
<li> Once your account is created, connect your chosen wallet fill in the amount to buy</li>
<li> Submit the order.</li>
<li> Wait for the transaction to be confirmed</li>
</ul>
<p>Once this is done, you will receive a confirmation email. You can then claim your tokens once the project launches.</p>
<p>Its that simple to own a private Jet that you will have a chance to take a group of friends in as part of your membership benefits.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>We all know fractional jet ownership in the blockchain industry is nothing new. Nonetheless, Jetshare is doing something different. However, developing a Web3 version with community at the center and a clear exit strategy is unique in the crypto market.</p>
<p>They are opening up the exclusive market of the rich and powerful to cryptocurrency users.Analysts predict Jetshare to be among the top cryptocurrencies of 2023 and expect the current 0.0125 price to increase rapidly over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>Join the organic community and help make Jet ownership possible for the average Joe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Jetshare is your gateway to investing in the aviation industry, even with a tiny budget. Got questions?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://jetshare.io/#</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT</p>
<p>Discord: https://discord.com/invite/uwUExmZsVt</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/jetsharecommunity</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are quite a handful of industries that produce the world&rsquo;s richest people. One such industry is the aviation industry. Entering the industry is reserved for the wealthy and powerful.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This goes to confirm the mantra, &ldquo;The rich keep getting richer." The average cost of a private aircraft is out of range for the average Joe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>But this is completely changing, thanks to a new blockchain project - Jetshare. In this article, we'll talk about how the Jetshare protocol is saving the global airline industry one fractional NFT at a time.</p>
The Fractional NFT Protocol
<p>The fractional NFT protocol of Jetshare makes it possible for people to own private jets without having to spend millions of dollars. Instead, the company purchases private Jets through its SPV and stores them at high security, insured airport hangars across the world.</p>
<p>A digital version of these jets is minted and made available to native JETT$ token holders. Jet ownership is registered on international databases like the Civil Aviation Authority website and the tokens are visible on the blockchain.</p>
<p>Benefits &amp; Returns</p>
<p>It's safe to say that there are many reasons to invest in Jetshare, from its price to the community the project is building. Additionally, Jetshare's smart contract audit was completed and approved by renowned Canadian auditors Soken, making the platform a secure investment in the eyes of blockchain specialists. RJ Aleksandrs the founder has over 25 years experience buying/selling Jets and as a pilot.</p>
<p>Community members will have access to free sightseeing flights, discount private Jet charters, flying lesson, access to Aviator NFTs and many more benefits. The JETT$ token can be utilised in a number of ways including as payment for booking Jet charters from third party companies, access to worldwide private jet events and for payment of goods at airports around the world.</p>
<p>Shareowners receive capital growth through Jet sales or income from lease contracts as well as organic token price increases and trading of fractional NFTs. This industry has always been seen as private and luxury so it makes it even more timely that projects like Jetshare exist to decentralize and democratize ownership. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
How To Invest
<p>To invest in the Jetshare project, you&rsquo;ll need to follow the steps listed below:</p>
<ul>
<li> Visit the Jetshare website.</li>
<li> Click on &ldquo;Buy JETT$ Now&rdquo;</li>
<li> Fill in your name and basic info and create a password</li>
<li> Select the token you wish to invest with. (Eg. BTC, USDT)</li>
<li> Tick all boxes</li>
<li> Click on &lsquo;create account&rdquo;</li>
<li> Once your account is created, connect your chosen wallet fill in the amount to buy</li>
<li> Submit the order.</li>
<li> Wait for the transaction to be confirmed</li>
</ul>
<p>Once this is done, you will receive a confirmation email. You can then claim your tokens once the project launches.</p>
<p>Its that simple to own a private Jet that you will have a chance to take a group of friends in as part of your membership benefits.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>We all know fractional jet ownership in the blockchain industry is nothing new. Nonetheless, Jetshare is doing something different. However, developing a Web3 version with community at the center and a clear exit strategy is unique in the crypto market.</p>
<p>They are opening up the exclusive market of the rich and powerful to cryptocurrency users.Analysts predict Jetshare to be among the top cryptocurrencies of 2023 and expect the current 0.0125 price to increase rapidly over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>Join the organic community and help make Jet ownership possible for the average Joe.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Jetshare is your gateway to investing in the aviation industry, even with a tiny budget. Got questions?&nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://jetshare.io/#</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Jetshare_JETT</p>
<p>Discord: https://discord.com/invite/uwUExmZsVt</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/jetsharecommunity</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FTX Co-Founders Plead Guilty To Fraud Charges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/ftx-co-founders-plead-guilty-to-fraud-charges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-plea-deal-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-plea-deal-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ftx-plea-deal-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/ftx-co-founders-plead-guilty-to-fraud-charges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Caroline Ellison, former CEO of Alameda Research and Sam Bankman-Fried's co-founder for FTX, has pleaded guilty to federal fraud charges as part of a deal for leniency in her own case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The plea deal also includes Zixiao (Gary) Wang, another FTX co-founder. Bankman-Fried and Ellison were charged with securities fraud, wire fraud and conspiracy to commit securities fraud. The two former FTX executives allegedly lied about the company's financial health and its ability to meet revenue expectations, while also hiding the fact that they had been selling most of their stock in order to pay off debts and disseminate investments into other shady dealings.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Wang was involved in the creation of certain features in the now-defunct exchange's contract and trading platform code which then allowed Alameda Research to maintain an "essentially unlimited line of credit on FTX" while also adjusting parameters for Alameda to gain an "unfair advantage when transacting on the platform," with faster trade execution finality and exemptions from other control parameters placed for regular clients.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"These critical code features and structural exceptions allowed Alameda to secretly and recklessly siphon FTX customer assets from the FTX platform," the CFTC stated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The plea deal was made in the Southern District of New York Court. Bankman-Fried, who just recently paid a $250 million bail after his hearing in Manhattan, faces eight charges for securities fraud and allegations of diverting cash to Alameda Research, which at the time was run by Ellison as a crypto hedge fund. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Bankman-Fried and Ellison also face separate charges in California, where they were charged for two counts of conspiracy to commit securities fraud and wire fraud, as well as one count of securities fraud. Alameda Research was also charged for its part in the alleged scheme. These charges include wire fraud, wire fraud conspiracy and conspiracy to commit money laundering, each of which carries a maximum prison terms of 20 years.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Until crypto platforms comply with time-tested securities laws, risks to investors will persist," he continued. "It remains a priority of the SEC to use all of our available tools to bring the industry into compliance." stated Gary Gensler, 33rd Chair of the SEC.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, a separate charge has also been made towards Wang and Ellison's involvement in defrauding equity investors from FTX. Statements from the authorities confirm that both Wang and Ellison have signed for full cooperation with New York officials, building the case against Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"If you participated in misconduct at FTX or Alameda, now is the time to get ahead of it. We are moving quickly and our patience is not eternal," warned U.S. Attorney Damian Williams in a video statement.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Statement of U.S. Attorney Damian Williams on U.S. v. Samuel Bankman-Fried, Caroline Ellison, and Gary Wang pic.twitter.com/u1y4cs3Koz</p>
&mdash; US Attorney SDNY (@SDNYnews) December 22, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankman-Fried was charged for a multiyear fraud that diverted billions in customer money towards personal use, as well as a series of real estate acquisitions in the Caribbean Islands.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Caroline Ellison, former CEO of Alameda Research and Sam Bankman-Fried's co-founder for FTX, has pleaded guilty to federal fraud charges as part of a deal for leniency in her own case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The plea deal also includes Zixiao (Gary) Wang, another FTX co-founder. Bankman-Fried and Ellison were charged with securities fraud, wire fraud and conspiracy to commit securities fraud. The two former FTX executives allegedly lied about the company's financial health and its ability to meet revenue expectations, while also hiding the fact that they had been selling most of their stock in order to pay off debts and disseminate investments into other shady dealings.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Wang was involved in the creation of certain features in the now-defunct exchange's contract and trading platform code which then allowed Alameda Research to maintain an "essentially unlimited line of credit on FTX" while also adjusting parameters for Alameda to gain an "unfair advantage when transacting on the platform," with faster trade execution finality and exemptions from other control parameters placed for regular clients.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"These critical code features and structural exceptions allowed Alameda to secretly and recklessly siphon FTX customer assets from the FTX platform," the CFTC stated.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The plea deal was made in the Southern District of New York Court. Bankman-Fried, who just recently paid a $250 million bail after his hearing in Manhattan, faces eight charges for securities fraud and allegations of diverting cash to Alameda Research, which at the time was run by Ellison as a crypto hedge fund. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Bankman-Fried and Ellison also face separate charges in California, where they were charged for two counts of conspiracy to commit securities fraud and wire fraud, as well as one count of securities fraud. Alameda Research was also charged for its part in the alleged scheme. These charges include wire fraud, wire fraud conspiracy and conspiracy to commit money laundering, each of which carries a maximum prison terms of 20 years.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Until crypto platforms comply with time-tested securities laws, risks to investors will persist," he continued. "It remains a priority of the SEC to use all of our available tools to bring the industry into compliance." stated Gary Gensler, 33rd Chair of the SEC.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, a separate charge has also been made towards Wang and Ellison's involvement in defrauding equity investors from FTX. Statements from the authorities confirm that both Wang and Ellison have signed for full cooperation with New York officials, building the case against Bankman-Fried.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">"If you participated in misconduct at FTX or Alameda, now is the time to get ahead of it. We are moving quickly and our patience is not eternal," warned U.S. Attorney Damian Williams in a video statement.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Statement of U.S. Attorney Damian Williams on U.S. v. Samuel Bankman-Fried, Caroline Ellison, and Gary Wang pic.twitter.com/u1y4cs3Koz</p>
&mdash; US Attorney SDNY (@SDNYnews) December 22, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bankman-Fried was charged for a multiyear fraud that diverted billions in customer money towards personal use, as well as a series of real estate acquisitions in the Caribbean Islands.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Attention Cardano (ADA) Holders: Further Drops Ahead]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/attention-cardano-ada-holders-further-drops-ahead</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/attention-cardano-ada-holders-further-drops-ahead</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) dropped to a multiyear low last week. The coin is currently trading at a critical threshold that could open up for further drops ahead.</p>
<p>It is by far ADA&rsquo;s most disappointing year, falling from its all-time high of $3 recorded just a year ago.</p>
<p>Analysts say this is the best time for Cardano (ADA) holders to jump into The Hideaways (HDWY) as a way to recover their losses and hedge against market volatility.</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) Still Has Room for a Big Retracement</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) declined to its lowest level in many years. ADA is currently trading at $0.25, carving another opportunity to print the lower low.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is down 14.27% in the last seven days which sent its total losses this year to 80%. This is a huge disappointment for the crypto community - Cardano (ADA) is known as the next Ethereum (ETH) killer, after all.</p>
<p>And although they are operating on the same business base, ADA underperformed against ETH by 29.93% year-on-year.</p>
<p>Analysts gave out their negative price forecast for Cardano (ADA) at the same time they upgraded projections for The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) is expected to reclaim the $0.15 support level if buying sentiment does not improve at $0.25. From the current state of things, we are more likely to see $0.15 back on the charts before the end of the year.</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA)&rsquo;s Technicals Point to Low Investor Sentiment</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA)&rsquo;s 24-hour trading volume has declined to $63.82 million from its $116 million level on December 16. This shows the lack of buying appetite for the crypto major as fear takes hold.</p>
<p>Moreover, its relative strength index remains in the oversold territory after falling to the critical level on December 15. RSI is now at 26.70 - a result below 30.0 shows strong selling pressure while a result above 70.0 indicates buyers&rsquo; dominance.</p>
<p>As of late, Cardano (ADA) is not working on any visible projects that could propel prices back to the green. This means we will be seeing more volatility in the coming weeks which is a clear signal to go elsewhere. Among the top investor choice is The Hideaways (HDWY), a real estate project everybody&rsquo;s taking an interest in.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) to Give a 9,000% ROI in 2023</p>
<p>If you are a Cardano (ADA) holder looking for a new investment to make, do not miss out on The Hideaways (HDWY).&nbsp;</p>
<p>The new cryptocurrency project works in the luxury real estate industry - the first to introduce decentralization into traditional property acquisitions.</p>
<p>Buying an NFT from The Hideaways (HDWY) is very similar to buying your real estate property. The project&rsquo;s digital collectibles are underpinned by real-world assets that yield at least 20% passive income monthly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The best thing about this is you are practically one of the owners of luxury real estate, but since you&rsquo;re splitting the ownership among many other people, the cost is affordable. The Hideaways (HDWY) fractionalized NFTs start at $100 - a good kickstart for your real estate investment career.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) is holding a $100,000 prize draw for all token holders. Score it at only $0.10 for a chance to win this fortune.</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cardano (ADA) dropped to a multiyear low last week. The coin is currently trading at a critical threshold that could open up for further drops ahead.</p>
<p>It is by far ADA&rsquo;s most disappointing year, falling from its all-time high of $3 recorded just a year ago.</p>
<p>Analysts say this is the best time for Cardano (ADA) holders to jump into The Hideaways (HDWY) as a way to recover their losses and hedge against market volatility.</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) Still Has Room for a Big Retracement</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) declined to its lowest level in many years. ADA is currently trading at $0.25, carving another opportunity to print the lower low.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The price is down 14.27% in the last seven days which sent its total losses this year to 80%. This is a huge disappointment for the crypto community - Cardano (ADA) is known as the next Ethereum (ETH) killer, after all.</p>
<p>And although they are operating on the same business base, ADA underperformed against ETH by 29.93% year-on-year.</p>
<p>Analysts gave out their negative price forecast for Cardano (ADA) at the same time they upgraded projections for The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) is expected to reclaim the $0.15 support level if buying sentiment does not improve at $0.25. From the current state of things, we are more likely to see $0.15 back on the charts before the end of the year.</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA)&rsquo;s Technicals Point to Low Investor Sentiment</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA)&rsquo;s 24-hour trading volume has declined to $63.82 million from its $116 million level on December 16. This shows the lack of buying appetite for the crypto major as fear takes hold.</p>
<p>Moreover, its relative strength index remains in the oversold territory after falling to the critical level on December 15. RSI is now at 26.70 - a result below 30.0 shows strong selling pressure while a result above 70.0 indicates buyers&rsquo; dominance.</p>
<p>As of late, Cardano (ADA) is not working on any visible projects that could propel prices back to the green. This means we will be seeing more volatility in the coming weeks which is a clear signal to go elsewhere. Among the top investor choice is The Hideaways (HDWY), a real estate project everybody&rsquo;s taking an interest in.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) to Give a 9,000% ROI in 2023</p>
<p>If you are a Cardano (ADA) holder looking for a new investment to make, do not miss out on The Hideaways (HDWY).&nbsp;</p>
<p>The new cryptocurrency project works in the luxury real estate industry - the first to introduce decentralization into traditional property acquisitions.</p>
<p>Buying an NFT from The Hideaways (HDWY) is very similar to buying your real estate property. The project&rsquo;s digital collectibles are underpinned by real-world assets that yield at least 20% passive income monthly.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The best thing about this is you are practically one of the owners of luxury real estate, but since you&rsquo;re splitting the ownership among many other people, the cost is affordable. The Hideaways (HDWY) fractionalized NFTs start at $100 - a good kickstart for your real estate investment career.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) is holding a $100,000 prize draw for all token holders. Score it at only $0.10 for a chance to win this fortune.</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Top Coin Bitcoin (BTC) Loses Investors As Coin Plummets, The Hideaways (HDWY) Becomes Shelter]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/top-coin-bitcoin-btc-loses-investors-as-coin-plummets-the-hideaways-hdwy-becomes-shelter</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/top-coin-bitcoin-btc-loses-investors-as-coin-plummets-the-hideaways-hdwy-becomes-shelter</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Top cryptocurrency Bitcoin (BTC) suffers from overwhelming declines as it trades less than its viable trading mark, losing numerous old-time investors and switching their holdings to the new real estate project in the market The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Loses Long-Term Holders</p>
<p>According to On-chain reports, Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) long-term holders are dumping all their coins as the crypto plunges below its $17,000 trading level. They foresee that the threshold of holding the king coin could result in either greater profit or massive losses.</p>
<p>At the same time, some short-term &ldquo;speculators&rdquo; felt acute problems caused by the bearish decline. Because of the sharp plunge, the long-term holders and speculators are gearing up their portfolios and purchasing The Hideaways (HDWY) for better momentum.</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) being the top digital asset could be in danger of losing even the most famed investors but several holders are still holding their capital in hopes of a bounce back by early 2023.</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Analysis For 2023</p>
<p>Within the past 24 trading hours, Bitcoin's (BTC) price broke the barrier below its $17,000 mark and dropped to its crucial support level of $16,500. Following the FTX fallout and the broader price correction, the crypto market is crashing massively.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to crypto analysts CredibleCrypto, the price of the crypto must hold the $16,500 mark to rebound from the red zone. He also mentioned that if it were to break past that barrier, then the danger of reaching the $15,600 mark is nearing.</p>
<p>Security is one of the top priorities of Bitcoin (BTC) users so if the bearish market occurs they will worry less as they could hedge themselves by purchasing&nbsp; The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Users Prefer The Hideaways (HDWY) For 2023</p>
<p>With the sudden spark of the Bitcoin (BTC) decline, market participants are exiting the doors to get better investment stability and growth. The Hideaways (HDWY) ramps itself and becomes a top pick for the king coin users for their 2023 investment journey.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) is also kicking off a prize draw that allows the winner to acquire $100,000 in cash in total. To make things more exciting, the project team announced that there will be a 100% bonus on all investments.</p>
<p>The presale event is nearing its end by December 31 and various investors are flocking their way to join the community and gain massive rewards that could accumulate to more than 6000% of their initial deposit by 2023.</p>
<p>The token is trading at $0.1. Don&rsquo;t miss the chance to be part of the millionaire club by 2023!</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top cryptocurrency Bitcoin (BTC) suffers from overwhelming declines as it trades less than its viable trading mark, losing numerous old-time investors and switching their holdings to the new real estate project in the market The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Loses Long-Term Holders</p>
<p>According to On-chain reports, Bitcoin&rsquo;s (BTC) long-term holders are dumping all their coins as the crypto plunges below its $17,000 trading level. They foresee that the threshold of holding the king coin could result in either greater profit or massive losses.</p>
<p>At the same time, some short-term &ldquo;speculators&rdquo; felt acute problems caused by the bearish decline. Because of the sharp plunge, the long-term holders and speculators are gearing up their portfolios and purchasing The Hideaways (HDWY) for better momentum.</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) being the top digital asset could be in danger of losing even the most famed investors but several holders are still holding their capital in hopes of a bounce back by early 2023.</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Analysis For 2023</p>
<p>Within the past 24 trading hours, Bitcoin's (BTC) price broke the barrier below its $17,000 mark and dropped to its crucial support level of $16,500. Following the FTX fallout and the broader price correction, the crypto market is crashing massively.&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to crypto analysts CredibleCrypto, the price of the crypto must hold the $16,500 mark to rebound from the red zone. He also mentioned that if it were to break past that barrier, then the danger of reaching the $15,600 mark is nearing.</p>
<p>Security is one of the top priorities of Bitcoin (BTC) users so if the bearish market occurs they will worry less as they could hedge themselves by purchasing&nbsp; The Hideaways (HDWY).</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) Users Prefer The Hideaways (HDWY) For 2023</p>
<p>With the sudden spark of the Bitcoin (BTC) decline, market participants are exiting the doors to get better investment stability and growth. The Hideaways (HDWY) ramps itself and becomes a top pick for the king coin users for their 2023 investment journey.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) is also kicking off a prize draw that allows the winner to acquire $100,000 in cash in total. To make things more exciting, the project team announced that there will be a 100% bonus on all investments.</p>
<p>The presale event is nearing its end by December 31 and various investors are flocking their way to join the community and gain massive rewards that could accumulate to more than 6000% of their initial deposit by 2023.</p>
<p>The token is trading at $0.1. Don&rsquo;t miss the chance to be part of the millionaire club by 2023!</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Are Litecoin (LTC)'s Glory Days Over?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/are-litecoin-ltcs-glory-days-over</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2022-12-13-161922.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/are-litecoin-ltcs-glory-days-over</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) went against all odds when it pulled a bull run whilst the FTX crashed. But it was not the same case lately - the price is down 16.88% in the last 7 days.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, The Hideaways (HDWY) takes the center stage after announcing a $100,000 prize draw for all token holders. The reward is a celebration of the success of its initial presale ending on December 31.</p>
<p>Litecoin (LTC) Trades on a Support Level</p>
<p>Litecoin (LTC) currently trades on a support level that historically sent the price to the $85.00 zone. LTC is selling at $63.62, down 8.34% in the latest charts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The question here is whether the crypto major will get enough buying support to send its price back to its December 5 high at $84.95.</p>
<p>Looking at its technical indicators, sellers will not likely give up their position. The relative strength index is at 34.56, indicating Litecoin (LTC) is nearing the oversold territory.</p>
<p>Moreover, the 50-day EMA takes above the 20-day EMA, indicating bears&rsquo; dominance.</p>
<p>Investors took the negative signals as a chance to buy into The Hideaways (HDWY) which is currently holding a $100,000 prize draw.</p>
<p>Whale Accumulation Spotted on Litecoin (LTC) Charts</p>
<p>Despite its recent depreciation, Litecoin (LTC) whales continue to accumulate.</p>
<p>The latest on-chain analysis reveals that whale addresses with 1 million or more LTC coins have accumulated an additional 2.95 million Litecoin (LTC) valued at $220 million at the current market price.</p>
<p>Other tokens enjoying massive acquisitions lately are Shiba Inu (SHIB) and The Hideaways (HDWY), with the latter promising a 9,000% growth for 2023.</p>
<p>Due to this strong whale support, analysts upgraded their Litecoin (LTC) price projections - LTC is expected to climb to $73.54 next week. On the other hand, a continued weak performance will show $47.88, a November 9 low, back on the daily charts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) Holds $100,000 Prize Draw for Crypto Fans</p>
<p>There is no question. The Hideaways (HDWY) is the most successful presale token of 2022. The project sold 50% of its offerings just a month after launch. What&rsquo;s behind this high demand? Its real estate backing. Everybody wants to get a hold of something steady lately.</p>
<p>To celebrate the success of its initial presale event, it will hold a $100,000 prize draw open for all crypto fans. Knowing how much you lost from the Terra Luna and FTX crash, this is a chance to get your crypto portfolio healthy again.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) token sells at $0.10, a small investment that could get you both an easy way to fortune and a steady, passive income monthly.</p>
<p>The new project underpins its NFTs with luxury real estate properties that yield at least 20% of passive income. This real estate link ensures your investment does not crumble on demand whenever volatility takes over the crypto market.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t miss your chance to get on the best investment of 2022.</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) went against all odds when it pulled a bull run whilst the FTX crashed. But it was not the same case lately - the price is down 16.88% in the last 7 days.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, The Hideaways (HDWY) takes the center stage after announcing a $100,000 prize draw for all token holders. The reward is a celebration of the success of its initial presale ending on December 31.</p>
<p>Litecoin (LTC) Trades on a Support Level</p>
<p>Litecoin (LTC) currently trades on a support level that historically sent the price to the $85.00 zone. LTC is selling at $63.62, down 8.34% in the latest charts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The question here is whether the crypto major will get enough buying support to send its price back to its December 5 high at $84.95.</p>
<p>Looking at its technical indicators, sellers will not likely give up their position. The relative strength index is at 34.56, indicating Litecoin (LTC) is nearing the oversold territory.</p>
<p>Moreover, the 50-day EMA takes above the 20-day EMA, indicating bears&rsquo; dominance.</p>
<p>Investors took the negative signals as a chance to buy into The Hideaways (HDWY) which is currently holding a $100,000 prize draw.</p>
<p>Whale Accumulation Spotted on Litecoin (LTC) Charts</p>
<p>Despite its recent depreciation, Litecoin (LTC) whales continue to accumulate.</p>
<p>The latest on-chain analysis reveals that whale addresses with 1 million or more LTC coins have accumulated an additional 2.95 million Litecoin (LTC) valued at $220 million at the current market price.</p>
<p>Other tokens enjoying massive acquisitions lately are Shiba Inu (SHIB) and The Hideaways (HDWY), with the latter promising a 9,000% growth for 2023.</p>
<p>Due to this strong whale support, analysts upgraded their Litecoin (LTC) price projections - LTC is expected to climb to $73.54 next week. On the other hand, a continued weak performance will show $47.88, a November 9 low, back on the daily charts.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) Holds $100,000 Prize Draw for Crypto Fans</p>
<p>There is no question. The Hideaways (HDWY) is the most successful presale token of 2022. The project sold 50% of its offerings just a month after launch. What&rsquo;s behind this high demand? Its real estate backing. Everybody wants to get a hold of something steady lately.</p>
<p>To celebrate the success of its initial presale event, it will hold a $100,000 prize draw open for all crypto fans. Knowing how much you lost from the Terra Luna and FTX crash, this is a chance to get your crypto portfolio healthy again.</p>
<p>The Hideaways (HDWY) token sells at $0.10, a small investment that could get you both an easy way to fortune and a steady, passive income monthly.</p>
<p>The new project underpins its NFTs with luxury real estate properties that yield at least 20% of passive income. This real estate link ensures your investment does not crumble on demand whenever volatility takes over the crypto market.</p>
<p>Don&rsquo;t miss your chance to get on the best investment of 2022.</p>
<p>Website: https://www.thehideaways.io&nbsp;</p>
<p>Pre-Sale: https://ticket.thehideaways.io/register&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/thehideawayscrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/hdwycrypto&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Twitter Unveils Crypto and Stock Charts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/twitter-unveils-crypto-and-stock-charts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/twitter-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/twitter-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/twitter-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 19:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2022/12/twitter-unveils-crypto-and-stock-charts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Twitter Business on Thursday unveiled price chart support for major crypto and stock assets. </p>
<p>Twitter on Thursday revealed a new feature called $Cashtags, with price chart support for major cryptocurrency and stock assets. Tech billionaire and Twitter&rsquo;s new owner, Elon Musk, shared a feature designed specifically for the financial sector, with particular benefit for traders, financial experts, investors, and organisations. $Cashtags helps users see graphs, charts, and other data of stocks, cryptos, and exchange-traded funds (ETFs) within a tweet.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">$Cashtags, now with data 📈👀 $SPY 👇 pic.twitter.com/XgOK6gf02E</p>
&mdash; Twitter Business (@TwitterBusiness) December 21, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>The official Twitter Business account said:</p>

<p>When you Tweet the symbol of a major stock, ETF, or cryptocurrency with a $ in front of it (like $BTC), people on Twitter see a clickable link that takes them to search results. Starting today, these search results will include the pricing graphs for major symbols.</p>

<p>It further added:</p>

<p>You can also search for symbols directly, without clicking on a link within a Tweet. Most symbols with and without the $ sign will work in search (QQQ or $QQQ).</p>

<p>To unlock the new feature, users can click on $BTC and $ETH or search for any crypto asset. A link &ndash; &lsquo;View on Robinhood&rsquo;- will take users to the wallet provider. The addition of a linkage to Robinhood may signal the possibility of a future partnership between the two firms, but no official announcement has been made.</p>
Could This Be a Hint at Integrating Crypto Payments?
<p>Elon Musk praised the team at Twitter and commented that this is just &ldquo;one of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter!&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">One of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter! Nice work by Twitter team. https://t.co/CKLH8OtDDW</p>
&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 22, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>Musk has in the past indicated that his personal crypto holdings consist of only Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin (DOGE) and since his takeover of Twitter, Doge holders have been eagerly awaiting the announcement of a payments integration. The tech mogul however announced that he is stepping down as chief of Twitter, and Dogecoin has naturally responded negatively in the market after it outperformed the market in November not long after the Tesla CEO acquired Twitter for $44 billion in October.</p>
<p>A lawsuit was also filed in September accusing Musk of running a pyramid scheme to support DOGE.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twitter Business on Thursday unveiled price chart support for major crypto and stock assets. </p>
<p>Twitter on Thursday revealed a new feature called $Cashtags, with price chart support for major cryptocurrency and stock assets. Tech billionaire and Twitter&rsquo;s new owner, Elon Musk, shared a feature designed specifically for the financial sector, with particular benefit for traders, financial experts, investors, and organisations. $Cashtags helps users see graphs, charts, and other data of stocks, cryptos, and exchange-traded funds (ETFs) within a tweet.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">$Cashtags, now with data 📈👀 $SPY 👇 pic.twitter.com/XgOK6gf02E</p>
&mdash; Twitter Business (@TwitterBusiness) December 21, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>The official Twitter Business account said:</p>

<p>When you Tweet the symbol of a major stock, ETF, or cryptocurrency with a $ in front of it (like $BTC), people on Twitter see a clickable link that takes them to search results. Starting today, these search results will include the pricing graphs for major symbols.</p>

<p>It further added:</p>

<p>You can also search for symbols directly, without clicking on a link within a Tweet. Most symbols with and without the $ sign will work in search (QQQ or $QQQ).</p>

<p>To unlock the new feature, users can click on $BTC and $ETH or search for any crypto asset. A link &ndash; &lsquo;View on Robinhood&rsquo;- will take users to the wallet provider. The addition of a linkage to Robinhood may signal the possibility of a future partnership between the two firms, but no official announcement has been made.</p>
Could This Be a Hint at Integrating Crypto Payments?
<p>Elon Musk praised the team at Twitter and commented that this is just &ldquo;one of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter!&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">One of many product improvements coming to financial Twitter! Nice work by Twitter team. https://t.co/CKLH8OtDDW</p>
&mdash; Elon Musk (@elonmusk) December 22, 2022
<p>

</p>
<p>Musk has in the past indicated that his personal crypto holdings consist of only Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Dogecoin (DOGE) and since his takeover of Twitter, Doge holders have been eagerly awaiting the announcement of a payments integration. The tech mogul however announced that he is stepping down as chief of Twitter, and Dogecoin has naturally responded negatively in the market after it outperformed the market in November not long after the Tesla CEO acquired Twitter for $44 billion in October.</p>
<p>A lawsuit was also filed in September accusing Musk of running a pyramid scheme to support DOGE.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
