<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ethereum Scaling Solution Aurora Unveils &#8216;Strategic Partnership&#8217; for Web3 Workers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-scaling-solution-aurora-unveils-strategic-partnership-for-web3-workers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254048</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Aurora.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Aurora.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The two platform aim to simplify crypto compensation for independent workers and freelancers in the Web3 sector. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aurora &#8211; an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) compatible scaling and bridge solution built on top of the NEAR Protocol blockchain network &#8211; announced a strategic partnership with blockchain-based employment cooperative for the Web3 ecosystem called Opolios.</p>
<h2>Aurora-Opolios Partnership</h2>
<p>According to the official press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the latest integration will enable USDC payments on the Aurora network for independent workers to ramp up payment processes, increase flexibility, and provide greater access to compensate workers in preferred currencies.</p>
<p>This partnership between Aurora and Opolios is also expected to positively affect both Web3 businesses as well as independent workers that function across the world to manage their payrolls in a more efficient way.</p>
<p>Members of Opolios will also be able to receive payments on-chain in USDC.e or USDC on the Aurora Network. On the other hand, the businesses operating within the Aurora ecosystem will be able to leverage the Opolis platform to streamline payments for freelancers and fund payroll. Such a move could potentially fuel increased &#8220;financial flexibility&#8221; along with &#8220;operational efficiency.&#8221;</p>
<p>Commenting on the latest development, Anton Paisov, Head of Integrations at Aurora, stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We’re on the brink of a workplace revolution that will provide workers greater autonomy, flexibility, and satisfaction than a traditional ‘career’ ever could. What Opolis wants to do is empower people to work the way they please and make all of the scary administrative stuff easy. This integration with Aurora furthers that goal by opening up access to the folks that prefer payment in digital currencies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Aurora Q1 Performance</h2>
<p>Aurora recently launched a new partner program aimed at supporting builders in the ecosystem. Its Aurora V2 Validator was also relaunched, thereby allowing Aurora DAO delegators to receive staking rewards in both AURORA and NEAR. Besides, it terminated its partnership with Etherscan, which resulted in the decommissioning of Aurorascan.</p>
<p>Aurora, along with Sweat Economy, Spin.fi, and NEAR Crowd, significantly contributed to the daily active accounts of Near Protocol in the first quarter of 2023. According to Messari&#8217;s <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-near-q1-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, the average count throughout the period was around 64,000.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-scaling-solution-aurora-unveils-strategic-partnership-for-web3-workers/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Scaling Solution Aurora Unveils &#8216;Strategic Partnership&#8217; for Web3 Workers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO Welcomes SEC Legal Battle: &#8220;We&#8217;ll Get The Job Done&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254138</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Brian-Armstrong-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Brian-Armstrong-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong believes a court battle may finally help establish much-needed clarity around crypto rules.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong is not shaken by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s new lawsuit against his exchange.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Both the executive and his company responded with brief arguments on Monday as to why Coinbase will reign victorious in its legal battle with the regulator. </span></p>
<h2>A Chance to Win Clarity</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://twitter.com/brian_armstrong/status/1666129111025324035" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweet</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Armstrong said that Coinbase would be “proud” to represent the crypto industry in its SEC court battle, and to “to finally get some clarity around crypto rules.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Armstrong has blasted the SEC for years for failing to clarify how securities laws apply to the crypto industry, such as which digital assets qualify as securities, and which as commodities. The exchange </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">sued</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the SEC in April for failing to reply to Coinbase’s petition to provide rules for digitally traded securities, but the regulator claimed that crypto already had clear rules and regulations governing it. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One of the SEC’s core allegations is that Coinbase has failed to register with the agency for various securities products it provides. Armstrong, however, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">argued</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that there is no reasonable path forward to do so. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We tried, repeatedly &#8211; so we don&#8217;t list securities,” he said. Furthermore, the SEC and CFTC have provided conflicting statements about which crypto assets qualify as securities – including </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chairman-warns-ethereum-update-could-classify-eth-as-a-security/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ethereum (ETH)</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and Tether (USDT).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">US Congress is already attempting to introduce crypto-specific legislation to remedy the situation, but that still leaves the nation behind “the rest of the world” when it comes to industry rulemaking. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We&#8217;ll get the job done,” he said. “In the meantime, let&#8217;s all keep moving forward and building as an industry. America will get this right in the end.”</span></p>
<h2>The Numbers</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a video published by Coinbase on Tuesday, the exchange provided stats to prove its commitment to regulatory compliance, and the SEC’s failure to cooperate. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The exchange </span><a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase/status/1666135834062467083" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">noted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that it mentioned its “staking” 57 times within its S1 report, which the SEC chose to approve. It also met privately with the SEC 30 times seeking guidance on how to stay legally compliant. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, the SEC has established 0 comprehensive rules pertaining to crypto, and uses a test written in 1946 to determine if tokens are securities (the Howey Test).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Critics of Coinbase pointed out, however, that the SEC made clear in its approval of the exchange’s S1 that it did not necessarily approve the legality of Coinbase’s underlying business. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">To the folks posting that it’s unfair that the SEC is filing an action when they approved the coinbase IPO, please stop. <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@coinbase</a> was warned that approval of the registration statement didn’t mean approval of the underlying business activity. It’s in the complaint. <a href="https://t.co/vvRYwD4pkd" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/vvRYwD4pkd</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Joe Carlasare (@JoeCarlasare) <a href="https://twitter.com/JoeCarlasare/status/1666069135388815361?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 6, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO Welcomes SEC Legal Battle: &#8220;We&#8217;ll Get The Job Done&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 3 Takeaways From the Lawsuit Between the SEC and Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254133</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Coinbase_Logo.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Coinbase_Logo.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Unlike Binance’s lawsuit, Coinbase is being targeted primarily for securities law violations. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)&#8217;s charges against Coinbase are largely reminiscent of its Binance case from just a day prior –  but also contain some key differences. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Here’s a closer look at the text and implications of the commission’s 101-page lawsuit against America’s largest crypto exchange.</span></p>
<h2>Coinbase and Binance: Lawsuits Compared</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Much like the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance lawsuit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Monday, the SEC’s </span><a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908.1.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">first charge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> against Coinbase was for serving functions of a broker, national securities exchange, or clearing agency, and yet neglecting to register as any such business. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the commission, failure to register has left investors “deprived of the disclosures and protections,” they are entitled to, and thus exposed them to “significant risk.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing also accused Coinbase of listing a plethora of “crypto-asset securities” on its platform and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">named 13 cryptocurrencies</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that fit the bill. These included multiple top 20 cryptos by market capitalization, such as Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase has claimed in the past to apply the Howey Test – the SEC’s primary litmus test for determining whether a financial asset constitutes an investment contract – when reviewing an asset for listing on its platform. According to the firm, it rejects 90% of assets due to legal standards and </span><a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/coinbase-does-not-list-securities-end-of-story" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">does not list</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> any securities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, the SEC accused Coinbase of merely paying “lip service” to the idea of legal compliance: “Coinbase has for years made available for trading crypto assets that are investment contracts under the Howey test and well-established principles of the federal securities laws,” it stated. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the Binance lawsuit, the SEC named only BNB and BUSD as securities. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The SEC’s third allegation pertained to Coinbase’s staking-as-a-service product, which the exchange did not register with the commission. The program lets users stake their proof-of-stake crypto assets through Coinbase’s platform and earn yield, while Coinbase earns a 25-35% commission. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The agency had already targeted the “BNB Vault,” “Simple Earn,” and “staking” schemes available through Binance US on Monday. State-level securities regulators also began </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-coin-shares-dump-13-as-alabama-regulator-joins-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">targeting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Coinbase for its staking product on Tuesday, including Alabama, California, and others. </span></p>
<h2>Different Punishments<b><br />
</b><b></b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase has been ordered to pay back all “ill-gotten gains” related to their securities violations, alongside prejudgement interest, civil money penalties, and other forms of equitable relief for investors. When Kraken </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-plunge-4-following-sec-termination-of-kraken-staking/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">settled</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> charges with the SEC in February for issues relating to its staking product alone, it was forced to pay a $30 million fine. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance was ordered to pay similar penalties but was also ordered to be permanently barred from engaging in the securities and crypto exchange business.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-3-takeaways-from-the-lawsuit-between-the-sec-and-coinbase/" rel="nofollow">The 3 Takeaways From the Lawsuit Between the SEC and Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance NFT Marketplace Announces Support for Bitcoin NFT Collections</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-nft-marketplace-announces-support-for-bitcoin-nft-collections/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254020</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Binance_NFT-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Binance_NFT-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin NFTs have slowly become a major part of the crypto market in recent months.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance doubled down its efforts on the non-fungible token sector as it announced support for Bitcoin NFTs on Tuesday amidst severe turmoil in the crypto industry.</p>
<p>The exchange&#8217;s NFT marketplace is the latest contender to step into the Bitcoin NFTs ring following Magic Eden&#8217;s support for the same.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the latest <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/faq/supported-bitcoin-nft-collections-on-binance-566a47f0ad50498cb7fb4bc00a7f4ee2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a>, the newly added list includes Bitcoin Bandits, Bitcoin Frogs, Bitcoin Pizzas, Bitcoin Punks, Bitcoin Wizards, Block Legends, BTC DeGods, Clay Pepes, DogePunks, etc.</li>
<li>Binance said the NFTs in question are based on the Inscription ID list provided by the project team.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;You can now buy, deposit, withdraw, and list specific NFT collections from the Bitcoin blockchain on Binance NFT.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Going forward, Binance plans to integrate more collections into its NFT marketplace.</li>
<li>The crypto giant recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-continues-nft-foray-launches-new-loan-feature/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a new feature that enabled users to borrow crypto while using their NFTs as collateral.</li>
<li>The loans were made available for select high-profile NFT projects only, such as Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), Mutant Ape Yacht Club (MAYC), Azuki, and Doodles, to name a few.</li>
<li>The crypto heavyweight also dipped its toes into the buzzy Bitcoin-based market after announcing support for Ordinals inscriptions on its NFT marketplace last month.</li>
<li>Binance NFT Marketplace expanded its roster of supported networks in the first quarter of this year when it added certain NFT collections from Polygon to the platform, alongside NFTs on Ethereum and BNB Chain.</li>
<li>The latest development comes a day after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> 13 charges against the platform and its founder CZ.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-nft-marketplace-announces-support-for-bitcoin-nft-collections/" rel="nofollow">Binance NFT Marketplace Announces Support for Bitcoin NFT Collections</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $90 Million in Liquidations As Bitcoin Mysteriously Rips to $27,000</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/over-90-million-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-mysteriously-rips-to-27000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254125</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Bitcoin_Green_Candle-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Bitcoin_Green_Candle-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the SEC suing crypto’s biggest players, Bitcoin is leaving short traders in the dust.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin is up 4.5% on Tuesday despite back-to-back lawsuits from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) targeting two of the world’s largest crypto exchanges this week.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The event has triggered $94 million in liquidations across the market over the last day – mostly consisting of shorts.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Per data from </span><a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinglass</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, $61.5 million in short trades have been cleared over the past 24 hours, alongside $32.4 million in long trades. At writing time, Bitcoin trades for $27,146.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">When solely observing Bitcoin trades, Coinglass counted $30.87 million in short liquidations, and $7.27 million in long liquidations.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The liquidation wave affected 32,000 traders, with the single largest liquidation order occurring on Binance at a size of $5.6 million. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s rally following Coinbase&#8217;s</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400"> legal challenge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the SEC stands in stark contrast to its </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">descent</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> following the SEC’s Binance lawsuit on Monday. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">On-chain data from </span><a href="https://twitter.com/MitchellHODL/status/1666151910976495617" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Blockware</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows that small BTC addresses (&lt;1 BTC) accumulated 2,545 BTC on Monday, meaning some investors may have bought the dip. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">By comparison, BNB and ADA posted relatively modest gains – two cryptos that were directly targeted in the Binance and Coinbase lawsuits respectively. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-90-million-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-mysteriously-rips-to-27000/" rel="nofollow">Over $90 Million in Liquidations As Bitcoin Mysteriously Rips to $27,000</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Judge Denies FTX&#8217;s Bid to Participate in Confidential Mediation Sessions: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-judge-denies-ftxs-bid-to-participate-in-confidential-mediation-sessions-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 19:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253983</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Genesis had estimated that FTX is entitied to nothing. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A judge ruled that FTX cannot join confidential mediation sessions between bankrupt crypto lender Genesis Global Holdco and its parent company Digital Currency Group (DCG).</p>
<p>The ruling days after Genesis denied owing FTX anything.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/genesis-judge-rejects-ftx-demand-to-join-crypto-bankruptcy-talks-1.1929134" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, US Bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane refused to open the settlement talks to the SBF-founded beleaguered crypto exchange, which claims that Genesis owes it $3.9 billion.</li>
<li>In a ruling on June 5th, Lane stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There will be a certain amount of radio silence because mediation needs that to work. Shortening the mediation does not shorten the case.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Genesis and DCG, on the other hand, have been granted a 100-day extension to arrange a revised payout proposal which would essentially underpin the Chapter 11 bankruptcy plan to compensate hundreds of thousands of Genesis creditors.</li>
<li>With this move, the judge has overruled the objections of FTX and several Genesis customers who had emailed the judge, calling to end the settlement talks and order payouts to creditors.</li>
<li>Some creditors have also complained about being excluded from mediation discussions.</li>
<li>In May, FTX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-attempts-3-9-billion-clawback-from-genesis/" data-wpel-link="internal">sought</a> $4 billion from the bankrupt crypto lender &#8211; part of efforts to recoup value for creditors. A month later, Gensis filed an estimation procedure motion which stated that FTX is entitled to claims totaling &#8220;$0.00.&#8221;</li>
<li>FTX debtors later objected to the nil claim estimation and said in a court <a href="https://assets.bwbx.io/documents/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/reIlzLM9ae4Q/v0" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> that they are by far the &#8220;largest unsecured creditors&#8221; in the Genesis Debtors&#8217; Chapter 11 cases, adding that it is &#8220;crucial they participate in the mediation.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-judge-denies-ftxs-bid-to-participate-in-confidential-mediation-sessions-report/" rel="nofollow">Genesis Judge Denies FTX&#8217;s Bid to Participate in Confidential Mediation Sessions: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase COIN Shares Dump 13% as Alabama Regulator Joins SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-coin-shares-dump-13-as-alabama-regulator-joins-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254111</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/coinbase_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/coinbase_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Alabama and 9 other state-level securities regulators are taking issue with Coinbase’s staking product.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Coinbase (COIN) fell 13% on Tuesday after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) launched a major lawsuit against the firm for violating securities laws. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yet the agency isn’t alone: Alabama’s securities regulator is also targeting Coinbase, specifically for its failure to register its staking product. </span></p>
<h2>The Need for Registration</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a separate </span><a href="https://asc.alabama.gov/News/2023%20News/6-6-2023_Coinbase.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, the Alabama Securities Commission (ASC) announced that it had issued a “Show Cause Order” against Coinbase. The order gives the exchange 28 days to explain why it shouldn’t be ordered to cease and desist from providing its staking services, which the regulator deems to be “unregistered securities.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The order was part of a “multi-state task force” including ten state securities regulators, representing Alabama, California, Illinois, Kentucky, Maryland, New Jersey, South Carolina, Vermont, Washington, and Wisconsin.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The ASC action does not prohibit Coinbase from offering staking as a service, so long as it complies with Alabama’s laws,” explained the commission. Through proper registration, Coinbase would provide investors with the material information needed to properly assess the risks of staking as an investment contract. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As the commission noted, Coinbase’s nearly 3.5 million nationwide staking accounts are not protected by the FDIC or SIPC, like accounts at banks or traditional brokerage firms.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“This action is another step toward ensuring that investors in crypto asset products are offered the same protections under our laws and are fully aware of the risks involved in these investments,” said ASC Director Amanda Senn.</span></p>
<h2>Staking and Securities</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Staking-as-a-service involves letting holders of proof of stake cryptocurrencies stake their assets through Coinbase’s platform. Stakers earn crypto rewards from their respective networks for providing them with economic security, from which Coinbase takes a 25-35% cut of their profits. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Though staking through a centralized exchange isn’t as profitable as staking independently, it’s generally more technically and economically accessible. The Ethereum blockchain, for instance – which became open to staking in September – requires 32 ETH ($60,000) to stake independently, while staking ETH on Coinbase has no minimum.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Per the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">SEC’s filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Tuesday, Coinbase has “offered and sold securities without registering its offers and sales,” through its staking program. The agency issued a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-and-legal-officer-respond-to-secs-wells-notice/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Wells Notice</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to Coinbase back in April, which the company suspected at the time would be related to its staking service. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-coin-shares-dump-13-as-alabama-regulator-joins-sec-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase COIN Shares Dump 13% as Alabama Regulator Joins SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Predicts: 6 Things That Will Trigger the Next Bitcoin Bull Market</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-6-things-that-will-trigger-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254018</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Bull_Chatgpt.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Bull_Chatgpt.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[From market and institutional adoption, to regulatory clarity and the BTC halving - these are the factors that will drive the next bull market, according to ChatGPT.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has undergone numerous ups and downs in its relatively short history, but only a few have been proclaimed as a full-on bull market. The latest one was back in late 2021 when the cryptocurrency skyrocketed to its ATH of $69,000.</p>
<p>What followed was a massive price decline that resulted in BTC dumping all the way down below $20,000 amid multiple collapses in the industry, as well as galloping global inflation and war in Europe.</p>
<p>As bitcoin has recovered a lot of ground since its sub-$16,000 endeavor, the community frequently speculates whether a new bull market has already started or is it right around the corner. In this topic, we will explore what the AI chatbot ChatGPT thinks about it.</p>
<h2>Adoption</h2>
<p>Although ChatGPT has had a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-has-a-big-misconception-about-bitcoins-ath-price/" data-wpel-link="internal">few things wrong</a> about BTC, such as its all-time high price, the chatbot provided some interesting findings on what could propel the next bull market. First and foremost, it highlighted global adoption, which comes in two parts &#8211; market and institutional &#8211; and we have combined them into one.</p>
<p>As far as market adoption goes, ChatGPT believes the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price will resume its upwards trajectory once more businesses start accepting it as a payment method. This will help &#8220;create positive sentiment and drive demand.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Factors such as the integration of Bitcoin payment options by major companies or the launch of regulated Bitcoin investment vehicles can contribute to a bull market.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Institutional adoption could also help push BTC&#8217;s price up. Recall that numerous firms, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-increased-its-btc-holdings-for-11-consecutive-quarters/" data-wpel-link="internal">MicroStrategy</a>, MassMutual, Tesla, BlackRock, and others, either purchased portions of the asset or engaged with it in a different way during the last bull market. A repeat of this scenario could start another bull run.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-113945" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments.jpg" alt="BitcoinPayments" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/BitcoinPayments-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Technological Developments</h2>
<p>The AI chatbot also brought up certain tech developments that could be among the reasons behind another run-up. For instance, the Bitcoin network start seeing enhanced adoption and engagement after the Tarpoot upgrade, which allowed for the creation of NFTs on top of it.</p>
<p>So far, this has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/" data-wpel-link="internal">benefited</a> miners in particular due to the increased number of transactions and the higher cost of fees. However, there are other factors and possibilities as well, according to ChatGPT.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Significant advancements in Bitcoin&#8217;s underlying technology or improvements in scalability, security, or privacy features can generate excitement and attract more users and investors.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Regulatory Clarity</h2>
<p>Although several countries have made initial attempts to regulate the cryptocurrency industry in the past few years, it still remains largely unsupervised. In fact, some of the largest nations, such as China and the US, have either officially banned the asset class or simply failed to provide detailed regulations that can help it prosper while protecting investors at the same time.</p>
<p>Should that finally change, ChatGPT believes BTC&#8217;s price will start heading north once again.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Clear and favorable regulations can provide a more stable environment for cryptocurrencies, increasing investor confidence. Positive regulatory developments, such as the recognition of Bitcoin as a legal form of payment or the establishment of supportive frameworks for cryptocurrency businesses, can encourage market growth.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The landscape in the US has been particularly harmful in the past several months as the SEC, without providing clear guidelines on which crypto assets are securities, has gone after the likes of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a>, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">Binance</a>, Kraken, and others.</p>
<h2>Economic and Geopolitical Factors</h2>
<p>As mentioned above, the war that broke out in Europe caused pain for investors in different sectors, including crypto. Additionally, the rising inflation and the central banks&#8217; desperate attempts to fight it resulted in outflows from risk-on assets, such as BTC.</p>
<p>But on a more macro scale, ChatGPT believes the dire economic situation, currency devaluation, or political turmoil could turn people toward Bitcoin. The interest in the primary cryptocurrency will likely increase as people will be looking for &#8220;decentralized and non-government-controlled assets like Bitcoin.&#8221;</p>
<p>We saw similar developments in countries like <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/got-bitcoin-argentinas-inflation-rate-is-now-over-100/" data-wpel-link="internal">Argentina</a> and Turkey, where locals have been struggling with double- and even triple-digit inflation rates for a while. As such, ChatGPT echoed the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/i-like-bitcoin-even-more-its-the-best-inflation-trade-billionaire-investor-paul-tudor-jones/" data-wpel-link="internal">words</a> of legendary legacy investor Paul Tudor Jones III,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In times of economic uncertainty, some investors may view Bitcoin as a hedge against traditional financial systems, potentially driving up its price.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>The Bitcoin Halving</h2>
<p>Last but not least, the AI chatbot brought up the halving events. Incorporated into Bitcoin&#8217;s network since its inception in 2009, they occur at every 210,000 blocks (roughly four years) and aim to reduce the block rewards, thus decreasing the speed at which new BTC is being created.</p>
<p>The previous three halvings were followed by massive bull runs, and ChatGPT asserted that the next one &#8211; expected to take place in April next year &#8211; will likely lead to the same price movements.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Historically, halving events have coincided with bull markets as reduced supply and potential increase in demand have had a positive effect on Bitcoin&#8217;s price.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>If you want to find more info on what ChatGPT believes will happen to BTC during and after the next halving, please check <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-what-will-happen-with-btcs-price-during-and-after-the-2024-bitcoin-halving/" data-wpel-link="internal">this article</a>.</p>
<p>And if a new bull cycle indeed transpires, you might want to prepare yourself by checking <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-to-prepare-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market-10-tips-you-must-know/" data-wpel-link="internal">these tips</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-predicts-6-things-that-will-trigger-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market/" rel="nofollow">ChatGPT Predicts: 6 Things That Will Trigger the Next Bitcoin Bull Market</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouTubers Still Bullish on Wall Street Memes Despite Crashing Crypto Prices After SEC Sues Binance</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/youtubers-still-bullish-on-wall-street-memes-despite-crashing-crypto-prices-after-sec-sues-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254084</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance_cover_art.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/binance_cover_art.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s been a challenging 24 hours for crypto investors, with most coins and tokens posting significant losses following the news that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao. Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) dropped by over 5% after the news broke, as investors opted [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been a challenging 24 hours for crypto investors, with most coins and tokens posting significant losses following the news that the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had filed a lawsuit against Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao.</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) dropped by over 5% after the news broke, as investors opted to sell off their crypto assets.</p>
<p>However, there were some glimmers of hope for these investors, with several prominent crypto personalities continuing to back <a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a> – which has now surpassed $4.4 million in its presale.</p>
<h2>SEC Cracks Down on Binance – What’s Next for the Crypto Market?</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/06/05/1180132574/sec-ftx-binance-cz-changpeng-zhao-crypto-exchanges" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">According</a> to NPR, the SEC has filed 13 charges against Binance and Changpeng Zhao in what is being viewed as one of the most significant events in the crypto market this year.</p>
<p>Zhao and his company are accused of misleading investors, misusing client funds, unregistered token offerings, and other violations of securities laws.</p>
<p>Moreover, the SEC has asserted that Binance and Zhao were well aware of what they were doing, engaging in an extensive web of deception to benefit financially from investors’ actions.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254086" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-4.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="399" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-4-300x199.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-4-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Binance has denied all of the SEC&#8217;s allegations, stating that it has cooperated in the ongoing investigation and even attempted to settle. However, the SEC had other plans.</p>
<p>This move from the SEC highlights the growing scrutiny around the crypto market and its participants. These actions will likely have significant implications for US investors in the future – but also for the prices of major coins and tokens.</p>
<p>In the wake of these events, Bitcoin dropped to $25,400, its lowest value since mid-March, while Ethereum slumped to $1,780.</p>
<p>The following heatmap shows a sea of red, with only a handful of cryptos able to resist the bearish wave.</p>
<p>Many analysts now believe this could be the start of an extended downturn as US regulators continue to ramp up the pressure on the market.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254087" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-6.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="365" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-6-300x182.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-6-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>However, such actions have been <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/05/08/coinbase-ceo-on-us-crypto-regulation-sec-lawsuit-international-plans.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">criticized</a> by many big names in the industry, such as Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong.</p>
<p>The crypto community is now on edge, awaiting further developments and their potential impact.</p>
<p>Although it’s too early to speculate on the outcome of the SEC’s litigation against Binance, some legal experts suggest that there could be severe penalties for the exchange if the lawsuit doesn’t go in their favor – which may result in restrictions to their operations.</p>
<p>As the saga continues to unfold, investors globally are bracing for more downside – meaning the next few weeks will be crucial in determining the trajectory of the crypto market.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Withstands Market Turmoil &amp; Raises $4.4 Million</h2>
<p>Amid the market turmoil, a new cryptocurrency,<a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"> Wall Street Memes (WSM)</a>, is bucking the trend and standing firm against the bearish tide.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes has carved out a niche for itself following the launch of its presale on May 26, rallying its followers and helping raise over $4.4 million in funding.</p>
<p>Although the broader crypto market has taken a hit, Wall Street Memes (WSM) has remained resilient – and become a hot topic among influential YouTubers in the crypto space.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254088" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-4.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="276" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-4.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-4-300x138.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-4-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>My Financial Friend, a YouTuber with over 236,000 subscribers, recently released a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WIcVkD9W3Q0&amp;ab_channel=MyFinancialFriend" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> discussing the WSM token in glowing terms and speculated that it could be the next 10x meme coin.</p>
<p>In addition, leading YouTube analyst Michael Wrubel also posted a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r7KWE-36lwc&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video breakdown</a> of the Wall Street Memes project, pointing to the strength of its community as one of the key reasons why he’s so optimistic about its prospects.</p>
<p>Wall Street Memes&#8217; robust community, combined with the support from these YouTubers, has prompted a considerable buzz around the project – with the official <a href="https://discord.com/invite/4E538pzeGX" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Discord server</a> seeing a massive influx of new members.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254089" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-3.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="360" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-3-300x179.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-3-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Currently, Wall Street Memes is in Stage 9 of its 30-stage presale, meaning investors can purchase WSM tokens for just $0.0274 ahead of their debut on exchanges later this year.</p>
<p>However, only 20 million tokens are available during each stage – once they’re depleted, the token price will increase in the following stage.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party. It is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/youtubers-still-bullish-on-wall-street-memes-despite-crashing-crypto-prices-after-sec-sues-binance/" rel="nofollow">YouTubers Still Bullish on Wall Street Memes Despite Crashing Crypto Prices After SEC Sues Binance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple&#8217;s XRP Not Named a Security in the SEC&#8217;s Case Against Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-xrp-not-named-a-security-in-the-secs-case-against-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254055</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[XRP is not even mentioned in the filing against Coinbase.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission has filed a lawsuit against Coinbase &#8211; in what seems to be the latest turn of events. The motion comes a day after the SEC also filed against Binance.</p>
<p>The two cryptocurrency heavyweights are under some serious fire, but a closer look into the lawsuit against Coinbase reveals some interesting details.</p>
<ul>
<li>One of the more interesting findings (or the lack of) in the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Coinbase is the list of altcoins that they consider to be securities.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908/gov.uscourts.nysd.599908.1.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">filing</a> reads:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>From the time of their first offer or sale, each of these Crypto Asset Securities was offered and sold, and continues to be offered and sold today, as an investment contract and thus a security.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>From there, the SEC goes on to name 13 altcoins (in a non-exhaustive list), which includes the likes of ADA, MATIC, SOL, and others. For the full list, please take a look at our latest report <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">here</a>.</li>
<li>The curious bit is that the SEC fails to even mention Ripple&#8217;s XRP. There&#8217;s literally no mention of it.</li>
<li>Recall that the SEC is also in a legal battle against Ripple &#8211; the company behind XRP. The agency has claimed that Ripple has conducted an unregistered sale of securities (XRP).</li>
<li>It&#8217;s entirely possible that the SEC has simply missed XRP in their latest claim, but it also leaves the door open for speculation on the ongoing case against Ripple.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-xrp-not-named-a-security-in-the-secs-case-against-coinbase/" rel="nofollow">Ripple&#8217;s XRP Not Named a Security in the SEC&#8217;s Case Against Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
