<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:31:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>First and Only Crypto Based EV Charging Platform Raises $330k in Presale - Don’t Miss Chance for 10x Green Gains</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/first-and-only-crypto-based-ev-charging-platform-raises-320k-in-presale-dont-miss-chance-for-10x-green-gains.htm</link><description>The electric vehicle market is continuing to take off, demanding a more efficient and user-friendly system to accommodate an increasing number of EVs. C+Charge has answered the call with their upcoming blockchain-based EV charging platform that will make charging EVs simpler and cheaper than ever before....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/first-and-only-crypto-based-ev-charging-platform-raises-320k-in-presale-dont-miss-chance-for-10x-green-gains.htm"&gt;Read More: First and Only Crypto Based EV Charging Platform Raises $330k in Presale - Don’t Miss Chance for 10x Green Gains&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Green Investing</category><category>Green Investment</category><category>Sustainable Cryptocurrency</category><category>Sustainable Crypto</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>C-Charge</category><category>CCHG</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 22:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/first-and-only-crypto-based-ev-charging-platform-raises-320k-in-presale-dont-miss-chance-for-10x-green-gains.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101901/251647/ev-charging-app-c-charge2.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="406125"/></item><item><title>How Solana Price Was Rescued By Unlikely Meme Coin BONK - Where Next for SOL Price?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-solana-price-was-rescued-by-unlikely-meme-coin-bonk-where-next-for-sol-price.htm</link><description>Solana's (SOL) recent recovery after its FTX-fueled downfall has been nothing short of impressive, with staggering gains of 76.21% in the past month. 56.31% of those were in the last 2 weeks, and 28.53% in just the past week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/how-solana-price-was-rescued-by-unlikely-meme-coin-bonk-where-next-for-sol-price.htm"&gt;Read More: How Solana Price Was Rescued By Unlikely Meme Coin BONK - Where Next for SOL Price?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bonk</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Solana Price</category><category>SOL price prediction</category><category>Solana Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 19:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/how-solana-price-was-rescued-by-unlikely-meme-coin-bonk-where-next-for-sol-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101895/251635/sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="558082"/></item><item><title>Why the Bitcoin Price Rally is Stalling on Mixed Rates and Growth Outlook, DOJ Action – But Will Climb Again</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-the-bitcoin-price-rally-is-stalling-on-shifting-interest-rates-and-growth-outlook-doj-enforcement-action-where-next-for-crypto.htm</link><description>The bitcoin price is up 0.4% at $20,910, recovering somewhat from a $1,000 plunge after a crypto exchange co-founder was arrested on Wednesday, and weak US data pointed to an economic hard landing. &lt;br /&gt;
Although there was good news on wholesale inflation in the US yesterday, the shock retail sales figures reminded market participants that a recession is coming, if not already here. &lt;br /&gt;
That, combined with weak factory output data, capped off a week that  sees US manufacturing ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/why-the-bitcoin-price-rally-is-stalling-on-shifting-interest-rates-and-growth-outlook-doj-enforcement-action-where-next-for-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Why the Bitcoin Price Rally is Stalling on Mixed Rates and Growth Outlook, DOJ Action – But Will Climb Again&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-the-bitcoin-price-rally-is-stalling-on-shifting-interest-rates-and-growth-outlook-doj-enforcement-action-where-next-for-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101839/251568/adobestock-192921653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="10256470"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: National Australia Bank to Create a Stablecoin, Customers Sue Compass Mining, NYX Professional Makeup Announces a DAO</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-national-australia-bank-to-create-a-stablecoin-customers-sue-compass-mining-nyx-professional-makeup-announces-a-dao.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-national-australia-bank-to-create-a-stablecoin-customers-sue-compass-mining-nyx-professional-makeup-announces-a-dao.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: National Australia Bank to Create a Stablecoin, Customers Sue Compass Mining, NYX Professional Makeup Announces a DAO&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Banking</category><category>Australia</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Mining</category><category>Legal</category><category>NFT</category><category>DAO</category><category>Gamin</category><category>Music</category><category>Decentralization</category><category>Investment</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Algorand</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-national-australia-bank-to-create-a-stablecoin-customers-sue-compass-mining-nyx-professional-makeup-announces-a-dao.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101811/251481/adobestock-l-martinez-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="161168"/></item><item><title>Indian Minister Says No Issue With Crypto if Laws Are Followed</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/indian-minister-says-no-issue-with-crypto-if-laws-are-followed.htm</link><description>Rajeev Chandrasekhar, India's Minister of Information Technology, has said crypto would face no issue within the country if related laws are followed.  &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at an event in the southern city of Bengaluru, Chandrasekhar said there is "nothing today that outlaws crypto as long as you follow the legal process." The remarks come just days after the country's central bank advised investors to stay away from crypto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/indian-minister-says-no-issue-with-crypto-if-laws-are-followed.htm"&gt;Read More: Indian Minister Says No Issue With Crypto if Laws Are Followed&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>India</category><category>Reserve Bank of India</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Crypto Ban</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/indian-minister-says-no-issue-with-crypto-if-laws-are-followed.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101886/251564/adobestock-wong-sze-fei-1-media-library-original-1140-758-media-library-original-1140-758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125561"/></item><item><title>Taboo Token Price is Up 267% in 7 Days - What is TABOO and Should You Consider Buying It?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/taboo-token-price-is-up-267-in-7-days-what-is-taboo-and-should-you-consider-buying-it.htm</link><description>Taboo Token price rally continues uninterrupted even as most crypto assets trim weekly gains in the wake of the United States Justice Department enforcement action on Wednesday that saw the founder of a little-known exchange, Bitzlato arrested and extradited to the US to answer to charges of money laundering. TABOO is up a whopping 267% in a week, which brings its total monthly cumulative gains to 361%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/taboo-token-price-is-up-267-in-7-days-what-is-taboo-and-should-you-consider-buying-it.htm"&gt;Read More: Taboo Token Price is Up 267% in 7 Days - What is TABOO and Should You Consider Buying It?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/taboo-token-price-is-up-267-in-7-days-what-is-taboo-and-should-you-consider-buying-it.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101875/251552/taboo-7d-graph-coinmarketcap.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="149456"/></item><item><title>Why Crypto Prices Are Lower Today But A Rebound is On the Cards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-prices-are-lower-today-but-rebound-cards.htm</link><description>Crypto prices have fallen a little today after over a week of consistently bullish news, but investors need not be worried as there are several opportunities left to capitalise on in the market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Although the retracement has only been in single digits, there are some who are lamenting the recent price decline in the crypto markets after the recent bullish streak over the course of the last few weeks. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-prices-are-lower-today-but-rebound-cards.htm"&gt;Read More: Why Crypto Prices Are Lower Today But A Rebound is On the Cards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-prices-are-lower-today-but-rebound-cards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101794/251405/learn-crypto-the-giving-block.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1120699"/></item><item><title>New Bitcoin Address Momentum Looking Bullish, What This Means For BTC Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-bitcoin-address-momentum-looking-bullish-what-means-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>A shift in new Bitcoin address momentum is sending a signal that the world’s largest cryptocurrency might be in the beginnings of a new bull market, data from crypto analytics firm Glassnode reveals. According to Glassnode, the 30-Day Simple Moving Average (SMA) of New Addresses has now been above the 200-Day SMA since the start of November, despite the collapse of cryptocurrency exchange FTX early that month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-bitcoin-address-momentum-looking-bullish-what-means-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: New Bitcoin Address Momentum Looking Bullish, What This Means For BTC Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Btc Price</category><category>New Address</category><category>Wallet</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-bitcoin-address-momentum-looking-bullish-what-means-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101874/251548/bitcoin-wallet.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6687285"/></item><item><title>'Dr Doom' Nouriel Roubini Calls Crypto A Scam - Is He Right?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dr-doom-nouriel-roubini-calls-crypto-a-scam-is-he-right.htm</link><description>Economist Nouriel Roubini, also known as Dr. Doom because of his overly pessimistic views on financial outcomes, took aim at cryptocurrencies yesterday, labelling 90% of them as a scam. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dr-doom-nouriel-roubini-calls-crypto-a-scam-is-he-right.htm"&gt;Read More: 'Dr Doom' Nouriel Roubini Calls Crypto A Scam - Is He Right?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/dr-doom-nouriel-roubini-calls-crypto-a-scam-is-he-right.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101850/251508/0x0.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="66853"/></item><item><title>Germany’s N26 Bank Bucks the Trend, Seeks to Expand its Crypto Trading Offering to More Countries</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/germanys-n26-bank-bucks-trend-seeks-expand-its-crypto-trading-offering-more-countries.htm</link><description>German digital bank N26 has announced it is increasing the number of nations where its clients are allowed to trade cryptocurrencies, adding Germany, Switzerland, Belgium, Portugal, and Ireland to the list.  &lt;br /&gt;
“Eligible N26 customers in these markets will soon be able to trade almost 200 cryptocurrencies – more than with any other European banking app,” the online bank said in a statement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/germanys-n26-bank-bucks-trend-seeks-expand-its-crypto-trading-offering-more-countries.htm"&gt;Read More: Germany’s N26 Bank Bucks the Trend, Seeks to Expand its Crypto Trading Offering to More Countries&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>N26</category><category>Germany</category><category>Bank</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/germanys-n26-bank-bucks-trend-seeks-expand-its-crypto-trading-offering-more-countries.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101862/251506/dc6a3e4916-media-library-original-900-600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="111453"/></item><item><title>Crypto Crowd Sentiment Surges as Bitcoin Bulls Bet the Bottom is In</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-crowd-sentiment-surges-as-bitcoin-bulls-bet-bottom.htm</link><description>Prior to the recent DoJ FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) and US equity market weakness-induced pullback in Bitcoin and broader cryptocurrency markets on Wednesday, the crypto trading crowd was having its second most bullish week in terms of sentiment in the past 14 months, crypto analytics firm Santiment revealed in a chart shared on Twitter on Thursday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-crowd-sentiment-surges-as-bitcoin-bulls-bet-bottom.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Crowd Sentiment Surges as Bitcoin Bulls Bet the Bottom is In&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Sentiment</category><category>btc</category><category>Bull</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-crowd-sentiment-surges-as-bitcoin-bulls-bet-bottom.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101860/251504/bitcoin-crowd.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="16931326"/></item><item><title>Binance Identified as Counterparty to Anatoly Legkodymov’s Bitzlato Alleged Money Laundering Scheme</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-identified-as-counterparty-anatoly-legkodymovs-bitzlato-alleged-money-laundering-scheme.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, has been identified as a counterparty to the little-known exchange Bitzlato, which is now facing money laundering charges in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
The controversy surrounding Bitzlato now also involves Binance, after the US Department of the Treasury wrote in an order that Binance was Bitzlato’s top receiving counterparty of bitcoin (BTC) between May 2018 and September 2022....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-identified-as-counterparty-anatoly-legkodymovs-bitzlato-alleged-money-laundering-scheme.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Identified as Counterparty to Anatoly Legkodymov’s Bitzlato Alleged Money Laundering Scheme&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Bitzlato</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-identified-as-counterparty-anatoly-legkodymovs-bitzlato-alleged-money-laundering-scheme.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101848/251492/money-laundering.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="449232"/></item><item><title>‘$3.2bn’ Kimchi Premium Traders to Stand Trial in South Korea</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/32bn-kimchi-premium-traders-stand-trial-south-korea.htm</link><description>South Korean prosecutors are continuing to wage war against illegal kimchi premium traders – and will seek to convict 20 people for allegedly conducting $3.2 billion worth of illegal crypto transactions. &lt;br /&gt;
The kimchi premium is a phenomenon whereby increased trading volumes on South Korean crypto exchanges drive prices above the global average....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/32bn-kimchi-premium-traders-stand-trial-south-korea.htm"&gt;Read More: ‘$3.2bn’ Kimchi Premium Traders to Stand Trial in South Korea&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/32bn-kimchi-premium-traders-stand-trial-south-korea.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101800/251404/adobestock-236034935.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4503243"/></item><item><title>Where Is The Bitcoin Resurgence Coming From ?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/where-bitcoin-resurgence-coming-from.htm</link><description>The beginning of 2023 has seen Bitcoin regain some of its old fervour and pull itself up above the $20,000 mark for the first time since early November. The big question, however, is why?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/where-bitcoin-resurgence-coming-from.htm"&gt;Read More: Where Is The Bitcoin Resurgence Coming From ?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/where-bitcoin-resurgence-coming-from.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101826/251454/screenshot-2023-01-19-12-50-25.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="521614"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price is Off 11% at $0.00001118 As Crypto Pulls Back After DOJ Action - Should Buy SHIB on the Dip</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-is-off-11-at-000001118-as-crypto-pulls-back-after-doj-action-should-buy-shib-on-the-dip.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu price appears to have taken a breather after a consistent push by bulls for slightly over two weeks. This pressure is not unique to SHIB, as Bitcoin price is down 2.2% in 24 hours to trade at $20,796, while Ethereum price is exchanging hands at $1,527 after sliding 3.3%. The most popular meme coin, DOGE is also in the red and trading at $0.081 after a 5.5% correction in 24 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-is-off-11-at-000001118-as-crypto-pulls-back-after-doj-action-should-buy-shib-on-the-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price is Off 11% at $0.00001118 As Crypto Pulls Back After DOJ Action - Should Buy SHIB on the Dip&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-is-off-11-at-000001118-as-crypto-pulls-back-after-doj-action-should-buy-shib-on-the-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101828/251459/shiba-nansen.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="84806"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 19th January – KAVA, MEMAG, APT, FGHT, FXS, CCHG, AGIX, RIA, TARO, D2T</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-19th-january-kava-memag-apt-fght-fxs-cchg-agix-ria-taro-d2t.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency market has witnessed a 2.5% drop in the past 24 hours, with gains over the last week giving way to a slight correction. Still, with its total cap at roughly $997 billion, it remains up by 8% in a week and by 20% in a month. &lt;br /&gt;
And despite today's losses, some coins have bucked the overall trend to record gains. We therefore compile the best-performing tokens into this list of the best crypto to buy today, including a variety of presale tokens with strong fundamentals....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-19th-january-kava-memag-apt-fght-fxs-cchg-agix-ria-taro-d2t.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 19th January – KAVA, MEMAG, APT, FGHT, FXS, CCHG, AGIX, RIA, TARO, D2T&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-19th-january-kava-memag-apt-fght-fxs-cchg-agix-ria-taro-d2t.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101815/251452/best-crypto-to-buy-19th-january.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="296745"/></item></channel></rss>
