<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:58:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Dumped to 2-Week Low, ApeCoin Nosedives 8% (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumped-to-2-week-low-apecoin-nosedives-8-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252281</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_ApeCoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_ApeCoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ApeCoin has dumped the most today from the larger-cap alts. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After several days of trading sideways around $27,000, bitcoin took a turn for the worse and dropped to its lowest price position in almost two weeks.</p>
<p>The altcoins are in no better shape, with ETH slipping below $1,800 and ADA dumping by 3% in a day. LDO is among the few exceptions with daily gains.</p>
<h2>BTC Down to 2-Week Low</h2>
<p>After the price slumped to $26,500 last week, bitcoin recovered most losses and stood at and above $27,000 during the weekend. The start of this week was even more positive as the cryptocurrency <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/conflux-cfx-skyrockets-16-bitcoin-btc-reclaims-27k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">jumped</a> to $27,500 on Tuesday to chart a multi-day high.</p>
<p>However, the bears intercepted the move and didn&#8217;t allow any further increases. Just the opposite, they <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-rejected-at-27-5k-while-ldo-ltc-dumped-by-6-daily-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">pushed</a> the asset back down to around $27,000.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours brought even more pain for the bulls as BTC dumped by over a grand at one point and dipped below $26,000 for the first time since May 13. Despite bouncing off and recovering a few hundred dollars since that low, bitcoin is still around 2% down on the day.</p>
<p>As such, its market capitalization has declined to $505 billion. Its dominance over the alts has also taken a slight hit and stands now at 46.1% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252291" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252291" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252291" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSD-24-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252291" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>APE Drops Hard</h2>
<p>As it typically happens when BTC heads south, so do most altcoins. Ethereum is a prime example. The second-largest digital asset is down by over 2% and trades below $1,800.</p>
<p>Binance Coin has retraced to $305 after a 1% daily decrease. More losses among the top 15 coins come from the likes of Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, Solana, Polkadot, Litecoin, Shiba Inu, and Avalanche.</p>
<p>However, ApeCoin and Algorand have dumped the most from the top 50. APE has slumped by over 8% to $3.2, while ALGO is down by 5% to $0.15.</p>
<p>The crypto market cap has shed another $20 billion in a day (and over $40 in two days) and is down to precisely $1.1 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_252292" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-252292" style="width: 1882px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-252292" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1882" height="852" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19.jpg 1882w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19-1024x464.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19-768x348.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19-1536x695.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Allcoins-19-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1882px) 100vw, 1882px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-252292" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dumped-to-2-week-low-apecoin-nosedives-8-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Dumped to 2-Week Low, ApeCoin Nosedives 8% (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Cryptocurrency Launches with Potential: Ecoterra Raises $4 Million, yPredict Hits $1.5 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-cryptocurrency-launches-with-potential-ecoterra-raises-4-million-ypredict-hits-1-5-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252274</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ecoterra-CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Ecoterra-CryptoPotato-1200x780-1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although the price of Bitcoin continues to move sideways, emerging crypto projects are seeing major success in the market. Recent coin launches have seen four-digit gains and billions of dollars in trading volume. Two new crypto launches worth watching are Ecoterra and yPredict. Let’s take a closer look at these potentially explosive projects. Ecoterra Raises [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although the price of Bitcoin continues to move sideways, emerging crypto projects are seeing major success in the market. Recent coin launches have seen four-digit gains and billions of dollars in trading volume.</p>
<p>Two new crypto launches worth watching are Ecoterra and yPredict. Let’s take a closer look at these potentially explosive projects.</p>
<h2>Ecoterra Raises $4 Million for Cutting-edge Recycle-to-earn Platform</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra</a>, a sustainable crypto project developing an innovative recycle-to-earn platform, has raised more than $4.2 million through its ongoing crypto presale.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252282" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-2.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="338" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-2-300x168.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture2-2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The project’s Web3 app enables users to scan packaging materials before recycling them to earn ECOTERRA. Once users deposit their recycling at a reverse vending machine, the Ecoterra app will release their reward.</p>
<p>The idea behind the project is to not only encourage recycling but incentivize it with crypto rewards. Users can hold or exchange their ECOTERRA, or use it to further support the planet.</p>
<p>To that end, <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Ecoterra</a> gives users the ability to buy certified carbon credits from solar and wind projects around the world. Users can purchase the credits with ECOTERRA to offset their own emissions.</p>
<p>Alternatively, users can spend ECOTERRA in the platform’s fast-growing marketplace. The marketplace is home to eco-friendly businesses, each of which has a transparent impact profile so consumers can see what efforts they’ve made to be more sustainable.</p>
<p>Ecoterra also offers features to help businesses be more sustainable. The platform includes a B2B marketplace for recycled packaging materials. It also gives businesses access to data about which of their products are being recycled so they can design more sustainable packaging.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252283" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-2.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="518" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-2-300x258.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture3-2-50x43.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>During Ecoterra’s presale, early investors can buy ECOTERRA at a price of $0.0085. That’s a 15% discount from the planned list price of $0.01.</p>
<p>The presale runs until June 19 or until it reaches its hard cap of $6.7 million. The project looks increasingly likely to sell out since more than 60% of allocated ECOTERRA has already been sold.</p>
<p>Early investors can buy ECOTERRA during the presale with Ethereum, USDT, or a credit card.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>yPredict Raises $1.5 Million for AI-powered Predictive Trading Models</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> is an all-in-one AI-powered ecosystem for crypto traders, analysts, quants, and developers. It has raised more than $1.5 million, blowing through the presale’s soft cap in just a few weeks.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252284" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="365" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-300x182.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture6-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>At the heart of yPredict is a set of AI tools for building predictive trading models. These models enable traders to determine what the price of a crypto token like Bitcoin is likely to do in the next minutes, hours, days, or weeks.</p>
<p>yPredict is making its suite of tools available to all users. Analysts, quants, and developers can create their own models within yPredict using their preferred technical indicators and assumptions. All models can be backtested to determine how they might perform under real-world trading conditions.</p>
<p>Model creators can share their models with traders on a subscription basis through yPredict’s marketplace. This enables quants and developers to earn passive income from the platform while also generating revenue for yPredict.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-252285" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="602" height="170" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7-300x85.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Picture7-50x14.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Traders who want to purchase model subscriptions will need <a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">YPRED</a>, the project’s native Polygon Matic-based token.</p>
<p>In addition to using YPRED to purchase models, traders can stake the token. Staking entitles YPRED token holders to revenue sharing with yPredict and discounts on premium yPredict tools.</p>
<p>yPredict plans to incorporate predictive models into a custom trading terminal to make it easy for traders to go from analysis to execution. The platform will also leverage AI to conduct automated chart pattern analysis, social media sentiment analysis, and more.</p>
<p>During the yPredict presale, traders and investors can buy YPRED at a price of $0.07—a discount of more than 40% from the anticipated list price of $0.12.</p>
<p>The presale has a hard cap of $6.5 million, but the next price increase is just over a week away. Presale investors can buy YPRED with Ethereum, Matic, BNB, USDT, or a credit card.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-cryptocurrency-launches-with-potential-ecoterra-raises-4-million-ypredict-hits-1-5-million/" rel="nofollow">New Cryptocurrency Launches with Potential: Ecoterra Raises $4 Million, yPredict Hits $1.5 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Freezes $4.4 Million in Crypto Related to North Korean Hackers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-freezes-4-4-million-in-crypto-related-to-north-korean-hackers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252272</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A timely tip from U.S. law enforcement led to the seizure of illegitimate funding for the Hermit Kingdom.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the 25th of May, Binance announced the seizure of approximately $4.4 million in cryptocurrency belonging to fronts for North Korean organizations operating in the country and abroad.</p>
<p>Due to sanctions against the rogue nation, agents working for it have often turned to illicit methods of raising funds, including theft of crypto.</p>
<h2>Illicit Research Funding Blocked</h2>
<p>The funds seized today were to be remitted to the Pyongyang University of Automation, responsible for the training of the infamous North Korean hackers, <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy1498" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to the U.S. Department of Treasury, and the North Korean Technical Reconnaissance Bureau, which employs said bad actors.</p>
<p>Most of the cybercriminals trained at the Pyongyang University of Automation are part of the 110th Research Center, the unit in charge of running the Lazarus Group and similar groups.</p>
<p>In order to fund these entities, North Korean IT professionals – often based in Russia and China – seek employment in companies around the world, turning over their salaries to the North Korean government. However, the latest batch of funding was stopped due to the efforts of the U.S. Government and Binance.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are proud to have assisted US law enforcement in seizing $4.4M and freezing accounts linked to North Korean organized crime.</p>
<p>Kudos to our law enforcement partners and the Binance Investigations team for their unwavering commitment to combating crime worldwide.</p>
<p>— Binance (@binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1661474674377740289?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Brian Nelson, a spokesperson for the U.S. Treasury, thanked their “partners in the private sector” for the help offered.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Today’s action continues to highlight the DPRK’s extensive illicit cyber and IT worker operations, which finance the regime’s unlawful weapons of mass destruction and ballistic missile programs. The United States and our partners remain committed to combatting the DPRK’s illicit revenue generation activities and continued efforts to steal money from financial institutions, virtual currency exchanges, companies, and private individuals around the world.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Commitment to a Safer World</h2>
<p>Binance has previously come under fire for allegedly not doing enough to prevent cybercriminals and radical groups from receiving <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-fires-back-at-reuters-over-report-about-confiscated-accounts-linked-to-terrorism/" data-wpel-link="internal">funding</a> from sympathizers worldwide.</p>
<p>The firm, though, has responded to the allegations, stating that the team does everything in its power to stop these actions.</p>
<p>Indeed, cybersecurity is a numbers game – the fact that a few bad actors manage to squeeze through the net says nothing about the much larger number of bad actors stopped. This is amplified by the fact that companies do not publicly announce which bad actors they stopped and how did they do it, as this would help others evade detection.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-freezes-4-4-million-in-crypto-related-to-north-korean-hackers/" rel="nofollow">Binance Freezes $4.4 Million in Crypto Related to North Korean Hackers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Community Update: Chain Of Alliance Alpha 1.0 Is Live, Roadmap and More</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/community-update-chain-of-alliance-alpha-1-0-is-live-roadmap-and-more/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252266</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Alpha1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Alpha1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Stockholm, Sweden, May 24th, 2023] Chain of Alliance Launches Public Alpha 1.0 on Chromia Testnet Sigma, Paving the Way to Become the Premier Turn-Based, Party-Builder RPG Multiverse Chain of Alliance is thrilled to unveil the next phase of its remarkable journey as it solidifies its position as the leading turn-based, party-builder RPG [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Stockholm, Sweden, May 24th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><em>Chain of Alliance Launches Public Alpha 1.0 on Chromia Testnet Sigma, Paving the Way to Become the Premier Turn-Based, Party-Builder RPG Multiverse</em></p>
<p><a href="https://www.chainofalliance.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Chain of Alliance</a> is thrilled to unveil the next phase of its remarkable journey as it solidifies its position as the leading turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse, catering to both Web3 and traditional players. This momentous milestone marks the beginning of an extraordinary adventure for Chain of Alliance as it sets its sights on redefining the landscape of turn-based RPG gaming. The company is committed to fostering a vibrant and inclusive community driven by a shared passion for the genre.</p>
<p>Building upon a foundation of innovation and community engagement, Chain of Alliance has implemented strategic structural adjustments and bolstered its team to propel the project forward. With a clear and attainable <a href="https://medium.com/@chainofalliance_10686/community-update-alpha-1-0-is-live-roadmap-and-more-e0c22a15b1ce" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">roadmap</a> for the remainder of the year, the company is proud to announce the official launch of its highly anticipated Public Alpha 1.0, now available on the Chromia Testnet Sigma. Experience the game firsthand by visiting the official website.</p>
<p>Chain of Alliance invites players to immerse themselves in a captivating world of strategic combat. The game’s innovative features and engaging gameplay mechanics aim to captivate both Web3 enthusiasts and traditional gamers.</p>
<p>The team is extending its gratitude to its esteemed badge holders, who have been granted an exclusive preview of the game, providing valuable feedback that has contributed to its refinement.</p>
<h2>Introducing The New Team</h2>
<p>Joining Chain of Alliance as the Lead Producer is Nicholas St. Louis, a seasoned professional with six years of industry experience. Nicholas has successfully managed projects at prestigious companies such as Sega, Moon Studios, and Rockstar and now brings his expertise to the team.</p>
<p>Overseeing the design of all new features is Clément Fitoussi, an exceptionally talented Game Designer with over six years of experience in the gaming industry. Clément’s impressive portfolio includes collaborations with renowned companies like Mattel, Ubisoft, and Seascape.</p>
<p>Leading the marketing and community management efforts is Jorn Wisman, a Marketing Lead with over 15 years of experience in the gaming industry. Jorn’s invaluable insights and expertise have been cultivated through his previous positions at PlayStation and Rockstar Games.</p>
<h2>Game Redesign: Alpha 1.0</h2>
<p>With the release of Alpha 1.0, Chain of Alliance invites players to experience a transformed gaming landscape. The latest Alpha build introduces significant changes and improvements. View the Chain of Alliance onboarding guide here, along with the following exciting new features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Character Creation: The introduction of the Blessing and Fragment system empowers players to customize their characters, adding depth and personalization to their gameplay experience.</li>
<li>Crafting System: Players can now select from various rare materials to craft items, offering enhanced gameplay depth and personalization.</li>
<li>New User Experience: The user interface has been revamped to provide step-by-step guidance within the game, ensuring seamless immersion for new and experienced players.</li>
<li>Core Game Mechanics: Based on valuable feedback from the previous public version, Chain of Alliance has implemented substantial changes to the core game mechanics, enhancing the gameplay and overall player experience.</li>
</ul>
<h2>A Glimpse of the First Multiverse Realm</h2>
<p><strong>Roadmap</strong></p>
<p>Looking ahead, Chain of Alliance is thrilled to share its exciting roadmap, which balances community excitement and achievable milestones. Get first-hand news and a detailed roadmap here.</p>
<h2>About Chain of Alliance</h2>
<p>Chain of Alliance is an innovative and immersive turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse that aims to redefine the gaming landscape. With a focus on appealing to Web3 enthusiasts and traditional players, Chain of Alliance offers a captivating gaming experience that combines strategic combat, engaging storytelling, and a robust multiverse. Creators have the long-term vision of allowing players to create their own campaigns and stories using the game’s API and leveraging characters and land offered by other players.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/community-update-chain-of-alliance-alpha-1-0-is-live-roadmap-and-more/" rel="nofollow">Community Update: Chain Of Alliance Alpha 1.0 Is Live, Roadmap and More</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zebec&#8217;s Modular L3 Nautilus Chain Debuts on Mainnet, Focused on DeFi Future and Continuous Payments</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/zebecs-modular-l3-nautilus-chain-debuts-on-mainnet-focused-on-defi-future-and-continuous-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 07:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252215</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/nautilus-chain-to-mainnet-V2_1684842047KgWCZvkdNn.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/nautilus-chain-to-mainnet-V2_1684842047KgWCZvkdNn.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, United States, May 24th, 2023] Following months of battle-testing by partner projects, developers, and community, production-ready Nautilus Chain graduates from testnet. Zebec, a pioneer in streaming finance, announced today the launch of Nautilus Chain &#8211; soon to be Zebec Chain &#8211; on mainnet, an important milestone in building its continuous [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, United States, May 24th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Following months of battle-testing by partner projects, developers, and community, production-ready Nautilus Chain graduates from testnet.</p>
<p><a href="https://zebec.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Zebec</a>, a pioneer in streaming finance, announced today the launch of Nautilus Chain &#8211; soon to be Zebec Chain &#8211; on mainnet, an important milestone in building its continuous payments infrastructure and global ecosystem. The first of its kind as an L3, Nautilus Chain offers the fastest EVM environment in web3 capable of parallel transaction processing, combining the speeds of Solana with the stability and functionality of EVM-based Solidity smart contracts, paving the way to the next generation of DeFi and consumer applications with a continuous stream of transactions or payments.</p>
<p>Nautilus Chain’s settlement layer is currently built on Solana node, its execution layer on Neon EVM and Solidity smart contract, with data availability hash stored off-chain in order to keep Nautilus’ modular blockchain architecture. With plans to transition settlement layer to optimistic roll-up and data availability stored on layer 1 chains such as Etherium, BSC or Bitcoin to further maximize throughput while remaining stable and reliable to support high-throughput payment applications such as payroll, DeFi applications, and on-chain gaming.</p>
<p>The mainnet upgrade brings over 80 projects, such as <a href="https://coraldex.finance/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Coral Finance</a>, <a href="https://witnet.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Witnet</a>, and <a href="https://www.poseiswap.xyz/?chain=triton" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">PoseiSwap</a> to name a few, with dozens more in the process of onboarding and a track record of seamlessly processing over 40 million transactions on testnet to date.</p>
<p><span style="color: #767676; font-size: 19px; font-style: italic;">&#8220;Zebec is helping to create a future where money is able to move more freely; giving individuals, businesses, investors, and teams faster and easier access to funds and tokens,&#8221; said Sam Thapaliya, Founder of Zebec. &#8220;The launch of Nautilus on mainnet is another breakthrough on the path towards this vision.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2>Key features of the Nautilus Chain</h2>
<p><strong>High Throughput</strong></p>
<p>Through parallelizing transactions instead of processing them linearly, Nautilus delivers an initial TPS of 2,000, with much higher rates soon to come.</p>
<p><strong>Developer-friendly</strong></p>
<p>Solidity developers are able to build high-throughput applications in an EVM environment. While the chain&#8217;s modular structure supports customization and gives developers control of the tech stack — or chain stack — in building dApps. The chain is highly interoperable and extensible and, with app-specific rollups, enables projects to strike the perfect balance between decentralization, throughput, performance, cost, and efficiency.</p>
<p><strong>Reliable</strong></p>
<p>The high speeds and performance of the Nautilus chain, because it is a sovereign rollup, do not compromise the overall reliability and security of the infrastructure. Its robust design ensures optimal uptime and resilience, even under the most demanding conditions.</p>
<h2>Built for the Real World</h2>
<p>With its core innovation in performance and security, Zebec’s technology has transformative potential in the world of traditional finance, blockchain adoption, and smart contract-based digital financial applications.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Zebec’s progress with Nautilus Chain development has the potential to bridge the gap between traditional finance and web2 payroll applications and the emerging web3 ecosystem.&#8221; &#8211; said Steve Chen, Head of Blockchain Development for Nautilus</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By harnessing the unparalleled speed, security, and interoperability of Nautilus, Zebec’s technology is poised to revolutionize traditional finance, bringing the benefits of blockchain technology to mainstream industries. As we continue to explore the potential of Zebec’s L3 chain, we foresee a future where seamless integration between web2 and web3 applications leads to the eventual replacement of conventional financial systems with blockchain technology and creating a more inclusive and efficient global economy.&#8221;- Chen continued.</p></blockquote>
<p>As Zebec continues to innovate and expand its ecosystem, it invites developers, companies, and projects from around the world to join it in creating a more connected, efficient, and accessible financial future.</p>
<h2>About Zebec</h2>
<p>Zebec enables real-time and continuous streams of payments and financial transactions for payroll, investments, and more. Founded in 2021, with investments by Circle, Coinbase, Solana Ventures, Breyer Capital, Republic, and Lightspeed Venture Partners, among others, Zebec services hundreds of companies, running thousands of continuous payment streams and bringing the blockchain to everyday lives.</p>
<h2>About Nautilus</h2>
<p>Nautilus is a high-performance modular blockchain built for real-world DeFi and Web3 applications delivering high speed and low cost of processing transactions within a highly secure and stable decentralized system.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zebecs-modular-l3-nautilus-chain-debuts-on-mainnet-focused-on-defi-future-and-continuous-payments/" rel="nofollow">Zebec&#8217;s Modular L3 Nautilus Chain Debuts on Mainnet, Focused on DeFi Future and Continuous Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Denied Bail By Montenegro Court</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/terra-co-founder-do-kwon-denied-bail-by-montenegro-court/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252240</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/ezgif.com-gif-maker.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/ezgif.com-gif-maker.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Do Kwon remains in jail, and the lower court will be forced to make another decision on his bail ruling. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Do Kwon – co-founder of the collapsed Terra (LUNA) blockchain – has been denied bail after receiving initial approval to be released for roughly $430,500. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">On Wednesday, a court </span><a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/crypto-mogul-do-kwon-s-bail-is-revoked-in-montenegro-1.1924367" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">spokesperson</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> told Bloomberg that a high court in Monetegro’s capital overturned a lower court decision to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terraform-labs-founder-do-kwon-to-be-released-on-440k-bail-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Kwon on €400,000. The founder remains in jail. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Prosecutors were quick to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwons-bail-appealed-by-montenegrin-prosecutors-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">appeal</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the lower court decision earlier this month, which left things to the higher court to decide. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400">
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The Basic court should now make another decision, taking into account what the High Court ruled,” said Marija Rakovic, the court spokeswoman. “There is no legal limit to how many motions can follow between the respective judges in deciding on bail for the two South Korean nationals.” </span></p></blockquote>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The ruling also applies to Kwon’s former chief financial officer Han Chong-Joon, both of whom have pleaded not guilty to document forgery charges after allegedly traveling to Montenegro on a forged passport.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Kwon was arrested in Montenegro in March, after which he was demanded by the United States, South Korea, and Singapore. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The Securities and Exchange Commission has already </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-sues-terraform-labs-and-do-kwon-for-crypto-fraud-involving-ust-and-luna/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">charged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the founder with fraud surrounding Terra’s UST and LUNA tokens and later </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-cashed-10k-btc-using-a-swiss-bank-claims-the-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">accused</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> him of cashing out 10,000 Bitcoin (BTC) with a Swiss bank. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Terra’s collapse in May 2022 kickstarted a wave of insolvencies throughout the crypto industry stretching until the year’s end, turning Kwon into of the industry’s most hated personalities. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terra-co-founder-do-kwon-denied-bail-by-montenegro-court/" rel="nofollow">Terra Co-Founder Do Kwon Denied Bail By Montenegro Court</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>“Citizens Have Every Right To Do Bitcoin”: Ron De Santis Announces Presidential Bid</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/citizens-have-every-right-to-do-bitcoin-ron-de-santis-announces-presidential-bid/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252248</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/230315183223-ron-desantis-0310.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/230315183223-ron-desantis-0310.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Florida’s governor is running for President on the Republican side – and he’s pro-Bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Florida Governor Ron De Santis has officially announced that he’s entering the United States 2024 Presidential race, poised to be former President Donald Trump’s greatest opponent within the Republican primary. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Unlike Trump, De Santis has pushed pro-crypto policy multiple times in the past and is staunchly opposed to Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs).</span></p>
<h2>De Santis Would Protect Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">De Santis announced his plans to run in a <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1661498079386931206" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Twitter Spaces</a> alongside the platform’s owner, Elon Musk, on Wednesday. Musk has </span><a href="https://twitter.com/MarioNawfal/status/1648128894979956736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1648128894979956736%7Ctwgr%5Ee49bdc41d2b7ccb906a7d10ce200a18b9ce17ef2%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.benzinga.com%2Fnews%2F23%2F04%2F31852077%2Felon-musk-reveals-he-voted-for-biden-in-2020-now-he-wants-a-normal-person-with-common-sense-as-next" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">expressed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> regret for voting for Joe Biden in the 2020 election, but also wasn’t interested in Trump since he desired a “normal person for president.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Both Musk and De Santis found common ground in their opposition to “woke” ideology, and their support for free speech. They also happen to both be </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/elon-musk-issues-warning-for-dogecoin-investors-explains-why-doge-is-his-favorite-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">crypto-friendly</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, while Trump has repeatedly called Bitcoin a “</span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-bitcoin-looks-like-a-scam/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">scam</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">When asked about his view on crypto’s regulatory situation in the United States, De Santis said that citizens have “every right to do Bitcoin,” and would oppose any statute to ban its use. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“As President, we’ll protect the ability to do things like Bitcoin,” said De Santis. “I just do not have the itch to control everything that people may be doing in this space.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">De Santis echoed comments from other crypto-supportive Republicans in agreeing that the Biden Administration is attempting to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/regulators-want-crypto-to-stay-the-f-away-caitlin-long-erik-voorhees-consensus-2023-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">kill the crypto industry</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in the United States through regulation. After a string of regulators’ enforcement actions against </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-addresses-the-cftc-in-house-trading-allegations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">exchanges</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, stablecoin issuers, and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fdic-chair-blames-crypto-exposure-for-signature-banks-demise/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">crypto-supportive banks</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, firms like Coinbase are desperate for clarity on the rules of the road surrounding crypto in the United States. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The current regime – clearly they have it out for Bitcoin, and if it continues for another four years, they’ll probably end up killing it,” he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At Bitcoin Miami 2023 last week, Democratic Presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-pledges-inviolable-right-to-hold-and-use-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pledged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to protect citizens’ “inviolable right” to hold and use Bitcoin. Miami Mayor Francis Suarez is himself a Bitcoin believer, believing it </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftxs-collapse-miamis-mayor-is-still-a-bitcoin-believer/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">provides advantages</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> over the fiat currency system. </span></p>
<h2>No CBDCs for De Santis</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By contrast, the Biden White House has expressed interest in implementing a potential CBDC to “bring the U.S. financial infrastructure into the digital era… without the risks or irrational exuberance brought by crypto assets.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Similar to Republic Congressmen Tom Emmer and </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sen-ted-cruz-introduces-a-bill-to-prevent-the-fed-from-issuing-a-cbdc/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ted Cruz</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, De Santis is outright opposed to CBDCs. He introduced legislation in March to </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-says-governor-ron-desantis/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">ban</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> any such technology from being used in Florida. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I see it as a massive transfer of power from individual consumers to a central authority, and I don’t think that’s good for a free society,” he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/citizens-have-every-right-to-do-bitcoin-ron-de-santis-announces-presidential-bid/" rel="nofollow">“Citizens Have Every Right To Do Bitcoin”: Ron De Santis Announces Presidential Bid</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korea&#8217;s PPP Seeks to Speed Up Bill Requiring Lawmakers&#8217; Crypto Holdings Disclosure</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-koreas-ppp-seeks-to-speed-up-bill-requiring-lawmakers-crypto-holdings-disclosure/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=251950</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/south_korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/south_korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The politician had recently quit the party over the crypto scandal.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Korea&#8217;s ruling party has called for early enforcement of the law that seeks the country&#8217;s lawmakers and high-level government officials to declare their cryptocurrency-related assets.</p>
<p>The proposed bill would require local officials and lawmakers to declare all personal crypto holdings over 1 million Korean won (worth around $760). The move was prompted by a major crypto scandal involving a former lawmaker of the opposing party.</p>
<h2>Calls to Expedite Bill</h2>
<p>A report by Yonhap news agency <a href="https://en.yna.co.kr/view/AEN20230523005800315?section=news" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">suggests</a> that People Power Party&#8217;s floor leader unveiled a bill last Friday proposing all public officials and candidates disclose their crypto holdings.</p>
<p>The original bill was previously scheduled for implementation in December this year. However, Rep. Yun Jae-ok, a third-term lawmaker, who was elected as the new floor leader of the conservative PPP last month, deemed the set date to be &#8220;too late&#8221; and added that the bill needs to be amended to add a clause moving up the enforcement.</p>
<p>The lawmaker said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Given the current high level of public interest, especially regarding lawmakers, it&#8217;s not appropriate to enforce the law six months later after the promulgation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Yun further revealed that he asked the leader of the Public Administration Committee to propose a modified version of the law. The bill is reportedly scheduled to be put to a vote on May 26.</p>
<p>The latest development emerges on the heels of the ongoing scandal surrounding former Democratic Party lawmaker Kim Nam-kuk who has been at the center of controversy over his cryptocurrency investments. He is currently under investigation by local prosecutors for alleged campaign finance violations and tax portals, as well as for hiding criminal proceeds of his crypto possessions and transactions.</p>
<p>Kim announced leaving the party last week and continued to maintain his innocence. While responding to allegations, the now-independent lawmaker asserted that he was not required to disclose activities surrounding his crypto assets and denied liquidating his holdings.</p>
<p>As part of the investigation against the politician, authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-prosecutors-raided-upbit-and-bithumb-hqs-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">raided</a> the offices of prominent crypto exchanges  &#8211; Upbit and Bithumb.</p>
<h2>South Korea&#8217;s Regulatory Standpoint</h2>
<p>South Korean lawmakers have increased regulatory scrutiny of the crypto-asset industry after the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-authorities-seize-terra-executives-assets-worth-160m-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse</a> of the Terra ecosystem tokens last May.</p>
<p>As such, the legislators passed a first phase review of proposed regulations that offers the Financial Services Commission authority to investigate and monitor financial activity related to the asset class with stipulations ranging from governing the sale, storage, and trading. Consumer protection and compliance reporting were some of the aspects that were particularly stressed.</p>
<p>If passed, the bill would require digital asset service providers to distinguish internal holdings from consumer assets, carry insurance and maintain reserves in the event of non-market-related losses.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-koreas-ppp-seeks-to-speed-up-bill-requiring-lawmakers-crypto-holdings-disclosure/" rel="nofollow">South Korea&#8217;s PPP Seeks to Speed Up Bill Requiring Lawmakers&#8217; Crypto Holdings Disclosure</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NBA Star Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit for Promoting Solana-Based Crypto Project Astrals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nba-star-shaquille-oneal-faces-lawsuit-for-promoting-solana-based-crypto-project-astrals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252121</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shaq.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Shaq.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[O'Neal has been summoned to court again over his involvement in promoting Astrals token, an alleged unregistered security.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American basketball legend Shaquille O&#8217;Neal is facing a new lawsuit for promoting the Solana-based crypto project, Astrals.</p>
<p>According to the class action lawsuit filed with a Floridan court by plaintiff Daniel Harper, Shaquille shilled the Astrals token through posts and videos on several of his social media handles.</p>
<h2>O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit Over Astrals Project</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/647748832/Harper-v-O-Neal#" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lawsuit</a>, Astrals is a 3D-modeled NFT collection founded by the NBA celebrity alongside his son, Mylers O&#8217;Neal. Shaq&#8217;s son headed the role of &#8220;Investors Relations&#8221; while his music manager, Brian Bayati, acted as the project&#8217;s CEO.</p>
<p>Building on the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-solana/" data-wpel-link="internal">Solana network</a>, Astrals seeks to onboard users into an ecosystem that offers gaming and metaverse experiences. These services are accessible through the Solana-based NFT marketplace Magic Eden.</p>
<p>Encouraging users to engage with Astrals&#8217; native cryptocurrency, the project launched the Shaq Signature Pass as an exclusive 50-piece collection of NFTs. These collectibles can only be claimed with the native token.</p>
<p>Harper&#8217;s lawsuit, which claims that Astrals tokens are unregistered securities, means that the assets will be subjected to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-launches-its-own-ico-howeycoin-to-educate-investors/" data-wpel-link="internal">Howey test</a>. This is a process used to determine whether a cryptocurrency (or any other type of asset) falls under the category of security or an investment contract.</p>
<p>If the Astrals token passes the Howey test, it will be classified as a security and must be registered with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). As such, the SEC will likely take legal action against Astrals and its executives, demanding a settlement.</p>
<h2>Not the First</h2>
<p>Since joining the industry, O&#8217;Neal has found himself in several crypto-related lawsuit cases. Earlier this month, he was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-icon-shaquille-oneal-describes-his-ftx-summons-as-inadequate-seeks-dismisal-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">involved</a> in a court case regarding the collapsed crypto exchange FTX.</p>
<p>After being summoned to the court regarding his interaction with FTX, the NBA celebrity stated that the notice was inadequate, as it was tossed at his moving car and not served at his home.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-star-shaquille-oneal-faces-lawsuit-for-promoting-solana-based-crypto-project-astrals/" rel="nofollow">NBA Star Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Faces Lawsuit for Promoting Solana-Based Crypto Project Astrals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase: SEC Has Made Up its Mind to Deny Petition</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sec-has-made-up-its-mind-to-deny-petition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=252093</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase lashed out on the SEC saying the agency has no plans to consider the crypto exchange's petition on any timeline. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In response to the SEC&#8217;s arguments against its petition for a writ of mandamus, Coinbase said the financial regulator &#8220;is talking out of both sides of its mouth, and it is wrong at each end.&#8221; The crypto exchange&#8217;s chief legal officer Paul Grewal described the mandamus as &#8220;the tailor-made remedy for the extraordinary facts.&#8221;</p>
<p>The longstanding dispute between the crypto exchange and the market regulator is at the heart of the battle. Last month, Coinbase sued the SEC, claiming that the latter failed to provide a response as the former sought a formal notice-and-comment process that would enable the public to weigh in. The SEC later responded, deeming Coinbase&#8217;s allegations to be &#8220;baseless.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Coinbase vs. SEC</h2>
<p>In a 23-page <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/4Y8RdHCBOhXBvqYH51pw5P/564dd375bfeaaf866180888ef9a96432/2023.05.22_-_Dkt._27_-_Coinbase_Mandamus_Reply.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> to the Third Circuit of the United States Court of Appeals, the crypto exchange said the SEC&#8217;s broad enforcement campaign on the same topic posed by Coinbase&#8217;s rulemaking petition renders the agency&#8217;s delay &#8220;unreasonable.&#8221;</p>
<p>Coinbase argued that mandamus is warranted and blamed the SEC for &#8220;making up its mind&#8221; to deny the petition. It also said the Commission&#8217;s enforcement actions confirm that it is not considering Coinbase&#8217;s Petition.</p>
<p>The filing also cited that the SEC has instituted over 25 digital asset-related enforcement actions since the filing of the petition in July 2022.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;These actions presuppose that the agency believes the securities laws are clear and workable as applied to digital assets and that additional rulemaking is unnecessary. And many of these enforcement actions require the Commission to take positions on the central questions in Coinbase’s rulemaking petition, such as the standard for identifying whether a digital asset is a security.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase also hit back at the SEC, saying the latter&#8217;s argument that &#8211; regulated entities should wait to be sued &#8211; ignores its obligations to create significant new legal standards through rulemaking and not enforcement.</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s Earlier Response</h2>
<p>After failed attempts to get a response from the SEC about its stance on proposing and adopting rules to govern the regulation of securities that are offered and traded via digitally native methods, a US court <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the commission to respond to Coinbase’s complaint in ten days.</p>
<p>The Commission then argued that it is under no obligation to issue new regulations and added that Coinbase has no standing to sue the agency. It also said the digital asset industry already has rules and regulations governing it.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sec-has-made-up-its-mind-to-deny-petition/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase: SEC Has Made Up its Mind to Deny Petition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
