<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Argentina Raises Electricity Tariffs for Crypto Miners – ‘Pressure’ Mounts on Miners?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-raises-electricity-tariffs-for-crypto-miners-pressure-mounts-miners.htm</link><description>Crypto miners in Argentina are set for a rise in energy costs, after the Ministry of Economy published a revised list of electricity rates. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Livecoins, the Ministry has set miners a new rate of 17,240 Argentine pesos (around $63.30 at the time of writing) per megawatt-hour (MWh), the highest band on the ministry’s scale. &lt;br /&gt;
By contrast, residential energy costs are heavily subsidized, with households entitled to enjoy subsidies of up to 70%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-raises-electricity-tariffs-for-crypto-miners-pressure-mounts-miners.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Raises Electricity Tariffs for Crypto Miners – ‘Pressure’ Mounts on Miners?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Crypto Mining</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-raises-electricity-tariffs-for-crypto-miners-pressure-mounts-miners.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120856/320306/arg-2807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1290030"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Police Swoop on Suspected Crypto Pyramid Operator Braiscompany</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-swoop-suspected-crypto-pyramid-operator-braiscompany.htm</link><description>Brazil’s police force has conducted raids on addresses linked with Braiscompany, a suspected crypto pyramid. The firm’s owners have allegedly escaped the country with around $160 million worth of customers’ funds. &lt;br /&gt;
Police launched an investigation into the firm, codenamed Operation Halving, earlier this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-swoop-suspected-crypto-pyramid-operator-braiscompany.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Police Swoop on Suspected Crypto Pyramid Operator Braiscompany&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>Police</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-police-swoop-suspected-crypto-pyramid-operator-braiscompany.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120761/320243/brazil-2707.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="793522"/></item><item><title>DOJ Drops Campaign Finance Charge Against Sam Bankman-Fried Due to Treaty Obligations with The Bahamas</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-drops-campaign-finance-charge-against-sam-bankman-fried-due-to-treaty-obligations-with-the-bahamas.htm</link><description>On July 26, the Department of Justice (DOJ) informed federal judge Lewis A. Kaplan that they "do not intend to proceed" with a campaign finance charge against FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried.  &lt;br /&gt;
This decision came after consulting with The Bahamas regarding the campaign finance charges mentioned in Bankman-Fried's extradition document last year. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-drops-campaign-finance-charge-against-sam-bankman-fried-due-to-treaty-obligations-with-the-bahamas.htm"&gt;Read More: DOJ Drops Campaign Finance Charge Against Sam Bankman-Fried Due to Treaty Obligations with The Bahamas&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried Extradition</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Trial</category><category>Bahamas</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-drops-campaign-finance-charge-against-sam-bankman-fried-due-to-treaty-obligations-with-the-bahamas.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120907/320398/107150385-1668177437483-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="164115"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 27 July – Synthetix, Pepe, Maker</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-27-july-synthetix-pepe-maker.htm</link><description>Mark Yusko, the principal of Morgan Creek Capital Management, a fund management organization with $1.6 billion in its custody, shared some thought-provoking predictions about the future value of Bitcoin today. &lt;br /&gt;
He sees the most prominent cryptocurrency achieving a value of $300,000 by the end of 2028, raising some eyes in the crypto space today as the markets remained relatively stable. In light of this, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-27-july-synthetix-pepe-maker.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 27 July – Synthetix, Pepe, Maker&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Synthetix</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Chimpzee</category><category>Maker</category><category>SNX price</category><category>SNX</category><category>Pepe Coin Price</category><category>Pepe Price</category><category>MKR price</category><category>MKR</category><category>CHMPZ</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-27-july-synthetix-pepe-maker.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120906/320385/bc27j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="354583"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Dips as DXY, US Yields Rise on Strong US Economic Data – Here’s Where BTC is Headed Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-nextbitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) has come under modest sell pressure on Thursday amid a rise in US bond yields and the US Dollar Index (DXY) as a result of stronger-than-expected US economic data. &lt;br /&gt;
The BTC price was last around $29,100, down nearly 1% on the day, with the bears eyeing a retest of this week’s sub-$29,000 lows....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-nextbitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Dips as DXY, US Yields Rise on Strong US Economic Data – Here’s Where BTC is Headed Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>US GDP</category><category>Fed</category><category>Economy</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-nextbitcoin-dips-as-dxy-us-yields-rise-strong-us-economic-data-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120904/320380/btc-10.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131590"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as US GDP Growth Data is Released – Is a Recession Likely?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-gdp-growth-data-released-recession-likely.htm</link><description>Amid the release of US GDP growth data, the Bitcoin price is being closely observed, raising questions about the possibility of a recession.  &lt;br /&gt;
As of now, Bitcoin is trading at $29,132, with a 24-hour trading volume of $12.4 billion. Over the last 24 hours, Bitcoin has experienced a nearly 1% decline. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-gdp-growth-data-released-recession-likely.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as US GDP Growth Data is Released – Is a Recession Likely?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-us-gdp-growth-data-released-recession-likely.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120900/320378/27.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="482719"/></item><item><title>Executive Director of Wyoming's Stablecoin Project to Earn More Than Governor Mark Gordon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/executive-director-of-wyomings-stablecoin-project-earn-more-than-governor-mark-gordon.htm</link><description>The US state of Wyoming is seeking to hire an executive director for its new stablecoin project, and the position will pay an annual salary of $150,000, which is $10,000 more than the state’s governor. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the job post for the position, the executive director will be in charge of carrying out the mission of the Wyoming Stable Token Commission, an entity that was set up following the passing of the Wyoming Stable Token Act earlier this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/executive-director-of-wyomings-stablecoin-project-earn-more-than-governor-mark-gordon.htm"&gt;Read More: Executive Director of Wyoming's Stablecoin Project to Earn More Than Governor Mark Gordon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Wyoming</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/executive-director-of-wyomings-stablecoin-project-earn-more-than-governor-mark-gordon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120878/320330/wyoming-flag.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="999232"/></item><item><title>CFA Institute Survey: Chinese and Indian Investment Professionals Show Strong Support for CBDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cfa-institute-survey-chinese-indian-investment-professionals-show-strong-support-for-cbdc.htm</link><description>Investment professionals in both China and India are largely bullish on Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC), according to a new survey from the CFA Institute. &lt;br /&gt;
The association, which provides credentialing for chartered financial analysts, found that 66% of its members in India and 70% in China supported the technology – vastly more than their United States-based counterparts at merely 31%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cfa-institute-survey-chinese-indian-investment-professionals-show-strong-support-for-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: CFA Institute Survey: Chinese and Indian Investment Professionals Show Strong Support for CBDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cfa-institute-survey-chinese-indian-investment-professionals-show-strong-support-for-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120895/320370/adobestock-382323810.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="266052"/></item><item><title>FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Tightened Bail Conditions and Possible Jail in Trial</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-faces-tightened-bail-conditions-and-possible-jail-in-trial.htm</link><description>Sam Bankman-Fried, the founder of now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange FTX, is facing tightened bail conditions and the possibility of jail time as he awaits trial over the collapse of his exchange.  &lt;br /&gt;
At a recent hearing, US District Judge Lewis Kaplan imposed a "gag order" on Bankman-Fried, restricting his ability to communicate publicly, Reuters reported Thursday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-faces-tightened-bail-conditions-and-possible-jail-in-trial.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Founder Sam Bankman-Fried Faces Tightened Bail Conditions and Possible Jail in Trial&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-founder-sam-bankman-fried-faces-tightened-bail-conditions-and-possible-jail-in-trial.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120888/320360/screenshot-2023-03-28-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="72251"/></item><item><title>North Korea's Lazarus Group Suspected in $37 Million Hack on CoinsPaid</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-koreas-lazarus-group-suspected-37-million-hack-coinspaid.htm</link><description>North Korean hackers at the infamous Lazarus Group are suspected to be behind a $37 million attack on crypto payment system CoinsPaid. &lt;br /&gt;
The attack, which happened on July 22, successfully drained funds from the company’s own reserves, while customer deposits were unaffected, CoinsPaid said in a statement. &lt;br /&gt;
“We suspect Lazarus Group, one of the most powerful hacker organisations, is responsible,” the company added....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/north-koreas-lazarus-group-suspected-37-million-hack-coinspaid.htm"&gt;Read More: North Korea's Lazarus Group Suspected in $37 Million Hack on CoinsPaid&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hack</category><category>CoinsPaid</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/north-koreas-lazarus-group-suspected-37-million-hack-coinspaid.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120868/320321/north-korea-hacker.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="34283"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – HUTAO, $PAAL, HOPPY</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-hutao-paal-hoppy.htm</link><description>Major blue chip cryptocurrencies for the most part remain within this week’s ranges, with bitcoin (BTC) in the low $29,000s and ether (ETH) in the mid-$1,800s, as traders continue to digest Wednesday’s Fed policy announcement. &lt;br /&gt;
The Fed lifted interest rates by 25 bps as expected to 5.25-5.5%, their highest level in 22 years and left the door open to further interest rate hikes, depending on incoming economic data....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-hutao-paal-hoppy.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – HUTAO, $PAAL, HOPPY&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETH</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-hutao-paal-hoppy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120887/320357/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>BTC20 Rivals Pepe Coin and Bitcoin in Google Trends, Next Crypto to Explode – Raises $3.4m as Sellout Looms</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-rivals-pepe-coin-bitcoin-google-trends-next-crypto-explode-raises-34m-as-sellout-looms.htm</link><description>The next crypto to explode, BTC20, rivals Pepe coin and bitcoin in Google Trends search terms data, and for many geographies is outperforming both of them as it blasts past $3.4 million in its presale. &lt;br /&gt;
In only nine days, BTC20, which runs on the Ethereum blockchain as an ERC-20 token, has raised $3,412,753 million of its $6 million target. &lt;br /&gt;
Investors are excited about buying ‘Bitcoin on Ethereum’ at the original bitcoin’s 2011 price of just $1....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-rivals-pepe-coin-bitcoin-google-trends-next-crypto-explode-raises-34m-as-sellout-looms.htm"&gt;Read More: BTC20 Rivals Pepe Coin and Bitcoin in Google Trends, Next Crypto to Explode – Raises $3.4m as Sellout Looms&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/btc20-rivals-pepe-coin-bitcoin-google-trends-next-crypto-explode-raises-34m-as-sellout-looms.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120876/320345/btc20-beating-pepe-coin-o.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2240808"/></item><item><title>Web3 Utility Coin LPX Secures $1.2 Million for Trading Alpha – Can it Find the Next Pepe Coin?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-secures-12-million-for-trading-alpha-can-it-find-next-pepe-coin.htm</link><description>When it comes to crypto investments, the hope is obviously always that a coin's price will increase over time. This hope, particularly prevalent for meme coins, comes from an economic principle known as the "Castle in the Air Theory". The theory, introduced by economist John Maynard Keynes, suggests that investors build hypothetical scenarios for potential price increases rather than focusing on intrinsic values. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-secures-12-million-for-trading-alpha-can-it-find-next-pepe-coin.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 Utility Coin LPX Secures $1.2 Million for Trading Alpha – Can it Find the Next Pepe Coin?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Price Prediction Tool</category><category>Ai Prediction Platform</category><category>Crypto Startup</category><category>Launchpad Presale</category><category>Best Coin To Buy</category><category>Best Meme Coin</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-secures-12-million-for-trading-alpha-can-it-find-next-pepe-coin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120870/320325/mathieu-stern-1zo4o3z0uja.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="254077"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: BNB Chain Report Shows Web3 Growth Despite Bear Market, Beam Wallet Leveraging Optimism and Base Launches, Binance Withdraws its Crypto License Application in Germany</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bnb-chain-report-shows-web3-growth-despite-bear-market-beam-wallet-leveraging-optimism-and-base-launches-binance-withdraws-its-crypto-license-application-in-germany.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bnb-chain-report-shows-web3-growth-despite-bear-market-beam-wallet-leveraging-optimism-and-base-launches-binance-withdraws-its-crypto-license-application-in-germany.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: BNB Chain Report Shows Web3 Growth Despite Bear Market, Beam Wallet Leveraging Optimism and Base Launches, Binance Withdraws its Crypto License Application in Germany&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Smart Contract</category><category>BNB Chain</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Fantom</category><category>Avalanche</category><category>Arbitrum</category><category>Optimism</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Beam</category><category>Base</category><category>Binance</category><category>Germany</category><category>KuCoin</category><category>Japan</category><category>Canada</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Blackrock</category><category>India</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bnb-chain-report-shows-web3-growth-despite-bear-market-beam-wallet-leveraging-optimism-and-base-launches-binance-withdraws-its-crypto-license-application-in-germany.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120834/320320/adobestock-emre-akkoyun-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="284277"/></item><item><title>Singapore High Court Declares Cryptocurrency as Property that Can Be Held in Trust</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-high-court-declares-cryptocurrency-as-property-that-can-held-trust.htm</link><description>A recent ruling by Judge Philip Jeyaretnam of the High Court of Singapore surprised the crypto community, as the judge declared that digital currencies are not different than fiat money.  &lt;br /&gt;
The ruling took place on July 25th, and the judge decided that crypto is a form of property eligible for trust status....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-high-court-declares-cryptocurrency-as-property-that-can-held-trust.htm"&gt;Read More: Singapore High Court Declares Cryptocurrency as Property that Can Be Held in Trust&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-high-court-declares-cryptocurrency-as-property-that-can-held-trust.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120869/320323/singapore-high-court-decl.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="275549"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Dogecoin? DOGE Price Shoots Up 10% and AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Raises $3.1 Million in Funding</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-dogecoin-doge-price-shoots-up-10-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-31-million-funding.htm</link><description>As the meme coin vertical springs into life, Dogecoin (DOGE) has shot up an impressive +19%, to test topside resistance as the leading coin attempts a recovery rally. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes in the aftermath of a similarly dramatic pump by Pepecoin (PEPE), which also saw an inticing +17% push up in the past 48 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-dogecoin-doge-price-shoots-up-10-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-31-million-funding.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Dogecoin? DOGE Price Shoots Up 10% and AI Crypto Signals Platform yPredict Raises $3.1 Million in Funding&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-dogecoin-doge-price-shoots-up-10-ai-crypto-signals-platform-ypredict-raises-31-million-funding.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120840/320294/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="709706"/></item><item><title>RFK Jr. Admits Buying Bitcoin for His Children After Attending Miami Conference</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-admits-buying-bitcoin-for-his-children-after-attending-miami-conference.htm</link><description>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has revealed that he has purchased two Bitcoins (BTC) for each of his seven children. &lt;br /&gt;
During a Twitter Spaces conversation on Wednesday with Scott Melker, the host of The Wolf of All Street podcast, Kennedy revealed that he purchased the tokens in response to criticism he faced for promoting a "volatile commodity" without having any personal stake in it....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-admits-buying-bitcoin-for-his-children-after-attending-miami-conference.htm"&gt;Read More: RFK Jr. Admits Buying Bitcoin for His Children After Attending Miami Conference&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Kennedy</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rfk-jr-admits-buying-bitcoin-for-his-children-after-attending-miami-conference.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120863/320315/dt4ocbp5-ojtwbm3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="231741"/></item><item><title>Ripple, Solana, And Stellar-based Products Record Massive Institutional Investments As Market Rebounds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-solana-and-stellar-based-products-record-massive-institutional-investments-as-market-rebounds.htm</link><description>Institutional investments continue to flow into digital asset-related products in recent weeks following market-swinging wins recorded by Ripple (XRP) and other macroeconomic factors.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to new data from crypto analytics firms CCData, XRP, Solana (SOL), and Stellar (XLM) saw major inflows in most products alongside the market leader, Bitcoin (BTC). &lt;br /&gt;
XLM-based products spiked by 62.7% this month with a total of $17.3 million in assets under management (AUM). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-solana-and-stellar-based-products-record-massive-institutional-investments-as-market-rebounds.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple, Solana, And Stellar-based Products Record Massive Institutional Investments As Market Rebounds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>XLM</category><category>SOL</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Products</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-solana-and-stellar-based-products-record-massive-institutional-investments-as-market-rebounds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120850/320305/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="707175"/></item><item><title>Bank of Italy's Innovation Hub to Work with Polygon and Fireblocks on DeFi Project</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-italys-innovation-hub-work-with-polygon-fireblocks-defi-project.htm</link><description>The Bank of Italy announced a partnership with the Ethereum scaling team Polygon and crypto infrastructure provider Fireblocks to initiate a pilot program aimed at establishing a regulated platform for "institutional DeFi."  &lt;br /&gt;
This collaboration sets a landmark as it involves a G7 Central Bank, financial regulators, and associations of banks working together on a large-scale tokenized asset initiative. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-italys-innovation-hub-work-with-polygon-fireblocks-defi-project.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of Italy's Innovation Hub to Work with Polygon and Fireblocks on DeFi Project&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Italy</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-italys-innovation-hub-work-with-polygon-fireblocks-defi-project.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120848/320303/italy.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="121370"/></item><item><title>Spain's A&amp;G Launches New Crypto Fund Under Spanish Law with PwC Oversight</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/spains-ag-launches-new-crypto-fund-under-spanish-law-with-pwc-oversight.htm</link><description>Spanish private bank A&amp;G has launched Spain’s first locally regulated crypto hedge fund, the firm announced this week. &lt;br /&gt;
The crypto hedge fund has been registered under the name Criptomonedas, F.I.L., and will be overseen by Spain’s financial markets regulator, Comisión Nacional del Mercado de Valores (CNMV), the announcement said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spains-ag-launches-new-crypto-fund-under-spanish-law-with-pwc-oversight.htm"&gt;Read More: Spain's A&amp;G Launches New Crypto Fund Under Spanish Law with PwC Oversight&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Investment</category><category/><category>Spain</category><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/spains-ag-launches-new-crypto-fund-under-spanish-law-with-pwc-oversight.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120849/320302/spain-bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="499443"/></item></channel></rss>
