<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Humayun Sheikh, CEO of Fetch.ai, on AI, Machine Learning, Autonomous Agents, and Blockchains | Ep. 243</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/humayun-sheikh-ceo-of-fetchai-ai-machine-learning-autonomous-agents-blockchains-ep-243.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Humayun Sheikh, Founder and CEO of Fetch.ai, talks about building the infrastructure required for autonomous software agent, connecting smart agents to automate web3 systems, and the intersection of AI and Crypto....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/humayun-sheikh-ceo-of-fetchai-ai-machine-learning-autonomous-agents-blockchains-ep-243.htm"&gt;Read More: Humayun Sheikh, CEO of Fetch.ai, on AI, Machine Learning, Autonomous Agents, and Blockchains | Ep. 243&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/humayun-sheikh-ceo-of-fetchai-ai-machine-learning-autonomous-agents-blockchains-ep-243.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118407/315586/humayun-sheikh-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="124676"/></item><item><title>Binance's Commitment to Compliance: An Inside Look at the Program</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-commitment-compliance-an-inside-look-at-program.htm</link><description>Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, is making an effort to to dispel myths that the crypto industry at large is a ‘non-compliant’. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday blog post, the firm summarized the extent of Binance’s efforts to work together with international regulators, contrasting a persistent narrative that the exchange is deliberately shrouded in opacity to evade the law. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-commitment-compliance-an-inside-look-at-program.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance's Commitment to Compliance: An Inside Look at the Program&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-commitment-compliance-an-inside-look-at-program.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118406/315579/adobestock-286536391-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="128591"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Takes Hit As SEC Reportedly Brands ETF Filings 'Inadequate'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-takes-hit-as-sec-reportedly-brands-etf-filings-inadequate.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has raised concerns about recent applications for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs).  &lt;br /&gt;
The agency found that the applications, submitted by asset managers like BlackRock and Fidelity through exchanges Nasdaq and CBOE Global Markets, lacked clarity and completeness.  &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC has informed Nasdaq and CBOE about these inadequacies, but no official comments have been made by the parties involved....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-takes-hit-as-sec-reportedly-brands-etf-filings-inadequate.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Takes Hit As SEC Reportedly Brands ETF Filings 'Inadequate'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-takes-hit-as-sec-reportedly-brands-etf-filings-inadequate.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118405/315575/107019404-1645640859659-g.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="225330"/></item><item><title>Former Goldman Sachs Executive Craig Broderick Joins Stablecoin-Issuer Circle's Board</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-goldman-sachs-executive-craig-broderick-joins-stablecoin-issuer-circles-board.htm</link><description>The former Goldman Sachs executive Craig Broderick has joined the Board of Directors of Circle Internet Financial, the issuer of the USDC stablecoin.  &lt;br /&gt;
Broderick served as the chief risk officer at Goldman Sachs for over three decades.  &lt;br /&gt;
During his tenure at the investment bank, Broderick also served as co-chair of the "Firmwide Risk Committee along with other control-related committees."...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-goldman-sachs-executive-craig-broderick-joins-stablecoin-issuer-circles-board.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Goldman Sachs Executive Craig Broderick Joins Stablecoin-Issuer Circle's Board&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>USDC</category><category>Circle</category><category>Jeremy Allaire</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-goldman-sachs-executive-craig-broderick-joins-stablecoin-issuer-circles-board.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118399/315573/circle.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="78535"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin To Secure Second Quarterly Gain As Smaller Tokens Struggle</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-secure-second-quarterly-gain-as-smaller-tokens-struggle.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) continues to establish its dominance in the digital asset market as it records new gains in the wake of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) crackdown on altcoins.  &lt;br /&gt;
The largest asset by market capitalization has surged 86.31% year-to-date (YTD) to recover from a turbulent 2022 which saw over 55% wiped off its market cap. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-secure-second-quarterly-gain-as-smaller-tokens-struggle.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin To Secure Second Quarterly Gain As Smaller Tokens Struggle&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>SEC</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-secure-second-quarterly-gain-as-smaller-tokens-struggle.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118380/315506/bitcoin-gc1b77a1e5-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="267928"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Is Going to Zero as LUNC Plummets 10%, But Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Just Hit $5.6 Million – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-is-going-to-zero-as-lunc-plummets-10-but-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-just-hit-56-million-how-to-buy-early.htm</link><description>The crypto market's current valuation sits at a remarkable $1.19 trillion, indicating an increase of 1.75% in the last 24 hours.  &lt;br /&gt;
This surge points towards positive market conditions, with several altcoins experiencing price uptrends. &lt;br /&gt;
However, some assets like Terra Luna Classic ($LUNC) have been on a continuous decline, resulting in over 99.9% loss for early investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-is-going-to-zero-as-lunc-plummets-10-but-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-just-hit-56-million-how-to-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Is Going to Zero as LUNC Plummets 10%, But Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Just Hit $5.6 Million – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-is-going-to-zero-as-lunc-plummets-10-but-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-just-hit-56-million-how-to-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118387/315534/terra-luna.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1403771"/></item><item><title>Scaramucci Accuses Sam Bankman-Fried of 'Hurting' Crypto Industry in the U.S</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/scaramucci-accuses-sam-bankman-fried-of-hurting-crypto-industry-in-the-us.htm</link><description>Disgraced FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried “really hurt the industry in the United States from a regulatory perspective,” according to the venture investor and former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/scaramucci-accuses-sam-bankman-fried-of-hurting-crypto-industry-in-the-us.htm"&gt;Read More: Scaramucci Accuses Sam Bankman-Fried of 'Hurting' Crypto Industry in the U.S&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Anthony Scaramucci</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/scaramucci-accuses-sam-bankman-fried-of-hurting-crypto-industry-in-the-us.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118388/315529/anthony-scaramucci.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="449125"/></item><item><title>Rise in Salaries Paid in Bitcoin as Employees Opt for Crypto Amid Economic Uncertainty</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-salaries-paid-bitcoin-as-employees-opt-for-crypto-amid-economic-uncertainty.htm</link><description>Human Resources industry executives have noted that employees are willing to receive their salaries in Bitcoin (BTC), given the current hyperinflation and political conundrum in many regions worldwide. &lt;br /&gt;
Recent bank failures and volatility among fiat money are shifting people to opt for stablecoins like USD Coin (USDC), sources told Cointelegraph....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-salaries-paid-bitcoin-as-employees-opt-for-crypto-amid-economic-uncertainty.htm"&gt;Read More: Rise in Salaries Paid in Bitcoin as Employees Opt for Crypto Amid Economic Uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-salaries-paid-bitcoin-as-employees-opt-for-crypto-amid-economic-uncertainty.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118378/315494/pexels-david-mcbee-730547.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2358913"/></item><item><title>Canadian Lawmakers Call for National Blockchain Strategy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-lawmakers-call-for-national-blockchain-strategy.htm</link><description>Canada appears ready to take a strong step toward blockchain adoption, with an influential group of lawmakers requesting that the government comes up with a national blockchain strategy.  &lt;br /&gt;
Like the US, Canada lacks regulatory clarity in the crypto/blockchain market, which is putting the country at a disadvantage....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-lawmakers-call-for-national-blockchain-strategy.htm"&gt;Read More: Canadian Lawmakers Call for National Blockchain Strategy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/canadian-lawmakers-call-for-national-blockchain-strategy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118381/315502/canadian-lawmakers-call-f.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="161889"/></item><item><title>Web3 and Blockchain: Key Drivers of Gaming Innovation and Player Engagement</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-blockchain-key-drivers-of-gaming-innovation-player-engagement.htm</link><description>The gaming industry has seen massive progress over the last few decades. However, with blockchain technology around, the gaming world has a chance to expand into a new GameFi sector and innovate.  &lt;br /&gt;
The advantages of blockchain elements in games could also boost engagement and adoption, where blockchain users could become new gamers, and existing gamers could become blockchain users....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-blockchain-key-drivers-of-gaming-innovation-player-engagement.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 and Blockchain: Key Drivers of Gaming Innovation and Player Engagement&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-blockchain-key-drivers-of-gaming-innovation-player-engagement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118383/315509/web3-and-blockchain-key-d.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="234926"/></item><item><title>Sam Altman's Worldcoin Debuts in Germany, Incorporates Okta for Enhanced Identity Management</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-worldcoin-debuts-germany-incorporates-okta-for-enhanced-identity-management.htm</link><description>Sam Altman’s Worldcoin is integrating with one of the world’s largest identity management platforms and is launching a new identity protocol in Germany. &lt;br /&gt;
This is according to the company’s press release, shared with Cryptonews earlier this week. As per the anouncement, Worldcoin has now integrated with Okta and is launching World ID, the project’s identity protocol....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-worldcoin-debuts-germany-incorporates-okta-for-enhanced-identity-management.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Altman's Worldcoin Debuts in Germany, Incorporates Okta for Enhanced Identity Management&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Germany</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>Identity</category><category>Privacy</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-worldcoin-debuts-germany-incorporates-okta-for-enhanced-identity-management.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118364/315468/world-media-library-origi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="298124"/></item><item><title>Bobo Coin Rallies Up 3,000% on Dextools but All Attention is on Wall Street Memes as the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>The price of Bobo Coin (BOBO) has risen by over 200% in the past 24 hours, with its jump to $0.000000050417 representing a massive 3,000% growth since it first listed on Uniswap a couple of months ago. &lt;br /&gt;
This makes BOBO the latest in a growing list of meme tokens to have comfortably outperformed the market at times this year, although it remains about 23% down from its all-time high of $0.000000065803, which was recorded in early May....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Bobo Coin Rallies Up 3,000% on Dextools but All Attention is on Wall Street Memes as the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118363/315482/bobo-coin-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="657826"/></item><item><title>Coinbase’s Ethereum Layer-2 Network, Base, Nears Mainnet Launch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm</link><description>Coinbase’s layer 2 blockchain, Base, is preparing its mainnet launch after completing a series of security audits.  &lt;br /&gt;
Base aims to attract as much as one million new crypto users in the next few years, Coinbase said in a press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
Built on the OP stack in partnership with Optimism, Base’s code was scrutinized by over 100 people as a part of an audit contest launched by Coinbase. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase’s Ethereum Layer-2 Network, Base, Nears Mainnet Launch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Base</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118365/315487/coinbase.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115622"/></item><item><title>Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools –  WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0, OSLAI – 1,000x Potential?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm</link><description>Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools is the place to look for smart profitable trades, and WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0 and OSLAI are the latest tokens leading the charge for outsized profits. &lt;br /&gt;
The latest micro trend in crypto, which threatens to become a mega trend is the 2.0 meta, primarily for now in the meme coin arena, but likely to be spreading fast from there.  &lt;br /&gt;
Even the most mildly successful of the 2.0-themed coins have the potential to deliver quick 1,000x gains....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools –  WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0, OSLAI – 1,000x Potential?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118356/315476/wojak2-0-usd-uni-dextools.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="534221"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Blasts Up 10% but Crypto Whales are Accumulating Another Coin Instead – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>The price of Solana (SOL) has risen by more than 10% in the past 24 hours, surging to $18.89 after the launch of deBridge, a protocol enabling cross-chain transfers between Solana and Ethereum-compatible networks. &lt;br /&gt;
The bridge's launch has already been a big boost to SOL, which is now also up by 27% in the past two weeks, while remaining down by 9% in the last 30 days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Blasts Up 10% but Crypto Whales are Accumulating Another Coin Instead – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118357/315462/is-it-too-late-to-buy-sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1315347"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Up 2% in 24 Hours – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</link><description>The XRP price has risen by 2% in the past 24 hours, reaching $0.476333 as the wider cryptocurrency market gains by the same percentage today. &lt;br /&gt;
Today's increase goes part of the way towards compensating XRP holders for recent losses, yet the altcoin remains 3% down in the last seven days and 6.5% down in the last 30, although it has risen by 40% since the beginning of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Up 2% in 24 Hours – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118346/315455/xrp-price-up-2-in-24-hour.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1425165"/></item><item><title>Chinese Firms Using Digital Yuan to Pay Electricity Bills</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm</link><description>Energy providers in China are adding digital yuan payment options, allowing companies and individuals to settle their bills in the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per the news outlet Dizo, the city of Suzhou’s Xiangcheng District’s drainage and sanitation companies recently used the digital yuan to settle a power bill of around $83,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Adoption efforts are being spearheaded by the State Grid Corporation of China (SGCC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Firms Using Digital Yuan to Pay Electricity Bills&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118317/315403/china-2906-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="674671"/></item><item><title>China Looks to Add Digital Yuan Functionality to Social Security Cards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm</link><description>China may add digital yuan functionality to government-issued social security cards, in a possible new breakthrough for the central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per the 21st Century Business Herald (via NBD), the Ministry of Human Resources and Social Security wants to “explore and promote” ways to “add digital yuan payment functions” to social security cards. &lt;br /&gt;
Existing plastic social security cards already have smartcard functionality, with bank card-like chips....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm"&gt;Read More: China Looks to Add Digital Yuan Functionality to Social Security Cards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118266/315315/china-2906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="618381"/></item><item><title>Cryptos On Coinbase Fall Outside SEC Jurisdiction, Says Exchange In Response To Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Coinbase, the largest U.S.-based digital asset exchange, has fired back at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a court filing, stating that the regulator lacks the jurisdiction to institute an enforcement action against the exchange. &lt;br /&gt;
Both the SEC and Coinbase are bracing themselves for a lengthy legal battle with the securities watchdog claiming in a June complaint that the exchange listed unregistered securities on its platform. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Cryptos On Coinbase Fall Outside SEC Jurisdiction, Says Exchange In Response To Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Altcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118272/315396/gavel-g32a3c70ac-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="157683"/></item><item><title>Ex-Trader Ackerman Ordered to Pay $54 Million Fine for Crypto Fraud</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm</link><description>The former New York Stock Exchange broker Micahel Ackerman has been ordered to pay $54 million in penalties by a federal court for running a crypto fraud, as per a release from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). &lt;br /&gt;
A judge at the Southern District of New York court has banned Ackerman from trading in any markets supervised by the financial watchdog, CFTC revealed. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm"&gt;Read More: Ex-Trader Ackerman Ordered to Pay $54 Million Fine for Crypto Fraud&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Crypto Scam</category><category>Michael Ackerman</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118320/315421/michael-ackerman-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="102801"/></item></channel></rss>
