<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bobo Coin Rallies Up 3,000% on Dextools but All Attention is on Wall Street Memes as the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>The price of Bobo Coin (BOBO) has risen by over 200% in the past 24 hours, with its jump to $0.000000050417 representing a massive 3,000% since it first listed on Uniswap a couple of months ago. &lt;br /&gt;
This makes BOBO the latest in a growing list of meme tokens to have comfortably outperformed the market at times this year, although it remains about 23% down from its all-time high of $0.000000065803, which was recorded in early May....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Bobo Coin Rallies Up 3,000% on Dextools but All Attention is on Wall Street Memes as the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000-dextools-but-all-attention-wall-street-memes-as-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118363/315490/bobo-coin-rallies-up-3000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="171597"/></item><item><title>Coinbase’s Ethereum Layer-2 Network, Base, Nears Mainnet Launch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm</link><description>Coinbase’s layer 2 blockchain, Base, is preparing its mainnet launch after completing a series of security audits.  &lt;br /&gt;
Base aims to attract as much as one million new crypto users in the next few years, Coinbase said in a press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
Built on the OP stack in partnership with Optimism, Base’s code was scrutinized by over 100 people as a part of an audit contest launched by Coinbase. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase’s Ethereum Layer-2 Network, Base, Nears Mainnet Launch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Base</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-ethereum-layer-2-network-base-nears-mainnet-launch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118365/315487/coinbase.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="115622"/></item><item><title>Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools –  WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0, OSLAI – 1,000x Potential?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm</link><description>Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools is the place to look for smart profitable trades, and WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0 and OSLAI are the latest tokens leading the charge for outsized profits. &lt;br /&gt;
The latest micro trend in crypto, which threatens to become a mega trend is the 2.0 meta, primarily for now in the meme coin arena, but likely to be spreading fast from there.  &lt;br /&gt;
Even the most mildly successful of the 2.0-themed coins have the potential to deliver quick 1,000x gains....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Crypto Gainers on DexTools –  WOJAK2.0, PEPE2.0, OSLAI – 1,000x Potential?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers-dextools-wojak20-pepe20-oslai-1000x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118356/315476/wojak2-0-usd-uni-dextools.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="534221"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Blasts Up 10% but Crypto Whales are Accumulating Another Coin Instead – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</link><description>The price of Solana (SOL) has risen by more than 10% in the past 24 hours, surging to $18.89 after the launch of deBridge, a protocol enabling cross-chain transfers between Solana and Ethereum-compatible networks. &lt;br /&gt;
The bridge's launch has already been a big boost to SOL, which is now also up by 27% in the past two weeks, while remaining down by 9% in the last 30 days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Solana? SOL Price Blasts Up 10% but Crypto Whales are Accumulating Another Coin Instead – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-solana-sol-price-blasts-up-10-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-another-coin-instead-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118357/315462/is-it-too-late-to-buy-sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1315347"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Up 2% in 24 Hours – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</link><description>The XRP price has risen by 2% in the past 24 hours, reaching $0.476333 as the wider cryptocurrency market gains by the same percentage today. &lt;br /&gt;
Today's increase goes part of the way towards compensating XRP holders for recent losses, yet the altcoin remains 3% down in the last seven days and 6.5% down in the last 30, although it has risen by 40% since the beginning of the year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Up 2% in 24 Hours – Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-up-2-24-hours-can-xrp-reach-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118346/315455/xrp-price-up-2-in-24-hour.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1425165"/></item><item><title>Chinese Firms Using Digital Yuan to Pay Electricity Bills</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm</link><description>Energy providers in China are adding digital yuan payment options, allowing companies and individuals to settle their bills in the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per the news outlet Dizo, the city of Suzhou’s Xiangcheng District’s drainage and sanitation companies recently used the digital yuan to settle a power bill of around $83,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Adoption efforts are being spearheaded by the State Grid Corporation of China (SGCC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Firms Using Digital Yuan to Pay Electricity Bills&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-firms-using-digital-yuan-pay-electricity-bills.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118317/315403/china-2906-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="674671"/></item><item><title>China Looks to Add Digital Yuan Functionality to Social Security Cards</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm</link><description>China may add digital yuan functionality to government-issued social security cards, in a possible new breakthrough for the central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per the 21st Century Business Herald (via NBD), the Ministry of Human Resources and Social Security wants to “explore and promote” ways to “add digital yuan payment functions” to social security cards. &lt;br /&gt;
Existing plastic social security cards already have smartcard functionality, with bank card-like chips....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm"&gt;Read More: China Looks to Add Digital Yuan Functionality to Social Security Cards&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/china-looks-add-digital-yuan-functionality-social-security-cards.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118266/315315/china-2906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="618381"/></item><item><title>Cryptos On Coinbase Fall Outside SEC Jurisdiction, Says Exchange In Response To Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Coinbase, the largest U.S.-based digital asset exchange, has fired back at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a court filing, stating that the regulator lacks the jurisdiction to institute an enforcement action against the exchange. &lt;br /&gt;
Both the SEC and Coinbase are bracing themselves for a lengthy legal battle with the securities watchdog claiming in a June complaint that the exchange listed unregistered securities on its platform. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Cryptos On Coinbase Fall Outside SEC Jurisdiction, Says Exchange In Response To Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Altcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cryptos-coinbase-fall-outside-sec-jurisdiction-says-exchange-response-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118272/315396/gavel-g32a3c70ac-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="157683"/></item><item><title>Ex-Trader Ackerman Ordered to Pay $54 Million Fine for Crypto Fraud</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm</link><description>The former New York Stock Exchange broker Micahel Ackerman has been ordered to pay $54 million in penalties by a federal court for running a crypto fraud, as per a release from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). &lt;br /&gt;
A judge at the Southern District of New York court has banned Ackerman from trading in any markets supervised by the financial watchdog, CFTC revealed. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm"&gt;Read More: Ex-Trader Ackerman Ordered to Pay $54 Million Fine for Crypto Fraud&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Crypto Scam</category><category>Michael Ackerman</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ex-trader-ackerman-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-for-crypto-fraud.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118320/315421/michael-ackerman-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="102801"/></item><item><title>Cathie Wood’s ARK Adds Surveillance-Sharing Agreement to Bitcoin ETF Application</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-adds-surveillance-sharing-agreement-to-bitcoin-etf-application.htm</link><description>Cathie Wood's investment management firm, ARK Invest, is on the growing list of US-based firms that filed for spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) approval with the SEC.   &lt;br /&gt;
The investment manager, alongside crypto asset manager 21Shares, filed an amended spot BTC ETF proposal and added a surveillance sharing agreement. &lt;br /&gt;
This amendment followed almost two weeks after BlackRock's spot Bitcoin ETF filing that generated a loud buzz within the crypto ecosystem....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-adds-surveillance-sharing-agreement-to-bitcoin-etf-application.htm"&gt;Read More: Cathie Wood’s ARK Adds Surveillance-Sharing Agreement to Bitcoin ETF Application&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cathie-woods-ark-adds-surveillance-sharing-agreement-to-bitcoin-etf-application.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118321/315420/shutterstock-1386484187.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="757472"/></item><item><title>Insider Trading Rampant in Crypto Market, According to Ex-Goldman Technologists</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/insider-trading-rampant-in-crypto-market-according-to-ex-goldman-technologists.htm</link><description>Insider trading is rampant before new ERC-20 tokens are listed on centralized exchanges (CEXs), according to blockchain intelligence firm Solidus Labs. &lt;br /&gt;
In a report published on Wednesday, Solidus Labs said it found suspicious transactions ahead of major CEX listings of ERC-20 tokens in 56% of cases by looking at data going back to January of 2021. &lt;br /&gt;
ERC-20 tokens are the most commonly created types of tokens, and are built on the Ethereum blockchain....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/insider-trading-rampant-in-crypto-market-according-to-ex-goldman-technologists.htm"&gt;Read More: Insider Trading Rampant in Crypto Market, According to Ex-Goldman Technologists&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/insider-trading-rampant-in-crypto-market-according-to-ex-goldman-technologists.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118305/315383/insider-trading.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="296828"/></item><item><title>Ledger Hardware Wallet Firm Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network with Major Crypto Partners</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-firm-launches-institutional-grade-trading-network-with-major-crypto-partners.htm</link><description>French hardware wallet maker Ledger has ventured into the institutional trading technology market with the launch of the custodial trading platform Ledger Enterprise TRADELINK. &lt;br /&gt;
This new platform aims to revolutionize custodial trading by providing an open network that enables seamless trading through partnerships with major crypto exchanges, custodians, and platform providers, an announcement from Ledger on Wednesday said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-firm-launches-institutional-grade-trading-network-with-major-crypto-partners.htm"&gt;Read More: Ledger Hardware Wallet Firm Launches Institutional-Grade Trading Network with Major Crypto Partners&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ledger</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ledger-hardware-wallet-firm-launches-institutional-grade-trading-network-with-major-crypto-partners.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118298/315372/ledger.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="106389"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces Back Above $30,000 Resistance – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-back-above-30000-resistance-time-buy.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) saw a second strong bounce from support in the $30,000 area late on Wednesday, with the bulls remaining in control for now. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization was last trading around $30,500, within this week’s ranges as support in the form of the late-April/early May highs in the $30,000 continues to hold firm. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin is on the cusp of closing out a strong month, with June’s gains currently standing around 12%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-back-above-30000-resistance-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Bounces Back Above $30,000 Resistance – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-bounces-back-above-30000-resistance-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118309/315387/btc-3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="153373"/></item><item><title>Slovakia Significantly Lowers Crypto Tax Rates Amid Digital Euro Fears</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/slovakia-significantly-lowers-crypto-tax-rates-amid-digital-euro-plans.htm</link><description>The deputies of Slovakia's National Council, the country's legislative body, voted on June 28 to endorse an amendment that will reduce the taxation of cryptocurrencies in the country. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the approval, the personal income tax for profits made from the sale of cryptocurrencies, held by the user for at least one year, will be lowered to 7%. The current taxation sliding scale for digital assets is either 19% or 25%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/slovakia-significantly-lowers-crypto-tax-rates-amid-digital-euro-plans.htm"&gt;Read More: Slovakia Significantly Lowers Crypto Tax Rates Amid Digital Euro Fears&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/slovakia-significantly-lowers-crypto-tax-rates-amid-digital-euro-plans.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118292/315366/pexels-nataliya-vaitkevic.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="5505438"/></item><item><title>Binance's Powerful Co-founder Yi He Breaks Silence Amidst Regulatory Turmoil</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-powerful-co-founder-yi-he-breaks-silence-amidst-regulatory-turmoil.htm</link><description>Despite a long history spent away from the public spotlight, Binance co-founder and senior executive Yi He is finally speaking up as two of the United States’ chief market regulators sue her company. &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview with Bloomberg last month in Dubai, she argued that Binance is a greater ally to regulatory compliance than virtually any other company in the global crypto industry. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-powerful-co-founder-yi-he-breaks-silence-amidst-regulatory-turmoil.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance's Powerful Co-founder Yi He Breaks Silence Amidst Regulatory Turmoil&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binances-powerful-co-founder-yi-he-breaks-silence-amidst-regulatory-turmoil.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118293/315367/adobestock-286537788-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="78035"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 29 June – BitDAO, Stellar, Bitcoin SV</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-29-june-bitdao-stellar-bitcoin-sv.htm</link><description>  &lt;br /&gt;
Broader cryptocurrency markets are a little higher on Thursday, but remain stuck within recent ranges, with Bitcoin (BTC) just above $30,000 and Ether (ETH) in the mid-$1,800s. &lt;br /&gt;
Markets continue to balance optimism about potential upcoming spot bitcoin ETFs, which helped spur a recent recovery in sentiment, against macro headwinds. &lt;br /&gt;
These include strong US data which continue to bolster Fed tightening bets, which is keeping the US dollar and US yields underpinned....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-29-june-bitdao-stellar-bitcoin-sv.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 29 June – BitDAO, Stellar, Bitcoin SV&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>BitDAO</category><category>BITD</category><category>Stellar</category><category>XLM</category><category>Bitcoin SV</category><category>Bsv</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-29-june-bitdao-stellar-bitcoin-sv.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118291/315360/best-crypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="333587"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Germany's Financial Watchdog Reportedly Decides Against Granting Binance a Custody License, Binance to Lose Support of Its Euro Banking Partner, Slovakia Reduces Crypto Taxes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-germanys-financial-watchdog-reportedly-decides-against-granting-binance-a-custody-license-binance-to-lose-support-of-its-euro-banking-partner-slovakia-reduces-crypto-taxes.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-germanys-financial-watchdog-reportedly-decides-against-granting-binance-a-custody-license-binance-to-lose-support-of-its-euro-banking-partner-slovakia-reduces-crypto-taxes.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Germany's Financial Watchdog Reportedly Decides Against Granting Binance a Custody License, Binance to Lose Support of Its Euro Banking Partner, Slovakia Reduces Crypto Taxes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Germany</category><category>Binance</category><category>Europe</category><category>Euro</category><category>Regulation</category><category>ECB</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Shina</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>Slovakia</category><category>Tax</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>OpenAI</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Tokenization</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-germanys-financial-watchdog-reportedly-decides-against-granting-binance-a-custody-license-binance-to-lose-support-of-its-euro-banking-partner-slovakia-reduces-crypto-taxes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118252/315346/adobestock-sergio-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="249448"/></item><item><title>Is Shiba Inu Price Dead? SHIB 2.0 Shitcoin Pumps Instead and These 2 Meme Coins Could Be Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-dead-shib-20-shitcoin-pumps-instead-these-2-meme-coins-could-next.htm</link><description>Is the Shiba Inu price dead? $SHIB is down 5.4% as its selloff of recent weeks continues. Meanwhile, new coin SHIB 2.0 is pumping 1,635% in the past 24 hours and attracting all the excitement, plus two other newcomers. &lt;br /&gt;
Launched at 11:30pm UT yesterday, SHIB 2.0 token has already reached a high of $0.001071, although it has since lost a zero to trade at $0.0002919. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-dead-shib-20-shitcoin-pumps-instead-these-2-meme-coins-could-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Shiba Inu Price Dead? SHIB 2.0 Shitcoin Pumps Instead and These 2 Meme Coins Could Be Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-dead-shib-20-shitcoin-pumps-instead-these-2-meme-coins-could-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118278/315352/shib2-0-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="655268"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Becomes Best Performer of the Week While Web3 Trading Alpha Platform LPX Raises $1,000,000</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-becomes-best-performer-of-week-while-web3-trading-alpha-platform-lpx-raises-1000000.htm</link><description>An intense price melt-up in Bitcoin Cash (BCH) that started just over a week ago has continued on Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;
BCHUSD was last changing hands to the north of $240 per token, up 120% versus its opening levels from last Wednesday around $110, having gained another 7% on the day....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-becomes-best-performer-of-week-while-web3-trading-alpha-platform-lpx-raises-1000000.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Becomes Best Performer of the Week While Web3 Trading Alpha Platform LPX Raises $1,000,000&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Bitcoin Cash</category><category>BCH</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-bitcoin-cash-bch-becomes-best-performer-of-week-while-web3-trading-alpha-platform-lpx-raises-1000000.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118288/315357/bch-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="702811"/></item><item><title>PwC Forecasts Smart Contracts as Future Replacement for Traditional Contracts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/pwc-forecasts-smart-contracts-as-future-replacement-for-traditional-contracts.htm</link><description>The use of smart contracts in the financial industry is increasing, and they are expected to become the standard in the long term, according to a study by PwC. &lt;br /&gt;
The study found that 52% of IT decision-makers in the financial sector plan to introduce smart contracts in the near future. &lt;br /&gt;
Over a third of respondents expect smart contracts to replace traditional financial transactions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/pwc-forecasts-smart-contracts-as-future-replacement-for-traditional-contracts.htm"&gt;Read More: PwC Forecasts Smart Contracts as Future Replacement for Traditional Contracts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/pwc-forecasts-smart-contracts-as-future-replacement-for-traditional-contracts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118286/315351/blockchain-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="226291"/></item></channel></rss>
