<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 22:17:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitfarms CEO Emiliano Grodzki Resigns Amid Industry Struggles</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitfarms-ceo-emiliano-grodzki-resigns-amid-industry-struggles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230876</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitfarms_Quit.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitfarms_Quit.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The mining firm has named president and COO Geoffrey Morphy as its new chief executive officer.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Emiliano Grodzki has stepped down as CEO of leading Bitcoin mining firm Bitfarms, joining a long list of crypto executives who resigned from their positions amid the bear market this year.</p>
<p class="p2">The mining company <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/12/29/2580596/0/en/Bitfarms-Promotes-Geoffrey-Morphy-to-Chief-Executive-Officer.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">named</a> Geoffrey Morphy as its new CEO, promoting him from his role as president and chief operating officer (COO).</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;Our foundational work over the last years built the strength and depth of skills we needed to navigate external factors. I&#8217;m even more optimistic today about Bitfarms&#8217; long-term prospects than when I joined the company back in 2020.&#8221; &#8211; Morphy said.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Grodzki to Remain as Board Director </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Grodzki and his partner Nicolas Bonta co-founded Bitfarms in Canada in 2017. Although Grodzki will no longer function as CEO, he will remain in the company as a Director on the Board.</p>
<p class="p2">Bonta will also function as the company&#8217;s new Chairman of the Board of Directors, moving from the position of Executive Chairman.</p>
<p class="p2">Commenting on Morphy&#8217;s new position, Bonta noted that the new CEO had played a significant role in developing the firm&#8217;s management team, corporate structure, governance and control, investor relations, and operations and strategy since he joined Bitfarm two years ago.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;In a little over two years, Geoff helped transform Bitfarms from a purely Canadian company trading on the TSX Venture Exchange with five farms in Quebec to an international powerhouse traded on both the Nasdaq and TSX with ten operating farms in four countries driving over 4.4 exahash/second (EH/s) today. I am proud to announce Geoff as Bitfarms&#8217; new CEO and am confident his expanded leadership will continue to bring success to Bitfarms in the coming years,&#8221; he added.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Crypto Mining Firms Struggle </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, Bitfarms&#8217; leadership change comes as many executives are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-crypto-executives-have-stepped-down-since-the-market-crash-in-may/" data-wpel-link="internal">stepping down</a> from their roles due to an intensifying bear market that has forced several top crypto firms, including miners, into financial issues and even bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">Last week, Bitcoin mining giant Core Scientific <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">became</a> the first publicly-traded crypto firm to declare insolvency despite receiving a $72 million loan offer from one of its creditors to avoid bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">In September, crypto mining infrastructure Compute North filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in the United States, with the firm owning at least $500 million to at least 200 creditors.</p>
<p class="p1">Bitfarms has also had its fair share of financial struggles this year. In June, the miner <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-mining-giant-bitfarms-sells-3000-btc-and-adjusts-its-hodl-strategy/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold</a> almost half of its bitcoin stash to improve its liquidity. The company repaid $27 million of its debt last month to strengthen its balance sheet.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitfarms-ceo-emiliano-grodzki-resigns-amid-industry-struggles/" rel="nofollow">Bitfarms CEO Emiliano Grodzki Resigns Amid Industry Struggles</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did SBF Just Cash Out $684K?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/did-sbf-just-cash-out-684k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 22:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231052</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The FTX boss allegedly withdrew the funds via a non-KYC platform and Ren Protocol despite court restrictions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the disgraced founder and former CEO of bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX, has reportedly cashed out $684,000 worth of crypto assets despite court restrictions on spendings above $1,000.</p>
<p class="p2">On-chain DeFi analyst BowTiedIguana took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/BowTiedIguana/status/1608653434387050496" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">unravel</span></a> the location where SBF transferred the funds.</p>
<h2>Following the Money Trail</h2>
<p class="p2">After Bankman-Fried’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">$250 million bail</span></a> last week, the FTX boss sent all the ether (ETH) in his public wallet to a<a href="https://etherscan.io/txs?a=0x7386df2Cf7e9776bCE0708072c27d6a7135D51CB&amp;p=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1"> new wallet address</span></a> – 0x7386df2Cf7e9776bCE0708072c27d6a7135D51CB.</p>
<p class="p2">Some hours later, $367,000 worth of cryptocurrencies were transferred from 32 addresses owned by SBF’s trading firm Alameda Research to the same wallet.</p>
<p class="p2">The address received another $322,000 from other wallets, bringing the total assets to roughly $689,000.</p>
<p class="p2">The wallet address, 0x7386, then sent $629,000 worth of tokens from its entire holding into<span class="s1"> another <a href="https://etherscan.io/txs?a=0x64e9B9cD74A46f71e7631CB033afA6E7849a8683" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wallet address</a></span> – 0x64e9B9cD74A46f71e7631CB033afA6E7849a8683.</p>
<p class="p2">Eleven wallet addresses labeled as Alameda-owned accounts sent a total of $1 million into the same wallet address, 0x64e9. Five transactions of less than 51 ETH were then conducted, as they were sent to a freshly created wallet address.</p>
<h2>Funds Transferred to Seychelles Exchange</h2>
<p class="p2">The funds were then transferred to a Seychelles-based crypto exchange that does not conduct Know-Your-Customer (KYC) activity for users.</p>
<p class="p2">Parts of the funds were also moved through the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ren-protocol-users-face-potential-losses-during-post-alameda-wind-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ren protocol</a> and subsequently to the Bitcoin network. The Ren protocol is a gateway that allows anyone to send BTC, ZEC, and BCH across blockchains. Alameda acquired the platform in February 2021.</p>
<p class="p2">Three sets of 200,000 USDT were also transferred to FixedFloat, a self-custodian crypto exchange that facilitates transactions through its Lightning Network.</p>
<p class="p2">It is still unclear if SBF was truly behind the withdrawals, but it is only a matter of time before U.S. attorneys begin to probe the transactions.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bahamian Regulators Seize $3.5B From FTX</h2>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, the Bahamas authorities have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-seized-3-5-billion-from-ftx-to-keep-them-from-vanishing/" data-wpel-link="internal">confiscated</a> $3.5 billion worth of assets belonging to FTX Digital Markets, the Bahamian subdivision of the bankrupt crypto exchange, to prevent the funds from vanishing.</p>
<p class="p2">According to regulators, the funds will be returned to investors at the court’s discretion.<span class="Apple-converted-space"> </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-sbf-just-cash-out-684k/" rel="nofollow">Did SBF Just Cash Out $684K?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>VP of Bithumb-Linked Company Found Dead in Seoul: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vp-of-bithumb-linked-company-found-dead-in-seoul-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231009</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Initial report suggests the exec may have died by suicide. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Vice President of Vidente, referred to as Mr. Park, was found dead in front of his house in southern Seoul.</p>
<p>Vidente happens to be the largest shareholder of Bithumb Holdings Co., the firm behind the South Korean crypto exchange Bithumb.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to local news <a href="https://news.mt.co.kr/mtview.php?no=2022123011073638881" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>, Park was under investigation on charges of embezzlement and manipulation of stock price. The exec was also rumored to have been overseeing accounting for Kang Ji-Yeon and her brother Kang Jong-Hyun when he was serving as the Vice President of Vidente.</li>
<li>For context, Ji-Yeon is the head of the kiosk supplier Inbiogen, which holds the largest share in Vidente and the duo was also under investigation.</li>
<li>Suspicions surrounding the Kang siblings framing Park for the wrongdoings have also emerged following his mysterious death.</li>
<li>Authorities are currently investigating several top executives of Inbiogen, a KOSDAQ-listed company.</li>
<li>Vidente <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-owner-confirms-acquisition-discussions-with-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> discussing a potential sale of its stakes in Bithumb Korea and Bithumb Holdings to the now-defunct FTX earlier this summer.</li>
<li>The former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried was reportedly in advanced talks to buy the South Korean crypto exchange.</li>
<li>Bithumb is part of the country&#8217;s largest crypto exchange group &#8211; DAXA &#8211; which made it fitting for FTX to approach considering its plans to enter the Korean digital asset market.</li>
<li>A regulatory filing shows that Vidente owns 34.2% of Bithumb Holdings and 10.22% of Bithumb Korea as of March 31.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vp-of-bithumb-linked-company-found-dead-in-seoul-report/" rel="nofollow">VP of Bithumb-Linked Company Found Dead in Seoul: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Comments on Solana&#8217;s Future</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-comments-on-solanas-future/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 18:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231001</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Vitalik_Buterin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Buterin believes Solana still has intrinsic value and can recover from its current predicament.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Last month, the Solana ecosystem was at the forefront of the FTX saga, taking a significant hit from the company&#8217;s bankruptcy filing. Since then, projects have left the network, while the native token lost a significant chunk of its USD value.</p>
<p class="p2">Interestingly, the blockchain, once regarded as an &#8220;Ethereum Killer,&#8221; has received support from Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin.</p>
<p class="p2">In a Twitter post on December 29, Buterin said the recent events in the crypto industry had washed away bad actors from the ecosystem, adding that Solana now has a greater chance of thriving in the future.</p>
<h2>FTX Bankruptcy Hits Solana Blockchain</h2>
<p class="p2">Solana, which describes itself as the most scalable protocol in the industry, was among the long list of firms with <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-foundation-lost-over-180-million-in-crypto-on-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">significant exposure</a> to FTX due to its strong ties with the exchange and its sister trading firm Alameda Research.</p>
<p class="p2">The network&#8217;s native token, SOL, was one of the altcoins held by FTX&#8217;s founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) and Alameda Research, which was then headed by Caroline Allison before the sudden collapse.</p>
<p class="p2">According to a leaked financial report with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Alameda held approximately $1.2 billion in SOL.</p>
<p class="p2">The crypto asset quickly took a hit following the news of the FTX bankruptcy on November 11. SOL <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dips-below-16-5k-solana-down-23-weekly-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">declined</span></a> from $22 to $14 the same month before dropping to as low as $8 yesterday. The token now has a market capitalization of $3.5 billion, ranking as the 17th largest crypto asset according to CoinMarketCap.</p>
<h2 class="p1">Buterin Believes Solana Protocol Still Has Intrinsic Value</h2>
<p class="p2">Despite the challenges in the Solana ecosystem, Buterin believes the protocol still has intrinsic value and can recover from its current state.</p>
<p class="p2">The Ethereum co-founder disclosed that while it is difficult for him to assess the platform from the outside, he believes Solana has a strong team backing the project.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Some smart people tell me there is an earnest smart developer community in Solana, and now that the awful opportunistic money people have been washed out, the chain has a bright future.</p>
<p>Hard for me to tell from outside, but I hope the community gets its fair chance to thrive<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9be.png" alt="🦾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9be.png" alt="🦾" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) <a href="https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin/status/1608591727316684804?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">December 29, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>SOL to Bounce Back?</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Like Buterin, Solana&#8217;s co-founder and COO Raj Gokal <a href="https://twitter.com/rajgokal/status/1590359525521264640" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> in an earlier tweet that the crucible moment for the protocol would pass. He noted that the project&#8217;s recent challenges are as complex as the previous ones. However, Solana now has a large and dedicated team to combat the current predicament.</p>
<p class="p2">While it is unclear how the team plans to revive the project, a Twitter user <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoApe0/status/1608578291560218625?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1608578291560218625%7Ctwgr%5E0a15e13185c875b169c5992de613ec4b1ff19011%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coindesk.com%2Fmarkets%2F2022%2F12%2F30%2Fsolana-token-rebounds-off-thursday-lows-as-buterin-tweets-support%2F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">claimed</span></a> that the comeback would be similar to Ethereum&#8217;s recovery in 2018.</p>
<p class="p2">Last month, Solana Labs CEO Anatoly Yakovenko <a href="https://twitter.com/aeyakovenko/status/1590369260727341057" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noted</a> that the project learned the hard way in the 2018 bear market and now maintains reserves to support its new burn rate for approximately 30 months<span class="s1">.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-comments-on-solanas-future/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum’s Vitalik Buterin Comments on Solana&#8217;s Future</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Buys More BTC, FTX Revelations and More Contagion: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-ftx-revelations-and-more-contagion-this-weeks-crypto-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231044</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Bears.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Bears.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FTX contagion goes on, and Bitcoin's price continues trading in a range while MicroStrategy buys more of it.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The last week of 2022 ends with a bang but not in terms of price action, which remains as dull as possible. However, it was marked by multiple events, so let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<p>First things first, Michael Saylor&#8217;s MicroStrategy seems far from being done with buying BTC. The company revealed another purchase of more than 2,000 bitcoins, bringing its total to more than 132K. It&#8217;s also worth noting, though, that the company also sold around 700 BTC for the first time ever &#8211; for tax purposes.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also interesting to note that the company revealed that it plans to introduce Bitcoin lightning Network applications during the following year.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, revelations in the case against FTX, Alameda, and its executives (in the face of SBF, Caroline Ellison, and Gary Wang) continue with full force. This week, it became clear that Bankman-Fried used a loan from Alameda to buy his shares in the popular retail-oriented trading platform Robinhood. Later in the week, it also became clear that the Bahamas seized a whopping $3.5 billion from the exchange to keep them from vanishing.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, it appears that there&#8217;s a lot that is yet to be unraveled. For example, what was once one of the largest and most active networks, is now getting ripped to shreds. Solana is down over 96% from its all-time high. This week alone, the cryptocurrency lost over 22%. Alameda and SBF used to be amongst its backers.</p>
<p>Price-wise, the market remains rather dull, with a slight decrease throughout the past 7 days. BTC lost a little over one percent, and it trades at $16,500, unable to break towards $17K. ETH is down about 2%, and it currently trades at slightly below $1.2K.</p>
<p>All in all and perhaps somewhat expectedly, there was no Christmas rally as volatility dissipates from broader markets as well. It remains very interesting to see what the next year has in store and if 2023 will bring about the much-anticipated recovery.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $825B | 24H Vol: 35B | BTC Dominance: 38.5%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BTC:</strong> $16,530 (-1.8%) | <strong>ETH:</strong> $1,194 (-1.9%) | <strong>BNB</strong>: $244 (-0.4%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-201301" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" alt="bears_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Bahamas Seized $3.5 Billion From FTX to Keep Them From Vanishing. </strong>Bahamian regulators <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-seized-3-5-billion-from-ftx-to-keep-them-from-vanishing/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that they have seized $3.5 billion in assets from FTX and that they are held in custody for safekeeping. They intend to return them to the defrauded investors as the courts see fit.</p>
<p><strong>MicroStrategy Adds 2500 BTC: Total Stack Now 132,251 Bitcoin. </strong>MicroStrategy once again <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-adds-2500-btc-total-stack-now-132251-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">bought</a> a huge amount of BTC &#8211; over 2,000, to be more precise. However, the company also sold some for the first time ever &#8211; for tax purposes.</p>
<p class="media-heading entry-title"><strong>FTX Japan Reveals When it Will Resume Withdrawals. </strong>The Japanese branch of FTX <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-reveals-when-it-will-resume-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that it will shut down its business operations once users are able to withdraw their assets from the platform. This is supposed to take place by February 2023.</p>
<p class="media-heading entry-title"><strong>MicroStrategy to Introduce Bitcoin Lightning Applications Next Year. </strong>The company said it will launch certain solutions powered by the Bitcoin layer-2 scaling solution &#8211; the Lightning Network. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-to-introduce-bitcoin-lightning-applications-next-year/" data-wpel-link="internal">According</a> to them, these applications could reach millions of users.</p>
<p class="media-heading entry-title"><strong>3Commas Admits APIs Were Leaked Contrary To Prior Statements. </strong>After months, during which victims were blamed for having poor security habits, 3Commas finally came clean and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3commas-admits-apis-were-leaked-contrary-to-prior-statements/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that there are stolen API Keys.</p>
<p class="media-heading entry-title"><strong>The FTX Contagion Goes on: Midas Investments Closes Down. </strong>The contagion stemming from the fallout of FTX continues. This time, a cryptocurrency platform called Midas Investments <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-ftx-contagion-goes-on-midas-investments-closes-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that it will be shutting down because it was heavily affected by the crash of both FTX and Celsius.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, and Solana – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-30-eth-xrp-ada-matic-and-sol/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-more-btc-ftx-revelations-and-more-contagion-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Buys More BTC, FTX Revelations and More Contagion: This Week&#8217;s Crypto Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MEXC Futures Business Grows, Highlighting the Advantages of Liquidity and Fee Rate</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mexc-futures-business-grows-highlighting-the-advantages-of-liquidity-and-fee-rate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231042</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] In early December, the cryptocurrency exchange MEXC announced that its futures business made a significant breakthrough in 2022, with an average daily trading volume growth of 1200%. This data can be verified from third-party public data. On December 20, CoinMarketCap&#8217;s data showed that among the main exchanges, the daily [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>In early December, the cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://support.mexc.com/hc/en-001/articles/12944864220185" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">MEXC</a> announced that its futures business made a significant breakthrough in 2022, with an average daily trading volume growth of 1200%. This data can be verified from third-party public data.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-231043" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1.jpg" alt="MEXC" width="943" height="560" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1.jpg 943w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1-300x178.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1-768x456.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MEXC-1-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 943px) 100vw, 943px" /></a></p>
<p>On December 20, CoinMarketCap&#8217;s <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/rankings/exchanges/derivatives" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data</a> showed that among the main exchanges, the daily trading volume of MEXC&#8217;s futures reached $2.4 billion, ranking fourth globally.</p>
<p>The main reason for the growth of MEXC futures business is that the exchange has reportedly continuously optimized the liquidity of the top 50 tokens by market cap since the beginning of this year. As a result, by the third quarter of this year, the liquidity of MEXC futures business had reached the leading level globally.</p>
<p>For futures traders, liquidity is the core indicator, which directly determines trading fees and experience. This is because the better the liquidity, the better the depth, the higher the turnover rate, the smaller the price difference, the lower the trading fees, and the faster the trading speed. At the same time, under extreme market conditions similar to March 12, 2020, futures products with high liquidity can avoid accidental &#8220;pin bar” patterns.</p>
<p>The figure below shows the futures liquidity data of BTC_USDT and ETH_USDT on main exchanges. From July to November, under the trading depth of 0.05%, the liquidity of MEXC and Bitget ranked first and second, respectively.</p>
<h2>Liquidity Comparison Among Mainstream Exchanges</h2>
<p>In addition to liquidity, the number of cryptocurrencies supported by the futures exchange and the trading fee rate are also comprehensive indicators considered by traders. One of the most important factors is the fee rate. The lower the fee rate, the lower the trading fee.</p>
<p>On Maker fees, Bybit’s fee rate is 0.01%, while Binance and others have a fee rate of 0.02%. On the other hand, MEXC reduced Maker fees to 0% from December 1 onwards, equivalent to giving up Maker fees and passing them on to futures users. On Taker fees, MEXC, Bybit, and Kucoin charge them at 0.06%, while Binance and Huobi have the lowest rate of 0.04%.</p>
<p>CoinGecko’s data shows that in terms of the number of trading pairs, Binance supports the most futures trading pairs, having 233 pairs at present. However, different trading pairs of the same cryptocurrency are listed on each exchange, such as BTCUSDT and BTCUSDC, etc. Excluding duplicate data, then MEXC has listed the most cryptocurrencies for futures products, with more than 179, while Binance has listed more than 137.</p>
<h2>The Number of Futures Trading Pairs on Mainstream CEXs</h2>
<p>The number of listed cryptocurrencies is more apparently advantageous during the bull market. Because of the high frequency of project list during the bull market, there will be a time difference between different exchanges. For some traders, the futures trade of minor market cap cryptocurrencies can better meet their needs. However, with the end of the bull market, the frequency of project lists on the secondary market will gradually decrease, and the gap between the number of cryptocurrencies listed on each exchange will gradually decrease as well.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mexc-futures-business-grows-highlighting-the-advantages-of-liquidity-and-fee-rate/" rel="nofollow">MEXC Futures Business Grows, Highlighting the Advantages of Liquidity and Fee Rate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis Dec-30: ETH, XRP, ADA, MATIC and SOL</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-30-eth-xrp-ada-matic-and-sol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 15:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MATICUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SOLUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230955</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/charts_friday_301201.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/charts_friday_301201.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, and Solana Ethereum (ETH) Another week has passed with little excitement for Ethereum investors as volatility was low &#8211; likely due to the Christmas holidays. However, ETH&#8217;s price did fall by 2% in the past seven days. This is a negligible move in [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, and Solana</p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>Another week has passed with little excitement for Ethereum investors as volatility was low &#8211; likely due to the Christmas holidays. However, ETH&#8217;s price did fall by 2% in the past seven days. This is a negligible move in the price, which still remains in a flat trend.</p>
<p>This cryptocurrency remains stuck between the key support at $1,160 and the resistance at $1,240. This channel is intact for the second half of December, and it is unlikely to be broken with the New Year celebrations around the corner.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, the volatility is more likely to return in January 2023. So long as the support levels above $1,000 hold, Ethereum has a chance to break away and attempt to make a higher high. The alternative would see it fall to a three-digit price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230961" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230961" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230961" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45.png" alt="ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-30_17-49-45-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230961" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>This past week, XRP had a good attempt at breaking the key resistance at $0.36 but was swiftly rejected by the bears. For this reason, the price fell by 3.4%, and XRP is now found just above the support at $0.33.</p>
<p>Should buyers hold here, then it&#8217;s likely that XRP moves sideways between the key levels. However, any weakness could quickly be exploited by sellers that could push the price back to $0.30, which is a critical support that must hold.</p>
<p>If buyers fail to stop this downtrend, then this cryptocurrency will quickly find itself in a precarious situation, particularly if it loses the support at $0.30. That would open the path to lower lows in 2023, which would make the new year start with a bearish price action.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230964" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230964" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230964" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-30_17-51-15-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230964" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>Cardano is about to close 2022 as one of its worst years. With a new low in 2022 at $0.24, there seems to be no stop to the current downtrend. After losing 5.7% of its valuation in the past seven days, ADA is still in search of support.</p>
<p>At this time, the most likely support level to stop the downtrend is found at $0.20. This key level may provide ADA with some relief because it could entice buyers to finally return after being absent for most of 2022.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, the outlook for this cryptocurrency remains bearish after losing more than 92% of its valuation since its all-time high at above $3. Hopefully, in 2023, ADA will be able to find support and start a sustained reversal to recover some of these most recent losses.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230959" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230959" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230959" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-30_17-50-27-1-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230959" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Polygon (MATIC)</h2>
<p>Polygon should consider itself lucky despite losing 4.8% of its valuation in the past week, particularly when compared to ADA or SOL. This is because, at 75 cents currently, MATIC managed to stay far away from its yearly low in June when the price fell to 32 cents.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, pressure is building up as buyers appear to be on the defensive again, trying to keep the cryptocurrency above the key support at $0.74. The price action also shows that a decisive move appears imminent.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, repeated tests of the key support at $0.74 could be interpreted as bearish. If bulls fail to hold here, it would open the way for sellers to take MATIC back toward its June levels in the first half of 2023.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230962" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230962" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230962" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11.png" alt="MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/MATICUSDT_2022-12-30_17-52-11-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230962" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Solana (SOL)</h2>
<p>Solana is one of the worst performers of 2022 after a 96% price crash since its all-time high. To make matters worst, SOL&#8217;s price also lost 22% of its valuations in the past week.</p>
<p>Moreover, the cryptocurrency also fell under $10 and is currently struggling to hold above $9. Considering the historical price action, it seems unlikely for Solana to find good support until $5. Such a crash in its price, after nearly reaching $260 in 2022, is stunning.</p>
<p>The reason for this most recent crash could be attributed to major projects and developers choosing to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-suffers-major-setback-as-development-activity-plunges-sol-dumps-hard/" data-wpel-link="internal">move away</a> from Solana after the FTX implosion. This has shaken investors&#8217; trust in its future, making the outlook for Solana quite grim as it enters 2023.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230963" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230963" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230963 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44.png" alt="SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/SOLUSDT_2022-12-30_17-53-44-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230963" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-30-eth-xrp-ada-matic-and-sol/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis Dec-30: ETH, XRP, ADA, MATIC and SOL</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Drifts Away From $17K as Bears Continue Settling in (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-drifts-away-from-17k-as-bears-continue-settling-in-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230944</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s price has been confided by a very tight price range between the 50-day moving average and the ascending trendline. Considering the importance of this price range, the breakout’s direction should determine the mid-term perspective of the cryptocurrency’s path. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Bitcoin’s price started recovering after the significant crash toward [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin’s price has been confided by a very tight price range between the 50-day moving average and the ascending trendline. Considering the importance of this price range, the breakout’s direction should determine the mid-term perspective of the cryptocurrency’s path.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3><strong>The Daily Chart</strong></h3>
<p>Bitcoin’s price started recovering after the significant crash toward $15K in mid-November. However, the rally didn’t last long and was halted at the $18K resistance level.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the $18K resistance level aligns with Bitcoin’s prior major pivot. In the classical price action analysis, major pivots are crucial in serving as resistance or support for the price based on the trend’s direction. A failure to surpass the prior main pivot in an uptrend rally is a clear bearish sign.</p>
<p>As the chart shows, Bitcoin’s uptrend rally stopped at the same level as the prior major pivot at $18.3K. In light of this, the price has initiated another bearish rally. Hence, considering the current market structure and price action, a drop below the blue trendline seems more likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230946" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230946" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230946 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_301201" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-1D-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230946" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>The 4-Hour Chart</strong></h3>
<p>After getting rejected at $18.3K, the price reversed and started an impulsive bearish rally. Short-term continuation correction phases always accompany an impulsive rally.</p>
<p>In the 4-hour timeframe, after a steep drop, the price entered a short-term continuation consolidation stage and formed an ascending bearish wedge pattern.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230947" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230947" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230947 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_301202" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230947" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>Most recently, the price plummeted below the lower boundary, which validated the continuation of the bearish trend and continued to plunge toward the next support level. The following critical support level is the prior major pivot at $15.9K. If it fails, market players should anticipate another price crash toward $15.4K, the recent cycle’s low.</p>
<h2>On-Chain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoVizArt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">CryptoVizArt</a></p>
<h3>Demand Momentum Active Addresses</h3>
<p>This indicator tracks the ratio of the monthly average to the yearly average of &#8220;Active Addresses&#8221; in the Bitcoin Network.</p>
<p>The ratio between the short-term moving average and long-term moving average mimics the new demand joining/leaving the network.</p>
<ul>
<li>30 DMA &gt; 356 DMA: in the early stages of a bull market, the monthly averaged indicator breaks above the yearly averaged line, denoting a solid wave of demand for utilizing the Bitcoin network</li>
<li>30 DMA &lt; 356 DMA: Oppositely, after realizing the primary signs of a bear market, the shorter moving average of the active address tends to plunge below the longer moving average. This pattern indicates the entities, mostly speculators, leaving the network due to the negative sentiment they foresee in the mid to long term.</li>
</ul>
<p>Revisiting the 2022 trend of this metric shows that since December 2021, the market began a range of diminishing demand across the network. The declining rate in this metric has been slowing down since the early Jun market capitulation.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230949" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230949" style="width: 2806px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230949 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1.png" alt="btc_demandmetric_chart_301201" width="2806" height="1098" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1.png 2806w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-300x117.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-1024x401.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-768x301.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-1536x601.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-2048x801.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Demand-Momentum-_-Active-Address-1-50x20.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2806px) 100vw, 2806px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230949" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>Presently, we are witnessing a fragile equilibrium status in the active address momentum, creating a potential for a possible rally if new demand enters the market in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-drifts-away-from-17k-as-bears-continue-settling-in-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Drifts Away From $17K as Bears Continue Settling in (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Remains Rangebound, is This the Calm Before the 2023 Storm? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-remains-rangebound-is-this-the-calm-before-the-2023-storm-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 14:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230954</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[It has been 51 days since Ethereum experienced a significant crash and dropped to a new yearly low of $1.1K. Meanwhile, the price has been stuck in a price range between $1.1K and $1.3K. Further consolidation in the mentioned range would be the most likely scenario in the upcoming days. Technical Analysis By Shayan The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been 51 days since Ethereum experienced a significant crash and dropped to a new yearly low of $1.1K. Meanwhile, the price has been stuck in a price range between $1.1K and $1.3K. Further consolidation in the mentioned range would be the most likely scenario in the upcoming days.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By Shayan</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum faces a critical price zone consisting of the 50-day moving average as a resistance and the multi-month channel’s middle level as a support.</p>
<p>The price should soon exit from this tight range and determine the short-term direction. If ETH surpasses the 50-day moving average at $1225, the bulls should expect a breakout of the consolidation range at $1.3K.</p>
<p>However, if the price drops below the channel’s middle boundary, another price crash might happen, resulting in a plunge toward $1.1K static support (the consolidation range’s lower level).</p>
<figure id="attachment_230972" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230972" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230972 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_301201" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230972" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The price has finally broken the continuation correction bearish flag pattern to the downside. The cryptocurrency retested the broken level in the form of a pullback and is consolidating with extremely low volatility. Furthermore, there are three static price levels in the 4-hour timeframe; a resistance level at $1230 and two support levels at $1160 and $1100.</p>
<p>The price is currently in a consolidation phase between the $1230 resistance level and the $1160 support. Considering the low volatility and current price action, the price might be stuck in this range for the short-term view. However, if Ethereum plunges below the $1160 support level, the market will enter a new consolidation stage between the $1160 and $1100 levels.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230973" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230973" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230973 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_301202" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230973" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The whales and big players are the most critical and influential cohorts among the market participants, as they hold a significant portion of the supply. Hence, tracking their activity might play an important role in anticipating the market condition.</p>
<p>The chart contains the Exchange Inflow Mean (7-day moving average) and the price. A higher value indicates investors who deposited a lot at once are increasing lately. It could imply higher selling pressure from the big hands and a possible future price drop.</p>
<p>The metric surged impulsively before the major crash in November, indicating that the bigger hands might have caused the price drop by distributing their assets. However, the metric has calmed and decreased significantly. This shows that the market is suffering from a lack of activity. Nevertheless, it might be the calm before the storm.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230974" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230974" style="width: 468px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Picture1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230974 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Picture1.png" alt="eth_whale_chart_301201" width="468" height="295" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Picture1.png 468w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Picture1-300x189.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Picture1-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230974" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-remains-rangebound-is-this-the-calm-before-the-2023-storm-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Remains Rangebound, is This the Calm Before the 2023 Storm? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Japan Reveals When it Will Resume Withdrawals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-reveals-when-it-will-resume-withdrawals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 11:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230934</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_japan_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_japan_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Japanese exchange will shut down its business operations once users withdraw their assets from the platform. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">FTX Japan, the Japanese division of the bankrupt crypto exchange, plans to re-enable customers&#8217; withdrawals in mid-February next year after suspending the service last month due to the bankruptcy filing of its parent company.</p>
<p class="p2">FTX Japan earlier pledged to build a new system different from the one used by its parent company to enable customers to access their funds on the platform.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>FTX Japan Collaborates With Liquid to Repay Customers </b></h2>
<p class="p2">According to a <a href="https://help-jp.ftx.com/hc/ja/articles/14007851154201-%E3%81%8A%E5%AE%A2%E6%A7%98%E3%81%B8%E3%81%AE%E8%B3%87%E7%94%A3%E8%BF%94%E9%82%84%E3%81%AB%E9%96%A2%E3%81%99%E3%82%8B%E3%81%94%E6%A1%88%E5%86%85" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">recent update</span></a>, the exchange is working with Liquid, a Japanese platform <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-to-acquire-japanese-fintech-company-liquid-group/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">acquired</span></a> by FTX this year to aid its Asian expansion, to facilitate the refund process to users.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;For the assets entrusted to us by our customers at FTX Japan and Liquid Japan, we are proceeding with system development so that withdrawals and withdrawals will be possible from the Liquid Japan web version,&#8221; the announcement reads.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">Under the collaboration, FTX Japan users can check their account balances and withdraw their assets directly from Liquid&#8217;s webpage. On the other hand, Liquid users can take out their funds on the Liquid app.</p>
<p class="p2">The two firms structured a comprehensive roadmap to aid the withdrawal process, making it a rare example of investors getting their assets back after a company fails.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>FTX Japan to Exit the Market Next Year</b></h2>
<p class="p2">FTX Japan is also set to exit the market next year after making its customers whole, according to a new order for the country&#8217;s regulator, the Kanto Local Finance Bureau.</p>
<p class="p2">The Financial Services Agency (FSA) previously <a href="https://www.fsa.go.jp/news/r4/sonota/20221110/20221110.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">mandated</span></a> the exchange to halt some of its services relating to OTC derivatives transactions and related margins, including withdrawals. The FSA also demanded that FTX Japan holds its assets domestically and update total liabilities on its balance sheet periodically.</p>
<p class="p2">The requests came after FTX Limited suspended operations without providing investors and creditors clear information regarding the action. The FSA said the move was to protect customers&#8217; interests and to prevent the FTX situation from spreading across its 130 affiliates worldwide.</p>
<p class="p2">Despite the FSA&#8217;s demands last month, the Kanto Local Finance Bureau has ordered FTX Japan to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-has-until-march-2023-to-cease-all-operations-report/?amp" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">exit</span></a> the market on March 9, 2023. The federal regulator initially asked the company to suspend all operations on December 9 but extended the deadline after the exchange failed to return users&#8217; assets within the timeframe.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-reveals-when-it-will-resume-withdrawals/" rel="nofollow">FTX Japan Reveals When it Will Resume Withdrawals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
