<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:40:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SHIB, APE, PEPE Jump 8% Daily, Bitcoin Maintains $29K: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shib-ape-pepe-jump-8-daily-bitcoin-maintains-29k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265946</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba_Inu_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Shiba_Inu_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SHIB continues to gain momentum, and so has done another asset from the Shiba Inu ecosystem - BONE.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price performance continues to be rather underwhelming, with the asset remaining at essentially the same spot as yesterday at just over $29,000.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also quite stagnant today, with little-to-no movements from ETH, BNB, XRP, and others. Shiba Inu is the only exception from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>SHIB, APE, PEPE on the Rise</h2>
<p>Shiba Inu&#8217;s largest digital asset &#8211; SHIB &#8211; has been among the best performers lately, gaining double digits in the past week, as <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-returns-to-29k-after-failing-at-30k-shiba-inu-pumps-16-in-7-days-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a>. Furthermore, the past 24 hours were quite positive for the second-largest meme coin as well, as it soared by another 8%. As a result, SHIB now trades close to $0.000011.</p>
<p>The situation with ApeCoin and Pepe is quite similar, at least on a daily scale. Both have jumped by somewhere between 7-8%. Consequently, APE has returned to $2, while PEPE is up to $0.000001333 on CMC.</p>
<p>The larger-cap alts have stalled since yesterday. ETH, DOGE, and TRX are slightly in the green, while BNB, XRP, ADA, and MATIC have posted insignificant losses.</p>
<p>Expectedly, the cumulative market cap of all crypto assets has remained at the same spot at just over $1.170 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265950" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265950" style="width: 1878px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265950" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1878" height="844" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2.jpg 1878w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-1024x460.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-768x345.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-1536x690.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Allcoins-2-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1878px) 100vw, 1878px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265950" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bitcoin Stalls</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency had a rather volatile start to the week as it dipped below $29,000 on Monday to register a weekly low. The bulls quickly intercepted the move and pushed the asset north. By Wednesday, BTC had bounced off to over $30,000.</p>
<p>Yet, that turned out to be another short-lived adventure for bitcoin above that level, and it quickly retraced to $29,500. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-unfazed-as-cpi-for-july-increases-by-0-2-mom/" data-wpel-link="internal">US CPI numbers</a> on Thursday didn&#8217;t change the landscape all that much.</p>
<p>In fact, BTC has been quite stagnant since then and has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stagnant-above-29k-as-rlb-skyrockets-to-0-2-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">remained</a> in a tight range between $29,000 and $29,500 for the past 48 hours.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization stands just inches above $570 billion, while its dominance is below 49% on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265951" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265951" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="869" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-1024x485.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-768x364.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-1536x727.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD-3-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265951" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-ape-pepe-jump-8-daily-bitcoin-maintains-29k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">SHIB, APE, PEPE Jump 8% Daily, Bitcoin Maintains $29K: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should the World Move Forward with Decentralization?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/should-the-world-move-forward-with-decentralization/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265788</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/13042023_LFPR-The-Three-Layers-of-LFi-and-Its-Promise-to-Crypto-Users-Copy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/13042023_LFPR-The-Three-Layers-of-LFi-and-Its-Promise-to-Crypto-Users-Copy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Imagine making an online payment to a stranger without going through a bank and you still get a reliable and verifiable transaction history. This is how decentralization works. It is the type of process that gives cryptocurrencies the upper hand against traditional currencies. It eliminates the need for intermediaries and allows parties to engage in [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine making an online payment to a stranger without going through a bank and you still get a reliable and verifiable transaction history. This is how decentralization works. It is the type of process that gives cryptocurrencies the upper hand against traditional currencies. It eliminates the need for intermediaries and allows parties to engage in different transactions without relying on any third party.</p>
<p>The concept has hugely influenced the crypto space, which led the crypto community to revolutionize financial services and other markets. For example, DeFi, or decentralized finance, and DAO, or decentralized autonomous organizations are two famous offsprings of decentralization. As these ideas become more widespread, it is essential to learn what decentralization has to offer to the crypto world.</p>
<h2>Do We Need to Decentralize Our Payment System?</h2>
<p>Cash and banks have existed for decades, and everyone put their trust in this form of centralized structure until the financial crisis that occurred in 2008. This worldwide economic crisis made it evident that a single entity should not be making decisions that will affect everyone. Thus, the need for decentralized currencies became apparent.</p>
<p>In October 2008, Satoshi Nakamoto published the Bitcoin whitepaper, where the idea of a global currency that would be managed and owned by the people was born. More than decades later, the question still remains: should we use decentralized currencies?</p>
<p>Decentralization transfers control and decision-making to the users, enabling the system to not be reliant on a single authority and eliminating the risk of a corrupt or compromised authority. Through this, decentralized systems can ensure better protection and independence. Moreover, decentralization promotes trustless connections, wherein the verification of transactions relies on the collective wisdom of numerous devices that are working together. This prevents the system from being compromised by keeping any bad actors at bay.</p>
<p>Moreover, decentralization reduces vulnerabilities by distributing them across the network. Trustless connections prevent single bad actors from forging transactions or corrupting the system. Cooperation from more than 50 percent of the nodes is required to gain influence, making it increasingly difficult in larger systems. Distributed networks also mitigate threats, as compromising a single node does not jeopardize the entire system.</p>
<h2>Moving Forward with Decentralization</h2>
<p>Decentralization is the defining and exceptional characteristic of cryptocurrency. And as we progress, there will be new decentralized cryptocurrencies and exchanges that will preserve the benefits of decentralization and address its limitations. These will strengthen the innovative structure and revolutionize the world of finance in the future.</p>
<p>To find out more please visit: <a href="https://lfi.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">lfi.io</a></p>
<p>White paper: <a href="https://white-paper.lfi.io/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://white-paper.lfi.io/</a></p>
<p>Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/lfiofficial" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.me/lfiofficial</a></p>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/LFioff" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://twitter.com/LFioff</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/should-the-world-move-forward-with-decentralization/" rel="nofollow">Should the World Move Forward with Decentralization?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried Sent to Jail for Witness Tampering: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265939</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Sam_Bankman_Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The founder of the crypto exchange FTX could spend at least two months in jail ahead of its trial. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sam Bankman-Fried was reportedly sent to jail on Friday as US Judge Lewis Kaplan denied his lawyers&#8217; request to delay detention.</p>
<p>The former crypto mogul&#8217;s court date is set for October 2nd, and he could sit in a jail cell until then if the appeal is unsuccessful.</p>
<ul>
<li><em>CryptoPotato</em> reported last month the allegations presented by the New York Times that SBF had tried to intimidate one of the key witnesses in his legal battle against US authorities &#8211; the former leader of Alameda Research &#8211; Caroline Ellison.</li>
<li>Prosecutors were quick to request Bankman-Fried&#8217;s detention, claiming he could not be trusted while residing in his parents&#8217; home.</li>
<li>Expectedly, his lawyers refuted the allegations, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-shouldnt-be-detained-for-leaking-details-from-ellisons-diary-lawyers-claim/" data-wpel-link="internal">indicating</a> that he didn&#8217;t try to intervene or intimidate anyone, especially his former girlfriend.</li>
<li>According to more recent <a href="https://twitter.com/innercitypress/status/1690061503645229056" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reports</a>, though, the attorneys&#8217; requests for delayed detention were denied by Judge Lewis Kaplan.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;My conclusion is there is probable cause to believe the defendant tried to tamper with witnesses at least twice,&#8221; reportedly said the Judge.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Interestingly, SBF will most likely be sent to a jail in Putnam, New York, and will have access to a laptop with an internet connection to prepare for his defense. The other option was sending him to Brooklyn&#8217;s Metropolitan Detention Center, where internet access is limited for prisoners.</li>
<li>SBF&#8217;s court date over his alleged involvement in defrauding investors and the massive crash of his former crypto empire is set to begin on October 2nd. He could spend the next almost two months in jail unless his lawyer&#8217;s appeal to revert Judge Kaplan&#8217;s ruling is successful.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-sent-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-report/" rel="nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried Sent to Jail for Witness Tampering: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This E-Gaming Company Earmarks $5M for Bitcoin, Ether Purchases</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-e-gaming-company-earmarks-5m-for-bitcoin-ether-purchases/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 04:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265827</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_ethereum_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Boyaa said that the purchase of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) aligns with the interests of the company as well as its shareholders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent Hong Kong-based e-gaming player &#8211; Boyaa Interactive International Limited &#8211; announced that its board of directors has approved a budget of $5 million to purchase cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Informing the company&#8217;s shareholders and future potential investors, Boyaa said it will buy mainly Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) on regulated and licensed trading platforms in the coming year.</p>
<ul>
<li>The purchases will be financed using cash reserves derived from the Group activities both in Hong Kong and internationally and will be executed at its discretion, taking into account the current market conditions. The Group essentially consists of Boyaa Interactive Limited and its subsidiaries.</li>
<li>According to the official <a href="https://www1.hkexnews.hk/listedco/listconews/sehk/2023/0810/2023081001308.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release,</a> the move aligns with the intention of shaping Boyaa&#8217;s future business strategy within the Web3 space.</li>
<li>Despite earmarking the $5 million budget for cryptocurrency purchases, the company reminded its investors and shareholders that the digital asset market is volatile in the near term.</li>
<li>Boyaa also advised them to exercise caution while dealing with its shares.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Company will strictly comply with the relevant management and control policies on cryptocurrencies in relevant jurisdictions with regard to the purchases of cryptocurrencies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Boyaa Interactive is an established developer and operator of chess and card games in Hong Kong.</li>
<li>The latest allocation depicted the increasing inclination to venture into Web3 in the city-state owing to favorable policies fostering the digital asset sector.</li>
<li>Hong Kong has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/in-a-first-for-hong-kong-hashkey-exchange-awarded-license-to-serve-retail-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">demonstrated</a> a serious commitment to advancing Web3 prompting more than 150 such firms to <a href="https://www.fso.gov.hk/chi/blog/blog20230618.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">establish</a> operations in Cyberport &#8211; a digital hub launched by the government to promote innovation.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-e-gaming-company-earmarks-5m-for-bitcoin-ether-purchases/" rel="nofollow">This E-Gaming Company Earmarks $5M for Bitcoin, Ether Purchases</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Delays Approval Of Ark&#8217;s Revised Bitcoin ETF For Public Comment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-delays-approval-of-arks-revised-bitcoin-etf-for-public-comment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 23:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265914</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_SEC_ETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC wants to know what the public thinks of using Coinbase as a surveillance-sharing partner.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed to postpone its decision on whether to approve or deny the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF for listing on BZX.</p>
<p>This marks the agency’s first delay on the latest wave of Bitcoin spot ETF applications, possibly indicating a similar short-term fate for rival applicants.</p>
<h2>Questions For the Public</h2>
<p>In its Friday <a href="https://www.sec.gov/files/rules/sro/cboebzx/2023/34-98112.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">letter</a>, the SEC said it seeks public comment on BZX’s application, which would list the very first Bitcoin spot ETF on a U.S.-regulated exchange.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Institution of proceedings is appropriate at this time in view of the legal and policy issues raised by the proposed rule change,” wrote the SEC. “Institution of proceedings does not indicate that the Commission has reached any conclusions with respect to any of the issues involved.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This is a STANDARD delay letter. There&#39;s some confusion but only the first few paragraphs of this letter are written by the SEC and its very standardized. The rest is just a copy paste of the 19b-4 application written by CBOE (&amp; Ark/21Shares) There isnt much to read into here IMO <a href="https://t.co/7HOMA6kLK4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/7HOMA6kLK4</a></p>
<p>&mdash; James Seyffart (@JSeyff) <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1690022142664945664?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Firstly, the agency asked for the public’s thoughts on whether the proposed ETF would be protected from “fraudulent and manipulative acts and practices,” and whether the Bitcoin market is inherently susceptible to manipulation. This issue is central to the agency’s hesitancy in approving a Bitcoin spot ETF until this point.</p>
<p>In the past, ETF applicants have attempted to form surveillance-sharing agreements with the CME Bitcoin Futures market to meet the SEC’s market monitoring needs. However, between ARK’s previous applications as well as those from Grayscale, the SEC has contended that this market cannot meet its benchmark.</p>
<p>That’s what its second public question pertains to: “Do commenters agree with the Exchange that the CME, on which CME Bitcoin Futures trade, represents a regulated market of significant size related to spot bitcoin?” asked the SEC. The regulator specifically wishes to know it someone attempting to manipulate the Bitcoin market would necessarily have to trade on the CME.</p>
<p>The SEC’s last question touched on Coinbase – America’s largest spot Bitcoin exchange, and ARK’s newly preferred surveillance sharing partner. 8 rival applicants have named the same exchange in their most recent filings, following the footsteps of both Fidelity and BlackRock.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Do commenters agree with the Exchange’s assertion that such an agreement with Coinbase would be “helpful in detecting, investigating, and deterring fraud and manipulation in the Commodity-Based Trust Shares”?” wrote the SEC.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Next Deadlines</h2>
<p>After ARK, the next approval deadlines for rival Bitcoin spot ETFs are in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-an-approximate-list-of-all-bitcoin-etf-approval-deadlines-bbg/" data-wpel-link="internal">early September</a>, including BlackRock’s – but decisions on those applications can be similarly delayed.</p>
<p>ARK’s true final deadline at which the SEC can delay its decision no longer is on January 10. Given its virtually identical structure to competitors, ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood expects that its approval will mean that of rival firms as well – and likely <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-sec-might-approve-numerous-spot-btc-etfs-at-the-same-time-cathie-wood-thinks/" data-wpel-link="internal">all at the same time</a>.</p>
<p>Before that, Grayscale expects to receive a ruling in its lawsuit with the SEC by the end of September. Bloomberg ETF analysts <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloomberg-boosts-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval-odds-to-65-heres-why/" data-wpel-link="internal">predict</a> that this lawsuit is still the most likely route to spot ETF approval.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-delays-approval-of-arks-revised-bitcoin-etf-for-public-comment/" rel="nofollow">SEC Delays Approval Of Ark&#8217;s Revised Bitcoin ETF For Public Comment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Embattled Crypto Exchange to Pay a $24 Million Penalty to Settle With SEC (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/embattled-crypto-exchange-to-pay-a-24-million-penalty-to-settle-with-sec-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 22:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265734</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Bittrex_US.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[William Shihara - co-founder of the company which filed for bankruptcy protection in May - called the settlement plan "a good outcome."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The once-prominent cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex has reportedly agreed to pay $24 million in penalties to resolve its quarrel with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency has previously accused the platform of offering services to American clients without obtaining the necessary registration.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange shuttered its US operations and filed for bankruptcy protection shortly after the regulator targeted it.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bittrex-to-pay-24-million-penalty-over-sec-crypto-allegations-1.1957621" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Bloomberg, Bittrex and its non-US subsidiary will part with $24 million to settle allegations that it violated several securities rules while providing cryptocurrency services to American users.</span></li>
<li>The company&#8217;s co-founder William Shihara called the settlement plan &#8220;a good outcome,&#8221; raising hopes that it could help the US authorities create a balance between safeguarding investors and promoting innovation.</li>
<li>Bittrex and Shihara have been coping with severe issues over the past several months caused by the hostile stance of the SEC.</li>
<li>The firm <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-to-close-operations-in-the-us-due-to-regulatory-hurdles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">terminated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> operations in the States at the end of March this year, citing the nation&#8217;s &#8220;regulatory and economic environment.&#8221; Nonetheless, it assured that &#8220;customer funds are safe, here and ready for retrieval.&#8221;</span></li>
<li>A few weeks later, the exchange <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-receives-wells-notice-from-sec-for-violating-investor-protection-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Wells Notice from the SEC. The latter alleged that Bittrex operated as an unregistered exchange, broker-dealer, and clearinghouse for securities. </span></li>
<li>The company <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-bittrex-files-for-us-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in the US approximately three weeks after the SEC&#8217;s attack. According to the filing, it had more than 100,000 creditors, with estimated liabilities and assets both worth between $500 million and $1 billion. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/embattled-crypto-exchange-to-pay-a-24-million-penalty-to-settle-with-sec-report/" rel="nofollow">Embattled Crypto Exchange to Pay a $24 Million Penalty to Settle With SEC (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another Country Begins Investigating Sam Altman&#8217;s Worldcoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/another-country-begins-investigating-sam-altmans-worldcoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Worldcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265768</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Worldcoin_investigation.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Worldcoin_investigation.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The AAIP will "carefully analyze" how Worldcoin processes personal data and whether it presents any risks for Argentines.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argentina&#8217;s Agency for Access to Public Information (AAIP) disclosed that it is currently conducting an investigation on Worldcoin to determine whether it complies with security and privacy rules.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The cryptocurrency project, which saw the light of day in July, sparked huge controversy due to its eye-scanning requirements. Other countries, including Kenya and Germany, have also raised concerns on the matter.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argentina Joining the Club</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The aforementioned agency </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.argentina.gob.ar/noticias/la-aaip-investiga-el-tratamiento-de-datos-personales-de-worldcoin-en-argentina" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it will investigate how the Worldcoin Foundation in Argentina processes personal data and whether the crypto project hides any risks to the privacy of consumers. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The investigation will carefully analyze the processes and practices in relation to the collection, storage, and use of personal data to identify possible effects on the rights recognized by Law 25,326.</span></p>
<p>In addition, appropriate steps will be taken to address any identified issues and ensure that the company complies with security and privacy standards,&#8221; the disclosure reads.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Worldcoin&#8217;s popularity has recently surged in the South American country due to the procedure of scanning the face and iris of multiple individuals in different regions, such as Buenos Aires, Córdoba, and Mendoza, in exchange for certain economic compensations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The AAIP outlined that the entity responsible for obtaining such biometric information should be registered with the relevant regulator. It added that users should also know who collects that sensitive data, where it gets stored, and what is the processing time.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Cases like this make visible the need to strengthen the current legal framework regarding the Protection of Personal Data, as has been raised repeatedly and in various national and international forums by the AAIP,&#8221; the agency concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Wolrdcoin&#8217;s Birth and the Triggered Controversy</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After years of trials and fundraisers, Worldcoin finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openai-ceo-sam-altmans-crypto-project-worldcoin-launches-wld-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> its native token WLD at the end of July. The project, led by the CEO of OpenAI &#8211; Sam Altman, presents itself as an open-source protocol &#8220;designed to become the world&#8217;s largest human identity and financial network, giving ownership to everyone.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The controversy behind it comes from Worldcoin&#8217;s intention to register new users and distribute certain crypto assets to those who scan their iris through a ball-like device called an &#8220;orb.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Somewhat expectedly, the project&#8217;s idea, which reminds the plot of a sci-fi movie, received a wave of criticism from numerous agencies. The government of Kenya, for example, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-authorities-suspend-worldcoin-activities-over-data-privacy-concerns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suspended</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> all Worldcoin activities and the distribution of WLD due to safety and privacy concerns. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Appropriate action will be taken on any natural or juristic person who furthers, aids, abets or otherwise engages in or is connected with the activities afore-described,” the Kenyan politician Kithure Kindiki stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulators of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/german-regulator-probes-worldcoin-crypto-currency-handelsblatt-2023-08-08/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Germany</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, France, and the United Kingdom have also questioned the legality of Worldcoin&#8217;s biometric data collection.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Privacy experts have warned that personal data, such as iris identification, is quite sensitive and could be breached by criminals. This, in turn, could lead to identity theft or stalking. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-country-begins-investigating-sam-altmans-worldcoin/" rel="nofollow">Another Country Begins Investigating Sam Altman&#8217;s Worldcoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase&#8217;s Base Notches 4th Rank in Daily TPS Among Layer 2 Solutions: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-notches-4th-rank-in-daily-tps-among-layer-2-solutions-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 19:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265772</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coinbase_base.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Coinbase_base.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Base hit 136,000 daily active users just two days after its public release. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The initial response to Coinbase&#8217;s layer 2 blockchain &#8211; Base &#8211; has been favorable so far. It has garnered substantial engagement in both DeFi operations and cross-chain bridge transactions. The daily active users on Base, for one, surpassed 100,000 for the first time. More importantly, the figure came just a day after the much-anticipated launch of the blockchain&#8217;s mainnet.</p>
<p>Base was already live for testing by developers but launched for the public officially with more than 100 apps and service providers on August 9th.</p>
<h2>Base&#8217;s Activity Spike</h2>
<p>Base blockchain went live on mainnet this week, in a move that was touted as the beginning of a new era of public companies running their own distributed networks. The positive reception was evident in terms of the total value bridged to Base, which surpassed $150 million on the day of the official launch. The figure currently stands near $173 million.</p>
<p>Data <a href="https://dune.com/tk-research/base" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">compiled</a> by Dune Analytics further recorded over 136k daily active users on August 10th. Judging by the pace, the number seems to be heading towards a new peak today.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the crypto data platform CryptoRank <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoRank_io/status/168963787529246310" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ranked</a> Base in the 4th position in daily TPS among layer-2 solutions despite trailing miles behind already established players such as zkSync Era, Arbitrum, and Optimism.</p>
<p>Initially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-launch-eth-layer-2-network-based-on-optimism-op-token-pumps-6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> in February, Coinbase heralded Base as a &#8220;bridge&#8221; for new crypto users into the crypto economy. However, unlike its peer Ethereum scaling networks such as Optimism, Arbitrum, or Polygon, the San Francisco-based crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sets-date-for-base-mainnet-launch-addresses-token-rumors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> having no immediate plans to release an accompanying token for Base.</p>
<h2>TVL Uptrend</h2>
<p>Part of Base&#8217;s success can be attributed to its soft launch, from the developer-only release in July to mainnet a month later. Prior to the public launch, Base witnessed substantial usage through the BALD memecoin.</p>
<p>However, it is a new social network project called friend.tech is the reason behind the heightened activity. Since the launch of friend.tech, <a href="https://dune.com/msilb7/friendtech-on-base-activity" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> suggest that there have been more than 7,000 users, and over 81,000 transactions have been completed with a transaction volume of 2,778 ETH on the layer-2 blockchain.</p>
<p>As such, the total value of assets locked (TVL) on Base <a href="https://l2beat.com/scaling/projects/base" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">soared</a> above $161 million during the same period, representing a nearly 81% increase over the past week alone.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbases-base-notches-4th-rank-in-daily-tps-among-layer-2-solutions-data/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase&#8217;s Base Notches 4th Rank in Daily TPS Among Layer 2 Solutions: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Dethroned Coinbase as Most Liquid US Exchange for Altcoins in July: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kraken-dethroned-coinbase-as-most-liquid-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265854</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/KrakenUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/KrakenUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[While Kraken records significant growth in its market share, Coinbase has faced regulatory challenges in recent months, possibly the reason for the decline in its volumes.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency trading platform Kraken dethroned its rival Coinbase to become the most liquid United States exchange for altcoins in July.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/DessislavaIane2/status/1689301335760363521?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> by Dessislava Laneva, a research analyst at crypto data platform Kaiko, by the end of July, Kraken had claimed 47% of the market depth in the US for the top 10 altcoins.</p>
<h2>Kraken Claims Largest U.S. Market Depth for Altcoins</h2>
<p>As of January 2023, Kraken had only a 39% share of the market depth of altcoins, while Coinbase had 45%. At the same time, Binance.US, the American arm of the world’s largest crypto exchange Binance, had a market share of 7% while six other platforms collectively accounted for 9%.</p>
<p>However, data analyzed by Kaiko researchers found that Kraken’s market share has increased to 47%, leaving Coinbase with 41%, Binance.US with 1%, and the remaining exchanges with 10%. This means that Kraken now has a greater ability to absorb large market orders without significantly impacting the price of the altcoin in question.</p>
<p>Besides Kraken’s growing market depth, the exchange’s market share among platforms supporting USD deposits has also increased recently. Data from The Block’s USD Support Exchange Volume dashboard <a href="https://www.theblock.co/data/crypto-markets/spot/usd-support-exchange-volume-market-share" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> Kraken’s market share rose from 14.78% in January to 21.1% in July. The growth is significant, as the platform had a share of 8.3% last August.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Faces challenges</h2>
<p>A spokesperson for Kraken told The Block that the exchange’s recent performance is due to the launch of its advanced trading platform Kraken Pro and the enhancement of several offerings. The representative said the exchange&#8217;s share of total volumes had hit an 18-month high since unveiling the new platform.</p>
<p>Kraken’s share of the EUR spot market has soared to 53% from 35%, and the exchange’s AUD spot market has also multiplied by six times in the past months, per the spokesperson.</p>
<p>While Kraken records significant growth in its digital asset market share, Coinbase has faced regulatory challenges in recent months, possibly due to the decline in its volumes. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> Coinbase in early June over several allegations, including operations as an unregistered broker, securities exchange, and clearing agency.</p>
<p>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wanted-coinbase-to-delist-all-crypto-assets-except-bitcoin-before-lawsuit-ft/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that the Commission instructed the exchange to halt the trading of all altcoins as they were securities and violated federal laws.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kraken-dethroned-coinbase-as-most-liquid-us-exchange-for-altcoins-in-july-data/" rel="nofollow">Kraken Dethroned Coinbase as Most Liquid US Exchange for Altcoins in July: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here is How XRP Holders Can Apply for Evernode&#8217;s (Evers) Airdrop</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-xrp-holders-can-apply-for-evernodes-evers-airdrop/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265818</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Evers_Airdrop.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Evers_Airdrop.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The decentralized platform will distribute 5,160,960 Evers to eligible XRP holders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Evernode &#8211; a layer 2 smart contract solution built on top of the XRP Ledger (XRPL) &#8211; announced the first details of its airdrop intended to reach XRP holders.</p>
<p>Such investors should provide a snapshot of their possessions by the beginning of September and must hold their tokens on-chain.</p>
<ul>
<li>The team behind the decentralized platform <a href="https://twitter.com/EvernodeXRPL/status/1689805394460463104?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that it will airdrop 5,160,960 Evers to eligible XRP holders. Investors will be required to send a snapshot of their stash (stored directly on-chain and not through an exchange) until September 1.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Because we&#8217;ll launch on the Hooks sidechain and because that sidechain will include a burn2mint, we need to snapshot the XRP Ledger before the Hooks sidechain goes live,&#8221; Evernode explained.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The token distribution will mainly focus on investors with balances of up to 50,000 XRP. Those owning more will need to hold it in separate accounts to benefit from the contribution.</li>
<li>Evernode promised to give further details once there is more information about the launch of the Hooks sidechain.</li>
<li>Subsequently, the team reminded that the airdrop is a gift, meaning not all XRP holders will be granted portions of the new token:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While we&#8217;ll use our best endeavors, we don&#8217;t in any way promise/warrant that you&#8217;ll receive any particular number of Evers. For any reason &#8211; or for no reason &#8211; we may decide not to proceed with the airdrop in this manner, or at all.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-how-xrp-holders-can-apply-for-evernodes-evers-airdrop/" rel="nofollow">Here is How XRP Holders Can Apply for Evernode&#8217;s (Evers) Airdrop</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
