<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:15:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume on Upbit Skyrockets as BCH Soars 120% Weekly</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257879</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Cash_Korea.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin_Cash_Korea.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinGecko's data shows that BCH/KRW trading volume on Upbit for the past 24 hours exceeded $560 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading South Korean cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Upbit &#8211; has recorded a trading volume of more than $350 million for the Bitcoin Cash (BCH)/Korean Won (KRW) pair for the past 24 hours. In comparison, trades involving Bitcoin (BTC) have been three times less.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BCH has been among the best performers in the crypto market lately, with its USD valuation up over 180% for the past two weeks.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BCH Grabs the Attention of Koreans </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As revealed by Wu Blockchain, BCH/KRW trades on South Korea&#8217;s biggest cryptocurrency exchange have accounted for approximately 24% of the total trading volume for the past day.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">South Korea may be the reason for the BCH PUMP. In the past 24h, the largest exchange in South Korea, Upbit, has recorded a trading volume of over $350 million for the BCH/KRW, contributing to 23.58% of the total trading volume for BCH. It is also the 3x the trading volume of the…</p>
<p>— Wu Blockchain (@WuBlockchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1674614453231562755?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 30, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/upbit" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CoinGecko&#8217;s data</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the latest figures are even more impressive, with BCH/KRW trading volume for the last 24 hours equaling over $560 million. Trades with Solana (SOL) rank second with 8.4%, whereas Bitcoin (BTC) is third, contributing 7.8% to the total volume.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash has been highly popular on other Korean crypto platforms, too. BCH/KRW trading volume on Bithumb on a daily basis has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/bithumb" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">surged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to $39 million. Trades involving BTC are first, with a mere $300,000 lead. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash&#8217;s Recent Rally</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The asset recently surpassed the $300 mark, a price last seen in April 2022. What&#8217;s more impressive is that its USD valuation was hovering at approximately $100 just two weeks ago.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_257890" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257890" style="width: 649px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-257890" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png" alt="BCH Price" width="649" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH.png 1033w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-300x185.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-1024x631.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-768x474.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH-50x31.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257890" class="wp-caption-text">BCH Price, Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One possible reason behind the increase could be the launch of the Wall Street-backed crypto exchange EDX Markets, which </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-backed-cryptocurrency-exchange-edx-goes-live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">went live</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on June 21. The platform, supported by finance giants such as Fidelity Digital Assets, Citadel Securities, and Charles Schwab, offers services with four cryptocurrencies, with BCH being one of them.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Cash was also not included in the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-sec-claims-these-coins-are-securities-in-the-lawsuit-against-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">list</a> of alleged unregistered securities when filing lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase earlier this month. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The overall revival of the cryptocurrency market could be another factor. The industry was boosted with optimistic news, such as BlackRock&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> to launch a Spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the United States and the Federal Reserve&#8217;s decision to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-trades-flat-after-federal-reserve-pauses-rate-hikes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">halt</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> interest hikes for the first time since March 2022.</span></p>
<p>As mentioned above, the blockchain journalist Colin Wu believes another factor that could be behind BCH&#8217;s massive surge is the</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-trading-volume-on-upbit-skyrockets-as-bch-soars-120-weekly/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Cash Trading Volume on Upbit Skyrockets as BCH Soars 120% Weekly</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How An Early Investment in Dogecoin Made This Investor a Millionaire: Which New Meme Coins Could Be Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-early-investment-in-dogecoin-made-this-investor-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-could-be-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 12:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257939</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_tl_doge_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/wsm_tl_doge_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Given the crypto market’s fast-moving nature, fortunes can be made and lost in the blink of an eye. Dogecoin ($DOGE) defied all the odds and turned early investors into millionaires during its bull run, launching an era of meme-based cryptocurrencies. Now investors are looking for the next wave of meme coins that could be the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Given the crypto market’s fast-moving nature, fortunes can be made and lost in the blink of an eye.</p>
<p>Dogecoin ($DOGE) defied all the odds and turned early investors into millionaires during its bull run, launching an era of meme-based cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Now investors are looking for the next wave of meme coins that could be the fabled crypto &#8220;millionaire makers.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Dogecoin Millionaire Learns Valuable Lessons in the Meme Coin Landscape</h2>
<p>Dogecoin was the first meme coin to gain significant mainstream attention, solidifying its place in the history of the crypto market.</p>
<p>From January 2021 to May 2021, the $DOGE price rocketed over 10,000%, marking the first time a crypto asset driven by social media hype had experienced such an astronomical surge.</p>
<p>This event forever altered the perception of what is possible in the world of cryptocurrencies since it demonstrated the immense power of community-driven enthusiasm.</p>
<p>One notable outcome of Dogecoin’s unprecedented surge was the emergence of the legendary “Dogecoin millionaire” – an individual who transformed an early $DOGE investment into a life-changing fortune.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/20/dogecoin-investor-is-no-longer-a-millionaire-but-still-buys-the-dips.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CNBC</a> article, Glauber Contessoto invested $250,000 in $DOGE in February 2021, and by April 2021, he became a millionaire on paper.</p>
<p>However, despite his initial success, Contessoto’s decision to hold onto his Dogecoin investment without taking profits proved to be a risky move.</p>
<p>As the hype around Dogecoin subsided, the price of the meme coin came crashing down – eroding a significant chunk of his paper gains.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257943" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="497" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29-300x248.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-29-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Fast forward to the present day, and Contessoto has embraced his past and become an <a href="https://twitter.com/ProTheDoge" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">influential voice on Twitter</a> – sharing insights and offering advice to fellow crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<p>In retrospect, many experts suggest that he could have benefited from taking profits during the peak of Dogecoin’s surge and diversifying into other promising projects.</p>
<p>By realizing gains at the right time, Contessoto may have mitigated the potential losses incurred during the $DOGE downfall, yet this wasn&#8217;t the approach he took.</p>
<p>Ultimately, hindsight serves as a stark reminder that effective risk management is key to maximizing outcomes in the crypto market – something that meme coin investors may wish to bear in mind going forward.</p>
<h2>Which Meme Coins Could Be the Next With Potential?</h2>
<p>With Dogecoin setting a precedent for what’s possible with meme coin investing, investors are eagerly searching for the next “millionaire makers” in the market.</p>
<p>Two promising candidates have recently emerged, Wall Street Memes and Thug Life, aiming to capture the imagination of meme coin enthusiasts worldwide.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Raises $11.5m As Investor Excitement Reaches Fever Pitch</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes ($WSM)</a> is a community-driven project that leverages the immense power of the Reddit subculture.</p>
<p>The core values of Wall Street Memes are designed to resonate with investors who have rallied behind meme cryptos in the past, making $WSM a particularly appealing prospect.</p>
<p>Since emerging last month, Wall Street Memes has made itself known to the masses – raising a staggering $11.5 million through its ongoing presale.</p>
<p>The presale has been an instant hit due to its 30-stage setup, which increases the $WSM price incrementally between stages.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257942" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4-24-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Currently, $WSM is available to purchase for just $0.0307 – although with over two-thirds of the presale allocation already gone, investors may need to act fast to take advantage of these prices.</p>
<p>The low purchase price has led to tremendous growth and momentum behind the project, evidenced by the influx of new members to the Wall Street Memes <a href="https://t.me/wallst_memes" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a>.</p>
<p>Additionally, the project has already been on the radar of some high-profile crypto influencers; for example, Michael Wrubel, who boasts over 310,000 subscribers, posted a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BTdUPbXVujc&amp;pp=ygUYd2FsbCBzdHJlZXQgbWVtZXMgY3J5cHRv" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video breakdown</a> of the project.</p>
<p>Overall, Wall Street Memes looks set to continue growing – positioning itself as a potential meme coin leader.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>New Contender Thug Life Disrupts Meme Coin Market with Huge Presale Launch</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a> is another brand-new meme coin that has gained huge attention from retail investors.</p>
<p>This fresh project centers around hip-hop culture and the essence of resilience while fostering a sense of camaraderie within the community.</p>
<p>The $THUG token has generated significant buzz through its presale phase launch, which has amassed over $140,000 in just two days.</p>
<p>Early investors can buy $THUG tokens for just $0.0007, presenting an appealing opportunity for those seeking the next meme coin sensation.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-257941" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="357" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11-300x178.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-11-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Importantly, the Thug Life team has already pledged to lock liquidity for three months once the token makes its DEX debut – protecting investors from rug pull scenarios.</p>
<p>Also, 70% of the total $THUG supply has been set aside for presale investors, demonstrating the team&#8217;s commitment to fostering a strong community.</p>
<p>This setup seems to be bearing fruit, with over 2,400 people following the Thug Life <a href="https://twitter.com/thug_life_token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter account</a> already.</p>
<p>In addition, crypto influencer Jacob Bury uploaded a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mVtbCRWEmgA&amp;t=1s&amp;pp=ygUQdGh1ZyBsaWZlIGNyeXB0bw%3D%3D" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">video</a> discussing $THUG, stating that he thinks the token’s price could 10x after its DEX listing.</p>
<p>Ultimately, the future looks exceedingly bright for Thug Life – setting the stage for a solid second half of 2023.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-an-early-investment-in-dogecoin-made-this-investor-a-millionaire-which-new-meme-coins-could-be-next/" rel="nofollow">How An Early Investment in Dogecoin Made This Investor a Millionaire: Which New Meme Coins Could Be Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 10:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/twt_101_1_1688059768gfAiBu9ZOa.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/twt_101_1_1688059768gfAiBu9ZOa.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, June 30th, 2023] Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign. Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; New York, New York, June 30th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>Memecoin Mooky is gearing up for its final presale phase, having raised $900,000 to date. More than just a novel crypto token, Mooky aims to support the environment through a major tree-planting campaign.</p>
<p>Mooky will be a community-driven platform whose governance lies in the hands of its token holders. While the MOOKY token draws its cues from other successful memecoins, the project has a more ambitious mandate. Mooky was conceived to increase awareness of global environmental challenges and to provide real-world solutions.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/1_1688110387jD2jn6a98F.jpg" /></p>
<p>The project aims to raise enough funds to sustain an extensive reforestation initiative in key locations around the world. As part of its commitment to nature, Mooky has earmarked donations to charities working on sustainable environmental causes.</p>
<p>From a crypto-economic perspective, the MOOKY token features zero tax and low slippage, providing ample incentives for traders to get involved. Underpinning the project is a deep lore that aligns with Mooky’s core goals.</p>
<p>Mooky is based on the concept of a mythical land called Pygmy. This fantastical realm has stunning landscapes, abundant vegetation, and wildlife. As settlers came to the island, they destroyed the vegetation and polluted the air. The monkeys of Pygmy decide to fight back peacefully, teaching the settlers how to respect nature and live harmoniously. Under the leadership of Mooky, they become united and restore nature.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IiPyd5VoQIg"></iframe></div></p>
<p>To support the project’s development while providing greater opportunities for community participation, Mooky has created a collection of 1,000 NFTs. Each NFT is linked to a tree planted in the real world. Holders can access the Ventures Club, which grants access to exclusive rewards and events.</p>
<p>With five days left in the <a href="blank" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">$MOOKY token presale</a>, there is still ample opportunity for crypto holders to get involved and capture the upside to a project that combines memes and nature to great effect.</p>
<h2>About MOOKY</h2>
<p>MOOKY is a community-driven initiative launched in 2023 that embraces the spirit of digital innovation to make a positive impact on the environment. More than just a meme token, MOOKY represents a global community united by a common goal: to inspire change and contribute to global tree-planting efforts.</p>
<p>MOOKY also stands as a symbol of creativity in the digital space, offering unique 3D NFTs that are each linked to real-world tree-planting initiatives. These NFTs serve not only as digital collectibles but also as an entry ticket to the exclusive Mooky Ventures Club, a vibrant community of environmentally conscious enthusiasts.</p>
<p>MOOKY is more than a digital token; it&#8217;s a movement aiming to better our environment while fostering a unique and engaging digital ecosystem. Join MOOKY in its journey to make a difference and follow the community on various social channels to stay updated.</p>
<p>Users can purchase MOOKY <a href="https://buy.mooky.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">here</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/memecoin-mooky-raises-900000-ahead-of-its-final-presale-stage/" rel="nofollow">Memecoin MOOKY Raises $900,000 Ahead of Its Final Presale Stage</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Files Request for Dismissal of Charges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257886</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coinbase_sec_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/coinbase_sec_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to Coinbase, the lawsuit is at best government overreach and at worst an abuse of due process.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Merely a few weeks after the SEC sued the platform for facilitating unregistered trading with 12 tokens that the agency considers to be securities, Coinbase’s legal representatives have filed for a complete dismissal of the lawsuit, citing concerns regarding the legal authority of the regulator.</p>
<h2>Prior Approval Disregarded</h2>
<p>One of the principal arguments laid out by Coinbase’s legal team is that six of the twelve cryptocurrencies at the heart of the lawsuit had already been <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/4oVJN5EioULD0QnSyg01b8/2b1f34594a800c727fb61a384f37e74a/SEC_v._Coinbase__Coinbase_Answer_to_Complaint__As-Filed_.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">greenlit</a> by the SEC back in 2021. At the time, the six cryptocurrencies in question had been confirmed to not be securities by the SEC, which reviewed 240 digital assets that were listed on the exchange shortly after.</p>
<p>Since the SEC had already confirmed that the tokens in question were not considered securities, Coinbase argued that the current lawsuit is merely the result of internal policy changes that were not communicated to the companies the watchdog wishes to regulate.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The SEC’s about-face is not a product of material changes to Coinbase’s business since 2021; none are alleged. Nor is it due to new information. Nowhere in its Complaint does the SEC suggest that Coinbase hid anything in the many years of cooperative discussion that preceded it becoming a public company. Nor is the reversal a product of legislative change. […] The only change is in the SEC’s position regarding its powers.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Out of Scope</h2>
<p>Not only are the charges brought against Coinbase possibly unfounded, but they are also outside of the scope of existing law and regulatory precedent, argued Coinbase representatives.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Today <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@coinbase</a> filed our answer and notice of intent to file a motion to dismiss the <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SECGov</a> case against us. You can read our response for yourself – our arguments speak for themselves. 1/2 <a href="https://t.co/Ld2ZEejhyM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/Ld2ZEejhyM</a></p>
<p>— paulgrewal.eth (@iampaulgrewal) <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1674271484263661569?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Coinbase’s leadership has repeatedly stressed that they are more than willing to entertain dialogue with regulatory bodies and stay well within the legal framework imposed upon them – so long as the given framework is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-responds-to-coinbase-request-for-crypto-clarity-wants-more-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">clearly</a> laid out.</p>
<p>In this case, however, Coinbase believes the tokens in question are outside of the SEC’s scope owing to them not being considered securities by the agency&#8217;s own admission. Even if the tokens were to come under the purview of the SEC, the current lawsuit represents a violation of Coinbase’s rights and an abuse of process.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Even if the SEC were correct that the assets and services it identifies are within the scope of its existing regulatory authority, this [legal] action must be dismissed on independent grounds that it violates Coinbase’s due process rights and constitutes an extraordinary abuse of process.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The request to dismiss charges is now pending with the judge, who will respond as he sees fit. Meanwhile, Coinbase’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-shares-have-jumped-nearly-40-since-the-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">stock</a> seems to be slowly recovering following the initial shock that sent it plunging to the depths.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-files-request-for-dismissal-of-charges/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Files Request for Dismissal of Charges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Cash Explodes 33% to 14-Month High, Solana and Litecoin Soar 15% (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-33-to-14-month-high-solana-and-litecoin-soar-15-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257889</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BCH_BTC_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BCH skyrocketed to over $320 earlier today for the first time since April 2022.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While BTC pushed toward $31,000 and even briefly surpassed that level, several altcoins have been on a massive roll in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Bitcoin Cash stands out as the most notable performer, having surged by over 30% on a daily scale to over $300 for the first time in over a year.</p>
<h2>It&#8217;s BCH&#8217;s Show</h2>
<p>The altcoins started a massive run-up last week before stalling for a few days. Today, though, the landscape for many of them is quite different.</p>
<p>While ETH, BNB, XRP, and TRX trade relatively quietly with gains of up to 3%, ADA, DOGE, and DOT have jumped by up to 5%.</p>
<p>However, SOL and LTC have taken the main stage with impressive 15% daily increases. As a result, SOL is up to $19, while LTC trades close to $100.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, Bitcoin Cash has stolen the show with a mind-blowing 33% surge to $305. Moreover, BCH even tapped $320 earlier today, charting its highest price tag in 14 months.</p>
<p>ETC has also jumped by a double-digit percentage (13%) and has reclaimed $20.</p>
<p>Most other altcoins are also in the green, which has helped the total crypto market cap add over $30 billion in a day and near $1.2 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257895" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257895" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-257895" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12-1024x458.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12-768x344.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12-1536x687.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-12-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257895" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<h2>BTC Tried $31K Again</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s most impressive price surge for the past few months came 10 days ago when the asset soared from $26,500 to over $30,000. It jumped to $31,500 in the following few days but failed there and remained relatively stagnant in a range between $30,000 and $31,000 ever since.</p>
<p>That changed yesterday when it briefly slipped below $30,000. However, that was short-lived, and the bulls took charge once again. They pushed the cryptocurrency north to $31,250 (on Bitstamp) earlier today, but it failed to continue upwards.</p>
<p>As of now, bitcoin trades just inches away from $31,000, and the rising altcoins have reduced some of its dominance over the market. Nevertheless, the metric is still above 50% on CMC.</p>
<p>The enhanced market volatility has resulted in over $130 million worth of liquidations as nearly 45,000 over-leveraged traders were wrecked in the past 24 hours.</p>
<figure id="attachment_257896" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-257896" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-257896" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-19-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-257896" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-cash-explodes-33-to-14-month-high-solana-and-litecoin-soar-15-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Cash Explodes 33% to 14-Month High, Solana and Litecoin Soar 15% (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Passes Bill Establishing Crypto and Stablecoins as Regulated Financial Activities</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-passes-bill-establishing-crypto-and-stablecoins-as-regulated-financial-activities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257873</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/UKUnitedKingdom.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/UKUnitedKingdom.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Britain has taken another step towards having a fully regulated crypto framework with the royal approval of the Financial Services and Markets Bill.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On June 28, King Charles III granted Royal Assent to a landmark bill to “regain control of the financial services rulebook.”</p>
<p>The Financial Services and Markets Bill 2023 was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-house-of-lords-approve-crypto-regulatory-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal">approved</a> by the upper chamber of the UK parliament on June 19.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/rocket-boost-for-uk-economy-as-financial-services-and-markets-bill-receives-royal-assent" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">bill</a> includes measures to bring crypto assets and stablecoins into the scope of regulation, giving them powers to oversee the digital asset sector.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f1ec-1f1e7.png" alt="🇬🇧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> The UK’s Financial Services &amp; Markets Bill has received Royal Assent, the final step for this major legislation, which brings <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/stablecoins?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#stablecoins</a> into the regulatory perimeter, designates <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#crypto</a> as regulated activity &amp; supervision of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#crypto</a> promotions<a href="https://t.co/wG4D3sgDgz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/wG4D3sgDgz</a></p>
<p>— Teana Baker-Taylor (@TeanaTaylor) <a href="https://twitter.com/TeanaTaylor/status/1674462519287590924?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 29, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Rocket Boost for UK Economy</h2>
<p>The Treasury described the bill as a “rocket boost” for the UK economy, which has been battered during the pandemic and its exit from Europe.</p>
<p>It clarified that the bill “enables the regulation of crypto assets to support their safe adoption in the UK.”</p>
<p>Economic Secretary to the Treasury, Andrew Griffith, said: “2023 is proving to be a banner year for reforming our financial services.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“This landmark piece of legislation gives us control of our financial services rulebook, so it supports UK businesses and consumers and drives growth.”</p></blockquote>
<p>During the formulation of the bill, amendments were made to include crypto as a regulated financial activity and to supervise crypto promotions and advertising. Stablecoins have also been included in the bill’s oversight of payment regulations.</p>
<p>The legislation could entice more crypto companies to the UK from the United States, which is currently trying to push them out by ‘carpet bombing’ the industry with <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-responds-to-coinbase-request-for-crypto-clarity-wants-more-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuits</a>.</p>
<p>Instead of rolling out its own regulatory framework, policymakers in America have been grappling over which agency will control the asset class. Furthermore, the Securities and Exchange Commission and its chair <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-lawyers-claim-gensler-offered-to-be-company-advisor/" data-wpel-link="internal">Gary Gensler</a> have taken acted on their own to proclaim that all digital assets aside from Bitcoin are securities.</p>
<p>Congress has yet to officially classify them as such, and the uncertainty is causing an exodus of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-gemini-launches-eth-staking-pro-in-the-uk/" data-wpel-link="internal">companies</a>, talent, innovation, and capital.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Crypto markets remain in consolidation, having gained just 1% on the day. As a result, total market capitalization remains around $1.21 trillion at the time of writing.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin prices</a> have barely moved, and the asset was trading for $30,400 during the Friday morning Asian session. It has failed to break resistance at this level but has also yet to pull back again.</p>
<p>Ethereum, which has been weaker recently, was flat on the day at $1,846. The only altcoins showing any progress at the time of writing were Solana (SOL) and Bitcoin Cash (BCH).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-passes-bill-establishing-crypto-and-stablecoins-as-regulated-financial-activities/" rel="nofollow">UK Passes Bill Establishing Crypto and Stablecoins as Regulated Financial Activities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paxos Gives USDP Stablecoin Access to Mexico With Mercado Libre Partnership</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paxos-gives-usdp-stablecoin-access-to-mexico-with-mercado-libre-partnership/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 04:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paxos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257675</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/paxos_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/paxos_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Paxos's Pax Dollar (USDP) is a regulated stablecoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain fintech company Paxos has announced partnering with online marketplace Mercado Libre to bring the Pax Dollar (USDP) stablecoin to users in Mexico. Transactions will be facilitated by MercadoPago, which happens to be a digital wallet app by Mercado Libre.</p>
<p>The latest move is part of Paxos&#8217; vision to position itself as an &#8220;established leader&#8221; in digital assets throughout the region. Data cited by the company stated that over 60% of its active wallets currently support customers in Latin America.</p>
<h2>Paxos&#8217;s Presence in Latin America</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://paxos.com/2023/06/28/paxos-partners-with-mercado-pago-to-open-access-to-pax-dollar-usdp-for-mexican-customers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, Paxos said that the adoption of USDP by Mercado Pago in Mexico further builds on the established partnership between the fintech firms, as Mexican users will now be able to access the regulated stablecoin via Mercado Pago.</p>
<p>In a statement, Arnoldo Reyes, Head of Latin America of Paxos, highlighted the increasing demand for &#8220;transformational technology&#8221; by digital asset consumers in the region. He added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Mexico is one of the most active marketplaces for digital assets with millions of users tapping into the ecosystem to gain access to key financial services. The launch of USDP within Mercado Pago represents another way that Mercado Libre continues to democratize access to commerce and financial services through innovative digital asset solutions throughout Latin America.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Paxos-issued stablecoin, USDP, is subject to strict regulatory oversight by the New York State Department of Financial Services. USDP reserves are held in cash and cash equivalents, while its attestation reports are issued by WithumSmith+Brown, PC, which happens to be an independent third-party accounting firm.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the company website states that Withum’s examination is carried out in accordance with attestation standards set up by the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (AICPA).</p>
<h2>Push For Stablecoin Regulations</h2>
<p>The stablecoin market has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-market-cap-marks-the-biggest-increase-in-3-months/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">grown</a> significantly over the past decade. Despite much new proliferation, the ecosystem has not managed to steer away from backlash and FUD. In fact, Paxos&#8217;s development comes amidst growing calls for stablecoin-related regulations across the world, especially after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/global-watchdogs-to-regulate-stablecoins-following-terrausd-ust-fiasco/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">TerraUSD&#8217;s</a> (UST) collapse and the subsequent FTX implosion.</p>
<p>Italy’s top banking authority, for one, <a href="https://twitter.com/bancaditalia/status/1673310957743886336" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">released</a> a new report titled &#8220;Markets, Infrastructures and Payment Systems,&#8221; calling on regulators to implement the same financial conduct standards for stablecoin issuers in the industry. It said that regulating stablecoins is crucial because of its close ties with the DeFi market.</p>
<p>Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA) <a href="https://www.thestandard.com.hk/section-news/section/2/253257/HKMA-seeks-views-on-stablecoins" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">aims</a> to roll out a regulatory framework for stablecoins by the end of 2024 and is currently in the process of seeking public views regarding the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxos-gives-usdp-stablecoin-access-to-mexico-with-mercado-libre-partnership/" rel="nofollow">Paxos Gives USDP Stablecoin Access to Mexico With Mercado Libre Partnership</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ledger Jumps Into Institutional Trading Tech Market With Tradelink&#8217;s Launch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-jumps-into-institutional-trading-tech-market-with-tradelinks-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 21:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ledger]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257604</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ledger_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ledger_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tradelink purpotedly reduces transaction charges by 80%. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Prominent crypto wallet service provider Ledger has announced the launch of a new trading and settlement network technology dubbed Tradelink.</p>
<p>The new product offering is designed for asset managers, custodians, and exchanges/OTC with off-exchange trading capabilities and aims to eliminate unnecessary complexities while simultaneously boosting operational speed.</p>
<ul>
<li>As per the company&#8217;s <a href="https://enterprise.ledger.com/tradelink/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">website</a>, Tradelink enables trade on multiple exchanges without on-chain liquidity re-balancing, as well as retaining custodial ownership of assets with off-exchange trading.</li>
<li>Other benefits include allowing mitigation of trading collateral risks across multiple third-party platforms, easy integration with preferred counter-parties, streamlined operations, and zero-transaction fees, among others.</li>
<li>At launch, partners will include asset managers such as Laser Digital and Hodl Group, digital asset trading and orchestration platforms such as Wyden, OTC brokers/providers, and platform partners such as Crypto.com, Bitstamp, Huobi, Wintermute, Coinsquare, NDAX, etc., will be in early stage access to all Ledger Enterprise clients at no additional cost.</li>
<li>Following the development, Sebastien Badault, VP of Enterprise Revenue at Ledger,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By unlocking better trading options for enterprises, we are empowering asset managers, custodians, and exchanges to navigate the changing landscape with confidence while making the whole ecosystem a safer and more transparent place.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Ledger recently came under fire from its online user after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-under-fire-for-allegedly-exposing-user-seed-phrases/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">releasing</a> a controversial update that sparked concerns of major security flaws exposure by the manufacturer, which later issued a statement clarifying its decision to delay the launch.</li>
<li>The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-taps-1-4-billion-valuation-after-securing-109-million-funding/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">secured</a> a $109 Million Series C extension fundraising round, tapping $1.4 billion in valuation this year with two more to go.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-jumps-into-institutional-trading-tech-market-with-tradelinks-launch/" rel="nofollow">Ledger Jumps Into Institutional Trading Tech Market With Tradelink&#8217;s Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Canadian Lawmakers Publish Report Defending And Supporting Crypto, Coinbase Approves</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-lawmakers-publish-report-defending-and-supporting-crypto-coinbase-approves/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 20:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257861</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/canada_flag-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/canada_flag-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Canadian House members want the government to protect citizens’ right to self custody, and recognize stablecoins as distinct from other cryptos.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Canadian House committee published a report on Wednesday providing 16 recommendations for how the nation’s government should regulate the blockchain industry – and they’re remarkably bullish.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Coinbase praised the report, saying it was “encouraged by the forward-thinking approach of the parliamentary committee.”</p>
<h2>Opening Canada to Crypto</h2>
<p>In its first <a href="https://www.ourcommons.ca/DocumentViewer/en/44-1/INDU/report-15/page-18" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recommendation</a>, The Parliamentary Standing Committee on Industry and Technology (INDU) asked that the Canadian government recognize blockchain as a growing industry with the potential to create jobs and foster economic growth.</p>
<p>The committee’s position mimics that of British Prime Minister <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-uk-prime-minister-rishi-sunak-crypto-believer-or-cbdc-backer/" data-wpel-link="internal">Rishi Sunak</a>, who spearheaded a newly passed bill to recognize crypto transactions as legitimate, regulated financial activity.</p>
<p>Canada’s Prime Minister <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-bitcoin-seizures-and-freezing-bank-accounts-canada-finally-ends-emergencies-act/" data-wpel-link="internal">Justin Trudeau</a> has generally been dismissive of crypto, but his conservative political rival <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadas-new-conservative-party-leader-is-a-crypto-proponent/" data-wpel-link="internal">Pierre Poilievre</a> is proudly pro-Bitcoin.</p>
<p>The composition of the House committee is slightly left-leaning, but in some ways better resembles Poilievre’s position. Regarding the Bitcoin mining industry, the report suggests maintaining a “neutral and equitable position” to “foster a competitive digital asset mining environment” and “attract investments.”</p>
<p>It suggested investigating “equity between provinces” in its application of the Excise Tax Act to the mining industry to “ensure fair taxation.” In the United States, the Biden Administration recommended a debilitating 30% excise tax specifically targeted at miners in May (which has been <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-scraps-plans-for-bitcoin-mining-excise-tax-congressman-confirms/" data-wpel-link="internal">cast aside</a> for the time being).</p>
<p>Canadian lawmakers also advocated for protecting individuals’ “right to self custody”, and for providing ease of access to “safe and reliable on and off ramps.”</p>
<h2>Coinbase Responds</h2>
<p>Canada’s report was a breath of fresh air for Coinbase, which has frequently criticized the lack of regulatory clarity and hostility from the United States, where it is headquartered.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/canadian-lawmakers-back-blockchain-with-landmark-recommendations" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">response letter</a>, the company showed a particular fondness for the committee’s stablecoin recommendation, advocating a “unique regulatory approach” to such assets.</p>
<p>“Stablecoins, a type of cryptocurrency pegged to a stable asset like fiat currency, present novel regulatory considerations,” wrote Coinbase. “This tailored approach will enable effective oversight while promoting innovation.”</p>
<p>Canada’s <a href="https://www.osc.ca/sites/default/files/2023-02/csa_20230222_21-332_crypto-trading-platforms-pre-reg-undertakings.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">current position</a> on stablecoins is that they are securities – a position not shared by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) appears to also think they’re securities, given its recent lawsuit against Binance alleging that its stablecoin BUSD fits the bill.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-lawmakers-publish-report-defending-and-supporting-crypto-coinbase-approves/" rel="nofollow">Canadian Lawmakers Publish Report Defending And Supporting Crypto, Coinbase Approves</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DYDX Announces New Date for Its Cosmos-Based Public Testnet</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-announces-new-date-for-its-cosmos-based-public-testnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 19:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=257769</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/dydx.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/dydx.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DYDX will release its public testnet on July 5, which is weeks earlier than previously announced. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DYDX Foundation, the non-profit organization behind the popular decentralized exchange (DEX) DYDX, has announced a new launch date for the public testnet of its Cosmos-based blockchain as it prepares to exit the Ethereum ecosystem later this year.</p>
<p>According to the foundation, the testnet is set to go live next week on July 5, which is earlier than the previous schedule. The team estimated in March that the public testnet would launch by the end of July after the third milestone (private testnet).</p>
<h2>DYDX Announces Public Testnet</h2>
<p>The upcoming release is the fourth phase of DYDX&#8217;s five-stage milestones to test its Cosmos-based blockchain before the full release of the mainnet.</p>
<p>During the private testnet, the team made several improvements to the network, including enabling documentation for market makers and validators, limit orders, dynamic funding rates, and ABCI 2.0 and other features of <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cosmos-chains-can-evolve-into-polkadot-parachains-thanks-to-new-sdk/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cosmos-SDK</a>.</p>
<p>The public testnet will allow users to test and explore more features, including accessing order books, account balances, order history, and market data. It will also include many validators running the network&#8217;s software.</p>
<p>Although the upcoming testnet will initially support only Bitcoin and Ethereum markets, the project plans to expand the network to include at least 30 markets in the future.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are happy to announce that we completed Milestone 4 ahead of schedule! Our public testnet is set to go live on July 5 at 17:00 UTC. This public testnet will launch with Bitcoin and Ethereum markets but we anticipate that the open-source software will include approximately 30+ markets as the network gets upgraded,&#8221; DYDX <a href="https://dydx.exchange/blog/public-testnet" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We are thrilled to announce that the dYdX Chain public testnet is set to launch on 7/05/2023 at 17:00 UTC! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f973.png" alt="🥳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/TD5caN6VSQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/TD5caN6VSQ</a></p>
<p>— dYdX (@dYdX) <a href="https://twitter.com/dYdX/status/1674124130462109699?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 28, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p></blockquote>
<h2>Exiting Ethereum</h2>
<p>On successful completion of the testnet, the DEX will move on to the last milestone (v5) before the eventual launch of the mainnet, which will see it migrate from Ethereum to Cosmos around September.</p>
<p>DYDX said <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchains-and-the-scalability-problem/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum&#8217;s scalability issue</a> was the primary reason it intends to move away from the network. The project noted that Ethereum could no longer process transactions fast enough, even after exploring several <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-are-layer-2-scaling-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">layer2 solutions</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dydx-announces-new-date-for-its-cosmos-based-public-testnet/" rel="nofollow">DYDX Announces New Date for Its Cosmos-Based Public Testnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
