<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:19:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>OpenEx Closes Funding Round</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/openex-closes-funding-round/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261676</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Beige_Minimalist_Rectangular_Menu_Collage_Cafe_Ins_1689852002EttCCgnBpB.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Beige_Minimalist_Rectangular_Menu_Collage_Cafe_Ins_1689852002EttCCgnBpB.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, July 20th, 2023] OpenEx Closed Funding Round to build an industry-unique hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, aiming to be the Hybrid,CEX+DEX, where certified partners can act as their own liquidity provider. OpenEx today announced it has its Pre-A close for a valuation of 50 Million USD. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, July 20th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>OpenEx Closed Funding Round to build an industry-unique hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, aiming to be the Hybrid,CEX+DEX, where certified partners can act as their own liquidity provider.</p>
<p>OpenEx today announced it has its Pre-A close for a valuation of 50 Million USD. The round includes prominent names in the Web3 space, including <a href="https://www.csquared.vc/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">C²</a> Ventures, Agallochum Capital, TKX Capital, Future Moneys, String Capital, and many other Web3 industry leaders. The new funding will be used to better the trading experience on the products.</p>
<p>The downfall of FTX reveals the chronic illness of the industry: many crypto exchanges enter the market to trade and form opposite trades with users leading to the exchange being exposed to huge price risks, rampant insider trading, and imperfect risk controls leading to user security issues such as capital safety.</p>
<p>By allowing certified partners to own their decentralized trading pool, autonomy and membership sovereignty is at the forefront. OpenEx’s core principles are neutrality, fairness, and impartiality. With decentralized trading pools, OpenEx will ensure fairness and foster increased participation in the trading ecosystem.</p>
<p>“OpenEx is growing at an exponential rate and we look forward to pushing out more fun and innovative products to our supporters,” said Bob Chien, Chief Business Officer of OpenEx, “Given the current market situation, we will soon initiate our trade mining program, where users will be rewarded as they trade.”</p>
<p>“Based on the OpenEx infrastructure and ecosystem, important links and participants of traditional financial markets, like brokers, will be able to provide more customized services to users in different regions and with different experience profiles.” stated Chris Lee from TKX Capital.</p>
<p>When asked about the future of OpenEx, CEO Jake Stolarski, replies, “We are here to democratize the traditional CEX model, with a focus on user empowerment and freedom, we hope that we can build a beginner-friendly platform that ensures fair transactions and personalized services.”</p>
<p>OpenEx has been online for nearly 3 months and already has an active community of over 100,000 monthly active users, with 60,000+ registered users and members respectively. The daily trading volume is approximately around 100 million USD.</p>
<p><strong>About OpenEx</strong></p>
<p>OpenEx is building an industry-unique new-generation hybrid exchange model that integrates centralization and decentralization, attracting diverse market entities through diverse trading modules to maximize liquidity creation and the most efficient pricing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openex-closes-funding-round/" rel="nofollow">OpenEx Closes Funding Round</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitget Expands Into the Middle East and Hires More Staff</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-expands-into-the-middle-east-and-hires-more-staff/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 23:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dubai]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261567</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitget.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitget.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exchange might recruit up to 60 people and select Dubai as an operational hub for the region. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading cryptocurrency exchange Bitget revealed its plans to expand into the Middle East region, specifically the United Arab Emirates and Bahrain. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The financial heart of the UAE &#8211; Dubai &#8211; has turned into a hotbed of cryptocurrency activity, attracting numerous companies with its friendly approach to the industry. Binance, Bybit, OKX, and other exchanges have recently obtained approval to offer services in the area. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Move Focused on &#8216;Core Values&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.prnewswire.com/in/news-releases/bitget-targets-middle-east-as-next-region-for-business-expansion-301881737.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announcement</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Bitget is preparing to expand its presence in the Middle East by establishing regional headquarters and recruiting more team members in the next two years. The new employees will be responsible for certain mid-office and back-office duties.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We hope to scale our Middle East team rapidly to support business growth, with between 30 to 60 hires over the next two years or more across the Middle East region. New team members will include various mid-office and back-office functions.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitget revealed that it might pick Dubai as an operational hub for the Middle East market. Managing Director Gracy Chen said this move &#8220;is not just about business, it is about our core values, which rest on advancing blockchain and crypto adoption worldwide.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange has already started exploring ways to secure the necessary licenses from domestic regulators. The step is considered a top priority since it will support expansion and enable the firm to open regional offices.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitget has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-bitget-expands-to-africa-plans-to-hire-400-new-workers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">displayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its intentions to increase its workforce by 50% (going from 800 workers to 1200) in Africa. Engineers and marketing professionals are among those that could aid its expansion mission on the continent. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitget&#8217;s Recent Success</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the market&#8217;s decline last year and the numerous negative events in the crypto sector, the exchange inked some major partnerships. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For one, it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-continuing-the-successful-journey-as-juventus-official-sleeve-partner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">continued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its collaboration with the Italian soccer giant &#8211; Juventus. It also</span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-partners-with-leo-messi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> teamed up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the seven-time Balon d&#8217;Or winner &#8211; Lionel &#8220;Leo&#8221; Messi. The athlete serves as a brand ambassador of the exchange, and some of his duties include introducing Bitget&#8217;s products and services to sports fans and organizations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Interestingly, the exchange emerged as one of the winners following the gigantic collapse of FTX. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-post-ftx-effect-bybit-kraken-and-bitget-with-growing-trading-volumes-nansen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">increased</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its derivatives trading volume to $204 billion. The average figure was $194 billion six months before the meltdown. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-expands-into-the-middle-east-and-hires-more-staff/" rel="nofollow">Bitget Expands Into the Middle East and Hires More Staff</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BitMEX Extends its Partnership With the Italian Soccer Club AC Milan</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitmex-extends-its-partnership-with-the-italian-soccer-club-ac-milan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMEX]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261623</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BitMEXMilan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/BitMEXMilan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BitMEX became the Premium Partner of AC Milan as part of the new agreement terms. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The cryptocurrency exchange BitMEX announced that it had extended its collaboration with one of the most successful Italian soccer teams &#8211; AC Milan. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This could be considered another proof that the company continues its recovery following the prolonger bear market last year when it laid off employees and saw its CEO resigning from his post.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Renewing the Partnership</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BitMEX <a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/ac-milan-partnership-update/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">disclosed</a> that it has transitioned to a Premium Partner of AC Milan according to the new terms. The exchange initially inked a Sleeve Sponsorship with the sports club in 2021. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company reminded about the numerous mutual initiatives launched with AC Milan over the past few years, such as celebrating its 19th Serie A title in 2022 and backing Fondazione Milan (a project aiming to support youngsters and local communities).</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;In the years ahead, we&#8217;ll be committed to organizing similar events and offering exclusive benefits to our fans worldwide,&#8221; BitMEX assured.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ac-milan-teams-up-with-bitmex-to-launch-its-first-ever-nft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year, the partners also released limited edition non-fungible tokens (NFTs), promising to use the proceeds to support Fondazione Milan&#8217;s efforts. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Casper Stylsvig &#8211; Chief Revenue Officer of AC Milan &#8211; said the team is &#8220;happy&#8221; to continue its &#8220;journey alongside a partner such as BitMEX.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stephan Lutz &#8211; CEO of the crypto platform &#8211; said the associates &#8220;appreciate and applaud the spirit of competition and the sense of connection that comes from it.&#8221; As such, the company is &#8220;thrilled&#8221; to have extended its deal with the club.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">AC Milan is the second most-successful Italian soccer team (in terms of winning domestic championships). However, it has performed much better on the European scene, lifting the Champions League trophy seven times &#8211; a record for an Italian club.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto and Soccer </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BitMEX is not the only digital asset entity that has teamed up with a popular European soccer club. The world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange Binance serves as the t-shirt sponsor of Lazio; Bitget </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-continuing-the-successful-journey-as-juventus-official-sleeve-partner/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">cooperated </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">with Juventus, whereas the reigning Italian champion SSC Napoli inked an agreement with Upbit. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the most famous soccer teams across the globe &#8211; Manchester United &#8211; also dipped its toes in the world of crypto. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/manchester-united-unveils-a-training-kit-sponsorship-with-tezos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">collaborated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the blockchain platform Tezos in February 2022 to put the latter&#8217;s logo on its training apparel.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For their part, two of the biggest soccer stars from the last decades &#8211; Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-partners-with-soccer-legend-cristiano-ronaldo-to-launch-exclusive-nft-collections/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">partnered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with Binance and Bitget, respectively. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitmex-extends-its-partnership-with-the-italian-soccer-club-ac-milan/" rel="nofollow">BitMEX Extends its Partnership With the Italian Soccer Club AC Milan</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Government Sells Another 8,200 Bitcoin, On-Chain Data Confirms</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-government-sells-another-8200-bitcoin-on-chain-data-confirms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 20:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261704</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The US government is slowly but surely ridding itself of its BTC connected to Silk Road. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On-chain analysts at CryptoQuant have confirmed previous rumors that the United States government has sold another large batch of Bitcoin (BTC) connected to the defunct darknet marketplace, Silk Road. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In a report shared with </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400">, the firm said that the firm sold 8,200 BTC from Silk Road hacker James Zhong on July 12.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">This was slightly under </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dump-incoming-us-government-moves-another-9000-btc-from-silk-road/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">previous estimates</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, indicating that the government had moved roughly 9,826 from its known wallets. It’s also less than the government’s first confirmed sale of 9,861 BTC for $216 million in March. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Most of the coins were moved in a single transaction of 9,319 BTC, which sent 8200 BTC to one address, and 1119 BTC to another. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The former address “ forwarded the 8,200 Bitcoin to different addresses, [and] each address received 79 Bitcoin,” wrote CryptoQuant. “These coins were eventually deposited into exchanges or recombined into fewer wallets.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Though not confirmed, the other address with 1119 BTC is believed to be controlled by the government. “This address is highly likely the change address of the transaction,” it said. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The firm said that the government still holds 195,307 BTC. These are related to seizures from other criminal incidents, including the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitfinex-returns-portion-of-assets-stolen-from-2016-hack/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitfinex hack</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.<br />
</span></li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_261706" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261706" style="width: 1009px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261706 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729.png" alt="" width="1009" height="527" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729.png 1009w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729-300x157.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729-768x401.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-160729-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1009px) 100vw, 1009px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261706" class="wp-caption-text">US Government Bitcoin Balance. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-government-sells-another-8200-bitcoin-on-chain-data-confirms/" rel="nofollow">US Government Sells Another 8,200 Bitcoin, On-Chain Data Confirms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bullish Ripple Ruling May Have Triggered Altcoin Season: CryptoQuant Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bullish-ripple-ruling-may-have-triggered-altcoin-season-cryptoquant-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoin Season]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Altcoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261697</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/altcoins_cover-2.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/altcoins_cover-2.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A number of market signals show rising interest in altcoins over the past week thanks to a judge’s favorable ruling on XRP’s legal status.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The landmark victory for Ripple in its lawsuit against the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) may have ignited a bull market for neighboring altcoins, according to a recent report from CryptoQuant.</p>
<p>The crypto market intelligence firm provided a series of stats reflecting growth in altcoin market activity over the past week, versus relative stagnancy within the Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) markets.</p>
<h2>The Return of Alt Season</h2>
<p>When analyzing price performance based on market capitalization, CryptoQuant&#8217;s data shows that MidCaps, which include XRP, outperformed other groups of cryptocurrencies, soaring by 29% on June 13th.</p>
<p>This included other cryptocurrencies that had previously been categorized as securities by the SEC in its lawsuit against Coinbase last month. The movements in the market caps of such coins – including Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and others – are plotted against those of BTC and ETH in the chart below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261698" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261698" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261698 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724-1024x542.png" alt="" width="1024" height="542" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724-1024x542.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724-300x159.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724-768x406.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724-50x26.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Screenshot-2023-07-20-134724.png 1053w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261698" class="wp-caption-text">Crypto SECurities Index. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Received on July 13, the summary judgment in the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-landmark-ripple-xrp-court-ruling-congressmen-slam-gensler-and-sec-for-predatory-approach/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple V. SEC</a> lawsuit ruled that XRP itself is not a security, nor are sales of the token on secondary markets securities transactions.</p>
<p>This marks the first time a cryptocurrency company has successfully fought off the SEC&#8217;s claims in a legal case that all crypto assets <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-reasserts-every-crypto-is-a-security-aside-from-bitcoin-lawyers-disagree/" data-wpel-link="internal">aside from Bitcoin</a> are securities.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Unaffected</h2>
<p>Though Bitcoin briefly rallied to $31,700 after the landmark ruling, its price has since retraced to ~$30,000 and remains rangebound.</p>
<p>Failing to maintain an elevated price level, the top asset’s market dominance has partially fallen, putting it back under 50%, according to TradingView.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s open interest also remained unaffected, despite ETH open interest rising substantially from $2.2 million to $2.7 million since that time. In terms of funding rates, XRP doesn’t appear to have substantially affected market sentiment.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We can witness mixed sentiments among derivatives traders as Bitcoin funding is relatively high while Ethereum’s funding rates just turned negative,” wrote CryptoQuant.</p></blockquote>
<p>Finally, analysts found that short-term sentiment among traders remains negative when observing Bitcoin and Ethereum’s Taker Buy Sell Ratio – a measure of buy and sell pressure for each asset. Both cryptos ratios are current &lt;1, meaning taker buy volumes are greater than taker sell volumes, reflecting bearish attitudes.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bullish-ripple-ruling-may-have-triggered-altcoin-season-cryptoquant-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bullish Ripple Ruling May Have Triggered Altcoin Season: CryptoQuant Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Compliance First: Binance&#8217;s Commitment to High Regulatory Standards and Trust</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/compliance-first-binances-commitment-to-high-regulatory-standards-and-trust/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261657</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency industry has undoubtedly witnessed tremendous growth and innovation since its inception, attracting millions of users and billions of dollars in investment. However, as the industry evolves, it faces increased scrutiny from regulators worldwide. For this reason, Binance, the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange, has taken significant steps to establish a robust compliance program and [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry has undoubtedly witnessed tremendous growth and innovation since its inception, attracting millions of users and billions of dollars in investment. However, as the industry evolves, it faces increased scrutiny from regulators worldwide. For this reason, Binance, the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange, has taken significant steps to establish a robust compliance program and assemble a dedicated team to ensure it complies with global regulations while fostering trust within the digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<h2>Building Compliance Culture</h2>
<p>Recognizing the importance of compliance in a rapidly evolving regulatory landscape, Binance has made substantial investments in developing a comprehensive compliance framework. The exchange has prioritized compliance as a core value, aiming to set the highest standards in the industry.</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s compliance program starts with a strong commitment from its leadership, emphasizing adherence to local and global regulatory requirements. This commitment is evident in the company&#8217;s proactive approach to working with regulators worldwide, seeking transparency and collaboration to shape responsible and sustainable regulations for the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>Establishing a Robust Compliance Team</h2>
<p>At the heart of Binance&#8217;s compliance efforts is its dedicated team, comprising legal experts, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-hires-former-fca-and-finra-regulators-to-strengthen-global-compliance-efforts/" data-wpel-link="internal">compliance officers</a>, and experienced professionals from various regulatory backgrounds. The team&#8217;s primary objective is to ensure that Binance adheres to the evolving regulatory landscape while driving industry-wide compliance initiatives.</p>
<p>Binance has strategically recruited professionals with deep knowledge of regulatory frameworks to ensure a thorough understanding of legal requirements across jurisdictions. By hiring individuals with diverse expertise, Binance has built a <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/community/playing-by-the-rules-an-overview-of-binances-compliance-program-7787599269355947143" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">compliance team</a> capable of navigating the complex regulatory landscape and proactively addressing emerging challenges.</p>
<p>For instance, the company has a Financial Crimes Compliance team that comprises a 150-staff workforce responsible for handling several tasks to combat financial misconduct on the platform. The team is structured into distinct roles, including a law enforcement response team, a global training team, and a team focused on handling suspicious activity reports.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-225492" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_binance_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/cryptocurrency_binance_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p>The Financial Crimes Compliance team is responsible for detecting and preventing financial vices such as money laundering and fraud, ensuring the protection of the company and its customers from potential risks. Highlighting the team&#8217;s significance, Tigran Gambaryan, the Head of Financial Crimes Compliance at Binance, emphasized their achievements, <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/community/what-does-the-binance-compliance-and-investigations-team-do-hear-from-our-experts-6727196362408244261" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealing</a> that they successfully managed &#8220;over 50,000 law enforcement requests&#8221; in 2022.</p>
<p>Aside from its Financial Crimes Compliance team, Binance has established several specialized divisions to ensure it continues to adhere to global regulations while mitigating risks. The units include the Global Money Laundering Reporting Officer (GMLRO) division, the Sanctions, Anti-Bribery &amp; Corruption (ABC), and Counter-Terrorist Financing (CTF) division, the Corporate Compliance division, the Customer Due Diligence (CDD) division, the High-Risk Clients division, and the Transaction Monitoring division.</p>
<p>The GMLRO team, consisting of four regional heads and over 60 experts, works closely with law enforcement agencies, regulators, and financial intelligence units to ensure compliance with anti-money laundering (AML) laws.</p>
<p>Similarly, the Sanctions, ABC, and CTF team, comprising approximately 40 individuals, develops policies and controls to minimize risks related to sanctions violations, anti-bribery and corruption laws, and counter-terrorist financing measures.</p>
<p>The Corporate Compliance team is made up of professionals with experience in crypto, payments, and traditional banking. They monitor compliance controls, test them, and embed them in all Binance products and services. The unit also handles regulatory examinations, audits, third-party due diligence efforts, and compliance training.</p>
<p>The CDD team focuses on verifying the identities of Binance users and business partners through Know-Your-Customer (KYC) and Know-Your-Business (KYB) initiatives, thereby preventing fraudulent activities and money laundering.</p>
<p>The High-Risk Clients team collaborates with the CDD team to oversee enhanced due diligence for high-risk users and businesses, implementing rigorous verification measures and advising the &#8220;first line of defense&#8221; on matters related to the source of funds and wealth verification.</p>
<p>Lastly, the company&#8217;s Transaction Monitoring team, consisting of 18 leads and 175 analysts, conducts transaction audits using advanced analytical tools to detect money laundering and terrorist financing activities, ensuring compliance with global regulations in these areas.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-225203" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" alt="binance_bitcoin_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Final Thoughts</h2>
<p>Binance&#8217;s strong compliance program and dedicated team highlight the exchange&#8217;s commitment to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-rebuilding-trust-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">upholding trust</a> and regulatory compliance within the crypto space. By leveraging the expertise of professionals from various domains and implementing stringent compliance measures, Binance aims to foster a secure and compliant environment for its users.</p>
<p>As the industry continues to evolve, Binance&#8217;s proactive approach to compliance sets an example for other platforms, emphasizing the importance of regulatory adherence for long-term success and protecting crypto users and stakeholders.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/compliance-first-binances-commitment-to-high-regulatory-standards-and-trust/" rel="nofollow">Compliance First: Binance&#8217;s Commitment to High Regulatory Standards and Trust</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>2 Crypto Investors Leave Sequoia Capital Following Botched FTX Investment: Bloomberg</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/2-crypto-investors-leave-sequoia-capital-following-botched-ftx-investment-bloomberg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261632</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Sequoia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Sequoia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Among the latest departures at Sequoia Capital, are two investors who were involved in the company’s failed FTX investment. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Major venture capital firm Sequoia Capital has seen the departure of five key partners, including two investors who were involved in the company’s failed investment in Sam Bankman-Fried’s bankrupt crypto exchange, FTX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While Sequoia claimed that the collapse of FTX had no significant impact on the firm, the VC was accused of promoting FTX.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Sequoia Reports Departure of Five Investors</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Sequoia Capital, which recently revealed its decision to <a href="https://twitter.com/sequoia/status/1666029996455112704?s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">split</a> into three independent partnerships — with its businesses in China and India/Southeast Asia adopting new names by March 2024, while the US/Europe branch will retail the Sequoia Capital name — announced five investor departures, according to a note to limited partners on Wednesday (July 19, 2023) <span style="font-weight: 400;">as <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-19/sequoia-shakeup-sees-mike-moritz-depart-along-with-two-crypto-vcs?accessToken=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJzb3VyY2UiOiJTdWJzY3JpYmVyR2lmdGVkQXJ0aWNsZSIsImlhdCI6MTY4OTgzMjA5NCwiZXhwIjoxNjkwNDM2ODk0LCJhcnRpY2xlSWQiOiJSWTJFOTVEV0xVNjgwMSIsImJjb25uZWN0SWQiOiIwODk4M0I3NjQ0RDk0NUZGQTFCRTk3QzQ4NjgxQzNEQyJ9.LOan3ANUUtQZYc43Tlm8oA0UH5J5FTM7a2253J8T7S4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">seen</a> by </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Bloomberg</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of the notable departing partners is Michael Moritz, who has been with Sequoia Capital for nearly 40 years. Moritz will move to Sequoia Heritage, a wealth fund he helped found in 2010, and will assume a senior advisory capacity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The Managing Partner of Sequoia Capital, Roelof Botha, acknowledged Moritz&#8217;s contribution to the company, stating that he helped establish the firm as one of the leading technology investment groups in the world. Partners Kais Khimji and Mike Vernal are also leaving the venture capital giant.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The remaining two departing investors are Michelle Fradin, who led Sequoia&#8217;s decision to invest in FTX, and partner Daniel Chen, who was previously at Andreessen Horowitz and describes himself as a &#8220;crypto maxi&#8221; according to his Twitter bio.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Sequoia Capital invested $213.5 million in FTX through its Global Fund Trust III and SCGE Fund. However, the investment did not prove fruitful following the collapse of what was one of the biggest crypto exchanges in the industry, FTX.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The venture capital firm subsequently marked down its investment to zero while stating that it conducted due diligence before making its investment. Sequoia further assured investors that its exposure to the bankrupt crypto exchange had no effect on the company.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Sequoia Faces Backlash for FTX Investment</h2>
<p dir="ltr">However, Sequoia&#8217;s decision to invest in FTX has not been without criticism. In February, the firm, along with other VC companies, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sequoia-capital-paradigm-thoma-bravo-accused-of-promoting-the-legitimacy-of-ftx-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> in an investor lawsuit of promoting FTX, stating that they added an &#8220;air of legitimacy&#8221; to the collapsed crypto exchange.</p>
<p dir="ltr">FTX&#8217;s investment trading outfit Alameda Research recently <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DownloadPDF?id1=MTQ2MjIyOQ==&amp;id2=-1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reached a deal</a> to sell its stake in Sequoia Capital to Abu Dhabi-based Al Nawwar Investments RSC Limited for $45 million.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/2-crypto-investors-leave-sequoia-capital-following-botched-ftx-investment-bloomberg/" rel="nofollow">2 Crypto Investors Leave Sequoia Capital Following Botched FTX Investment: Bloomberg</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Will BTC Plummet to $28K or Explode Higher? 3 Factors to Watch (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/will-btc-plummet-to-28k-or-explode-higher-3-factors-to-watch-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261633</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Recently, the market has been relatively uneventful, with Bitcoin&#8217;s price showing slight volatility but lacking a clear direction. This uncertainty has left traders puzzled about what the next move might be. However, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price breaks above the $30K resistance region, there might be a positive turn, leading to a potential long-term uptrend. Bitcoin Price [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recently, the market has been relatively uneventful, with Bitcoin&#8217;s price showing slight volatility but lacking a clear direction.</p>
<p>This uncertainty has left traders puzzled about what the next move might be. However, if Bitcoin&#8217;s price breaks above the $30K resistance region, there might be a positive turn, leading to a potential long-term uptrend.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Taking a closer look at the daily chart, a bearish double-top pattern is visible near the major resistance zone at $30K. Moreover, the price is encountering strong dynamic resistance from the middle-trendline of the ascending channel, resulting in some rejection.</p>
<p>Additionally, an extended noticeable divergence between the price and the RSI indicator indicates a possible shift in market conditions. If the prevailing supply around this crucial region dominates the demand for the cryptocurrency, the next target might be around the $28.5K level, which aligns with the 100-day moving average.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261637" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261637" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261637 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2007231" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-Daily-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261637" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Shifting the focus to the 4-hour chart, it becomes apparent that the price has entered a prolonged consolidation range after reaching the critical price zone of $30K. Notably, this range coincides with the prior significant swing high, which has served strong resistance due to expanded supply.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the price has formed a broadening wedge pattern, often indicating a potential reversal. If Bitcoin breaks below the lower edge of the wedge, it might signal a mid-term reversal.</p>
<p>In conclusion, if the cryptocurrency faces rejection, its next target could be the static support region of around $28K.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261638" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261638" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261638 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_2007232" width="2560" height="1385" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-1536x831.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-2048x1108.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC-4H-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261638" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By</strong> <strong><a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>The premium of a fund, such as a Bitcoin trust, serves as an essential indicator of the market price&#8217;s excess over the fund&#8217;s Net Asset Value (NAV), representing its underlying assets. Over the period between January 2023 and today, the consistent growth of the premium for the Bitcoin trust indicates a notable surge in investor interest in acquiring this fund.</p>
<p>This trend is indicative of a rising demand for Bitcoin in the market.</p>
<p>As the premium for the Bitcoin trust continues its upward trend, it narrows the gap between its market price and the actual market value of Bitcoin contracts. This convergence is a clear indication that investors are becoming increasingly optimistic about the potential of Bitcoin, and they are willing to pay a higher premium to gain exposure to this digital asset.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261639" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261639" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261639 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_fund_market_premium_chart_2007231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin-Fund-Market-Premium-All-Symbol-EMA-14-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261639" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-btc-plummet-to-28k-or-explode-higher-3-factors-to-watch-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Will BTC Plummet to $28K or Explode Higher? 3 Factors to Watch (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>$BITCOIN Meme Coin Explodes and Makes Traders Rich &#8211; Could BTC20 Token Pump Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-meme-coin-explodes-and-makes-traders-rich-could-btc20-token-pump-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 14:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261642</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_btc20_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_btc20_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin market frenzy shows no signs of slowing, meaning opportunities for huge gains are always around the corner. One recent example is $BITCOIN, a new meme coin that has generated huge gains for early investors. As traders revel in the success of $BITCOIN, a new player called BTC20 has entered the market, generating [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin market frenzy shows no signs of slowing, meaning opportunities for huge gains are always around the corner.</p>
<p>One recent example is $BITCOIN, a new meme coin that has generated huge gains for early investors.</p>
<p>As traders revel in the success of $BITCOIN, a new player called BTC20 has entered the market, generating speculation as to whether it could become the next breakout star.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261647" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="585" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17-300x292.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture1-17-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<h2>Traders Cashing In on Explosive New Meme Coins with $BITCOIN Leading the Way</h2>
<p>HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu ($BITCOIN), a trending ERC-20 token, has captivated the meme coin community in recent weeks.</p>
<p>This unique token may boast a confusing design and lengthy name, but that has yet to stop investors from piling in and buying $BITCOIN in their droves.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.dextools.io/app/en/ether/pair-explorer/0x2cc846fff0b08fb3bffad71f53a60b4b6e6d6482" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">DEXTools</a>, $BITCOIN has surged over 34,000% from its Uniswap launch price and now has a market cap exceeding $77 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-25.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261645" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-25.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-25.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-25-300x122.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-25-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Thanks to this rapid price rise, $BITCOIN has obtained a listing on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/harrypotterobamasonic10inu-eth/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CoinMarketCap</a>, boosting its credibility even more.</p>
<p>All of this has come while $BITCOIN is only available to trade on the Uniswap DEX, which is a testament to the strong community interest and demand surrounding this meme coin.</p>
<p>The immense hype surrounding $BITCOIN has created the ideal conditions for early adopters to achieve massive gains &#8211; with one trader&#8217;s story standing out.</p>
<p>With an initial investment of just $16,076, this savvy investor saw their gamble transform into a small fortune as their position size rocketed to a value of $635,965.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261644" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-24.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="493" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-24.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-24-300x246.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-24-50x41.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The QBS Twitter account reported that this brought the investor&#8217;s total crypto portfolio value to over $741,000 – highlighting the remarkable possibilities on offer in the low-cap crypto space.</p>
<p>This trader&#8217;s story shows how promising identifying meme coin gems can be in the early stages of their life cycle.</p>
<p>While obviously requiring near-perfect timing and a healthy dose of luck, the prospect of life-changing wealth from coins like $BITCOIN continues to attract bold investors happy to stomach the risk.</p>
<h2>Could BTC20 be the Next Bitcoin-Inspired Token to Explode?</h2>
<p>As traders look for the next $BITCOIN, one new coin that’s catching attention is BTC20.</p>
<p>The recently launched BTC20 presale has attracted a surge of interest, raising over $340,000 in just three days.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=bitcoin-meme-coin-explodes-and-makes-traders-rich-could-btc20-token-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BTC20 ($BTC20)</a> is an ERC-20 token that offers a promising combination of price potential and innovative staking mechanics.</p>
<p>Launched with a presale already generating tremendous traction, $BTC20&#8217;s rise in the crypto space has begun turning heads.</p>
<p>Part of BTC20’s appeal lies in its unique stake-to-earn setup, which doesn’t require any advanced hardware or technical know-how to benefit from.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-18.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261643" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-18.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="295" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-18.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-18-300x147.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-18-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The BTC20 <a href="https://btc20.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a> states that at least 14.95 million tokens will go to the staking pool after the presale ends.  These tokens will be released gradually over about 120 years.</p>
<p>Interestingly, the more $BTC20 a user stakes, the more significant the percentage of the staking rewards they&#8217;ll receive.</p>
<p>In addition, the token’s low presale price of $1 and potential for enormous growth has already led to comparisons with $BITCOIN’s rise.</p>
<p>Just as $BITCOIN generated huge returns for early backers, investors are speculating that BTC20 could follow a similar trajectory.</p>
<p>Lastly, the fact that BTC20 is built on the Ethereum blockchain opens up possibilities for smart contract functionality.</p>
<p>It also enables integration with decentralized applications (dApps), further enhancing the token’s value proposition.</p>
<p>With BTC20’s <a href="https://t.me/BTC20Token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a> already growing rapidly, it’s clear there’s mounting enthusiasm around the project, setting the stage for an exciting few weeks ahead.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b__34851?referrer=bitcoin-meme-coin-explodes-and-makes-traders-rich-could-btc20-token-pump-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit BTC20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-meme-coin-explodes-and-makes-traders-rich-could-btc20-token-pump-next/" rel="nofollow">$BITCOIN Meme Coin Explodes and Makes Traders Rich &#8211; Could BTC20 Token Pump Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Who Replaces Do Kwon as Terraform Labs&#8217; New CEO (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-who-replaces-do-kwon-as-terraform-labs-new-ceo-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 13:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261586</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra_Green.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra_Green.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CEO Amani said it "makes sense" that Terraform Labs continues its operations without Do Kwon.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The blockchain company Terraform Labs has reportedly named Chris Amani its new Chief Executive Officer. He vowed to shift the entity&#8217;s products toward other directions and not offer algorithmic stablecoins. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The previous CEO, Do Kwon, resigned several months ago to focus on his legal issues. He is currently imprisoned in Montenegro, while the USA and South Korea have argued he is the main culprit behind the LUNA/UST crash last year, insisting on his extradition.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Steering Away From Stablecoins</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/jailed-crypto-tycoon-do-kwons-company-appoints-new-ceo-d58fa058" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by The Wall Street Journal, the former Chief Operating Officer and Chief Financial Officer of Terraform Labs &#8211; Chris Amani &#8211; has climbed to the position of CEO. The company raised hopes that the new boss will be the right pick for the role.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amani promised that his administration will develop applications that provide real utility, saying further details will be released in the following months.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The process won&#8217;t be easy, but we have a clear vision of where Terra fits within the broader Web3 ecosystem and are hyper-focused on executing against that vision. We look forward to sharing more on this soon,&#8221; he stated.<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_261619" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261619" style="width: 605px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani.jpeg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261619" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani.jpeg" alt="Chris Amani" width="605" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani.jpeg 1241w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani-300x198.jpeg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani-1024x677.jpeg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani-768x507.jpeg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Chris-Amani-50x33.jpeg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 605px) 100vw, 605px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261619" class="wp-caption-text">Chris Amani, Source: Technext</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amani also asserted that rebuilding Terraform Labs will exclude the offering of algorithmic stablecoins. Recall that the company-issued UST <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-valuable-lessons-from-terras-collapse-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">de-pegged</a> in the spring of 2022, dropping eventually to zero. It triggered colossal investor losses and had a negative impact on the entire cryptocurrency market.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, the newly-appointed CEO touched upon Do Kwon. While he wished the ex-boss all the best in his court battles, he outlined that it is essential for Terraform Labs to continue its course without him:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We wish Do the best, and we hope that he&#8217;s able to clear himself of all charges. But while he&#8217;s incarcerated and while he&#8217;s facing his own legal challenges, it just makes sense for us to continue on without him.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite his legal issues and the fact that he is no longer a CEO, Kwon remains the majority shareholder of Terraform Labs. According to court filings, he owns 92% of the firm&#8217;s shares.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">From a Crypto Tycoon to a Prisoner</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The South Korean developer Do Kwon, who is among the most recognizable names in the crypto industry, has had quite a journey in the past few years. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was on the crest of a wave while Terra&#8217;s native token &#8211; LUNA &#8211; was charting all-time highs. However, it all changed in May last year when UST lost its peg, causing an excessive amount of LUNA to be minted. This, in turn, triggered a price crash for the latter, with both tokens eventually plummeting to zero.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Instead of collaborating with the authorities, Kwon started moving from one country to another, limiting his engagement on social media platforms such as Twitter.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was finally arrested in March in Montenegro while trying to onboard a plane with forged documents. The magistrates </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-sentenced-to-4-months-in-prison-in-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">slammed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> him with a four-month jail sentence despite his claim that he had no idea the passport was fake. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, this punishment seems like a walk in the park compared to what might happen to him should he be found guilty of other accusations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kwon faces a maximum prison sentence of 40 years in South Korea and 100 years in the USA (depending on where the legal process will take place). Both nations have requested his deportation, alleging him of orchestrating a massive scam and defrauding Terra&#8217;s investors.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-who-replaces-do-kwon-as-terraform-labs-new-ceo-report/" rel="nofollow">This Is Who Replaces Do Kwon as Terraform Labs&#8217; New CEO (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
