<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Can This New Cryptocurrency Pump like the Bitcoin Price? BTC20 Crypto Presale is Live, Offers Stake to Earn</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-new-cryptocurrency-pump-like-bitcoin-price-btc20-crypto-presale-live-offers-stake-earn.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC) has posted an impressive summer season so far this year, following a stunning +25% pump in mid-June - which has has left price action high in consolidation above $30,000. &lt;br /&gt;
With the leading cryptocurrency now trading strong at $30,178 (a 24 hour change of -0.18%), many side-lined investors have begun to wonder whether it is too late to invest....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/can-new-cryptocurrency-pump-like-bitcoin-price-btc20-crypto-presale-live-offers-stake-earn.htm"&gt;Read More: Can This New Cryptocurrency Pump like the Bitcoin Price? BTC20 Crypto Presale is Live, Offers Stake to Earn&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-new-cryptocurrency-pump-like-bitcoin-price-btc20-crypto-presale-live-offers-stake-earn.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119835/318299/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1147723"/></item><item><title>Report: Crypto Investment Declines for Fifth Consecutive Quarter, Fails to Find Bottom</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-crypto-investment-declines-for-fifth-consecutive-quarter-fails-find-bottom.htm</link><description>Venture capital firms are continuing to invest less money in the crypto sector, after five consecutive quarters of declines, according to a new report from crypto financial services firm Galaxy Digital. &lt;br /&gt;
During the second quarter of this year, VC firms invested $2.3 billion in crypto and blockchain firms, a sharp decline from the same quarter a year earlier when $8 billion was invested, the report said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/report-crypto-investment-declines-for-fifth-consecutive-quarter-fails-find-bottom.htm"&gt;Read More: Report: Crypto Investment Declines for Fifth Consecutive Quarter, Fails to Find Bottom&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Investment</category><category>Galaxy Digital</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/report-crypto-investment-declines-for-fifth-consecutive-quarter-fails-find-bottom.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119839/318293/falling-investments.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="258327"/></item><item><title>FSB Releases Proposals For a Tougher Global Crypto Framework</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fsb-releases-proposals-for-tougher-global-crypto-framework.htm</link><description>The Financial Stability Board (FSB) has called for improved global digital asset regulation with the safety of user assets at the center of policies. &lt;br /&gt;
The international financial body which acts as a standard-setter rolled out plans to proffer recommendations to help curb the crypto-related turmoils that hit the market last year. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the body, the need for a strict regulatory framework is borne out of the principle of “same activity, same risk, same regulation.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fsb-releases-proposals-for-tougher-global-crypto-framework.htm"&gt;Read More: FSB Releases Proposals For a Tougher Global Crypto Framework&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FSB</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Global</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fsb-releases-proposals-for-tougher-global-crypto-framework.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119832/318289/pexels-sevenstorm-juhaszi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="3080516"/></item><item><title>Celsius Liquidates $25 Million In Altcoins After Court’s Approval To Move Funds</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-liquidates-25-million-altcoins-after-courts-approval-move-funds.htm</link><description>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius has liquidated nearly $25 million in different altcoins after a US court approved the firm to convert altcoins to BTC and ETH earlier this month.  &lt;br /&gt;
Celsius Network liquidated several altcoins worth nearly $25 million, including Chainlink (LINK), BNB coin, Synthetix Network (SNX), 1Inch, and 0x Protocol (ZRX), Shiba Inu’s BONE among others....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-liquidates-25-million-altcoins-after-courts-approval-move-funds.htm"&gt;Read More: Celsius Liquidates $25 Million In Altcoins After Court’s Approval To Move Funds&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Alex Mashinsky</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-liquidates-25-million-altcoins-after-courts-approval-move-funds.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119831/318282/celsius-altcoins-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99417"/></item><item><title>National Australia Bank Halts Payment to Crypto Platforms Where Scams Are ‘More Prevalent’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/national-australia-bank-halts-payment-crypto-platforms-where-scams-are-more-prevalent.htm</link><description>National Australia Bank (NAB), one of the ‘big four’ banks in the nation, has blocked some payments to “high-risk” crypto exchanges, where scams are “more prevalent.” &lt;br /&gt;
In an official statement, detailing new measures to protect customers from scams, NAB identified crypto scams as the fastest-growing security threat costing Australians A$221 million (US$151 million) in 2022 alone....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/national-australia-bank-halts-payment-crypto-platforms-where-scams-are-more-prevalent.htm"&gt;Read More: National Australia Bank Halts Payment to Crypto Platforms Where Scams Are ‘More Prevalent’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/national-australia-bank-halts-payment-crypto-platforms-where-scams-are-more-prevalent.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119816/318254/pexels-ben-mack-5707610.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="5104661"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Jumps Up 5% – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-jumps-up-5-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Terra Luna Classic (LUNC) has jumped by as much as 5% in the past 24 hours, with the altcoin currently sitting on a 13% gain in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
At $0.00009271, LUNC is also up by 6% in a fortnight, although it remains down by 36% since the beginning of the year, with the market becoming increasingly frustrated with the Terra Luna Classic community's lack of progress in re-pegging sister stablecoin USTC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-jumps-up-5-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Jumps Up 5% – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-jumps-up-5-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119814/318267/terra-luna-classic-price-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1024475"/></item><item><title>SAFU Blasts Up 30,000% in 24 Hours But Crypto Experts Are Accumulating This Lesser Known Meme Coin Instead – $15 Million Raised Already</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/safu-blasts-up-30000-24-hours-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-lesser-known-meme-coin-instead-15-million-raised-already.htm</link><description>In the latest overnight sensation, SAFU - the new meme coin on the block - skyrocketed an eye-watering 30,000% in just 6 hours, as high-stakes DEX traders raced to ride the moon-shot. &lt;br /&gt;
The SAFU meme coin is a reference to the famous statement "funds are SAFU" by Changpeng Zhao (the industrious founder of Binance). &lt;br /&gt;
A sudden influx of $180k in volume in the early hours of this morning drove explosive price action, as SAFU exploded from a lowly $0.0164323 launch price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/safu-blasts-up-30000-24-hours-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-lesser-known-meme-coin-instead-15-million-raised-already.htm"&gt;Read More: SAFU Blasts Up 30,000% in 24 Hours But Crypto Experts Are Accumulating This Lesser Known Meme Coin Instead – $15 Million Raised Already&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/safu-blasts-up-30000-24-hours-but-crypto-experts-are-accumulating-lesser-known-meme-coin-instead-15-million-raised-already.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119815/318261/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="287912"/></item><item><title>Binance Successfully Integrates Bitcoin Lightning Network for Faster and Cheaper Transactions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-lightning-network-for-faster-cheaper-transactions.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange giant Binance has completed the integration of the Bitcoin Lightning Network, enabling its users to deposit and withdraw the world's number one crypto through this popular Layer 2 (L2). &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin Lightning Network is a second-layer solution that addresses scalability issues. It uses payment channels in order to settle transactions without having to wait for block confirmations....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-lightning-network-for-faster-cheaper-transactions.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Successfully Integrates Bitcoin Lightning Network for Faster and Cheaper Transactions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Lightning Network</category><category>Layer-2</category><category>Scaling</category><category>Scalability</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-successfully-integrates-bitcoin-lightning-network-for-faster-cheaper-transactions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119801/318251/adobestock-wrightstudio-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="334479"/></item><item><title>Stellar Price Prediction as XLM Blasts Up 30% in 7 Days – Can XLM Reach $1?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm</link><description>The Stellar price has dipped by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, yet its current level of $0.128569 represents an impressive 30% gain in the last 30 days. &lt;br /&gt;
As a cryptocurrency that also targets cross-border payments, XLM has benefitted from Ripple's success in its case with the SEC, with the altcoin joining XRP in the past few days to decisively outperform the wider market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Stellar Price Prediction as XLM Blasts Up 30% in 7 Days – Can XLM Reach $1?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/stellar-price-prediction-as-xlm-blasts-up-30-7-days-can-xlm-reach-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119803/318243/stellar-price-prediction-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1102045"/></item><item><title>Investigation Reveals Bitcoin's Creator Satoshi Nakamoto Could Be a Group, Not an Individual</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm</link><description>The identity of Satoshi Nakamoto, the enigmatic creator of Bitcoin (BTC), has been a subject of intense curiosity and speculation since the advent of the leading cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
While many envision a single genius behind its inception, there is growing evidence to suggest that Nakamoto may actually be a collective entity. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm"&gt;Read More: Investigation Reveals Bitcoin's Creator Satoshi Nakamoto Could Be a Group, Not an Individual&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Satoshi Nakamoto</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/investigation-reveals-bitcoins-creator-satoshi-nakamoto-could-group-not-an-individual.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119807/318233/satoshi-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="30507"/></item><item><title>Brazilian Central Bank Digital Currency Raises Alarm as Developer Uncovers Fund Freezing Feature</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm</link><description>A blockchain developer has found a code in Brazilian central bank-backed digital currency (CBDC) that would allow the government to freeze accounts or even drain them at will.  &lt;br /&gt;
Founder of Web3 consulting company Iora Labs and blockchain developer Pedro Magalhaes took to social media to reveal his findings in the Brazilian CBDC pilot. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm"&gt;Read More: Brazilian Central Bank Digital Currency Raises Alarm as Developer Uncovers Fund Freezing Feature&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Brazil</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Digital fiat</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/brazilian-central-bank-digital-currency-raises-alarm-as-developer-uncovers-fund-freezing-feature.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119802/318230/brazil-digital-currency-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="148180"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Sees Long Appeal Process for SEC in Lawsuit – Will the Decision be Overturned?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm</link><description>The XRP price has gained by 4% in the past 24 hours, with the coin's move to $0.748896 representing a 60% gain in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
This market-trouncing surge follows Ripple's success in its long-running legal battle with the SEC, with the presiding judge issuing a ruling last week which sided with the cryptocurreny firm on a significant number of counts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Ripple CEO Sees Long Appeal Process for SEC in Lawsuit – Will the Decision be Overturned?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-ripple-ceo-sees-long-appeal-process-for-sec-lawsuit-will-decision-overturned.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119799/318229/xrp-price-prediction-as-r.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="985516"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy XRP? XRP Price Nearly Doubles in 7 Days and Launchpad XYZ Just Raised $1.1 Million – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>After years of hard-fought legal struggle against the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple emerged victorious on July 13, following District Judge Torres' ruling that XRP token sales were not investment contracts (securities). &lt;br /&gt;
The highly anticipated judgement catalysed explosive price action across markets, as XRP holders were vindicated after months, and in some cases years, of cautiously-optimistic stacking....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy XRP? XRP Price Nearly Doubles in 7 Days and Launchpad XYZ Just Raised $1.1 Million – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-xrp-xrp-price-nearly-doubles-7-days-launchpad-xyz-just-raised-11-million-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119795/318226/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1002384"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Ripple's Legal Win and Global Interest Shape the Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm</link><description>Bitcoin price is currently trading at around $30,300, showing less than 0.50% surge during the Asian session on Monday. The recent favorable decision in the SEC vs. Ripple case has impacted the price, bringing it back to the level seen last Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a former SEC official expresses skepticism about the ruling on XRP, stating that "the decision rests on shaky ground" and anticipates a potential reversal in the future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Ripple's Legal Win and Global Interest Shape the Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-ripples-legal-win-global-interest-shape-market-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119786/318203/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1473618"/></item><item><title>China’s Changzhou to Give Away Digital Yuan Tokens, Coupons Worth $700k</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm</link><description>The city of Changzhou, China, is set to give away $700,000 worth of digital yuan tokens and coupons before the year is out, as the nation’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) pilot continues. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Changzhou Evening News (via JSChina), the city is hoping to boost CBDC spending during an upcoming citywide shopping festival by distributing e-CNY in “lucky red [digital] envelopes.” &lt;br /&gt;
Red is a symbol of good fortune in China....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm"&gt;Read More: China’s Changzhou to Give Away Digital Yuan Tokens, Coupons Worth $700k&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinas-changzhou-give-away-digital-yuan-tokens-coupons-worth-700k.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119767/318181/adobestock-529912803.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1014896"/></item><item><title>10 Meme Coin Price Predictions for 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm</link><description>2023 has been a blockbuster year for blue-chip cryptocurrencies. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) is up a staggering 80% year-to-date. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether (ETH) is up 58% over the same time period. &lt;br /&gt;
But the picture has been more mixed for meme coins. &lt;br /&gt;
Some have done very well, but others have struggled, suggesting risk appetite remains cautious and animal spirits are yet to fully return to the crypto space, despite the strong performance of the major coins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: 10 Meme Coin Price Predictions for 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>DOGE</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Floki</category><category>Shitcoins</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/10-meme-coin-price-predictions-for-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119701/318070/meme-coin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1736527"/></item><item><title>Ripple’s Victory in Court Drives up Crypto Trading Volumes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm</link><description>Ripple's win against the US Securities and Exchange Commission has boosted crypto trading volumes across spot exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;
Spot trading volumes on crypto exchanges surged to $16.56 billion on Friday from Wednesday's $12.74 billion, a growth of around 30% in just two days, according to The Block's data dashboard....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple’s Victory in Court Drives up Crypto Trading Volumes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripples-victory-court-drives-up-crypto-trading-volumes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119762/318173/adobestock-photo-gonzo-1-.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="64141"/></item><item><title>ARK Invest Bets Big on Meta Platforms and Robinhood, Reduces Coinbase Position</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm</link><description>Investment management firm ARK Invest has started accumulating Meta and Robinhood shares while selling more Coinbase shares.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, the company offloaded 478,356 Coinbase shares valued at $53 million as the crypto exchange’s stock prices reached a 52-week high....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm"&gt;Read More: ARK Invest Bets Big on Meta Platforms and Robinhood, Reduces Coinbase Position&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ARK Invest</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Robinhood</category><category>Meta</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ark-invest-bets-big-meta-platforms-robinhood-reduces-coinbase-position.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119756/318146/adobestock-wirestock-1-me.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="42420"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Falls Back Down to $30,000 Support – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price has encountered a setback as it falls back down to the key support level of $30,000. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at around $30,330.  &lt;br /&gt;
Recent news surrounding the cryptocurrency market includes a Coinbase user's claim of account closure by Bank of America due to Bitcoin transactions, drawing attention to potential challenges faced by banks in accommodating digital assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Falls Back Down to $30,000 Support – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-falls-back-down-30000-support-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119747/318135/16.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="526491"/></item><item><title>Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma Collaborate on NFT-Enhanced Sneakers</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm</link><description>Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma have joined forces to create a new sneaker collection that incorporates non-fungible tokens (NFTs). &lt;br /&gt;
The entertainment agency and the apparel giant have partnered with Legitimate, a startup that bridges the gap between physical and digital realms using its proprietary "LGT Tag" technology, to launch the RS-XL Mixtape sneaker collection, according to a Friday press release. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm"&gt;Read More: Jay-Z's Roc Nation and Puma Collaborate on NFT-Enhanced Sneakers&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><category>Puma</category><category>Jay-Z</category><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jay-zs-roc-nation-and-puma-collaborate-on-nft-enhanced-sneakers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119728/318115/pexels-ashutosh-sonwani-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="133238"/></item></channel></rss>
