<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Chinese Central Bank Unveils SIM Card-based Offline CBDC Wallet</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-central-bank-unveils-sim-card-based-offline-cbdc-wallet.htm</link><description>The Chinese central bank has unveiled an offline SIM card-based digital yuan “hard” wallet solution that lets users pay with the central bank digital currency (CBDC) with powered-down phones. &lt;br /&gt;
The innovation could eventually allow 2G phone-owning citizens to use their handsets to use the token when their phones are off....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-central-bank-unveils-sim-card-based-offline-cbdc-wallet.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Central Bank Unveils SIM Card-based Offline CBDC Wallet&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-central-bank-unveils-sim-card-based-offline-cbdc-wallet.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119351/317351/china1107.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="538390"/></item><item><title>New Research: Bitmain's S19 Miners Hold Majority of Bitcoin Network Hashrate</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/new-research-bitmains-s19-miners-hold-majority-of-bitcoin-network-hashrate.htm</link><description>Bitcoin’s energy efficiency has been a concern over the years as mining activities consumed rather massive amounts of electricity.  &lt;br /&gt;
Part of this resulted from the machines miners use, which have a high energy consumption. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a new report by Coinmetrics, three Bitcoin mining rig models account for 76% of the Bitcoin network's computing power.  &lt;br /&gt;
The report also revealed that Bitcoin’s energy efficiency has improved drastically in the past five years. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/new-research-bitmains-s19-miners-hold-majority-of-bitcoin-network-hashrate.htm"&gt;Read More: New Research: Bitmain's S19 Miners Hold Majority of Bitcoin Network Hashrate&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 01:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/new-research-bitmains-s19-miners-hold-majority-of-bitcoin-network-hashrate.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119368/317409/farm-gef883d896-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="255980"/></item><item><title>Russians ‘Can Pay Taxes on Their Crypto Earnings’ – Despite Crypto’s Lack of Legal Status</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-can-pay-taxes-their-crypto-earnings-despite-cryptos-lack-of-legal-status.htm</link><description>The Russian tax body says that citizens “can pay” taxes on their crypto earnings, despite the fact that tokens have no legal status in the country. &lt;br /&gt;
In another sign that the government appears to be sending mixed messages about its stance on crypto, the Federal Tax Service (FTS) stated that crypto earners could pay taxes using two different methodologies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-can-pay-taxes-their-crypto-earnings-despite-cryptos-lack-of-legal-status.htm"&gt;Read More: Russians ‘Can Pay Taxes on Their Crypto Earnings’ – Despite Crypto’s Lack of Legal Status&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russians-can-pay-taxes-their-crypto-earnings-despite-cryptos-lack-of-legal-status.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119226/317136/adobestock-256190172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="659323"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Standard Chartered Says Bitcoin Could Rise to $120,000 in 2024 – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-standard-chartered-says-bitcoin-could-rise-120000-2024-time-buy.htm</link><description>The leading cryptocurrency, Bitcoin (BTC), has maintained its upward trajectory and remains well above the $30,000 level.  &lt;br /&gt;
The surge in Bitcoin's value can be attributed to various factors, including positive predictions, increased institutional adoption, greater acceptance among mainstream financial institutions, and favorable regulatory environments in several countries....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-standard-chartered-says-bitcoin-could-rise-120000-2024-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Standard Chartered Says Bitcoin Could Rise to $120,000 in 2024 – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-standard-chartered-says-bitcoin-could-rise-120000-2024-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119362/317408/11.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="480960"/></item><item><title>Sui Chung of CF Benchmarks Confident in Approval of Spot Bitcoin ETF by SEC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-chung-of-cf-benchmarks-confident-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-by-sec.htm</link><description>Sui Chung, CEO of the crypto index provider CF Benchmarks, says he is “very optimistic” about the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). &lt;br /&gt;
“We are very optimistic that approval will be granted by the SEC because the SEC has consistently stated that it wants to see certain safeguards in place,” Chung said in an interview with Bloomberg TV on Monday...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-chung-of-cf-benchmarks-confident-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-by-sec.htm"&gt;Read More: Sui Chung of CF Benchmarks Confident in Approval of Spot Bitcoin ETF by SEC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sui-chung-of-cf-benchmarks-confident-approval-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-by-sec.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119336/317335/sui-chung.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="716009"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Winklevoss Twins and DCG's Barry Silbert Dispute Takes a Nasty Turn</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-winklevoss-twins-dcgs-barry-silbert-dispute-takes-nasty-turn.htm</link><description>Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, the billionaire twins who owns crypto exchange Gemini, may have a hidden agenda with their lawsuit against Barry Silbert’s crypto conglomerate Digital Currency Group (DCG), a recent Fortune article has suggested. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the article, there is a chance that the lawsuit filed by the Winklevoss twins’ Gemini exchange will not even go to court, but instead be used as leverage by Gemini in an attempt to get a better settlement from DCG....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-winklevoss-twins-dcgs-barry-silbert-dispute-takes-nasty-turn.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Winklevoss Twins and DCG's Barry Silbert Dispute Takes a Nasty Turn&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Barry Silbert</category><category>Winklevoss twins</category><category>Gemini</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-winklevoss-twins-dcgs-barry-silbert-dispute-takes-nasty-turn.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119327/317324/winklevoss-twins.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="67108"/></item><item><title>Microstrategy's Stock Poised to Benefit from Bitcoin Halving, Berenberg Predicts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategys-stock-poised-benefit-from-bitcoin-halving-berenberg-predicts.htm</link><description>Berenberg Capital has revealed its bullish case for Michael Saylor's Microstrategy ahead of the upcoming Bitcoin (BTC) halving event.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent research note, the investment firm said the Bitcoin halving, scheduled for April 26, 2024, serves as the primary driving force behind the firm's positive outlook.  &lt;br /&gt;
Berenberg currently holds a price target of $430 for the Virginia-based software company, a notable increase from its current price of $407.71 per share. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategys-stock-poised-benefit-from-bitcoin-halving-berenberg-predicts.htm"&gt;Read More: Microstrategy's Stock Poised to Benefit from Bitcoin Halving, Berenberg Predicts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>MicroStrategy</category><category>Berenberg Capital</category><category>Michael Saylor</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/microstrategys-stock-poised-benefit-from-bitcoin-halving-berenberg-predicts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119338/317339/4e7af61666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="33694"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 July – Mina Protocol, Compound, Solana</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-july-mina-protocol-compound-solana.htm</link><description>Major cryptocurrencies are trading with a modestly positive bias on Tuesday, but are still mostly within recent ranges ahead of Wednesday’s key US inflation data. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last trading up around 1% in the last 24 hours in the $30,600 area, while ether (ETH) was last around $1,870. &lt;br /&gt;
Positive reporting in the crypto press regarding BlackRock’s spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application could be acting as a mild tailwind for sentiment....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-july-mina-protocol-compound-solana.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 July – Mina Protocol, Compound, Solana&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Compound</category><category>COMP</category><category>Mina Protocol</category><category>MINA</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-july-mina-protocol-compound-solana.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119347/317345/best-crypto.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Predicts US Dollar's Demise Imminent as BRICS Nations Soon to Unveil Gold-Backed Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-robert-kiyosaki-predicts-us-dollars-demise-imminent-as-brics-nations-soon-to-unveil-gold-backed-crypto.htm</link><description>Robert Kiyosaki – author of the famous personal finance book Rich Dad Poor Dad – is bearish on the U.S. dollar after BRICS nations reportedly agreed to establish a gold-backed currency.  &lt;br /&gt;
The agreement, reported by Russia Today (RT) last week, will supposedly be officially announced in August at an alliance summit in Johannesburg, South Africa. In response on Monday, Kiyosaki said he expects the US dollar to “die” – and for Bitcoin to surge to $120,000 per coin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-robert-kiyosaki-predicts-us-dollars-demise-imminent-as-brics-nations-soon-to-unveil-gold-backed-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Rich Dad Poor Dad Author Robert Kiyosaki Predicts US Dollar's Demise Imminent as BRICS Nations Soon to Unveil Gold-Backed Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-robert-kiyosaki-predicts-us-dollars-demise-imminent-as-brics-nations-soon-to-unveil-gold-backed-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119346/317344/c8f9cea2e7-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="90760"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Falls 90% From Its All-Time High – Is Now a Good Time to Start Accumulating?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-falls-90-from-its-all-time-high-is-now-a-good-time-to-start-accumulating.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the ERC-20 meme coin token that powers the Shiba Inu web3 ecosystem, was last trading around $0.0000075, down more than 90% from its 2021 all-time highs in the $0.000088 area. &lt;br /&gt;
For now, the crypto token is consolidating within recent $0.000007-8 ranges and is just below its 21 and 50-Day Moving Averages (DMAs)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-falls-90-from-its-all-time-high-is-now-a-good-time-to-start-accumulating.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Falls 90% From Its All-Time High – Is Now a Good Time to Start Accumulating?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-falls-90-from-its-all-time-high-is-now-a-good-time-to-start-accumulating.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119337/317336/shib-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="624593"/></item><item><title>Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Raises $6 Million as Global Investors Flock to the New Recycle2Earn Platform – Less Than 48 Hours Left</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-raises-6-million-as-global-investors-flock-to-the-new-recycle2earn-platform-less-than-48-hours-left.htm</link><description>The eco-friendly crypto project has raised a whopping $6 million investment from early investors as it gears towards the last lap of its burgeoning presale.  &lt;br /&gt;
Its $ECOTERRA token has piqued the interest of global investors looking to invest in the next biggest asset before it launches on public exchanges. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-raises-6-million-as-global-investors-flock-to-the-new-recycle2earn-platform-less-than-48-hours-left.htm"&gt;Read More: Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Raises $6 Million as Global Investors Flock to the New Recycle2Earn Platform – Less Than 48 Hours Left&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-raises-6-million-as-global-investors-flock-to-the-new-recycle2earn-platform-less-than-48-hours-left.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119332/317334/eco-friendly-crypto-start.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227308"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Crypto's 'Inherent Structural Flaws' Make It Unsuitable for Monetary System, BIP39 Mnemonic Phrases Can be Turned into Colors, Dev Says He Reverse-Engineered Brazil CBDC Source Code, Algofi to Shut Down</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-cryptos-inherent-structural-flaws-make-it-unsuitable-for-monetary-system-bip39-mnemonic-phrases-can-be-turned-into-colors-dev-says-he-reverse-engineered-brazil-cbdc-source-code-algofi-to-shut-down.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-cryptos-inherent-structural-flaws-make-it-unsuitable-for-monetary-system-bip39-mnemonic-phrases-can-be-turned-into-colors-dev-says-he-reverse-engineered-brazil-cbdc-source-code-algofi-to-shut-down.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Crypto's 'Inherent Structural Flaws' Make It Unsuitable for Monetary System, BIP39 Mnemonic Phrases Can be Turned into Colors, Dev Says He Reverse-Engineered Brazil CBDC Source Code, Algofi to Shut Down&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>BIS</category><category>G20</category><category>UK</category><category>Treasury</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Wallet</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Brazil</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Algorand</category><category>Paradigm</category><category>Bittrex</category><category>Legal</category><category>SEC</category><category>Circle</category><category>Jeremy Allaire</category><category>China</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-cryptos-inherent-structural-flaws-make-it-unsuitable-for-monetary-system-bip39-mnemonic-phrases-can-be-turned-into-colors-dev-says-he-reverse-engineered-brazil-cbdc-source-code-algofi-to-shut-down.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119286/317276/adobestock-domagoj8888-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="193962"/></item><item><title>DOJ Charges 25-Year-Old with Stealing $450,000 in NFTs and Crypto from OpenSea</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-charges-25-year-old-with-stealing-450000-in-nfts-and-crypto-from-opensea.htm</link><description>A Moroccan man, Soufiane Oulahyane, aged 25, has been charged by the Department of Justice (DOJ) for his alleged involvement in stealing approximately $450,000 worth of cryptocurrency and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).  &lt;br /&gt;
Oulahyane is accused of creating a fake version of the popular marketplace OpenSea, tricking victims into providing their private crypto wallet keys....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-charges-25-year-old-with-stealing-450000-in-nfts-and-crypto-from-opensea.htm"&gt;Read More: DOJ Charges 25-Year-Old with Stealing $450,000 in NFTs and Crypto from OpenSea&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Crime</category><category>Theft</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/doj-charges-25-year-old-with-stealing-450000-in-nfts-and-crypto-from-opensea.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119317/317313/screenshot-2023-07-11-151648.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1151731"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Polygon? MATIC Price Rallies Up 5% in 24 Hours as Green Crypto Chimpzee Sails Past $800,000 Milestone</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-polygon-matic-price-rallies-up-5-24-hours-as-green-crypto-chimpzee-sails-past-800000-milestone.htm</link><description>The price of MATIC, the native token of Ethereum’s largest layer-2 scaling protocol by market capitalization Polygon, is up over 5% in the last 24 hours, as per CoinGecko. &lt;br /&gt;
MATIC was last trading just above $0.74 and to the north of its 50-Day Moving Average (DMA) for the first since April, as the cryptocurrency continues to unwind the losses it experienced in June as a result of the US Security and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s claim that it is actually a security....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-polygon-matic-price-rallies-up-5-24-hours-as-green-crypto-chimpzee-sails-past-800000-milestone.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Polygon? MATIC Price Rallies Up 5% in 24 Hours as Green Crypto Chimpzee Sails Past $800,000 Milestone&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Polygon</category><category>MATIC</category><category>Layer-2 scaling solution</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Is It Too Late</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-polygon-matic-price-rallies-up-5-24-hours-as-green-crypto-chimpzee-sails-past-800000-milestone.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119320/317316/matic1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1097475"/></item><item><title>Sue Ennis, VP at Hut 8, on Bitcoin, A.I Infrastructure, and Bitcoin Mining | Ep. 246</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sue-ennis-vp-at-hut-8-bitcoin-ai-infrastructure-bitcoin-mining-ep-246.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Sue Ennis, Vice President of Corporate Development and Investor Relations at Hut 8 Mining, talks about how A.I infrastructure is different from traditional data centers, the opportunity for miners in the data center space, and strategies &amp; impact on miners in next years bitcoin halving....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sue-ennis-vp-at-hut-8-bitcoin-ai-infrastructure-bitcoin-mining-ep-246.htm"&gt;Read More: Sue Ennis, VP at Hut 8, on Bitcoin, A.I Infrastructure, and Bitcoin Mining | Ep. 246&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sue-ennis-vp-at-hut-8-bitcoin-ai-infrastructure-bitcoin-mining-ep-246.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119308/317281/sue-ennis-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="116929"/></item><item><title>Crypto Startup Arkham Faces Backlash for Doxxing Users and Privacy Breach</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-startup-arkham-faces-backlash-for-doxxing-users-privacy-breach.htm</link><description>Blockchain analysis platform Arkham has found itself in hot water after it was revealed that the company had leaked its own customers' private information.  &lt;br /&gt;
The issue stems from Arkham's weblink referral program, where users can invite others onto the platform by sharing their unique referral URL.  &lt;br /&gt;
While these URLs appear to be a random sequence of characters, they are actually an easily decodable version of the user's email address written in Base64. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-startup-arkham-faces-backlash-for-doxxing-users-privacy-breach.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Startup Arkham Faces Backlash for Doxxing Users and Privacy Breach&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Arkham</category><category>Privacy</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-startup-arkham-faces-backlash-for-doxxing-users-privacy-breach.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119305/317277/62ebfa21a4f21f3f4499c5a7-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="25692"/></item><item><title>Rodeo Finance Exploited For $888,000 In Another DeFi Hack on Arbitrum Network</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm</link><description>Arbitrum Network-based Rodeo Finance lost 472 ether ($888,000) in a DeFi exploit today. &lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain security firm PeckShield revealed that the Rodeo Finance hacker transferred the stolen funds from Arbitrum to Ethereum. &lt;br /&gt;
Further analysis revealed that the attacker exchanged the stolen tokens for various other assets before converting them back to ether. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm"&gt;Read More: Rodeo Finance Exploited For $888,000 In Another DeFi Hack on Arbitrum Network&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/arbitrum-based-rodeo-finance-exploited.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119292/317267/crypto-hack-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="116999"/></item><item><title>Former SEC Chairman Highlights Conditions for Bitcoin ETF Approval</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm</link><description>Former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) chairman Jay Clayton has said that a spot Bitcoin (BTC) exchange-traded fund (ETF) is likely to get approved if it can be shown that the Bitcoin spot market offers the same “efficacy” as the futures market. &lt;br /&gt;
“If they’re [applicants] right—that the spot market has similar efficacy to the futures market—it would be hard to resist approving a Bitcoin ETF,” Clayton said in an interview with CNBC on Monday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Former SEC Chairman Highlights Conditions for Bitcoin ETF Approval&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Jay Clayton</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-sec-chairman-highlights-conditions-for-bitcoin-etf-approval-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119299/317266/jay-clayton.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="610480"/></item><item><title>Apple vs. Zapple Pay: Bitcoin Tipping on Damus App Challenges App Store Policies</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm</link><description>In June, Apple (AAPL) threatened to remove the Bitcoin-friendly social media app, Damus from its App Store, which led to the rise of Zapple Pay. The reason behind this threat is Damus' feature that allows users to tip each other with bitcoin (BTC) on the app, which Apple considers equivalent to selling digital media. &lt;br /&gt;
Damus operates on the Nostr protocol, a decentralized social media platform popular among Bitcoiners due to its support for Lightning Network payments. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm"&gt;Read More: Apple vs. Zapple Pay: Bitcoin Tipping on Damus App Challenges App Store Policies&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Apple</category><category>Apple app store</category><category>Jack Dorsey</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/apple-vs-zapple-pay-bitcoin-tipping-damus-app-challenges-app-store-policies.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119294/317302/screenshot-2023-07-11-144231.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="59069"/></item><item><title>Crypto and Stablecoins Are Not Money, Says Bank of England Governor in Favor of 'Enhanced Digital Money'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm</link><description>Andrew Bailey, Governor of the Bank of England (BoE), reiterated his stance against cryptocurrencies, during his recent speech at the Mansion House in London. &lt;br /&gt;
Bailey, who previously voiced concerns about the speculative nature of cryptocurrencies, said on Monday that Bitcoin has “no intrinsic value and it's highly volatile.” He also noted that crypto assets such as Bitcoin (BTC) are “best treated as extremely speculative investments.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto and Stablecoins Are Not Money, Says Bank of England Governor in Favor of 'Enhanced Digital Money'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-stablecoins-are-not-money-says-bank-of-england-governor-favor-of-enhanced-digital-money.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/119285/317249/adobestock-94685515.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="604663"/></item></channel></rss>
