<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 21:15:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nearly 60% of NFT Trading Volumes in 2022 Was Wash Trading: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nearly-60-of-nft-trading-volumes-in-2022-was-wash-trading-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 05:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229944</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/NFT_Wash.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/NFT_Wash.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[NFT marketplaces use token reward trading strategies to entice traders, boost volume, and appear to be the most successful platforms.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">A recent report published by blockchain analytics firm Dune revealed that nearly 60% of non-fungible token (NFT) trading volumes this year were wash trades.</p>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wash-trading-in-the-nft-space-the-problem-and-possible-solutions/" data-wpel-link="internal">Wash trading</a> is a form of market manipulation in which a trader buys and sells a security to create the appearance of increased trading volume and activity in the market. In crypto, these activities involve buying and selling digital assets &#8211; fungible or non-fungible tokens &#8211; on trading platforms, intending to inflate transaction volumes. The end goal is to mislead other traders about the demand level for the asset.</p>
<p class="p2">One example of wash trading in the context of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) might involve a trader who owns a particular NFT and wants to create the impression that it is in high demand. The trader could set up multiple accounts on an NFT marketplace and use them to buy and sell the NFT back and forth, creating the appearance of high trading volume and driving up the price of that asset.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Most NFT Platforms Engage in Wash Trading</b></h2>
<p class="p2">According to Dune, wash trades <a href="https://community.dune.com/blog/nft-wash-trading-on-ethereum" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">started</span></a> gaining traction in the crypto industry in 2019 but became pertinent to the NFT space in 2022.</p>
<p class="p2">The analytics firm noted that NFT wash trading is boosted by enticing traders with token rewards due to the high competitiveness of the space and the frequent launch of new platforms.</p>
<p class="p2">The most common wash trading methods involve investors trading their NFTs between two or more wallets, which they control, for the highest amount of Ether (ETH) possible. They aim to accumulate token rewards more valuable than the gas fees spent.</p>
<p class="p2">In February, blockchain analytics firm Chainalysis <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-crypto-crime-report-preview-nft-wash-trading-money-laundering/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">reported</span></a> that about 110 wash trading addresses had generated $8.9 million in profit. Notably, a significant number of such wallets lost money to transaction fees. However, the profitable addresses exceeded the losses of the unprofitable ones.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>$30B of NFT Trading Volume on Ethereum is Wash Trades</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Notably, the wash trade ratio varies among NFT marketplaces, but some platforms depend more on the activity. According to the report, platforms such as LooksRare and X2Y2 depend on wash trading with 98% and 87% of their respective volumes, depending on the activity. However, only 25% and 22% of their total trades are washes.</p>
<p class="p2">Furthermore, Element and Sudoswap are major wash trading platforms, with their respective volumes accounting for 66% and 11% of the activity. On the other hand, only 18.5% and 14.5% of their total trades are washes.</p>
<p class="p2">Dune also revealed that approximately 45% of all NFT trading volume on <span class="s1">Ethereum</span> are wash trades, accounting for $30 billion of the volume. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/transition-in-nft-markets-as-openseas-monopoly-diminishes-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">OpenSea</span></a> has just 2.4% of wash trading volume and less than 1% of trades.</p>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, in June, <span class="s1">Vijay Pravin</span>, CEO and founder of NFT analytics provider bitsCrunch, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-33-of-nft-volume-is-wash-trading-bitscrunch-ceo-interview/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> that over 33% of NFT trading volume was fake.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nearly-60-of-nft-trading-volumes-in-2022-was-wash-trading-report/" rel="nofollow">Nearly 60% of NFT Trading Volumes in 2022 Was Wash Trading: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Freedom? OpenSea Blocks Cuban Artists due to US Sanctions</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/web3-freedom-opensea-blocks-cuban-artists-due-to-us-sanctions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 23:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OpenSea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230151</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/OpenSea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/OpenSea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[OpenSea is blocking Cuban artists from using its platform, arguably working against Web3’s promise of economic freedom.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In compliance with U.S. sanctions law, OpenSea – the world’s largest NFT marketplace – is delisting Cuban artist and collector accounts from its platform. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A recent statement from the company confirms previously held suspicions that its platform discriminates against Cuban users. </span></p>
<h2>Compliance With Sanctions</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an email received by </span><a href="https://news.artnet.com/market/nft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Artnet News</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, an OpenSea spokesperson clarified that the company bars “sanctioned individuals, individuals in sanctioned jurisdictions, or services,” from using its platform. That extends to the likes of Cuba, as well as Venezuela, Iran, and Syria. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The confirmation is a blow to Cuban artists who leveraged NFTs to make a profit when the asset class boomed in 2021 – especially after tourist money in the region dried up due to pandemic travel restrictions. Earlier this year, NBC News </span><a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/now/video/cubans-turn-to-cryptocurrency-amid-heavy-u-s-sanctions-139124805728" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interviewed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Ernesto Cisneros – a Cuban musician who revived his music business by tokenizing his music and videos and selling them for money over the internet. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Another artist to benefit was photographer Gabriel Bianchini, whose work has been featured at the Havana Biennial and Milan’s MIA Photo Fair. His NFT Hotel Havana, which contrasts the Cuban capital’s colorful and decaying buildings, sold out within days of listing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Speaking with Artnet News, Bianchini explained that the technology helped people like him navigate the tough economic and political climate of the past two years. “This technology was a liberation, not only economically but creatively, a bridge that allowed us Cuban artists to connect with the world,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The restrictions appear to even expand to the Cuban diaspora. NFTCuba.ART, a </span><a href="https://nftcuba.art/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> promoting Cuban artists’ NFT drops, claims to have had its OpenSea profile </span><a href="https://twitter.com/nftcubaart/status/1602301816749842433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1602301816749842433%7Ctwgr%5E8bb3dc1dd1d475714f9dd4e9f149fb4c2d4dec97%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.artnet.com%2Fmarket%2Fnft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">disabled.</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span></a></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/nftcubaart/status/1602301816749842433?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1602301816749842433%7Ctwgr%5E8bb3dc1dd1d475714f9dd4e9f149fb4c2d4dec97%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&#038;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.artnet.com%2Fmarket%2Fnft-marketplace-opensea-delisting-cuban-artists-us-sanctions-2235440</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Your account has been disabled due to activity that goes against our Terms of Service,” read a notice from OpenSea received by the group. “This means you can no longer access OpenSea with your account.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A notice on the group’s website notes that OpenSea’s ban of its account is “sad and unfortunate” and that it was likely only enacted “because it has the name Cuba in it and or they are fearful of sanctions.”</span></p>
<h2>Against Web3 Principles?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One of the core principles of Web3 is the extension of financial services to all, irrespective of nationality or geographic borders. As such, some users interpreted OpenSea’s ban as going against those principles – and surprising given that it was encouraging of Cuban artists not long ago. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/threadoor/status/1606367793724768256</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others expected this outcome, however. Cuban NFT artist Yordanis García Delgado told Artnet News that he “saw it coming,” adding that “It is very difficult to be decentralized and not be accountable” to US sanctions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">NFTs are difficult to directly monetize without some sort of centralized exchange or marketplace to facilitate trades. On the other hand, fungible and divisible cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ether are easier to directly transact with for goods and services – making sanctions enforcement on such transactions more difficult. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoPotato </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-100000-cubans-are-now-using-cryptocurrency-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in May that over 100,000 Cubans have turned to crypto to bypass centralized payment service providers that must comply with sanctions law. Nevertheless, Chainalysis </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-warrens-bill-will-hurt-crypto-not-russia-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">maintains</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that it is too difficult for large-scale parties, like national governments, to work around such restrictions using crypto. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/web3-freedom-opensea-blocks-cuban-artists-due-to-us-sanctions/" rel="nofollow">Web3 Freedom? OpenSea Blocks Cuban Artists due to US Sanctions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peter Thiel-Backed Bullish Pulls the Plug on $9B SPAC Deal</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiel-backed-bullish-pulls-the-plug-on-9b-spac-deal/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=229978</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Stop.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Stop.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The decision to end the drawn-out deal was amicable.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Bullish has called off the planned merger worth $9 billion with Far Peak Acquisition Corp.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://bullish.com/news/press-releases/far-peak-acquisition-corporation-and-bullish-announce-the-termination-of-proposed-business-combination/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, the two entities have mutually agreed to terminate their proposed business combination.</p>
<p>Far Peak is led by Thomas Farley, a former president of the New York Stock Exchange.</p>
<h2>Terminated Merger</h2>
<p>Bullish is audited by Deloitte and recently assured that it has no exposure to FTX or related entities. The Gibraltar-based exchange, which is backed by tech investor Peter Thiel, had planned to go public via a merger with a special purpose acquisition company (SPAC), Far Peak Acquisition (FPAC), in July 2021</p>
<p>Since then, its merger prospectus has undergone several amendments, but the SEC remains unsatisfied. The latest allowed the two companies to terminate the merger agreement on December 31 if not completed before then. But that deadline now appears moot, given Friday&#8217;s announcement.</p>
<p>Commenting on the terminated SPAC merger, Brendan Blumer, Chairman and CEO of Bullish, said that the &#8220;quest to become a public company&#8221; is taking longer than previously anticipated. He added that he &#8220;respects&#8221; the ongoing work by the securities watchdogs in bringing out a relevant framework on digital asset space. The exec also noted,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I’m proud of the dedicated team of Bullish employees and advisors who have devoted countless hours to ensure Bullish operates with the highest standards of transparency and responsibility. This work has formed the operating foundation required to service our customers in the best and safest possible way.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto-SPAC Deals</h2>
<p>As a result of the ongoing market rout, several planned mergers between Web 3 companies and SPACs have been either delayed or canceled. SPACs, also known as blank-check firms, are essentially publicly traded shell companies that are created to take private firms public.</p>
<p>These entities have a reputation for being a backdoor way of going public and gained traction during the pandemic-driven market boom. In fact, SPAC deals skyrocketed at 81, climbing over $155 billion last year.</p>
<p>Over the last two years, SPACs have become a preferred route for crypto companies looking to sidestep a traditional initial public offering. Several prominent players, including Cipher Mining, Bakkt, and Core Scientific entering merger agreements with SPACs but only five out of 14 deals have actually been successful since 2019.</p>
<p>A crypto mining and infrastructure company Prime Blockchain mutually ended its $1.25 billion merger deal Blank-check vehicle 10X Capital Venture Acquisition Corp II in August this year.</p>
<p>More recently, USDC stablecoin issuer Circle mutually <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-nixes-spac-deal-with-concord-still-nurses-public-listing-ambition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">terminated</a> its merger agreement with SPAC partner Concord Acquisition.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/peter-thiel-backed-bullish-pulls-the-plug-on-9b-spac-deal/" rel="nofollow">Peter Thiel-Backed Bullish Pulls the Plug on $9B SPAC Deal</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Battles for Control of $450M Robinhood Shares in US Bankruptcy Court</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-battles-for-control-of-450m-robinhood-shares-in-us-bankruptcy-court/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 20:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230037</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTX_Robinhood.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/FTX_Robinhood.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FTX CEO, crypto lender, and creditor battle for control of multi-million dollar Robinhood stake in US court]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX is seeking help from a United States Bankruptcy Court to gain control of $450 million worth of Robinhood shares.</p>
<p class="p2">The portfolio holds 56 million brokerage shares owned by Emergent Fidelity Technologies, a corporate entity incorporated in Antigua and Barbuda. In March, these shares represented a 7.6% stake in Robinhood and were acquired by FTX&#8217;s founder and former CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF).</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>FTX in Court Battle Over Robinhood Shares Worth Millions</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Three parties are contesting ownership of the shares &#8211; crypto lender BlockFi, FTX creditor Yonathan Ben Shimon, and SBF. FTX is now <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.deb.188450/gov.uscourts.deb.188450.291.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">asking</a> the court to stop BlockFi and other parties from gaining control of the shares.</p>
<p class="p2">On 28 November, BlockFi <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-sues-sbf-over-robinhood-shares-after-filing-for-bankruptcy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> a lawsuit requesting the turnover of the shares, which it claimed had been pledged as collateral to secure a $680m loan for FTX&#8217;s sister company, Alameda Research.</p>
<p class="p2">BlockFi stated that the debt repayment was due on 9 November, but Alameda and FTX filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection before this date without repaying the loan. FTX argued that bankruptcy protection shields it from debt collection efforts.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Who Will Control the Valuable Robinhood Stake?</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The shares were frozen by Emergent&#8217;s broker, ED&amp;F Man Capital Markets, on the order of the Bankruptcy Court following the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">Chapter 11 filing</a> on 11 November. SBF also reportedly attempted to sell the shares via a Signal app before the bankruptcy filing.</p>
<p class="p2">FTX is asking the court to allow the shares to remain frozen while it seeks ways to repay its creditors. The troubled company claims that Emergent only &#8220;nominally&#8221; owns the shares and that they rightfully belong to FTX. The exchange also claims that Emergent is a &#8220;special-purpose holding company that appears to have no other business.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p2">In its court filing, FTX argued that the fact that multiple creditors of different Debtors and SBF are all seeking possession of the Robinhood shares demonstrates that the asset should be frozen until the court can &#8220;resolve the issues in a manner that is fair to all creditors of the Debtors.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-battles-for-control-of-450m-robinhood-shares-in-us-bankruptcy-court/" rel="nofollow">FTX Battles for Control of $450M Robinhood Shares in US Bankruptcy Court</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Proof-of-Reserves Report: Bitcoin, Ether, Tether Reserve Ratios Over 100%</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-proof-of-reserves-report-bitcoin-ether-tether-reserve-ratios-over-100/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKEx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230035</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/OKX_Bitcoin_Ethereum.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The recently published Merkle tree PoR program covers Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tether.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency exchange OKX released its second Proof of Reserves (PoR) on its website on December 22nd.</p>
<p>The new report would enable users to view and self-verify the results of two PoRs with the help of open-source tools, the company said in an official statement. OKX also promised to publish the PoR report every month.</p>
<h2>OKX&#8217;s Proof-of-Reserves</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://www.okx.com/proof-of-reserves/detail" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> shows that OKX&#8217;s wallets held 113,754 BTC against a user balance of 112,192 BTC as of December 20th, 14:00 UTC. It has a Bitcoin reserve ratio of 101%, this is a minor decrease from the 102% revealed in the PoR last month.</p>
<p>The reserve ratio for Ethereum stood at 103%, increasing from 102%, while Tether reserves stood firm at 101%. The OKX Nansen dashboard covers additional digital assets and shows that Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tether make up more than 90% of holdings.</p>
<p>OKX CMO Haider Rafique commented,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Publishing PoR results on a monthly basis strengthens our commitment to lead the industry when it comes to transparency and trust. At OKX, we believe that PoR should be verifiable via open source tools so that users can self-verify the balances and ownership of our reserve addresses.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, OKX also has included new features for its PoR that will allow users to check the reserve ratios for new as well as historical data. Users will also be able to download the files with both types of data after they self-verify on-chain assets.</p>
<p>Lennix Lai, OKX&#8217;s Director of Financial Markets, said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We would gradually enhance our standard of transparency. The industry would eventually achieve the same level of transparency and governance standards as in or better than in tradfi &#8211; primarily via technological/ cryptographic method.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Lai earlier stated that third-party audits are also being carried out by the Seychelles-based crypto exchange to provide additional reassurance in addition to the report.</p>
<h2>Proof-of-Reserves Auditors Under SEC&#8217;s Scrutiny</h2>
<p>The collapse of FTX has spurred several crypto exchanges to commission proof-of-reserve audits to quash concerns about their financial standing by allowing users to verify the numbers. Despite this, a senior official from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has warned investors about relying on this platform.</p>
<p>The agency&#8217;s chief accountant Paul Munter reportedly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-targets-crypto-auditors-seeking-greater-scrutiny/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">asked</a> that users to be careful of the claims that are being made by crypto companies.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-proof-of-reserves-report-bitcoin-ether-tether-reserve-ratios-over-100/" rel="nofollow">OKX Proof-of-Reserves Report: Bitcoin, Ether, Tether Reserve Ratios Over 100%</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Needs to Break This Level to Initiate a Rally (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-needs-to-break-this-level-to-initiate-a-rally-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230102</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum’s price has dropped below a significant resistance zone where the 100-day and 50-day moving averages and a recently formed channel’s middle boundary had a stronger confluence. Therefore, a possible uptrend will be possible only if the price exceeds this range. Oppositely, a rejection might trigger another bearish leg. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum’s price has dropped below a significant resistance zone where the 100-day and 50-day moving averages and a recently formed channel’s middle boundary had a stronger confluence. Therefore, a possible uptrend will be possible only if the price exceeds this range. Oppositely, a rejection might trigger another bearish leg.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By Shayan</p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum’s price has been moving inside a descending price channel for six months. Most recently, the price failed to surpass the 100-day and 50-day moving averages at $1300. As a result, Ethereum plunged below the channel’s middle boundary and is currently attempting to retest it.</p>
<p>The alignment of the 50-day and 100-day moving averages and the static resistance level of $1300 makes this level a decisive one for the cryptocurrency. If the price breaks above the resistance zone mentioned above, the channel’s upper trendline around the $1500 mark would be the main barrier to the price. However, based on the current market sentiment, a drop toward $1000 would be the more likely scenario in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230107" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230107" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230107 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_231201" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-1D-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230107" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>In the 4-hour timeframe, the price had experienced an impulsive bearish rally and is consolidating in the form of a well-known continuation correction pattern called an ascending flag. On the other hand, the 0.5-0.618 area of the Fibonacci retracement, standing at $1251-$1275, coincides with the static resistance level of $1260.</p>
<p>Considering the importance of this resistance level and the bearish continuation flag pattern, the potential of getting rejected from the $1251-$1275 region, marking another bearish impulsive move towards the $1000 level, is high. Nevertheless, if the price surpasses the abovementioned level, the bulls could push the price higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230106" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230106" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230106 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_231202" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230106" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By Shayan</strong></p>
<p>The following chart demonstrates the Exchange Reserves metric alongside Ethereum’s price. The metric has been in a downtrend since July 2020. However, after the massive price crash in November, the Exchange reserves metric experienced a significant decline and dropped to a new low.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230105" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230105" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-230105 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_exchange_reserves_chart_231203" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-All-Exchanges-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230105" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>This indicates that the market participants are offloading their assets from exchanges following the FTX collapse. This results in a substantial market capitulation stage that might finally trigger the last phase of the recent bear market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-needs-to-break-this-level-to-initiate-a-rally-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Needs to Break This Level to Initiate a Rally (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Deported and Released on Bail, FTX Fiasco Rageson, Bitcoin Stuck Below $17K: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-deported-and-released-on-bail-ftx-fiasco-rageson-bitcoin-stuck-below-17k-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 16:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230065</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bankruptcy.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bankruptcy.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SBF got deported to the US and was immediately released under bail. Caroline Ellison pleaded guilty and got a deal. Bitcoin remains below $17k.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Quite a lot has been going on in the cryptocurrency industry over the past seven days, but most of it failed to impact the price action,Week&#8217;s remains rather dull. Can&#8217;toin is trading below $17K, down about 2.9% in the past seven dParents&#8217;ble to recover the coveted level. The volatility has seemingly disappeared from the market, but that&#8217;s not necessarily truparents&#8217;e altcoins. All of them are trading in the red, with the most considerable loss being that of Cardano which plunged by a whopping 14%.  XRP is down 7%, DOGE &#8211; 8.3%, MATIC &#8211; around 9%, and so forth.</p>
<p>This has caused the Bitcoin dominance to raise and it currently sits at 38.3%. It means that the altcoins have failed to capitalize on BTC&#8217;s indecisiveness and have struggled a lot more in comparison.</p>
<p>The week was quite interesting and news-heavy, mostly with developments surrounding the FTX fiasco. Sam Bankman-Fried was deported to the US where he is currently facing criminal charges on multiple counts. However, he was also released to remain at his parenusers&#8217;use under a $250 million bail.</p>
<p>Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang &#8211; both high-ranking executives in FTX and Alameda &#8211; have pleaded guilty to multiple fraud charges. It&#8217;s also worth noting that Ellison&#8217;s plea agreement was recently unsealed. It appears that she has made a deal where the prosecution will drop most criminal charges in return for her full compliance and cooperation.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the US SEC has made it clear that the clampdown on cryptocurrencies is just getting started, while also saying that FTX&#8217;s native token &#8211; FTT &#8211; is a security. It was also revealed that FTX used predominaFTX&#8217;sFTT to finance 94% of its Blockfolio acquisition.</p>
<p>In any case, it remains very interesting to see how the case will unfold and if FTX creditors will be made whole.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $845B | 24H Vol: 38B | BTC Dominance: 38.3%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BTC:</strong> $16,848 (-2.9%) | <strong>ETH:</strong> $1,219 (-3.5%) | <strong>BNB</strong>: $245 (-4.5%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-230070" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12.jpg" alt="23.12" width="1000" height="500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12-768x384.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/23.12-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Sam Bankman-Fried Released on a $250M Bail, Can Stay at Parents’ House. </strong>The former CEO of FTX, Sam Bankman-Fried, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">released</a> on a whopping $250M bail and was required to remain at his parents&#8217; house in California. This happened immediately after he was extradited to the US.</p>
<p><strong>FTX, Alameda Crisis: Caroline Ellison, Gary Wang Plead Guilty to Fraud. </strong>Caroline Ellison and Gary Wang &#8211; both executives at FTX and Alameda &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-alameda-crisis-caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud/" data-wpel-link="internal">pleaded</a> guilty to fraud. Ellison also has a plea agreement where she can avoid most of the criminal charges in return for her full compliance and cooperation.</p>
<p><strong>BlockFi Seeks Permission to Allow Some Users to Withdraw Assets. </strong>The troubled cryptocurrency lender has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-seeks-permission-to-allow-some-users-to-withdraw-assets/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed a motion</a> with the US Bankruptcy Court to allow its customers to withdraw some of their cryptocurrency. More specifically, the motion is related to funds kept at the users&#8217; BlockFi Wallet.</p>
<p><strong>Twitter Integrates Live Market Charts for Bitcoin and Ether. </strong>Social media giant Twitter has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-integrates-live-market-charts-for-bitcoin-and-ether/" data-wpel-link="internal">integrated</a> a new cryptocurrency feature on its platform, allowing users to check the current prices of Bitcoin and Ethereum. Elon Musk stated that this is just one of the many product improvements.</p>
<p><strong>FTX Completed the Blockfolio Deal Mainly in FTT Tokens: Report. </strong>It recently came to light that the collapsed cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; FTX &#8211; used mostly its native token (FTT) to fund the Blockfolio acquisition deal. More specifically, 94% of the cost was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-completed-the-blockfolio-deal-mainly-in-ftt-tokens-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">funded</a> with FTT.</p>
<p><strong>SEC Believes FTX’s FTT Token Classifies as Security. </strong>The US Securities and Exchange Commission <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-believes-ftxs-ftt-token-classifies-as-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">believes</a> that FTT is a security. This could have considerable implications for the future of the market for exchange-issued cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Polkadot – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-23-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-dot/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-deported-and-released-on-bail-ftx-fiasco-rageson-bitcoin-stuck-below-17k-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">SBF Deported and Released on Bail, FTX Fiasco Rageson, Bitcoin Stuck Below $17K: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Inflation Gauge PCE Clocks in at 4.7% YoY</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-inflation-gauge-pce-clocks-in-at-4-7-yoy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 14:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230087</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/united-states-2361405_640-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/united-states-2361405_640-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin went up and down by a few hundred dollars after the PCE numbers came out.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Personal Consumption Expenditures price index (PCE) increased by 0.1% in November compared to October and by 4.7% compared to a year ago.</p>
<p>As the world&#8217;s most powerful economy made the announcement, BTC reacted with minor price volatility.</p>
<ul>
<li>The US Commerce Department outlined the PCE increase on Friday. The metric is typically the go-to point for the Federal Reserve, as it provides a clearer picture of consumer prices.</li>
<li>The 5.5% jump in the Core PCE (which includes food and energy) is slightly higher than the 4.7% estimation. The <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/pce-index-inflation-data-report-today-51671744394" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> also showed that general spending was also on the rise in November (0.1%) but not as much as in previous months (0.8%).</li>
<li>On the other hand, personal income increased by 0.4% in November, which is slightly lower than the October figures (0.7%).</li>
<li>Aside from the more well-known Consumer Price Index (CPI), the PCE is the other most frequently cited index for calculating inflation rates in the States.</li>
<li>Unlike the CPI announcements, which typically carry a heavy toll on BTC&#8217;s price, the PCE brought minor volatility.</li>
<li>The primary cryptocurrency dipped by a few hundred dollars from its familiar ground of $16,800 before it pumped to a daily high of over $16,900.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_230088" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230088" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230088" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="907" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD-300x148.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD-1024x506.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD-768x380.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD-1536x760.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDD-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230088" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-inflation-gauge-pce-clocks-in-at-4-7-yoy/" rel="nofollow">US Inflation Gauge PCE Clocks in at 4.7% YoY</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis Dec-23: ETH, XRP, ADA, BNB and DOT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-23-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-dot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOTUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polkadot (DOT) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230039</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Polkadot Ethereum (ETH) ETH fell by 3.1% in the past seven days after it lost the support at $1,240, which has now turned into a resistance. The bulls stepped up at $1,150, and since then, ETH has been trending upwards. In [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Polkadot</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-230074" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_charts_231201" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_charts_231201-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>ETH fell by 3.1% in the past seven days after it lost the support at $1,240, which has now turned into a resistance. The bulls stepped up at $1,150, and since then, ETH has been trending upwards.</p>
<p>In the next few days, this cryptocurrency seems likely to attempt to reclaim the $1,240 level as support. However, to achieve this, buyers need to keep it up. So far in December, the bulls have been rather shy in taking over the price action.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, ETH did manage to stop the price from making lower lows in contrast to many other altcoins that fell to new yearly lows (see ADA and DOT below). This is a sign of strength for ETH. As long as the price does not fall under $1,100, then buyers have a good shot at pushing ETH higher in the new year.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230048" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230048" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230048" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21.png" alt="ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-23_18-32-21-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230048" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>XRP suffered a significant drop in price, falling by 6.7% in the past seven days. At the time of this post, this it appears to have found good support at $0.33, and the key resistance is at $0.36.</p>
<p>The good news for XRP is that its price did not make a lower low with this most recent drop. This gives hope that the worst might be behind us, and buyers may prevent a lower low from happening in the future.</p>
<p>Due to low volatility at this time, XRP could range between the key levels for a while before breaking out. To flip the bias to bullish, the price has to break above the resistance at $0.36 with good volume.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230055" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230055" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230055" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-23_18-54-47-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230055" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>With a new low at $0.25 this year, ADA&#8217;s price action remains bearish after falling by 13.4% in the past seven days. Buyers simply vanished from the market, and they consistently failed to prevent lower lows. This does not inspire confidence.</p>
<p>The current resistance is found at $0.27, and it could be retested in the following days. If buyers fail to move ADA&#8217;s price above it, then that will be another bearish signal to market participants. This could then trigger even more selling and new lows.</p>
<p>The outlook for ADA remains grim. If bears continue to dominate the price action, then the next key levels of support below $0.25 will be found at $0.20, $0.17, and $0.15. These are also potential targets for the beginning of a sustained recovery once ADA&#8217;s price arrives there.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230045" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230045" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230045" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-23_18-33-50-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230045" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Binance Coin (BNB)</h2>
<p>Binance Coin lost 4.3% in the past seven days. Despite this, buyers did manage to stop BNB from falling to new lows. With good support at $220, the price could end up moving sideways until volatility returns to decide the next steps.</p>
<p>The resistance at $260 was not yet tested. This could be interpreted as a weakness in the price action that already reversed at $250 from its bounce on the key support. It is crucial for buyers to sustain the momentum and push BNB above $260. Otherwise, the key support may be put under pressure again.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, as long buyers as manage to defend the key support at $220 and $200, then Binance Coin has a good chance to avoid lower lows this year which would be a significant achievement, similar to ETH.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230046" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230046" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230046" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59.png" alt="BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-23_18-36-59-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230046" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Polkadot (DOT)</h2>
<p>Polkadot is the worst performer on our list this week after its price fell by 13.6%. In the process, DOT also made a lower low this year, similar to ADA. However, there is hope for a bounce in the near term as the current price action has formed a bullish wedge (represented in blue on the chart).</p>
<p>Should the support at $4.4 hold, then DOT could attempt to rally towards $5 and range in the near future between these two key levels. If the price falls under $4.4, then that would turn the chart extremely bearish, and DOT could fall to new lows again.</p>
<p>With a 92% drop from its all-time high at $55, DOT appears to quickly close in on a possible bottom which was found just under $4 back in 2020.</p>
<figure id="attachment_230047" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-230047" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-230047" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45.png" alt="DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/DOTUSDT_2022-12-23_18-40-45-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-230047" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-23-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-dot/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis Dec-23: ETH, XRP, ADA, BNB and DOT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC General Counsel Dan Berkovitz to Step Down in January 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-general-counsel-dan-berkovitz-to-step-down-in-january-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 11:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230036</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dan_Berkovitz.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Dan_Berkovitz.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Berkovitz reportedly had at least one recent dinner with former FTX CEO - Sam Bankman-Fried.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US Securities and Exchange Commission announced that Dan Berkovitz will step down from his General Counsel position as of the end of January 2023.</p>
<p>The current SEC Principal Deputy General Counsel &#8211; Megan Barbero &#8211; will replace Berkovitz upon his departure.</p>
<ul>
<li>SEC Chair Gary Gensler said he was &#8220;grateful&#8221; for Berkovitz&#8217;s &#8220;exceptional public service and his dedication to this agency&#8221; in the official <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2022-235" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement </a>before adding,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Dan has led the Office of General Counsel during a time in which we’ve proposed critical reforms throughout the capital markets. His counsel, judgment, and leadership have been invaluable to our work at the SEC. I have been blessed to work with Dan at two great market regulators, and I congratulate him for his 34 years in public service.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Berkovitz occupied the position for a little over a year after serving as the CFTC Commissioner for three years (from 2018 to 2021).</li>
<li>He noted that his departure from the SEC was because it was time for him to &#8220;pursue new and different challenges and opportunities.&#8221;</li>
<li>Although it may not be directly related, Berkovitz recently had dinner at a luxury Indian restaurant in Washington DC with several FTX execs, including the now-disgraced former CEO &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried, <a href="https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-washington-dc-emails-crypto" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to emails seen by the Washington Examiner.</li>
<li>The details of the conversation are still unclear, but the emails reveal that the bill was covered by FTX General Counsel Ryne Miller, who then asked for $50 from Berkovitz.</li>
<li>The former crypto exchange giant was known for having warm relationships with several US watchdogs before its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">loud collapse</a> in October. Interestingly, the dinner took place just days before FTX filed for bankruptcy.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“If ever there were a scene to conjure up a vision of a D.C. rigged toward corrupt insiders at the expense of the little guy, it would be difficult to top this one. Not long before its collapse and a raft of fraud charges, SBF and his gang were wooing one of their would-be regulators no doubt to try to manipulate the regulations to their advantage.&#8221; &#8211; commented Michael Chamberlain, director of Protect the Public&#8217;s Trust.</p></blockquote>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of WSJ</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-general-counsel-dan-berkovitz-to-step-down-in-january-2023/" rel="nofollow">SEC General Counsel Dan Berkovitz to Step Down in January 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
