<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>G7 Nations Must Do More to Stop North Korea Crypto Hacks, Japan Suggests</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/g7-nations-must-do-more-stop-north-korea-crypto-hacks-japan-suggests.htm</link><description>Not enough is being done to stop North Korea hacking crypto, Japanese government leaders have hinted at the latest G7 central bank governors and finance ministers’ summit. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Nikkei, an unnamed “high-ranking official” from the Japanese Ministry of Finance explained that North Korea is currently “able to continue its missile and other activities” in spite of sanctions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/g7-nations-must-do-more-stop-north-korea-crypto-hacks-japan-suggests.htm"&gt;Read More: G7 Nations Must Do More to Stop North Korea Crypto Hacks, Japan Suggests&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Japan</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/g7-nations-must-do-more-stop-north-korea-crypto-hacks-japan-suggests.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113939/275574/adobestock-554683865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="602480"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Has a Problem in the US Says Prominent Hedge Fund Manager Paul Tudor Jones</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-problem-us-says-prominent-hedge-fund-manager-paul-tudor-jones.htm</link><description>American billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor Jones said bitcoin has a “real problem” due to unfriendly regulation in the US, in a recent interview with CNBC. &lt;br /&gt;
“Bitcoin has a real problem because in the United States, you have an entire regulatory apparatus against it,” Jones said.  &lt;br /&gt;
Appearing on CNBC’s Squawk Box on Monday, the infamous trader spoke about his investments in bitcoin and said he planned to stick with it. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-problem-us-says-prominent-hedge-fund-manager-paul-tudor-jones.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Has a Problem in the US Says Prominent Hedge Fund Manager Paul Tudor Jones&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-problem-us-says-prominent-hedge-fund-manager-paul-tudor-jones.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113987/275674/bitcoin-g90d8026a0-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="251105"/></item><item><title>Number of Bitcoin Wallets With At Least 1 BTC Hits 1 Million – Smart Money Still Moving In?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/number-of-bitcoin-wallets-with-at-least-1-btc-hits-1-million-smart-money-still-moving-in.htm</link><description>Last Friday was a historic day for the Bitcoin network. &lt;br /&gt;
For the first time in Bitcoin’s history, the number of wallet addresses holding at least 1 BTC entire token surpassed one million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/number-of-bitcoin-wallets-with-at-least-1-btc-hits-1-million-smart-money-still-moving-in.htm"&gt;Read More: Number of Bitcoin Wallets With At Least 1 BTC Hits 1 Million – Smart Money Still Moving In?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/number-of-bitcoin-wallets-with-at-least-1-btc-hits-1-million-smart-money-still-moving-in.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113994/275677/btc-2.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="280028"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 15 May – Conflux, Sui, Bitcoin SV</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-may-conflux-sui-bitcoin-sv.htm</link><description>After a weekend of volatile trading, Bitcoin is on an upward trajectory, albeit still below significant thresholds. &lt;br /&gt;
As we head into a week potentially lacking in market catalysts, the focus remains on Bitcoin's performance. &lt;br /&gt;
How might this recent cryptocurrency market activity affect the best cryptos to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin is currently trading at $27,337, with a gain of 1.49% in the past 24 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-may-conflux-sui-bitcoin-sv.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 15 May – Conflux, Sui, Bitcoin SV&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>CFX</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>SUI</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Bsv</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Conflux</category><category>Bitcoin SV</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Web3</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-15-may-conflux-sui-bitcoin-sv.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113992/275675/best-crypto-15-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="362360"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Dormant Bitcoin Wallet from 2011 Comes Alive, Moves 139 BTC Worth $3.5 Million – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-dormant-bitcoin-wallet-from-2011-comes-alive-moves-139-btc-worth-35-million-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>In a surprising turn of events, a dormant Bitcoin wallet from 2011 has recently reappeared, raising questions about the motives behind this sudden activity. &lt;br /&gt;
The wallet, which holds 139 BTC with a current value of approximately $3.5 million, has caught the attention of the cryptocurrency community. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-dormant-bitcoin-wallet-from-2011-comes-alive-moves-139-btc-worth-35-million-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Dormant Bitcoin Wallet from 2011 Comes Alive, Moves 139 BTC Worth $3.5 Million – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-dormant-bitcoin-wallet-from-2011-comes-alive-moves-139-btc-worth-35-million-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113981/275669/15-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481003"/></item><item><title>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman on Verge of Securing $100 Million for Worldcoin Crypto Project</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/openai-ceo-sam-altman-verge-of-securing-100-million-for-worldcoin-crypto-project.htm</link><description>Tech entrepreneur Sam Altman’s crypto project Worldcoin is reportedly on the verge of securing $100 million worth of investments from “existing and new investors.” &lt;br /&gt;
Citing unnamed sources familiar with the matter, a Financial Times report from Monday said Worldcoin is in “advanced talks” with a group of investors who combined is expected to contribute some $100 million for the project’s further development....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/openai-ceo-sam-altman-verge-of-securing-100-million-for-worldcoin-crypto-project.htm"&gt;Read More: OpenAI CEO Sam Altman on Verge of Securing $100 Million for Worldcoin Crypto Project&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Investment</category><category>Altcoins</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/openai-ceo-sam-altman-verge-of-securing-100-million-for-worldcoin-crypto-project.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113979/275650/the-orb.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="42893"/></item><item><title>SEC Chair Says Crypto Intermediaries Are Rife With Conflict and Urges Compliance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-says-crypto-intermediaries-are-rife-with-conflict-urges-compliance.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission stands ready to help crypto intermediaries come into compliance, said the agency’s Chair Gary Gensler. &lt;br /&gt;
Gensler spoke Monday at the Atlanta Fed's 2023 Financial Markets Conference, following rising tension between the regulator and exchanges on how to go about registering with the agency. &lt;br /&gt;
“I would say that their business models though tend to be built on noncompliance,” Gensler said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-says-crypto-intermediaries-are-rife-with-conflict-urges-compliance.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Chair Says Crypto Intermediaries Are Rife With Conflict and Urges Compliance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bittrex</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Exchanges</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-says-crypto-intermediaries-are-rife-with-conflict-urges-compliance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113977/275646/gavel-gc61e5a16d-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="148767"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: May 15, 2023 – $LADYS, $CETUS, $CAPO</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-15-2023-ladys-cetus-capo.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:CT Coin (CT)Capybara (CAPY)Milady Meme Coin (LADYS)ILCAPO (CAPO)BOB (BOB) &lt;br /&gt;
BigONEListings:Milady Meme Coin (LADYS) ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-15-2023-ladys-cetus-capo.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: May 15, 2023 – $LADYS, $CETUS, $CAPO&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Trading</category><category>Exchange</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-and-delisting-announcements-may-15-2023-ladys-cetus-capo.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113959/275619/ld.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Lawsuit Conclusion Approaches – Can XRP Hit $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-lawsuit-conclusion-approaches-can-xrp-hit-1-2023.htm</link><description>XRP, the cryptocurrency that powers the global payments-focused decentralized layer-1 blockchain protocol the XRP Ledger that was created by US fintech company Ripple, continues to consolidate just to the north of its 200-Day Moving Average, having found robust support above this key level last week. &lt;br /&gt;
But XRP remains stuck within an aggressive downtrend that has been in play since mid-April, meaning that near-term price predictions remain somewhat downbeat....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-lawsuit-conclusion-approaches-can-xrp-hit-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Lawsuit Conclusion Approaches – Can XRP Hit $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>XRP Ledger</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-lawsuit-conclusion-approaches-can-xrp-hit-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113975/275644/xrp-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="559077"/></item><item><title>MiCA: A Catalyst for Increased VC Funding in European Crypto Startups</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mica-catalyst-for-increased-vc-funding-european-crypto-startups.htm</link><description>The European Union’s new regulatory framework for crypto, MiCA, will make European crypto startups far more attractive to investors, one expert has argued. &lt;br /&gt;
Writing on Twitter last week, Patrick Hansen, Director of Strategy and Policy at USDC-issuer Circle, said that “the MiCA effect” can already be seen in investments flowing into European crypto firms....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mica-catalyst-for-increased-vc-funding-european-crypto-startups.htm"&gt;Read More: MiCA: A Catalyst for Increased VC Funding in European Crypto Startups&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>EU</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mica-catalyst-for-increased-vc-funding-european-crypto-startups.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113941/275577/eu-flag.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="80680"/></item><item><title>Bakkt Crypto Platform for Institutional Investors Delists Several Digital Assets – Which Cryptos Are Facing the Axe?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-crypto-platform-for-institutional-investors-delists-several-digital-assets-which-cryptos-are-facing-axe.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency platform Bakkt is removing support for 25 out of the 36 tokens offered by its recently-acquired trading platform Apex Crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
Bakkt's decision to delist these tokens is part of a wider trend of companies reducing their exposure to risk as they try to navigate uncertain regulatory changes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-crypto-platform-for-institutional-investors-delists-several-digital-assets-which-cryptos-are-facing-axe.htm"&gt;Read More: Bakkt Crypto Platform for Institutional Investors Delists Several Digital Assets – Which Cryptos Are Facing the Axe?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bakkt</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Uniswap</category><category>Aave</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bakkt-crypto-platform-for-institutional-investors-delists-several-digital-assets-which-cryptos-are-facing-axe.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113955/275605/33dee2b561-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="40253"/></item><item><title>SEC Chair Gensler Argues That Rules Already Exist To Regulate Crypto in Light of Coinbase Pushback</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-argues-that-rules-already-exist-regulate-crypto-light-of-coinbase-pushback.htm</link><description>US Securities and Exchange Commission’s Chair Gary Gensler pushed back against Coinbase’s call to have the agency propose and adopt rules for digital assets. &lt;br /&gt;
Gensler was asked on Monday during Atlanta Fed's 2023 Financial Markets Conference to comment on the dispute with Coinbase why the SEC doesn’t want to publish crypto rules.  &lt;br /&gt;
The rules have already been published, Gensler said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-argues-that-rules-already-exist-regulate-crypto-light-of-coinbase-pushback.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Chair Gensler Argues That Rules Already Exist To Regulate Crypto in Light of Coinbase Pushback&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gensler</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gensler-argues-that-rules-already-exist-regulate-crypto-light-of-coinbase-pushback.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113973/275641/chair-gary-gensler-01-2022.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="46920"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk Inspired Crypto Coin NoMeme Approaches Long Time Support Level – Are Exchange Listings on the Way?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-inspired-crypto-coin-nomeme-approaches-long-time-support-level-are-exchange-listings-way.htm</link><description>Elon Musk-inspired memecoin No Meme Token (NOMEME) is approaching a long-term support level. &lt;br /&gt;
NOMEME was last trading just above $0.00011, slightly to the north of its initial listing price on Uniswap of $0.00010 five days ago. &lt;br /&gt;
No Meme Token was launched in the wake of a tweet by Twitter, Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk, who shared a picture of a Milady Maker with the caption “There Is No Meme” and “I Love You” on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-inspired-crypto-coin-nomeme-approaches-long-time-support-level-are-exchange-listings-way.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk Inspired Crypto Coin NoMeme Approaches Long Time Support Level – Are Exchange Listings on the Way?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>No Meme Token</category><category>NOMEME</category><category>Exchange Listing</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-inspired-crypto-coin-nomeme-approaches-long-time-support-level-are-exchange-listings-way.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113974/275639/nomeme-website.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="966986"/></item><item><title>Tamadoge Launches New Website, Leading the Pack for the Future of Web3 Gaming</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tamadoge-launches-new-website-leading-pack-for-future-of-web3-gaming.htm</link><description>London, 15 May 2023 - Tamadoge is excited to announce the highly anticipated launch of its new website.  &lt;br /&gt;
This significant milestone marks a major leap forward for Tamadoge and sets the stage for a new era of immersive web3 gaming experiences. &lt;br /&gt;
Tamadoge's new website is the warp-speed evolution of development and user feedback resulting in a cutting-edge platform that offers a pawsome gaming ecosystem. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tamadoge-launches-new-website-leading-pack-for-future-of-web3-gaming.htm"&gt;Read More: Tamadoge Launches New Website, Leading the Pack for the Future of Web3 Gaming&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>TAMADOGE</category><category>TAMA</category><category>Web3 Gaming</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tamadoge-launches-new-website-leading-pack-for-future-of-web3-gaming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113971/275637/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="691638"/></item><item><title>LG Electronics Pursues Patent for TV with Built-in NFT Trading Features – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lg-electronics-pursues-patent-for-tv-with-built-in-nft-trading-features-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>LG Electronics' filing for a blockchain-based smart TV was recently recorded by the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO).  &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, the company applied for the patent in November 2021 but WIPO’s documentation mandates an 18-month waiting period before such publications implying that the process has been ongoing.   ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lg-electronics-pursues-patent-for-tv-with-built-in-nft-trading-features-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: LG Electronics Pursues Patent for TV with Built-in NFT Trading Features – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lg-electronics-pursues-patent-for-tv-with-built-in-nft-trading-features-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113966/275636/lg.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="422387"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late To Buy Wen Token? WEN Price Rallies Up 4,000% and Whales Are Now Accumulating This New Coin – Here’s Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-wen-token-wen-price-rallies-up-4000-whales-are-now-accumulating-new-coin-heres-why.htm</link><description>WEN token has enjoyed a sensational run, with supercharged profits fuelling an electric meme coin rally, but has this high-flying project run out of steam? &lt;br /&gt;
WEN is currently trading at a lowly $0.000000005315 (representing a bleak 24-hour change of -22%). &lt;br /&gt;
This comes following a brutal -75% bleed-out for the latest meme coin poster child, with a retracement move from a local moon-shot high at $0.000000022 erupting into a cascade of capital flight from the project on Sunday 14....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-wen-token-wen-price-rallies-up-4000-whales-are-now-accumulating-new-coin-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late To Buy Wen Token? WEN Price Rallies Up 4,000% and Whales Are Now Accumulating This New Coin – Here’s Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-wen-token-wen-price-rallies-up-4000-whales-are-now-accumulating-new-coin-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113961/275634/stock-market-g5accb2a09-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="609360"/></item><item><title>US DOJ Ramps Up Efforts to Crack Down on DeFi Hacks and Thefts</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-ramps-up-efforts-crack-down-defi-hacks-thefts.htm</link><description>The US Department of Justice has taken notice of the concerning frequency of DeFi hacks. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a recent report by the Financial Times, the DoJ has described these thefts and hacks as a "pretty significant issue." &lt;br /&gt;
In addition to the hacks and exploits carried out by other bad actors, there have been instances where North Korean hackers have targeted DeFi platforms, resulting in the looting of billions of funds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-ramps-up-efforts-crack-down-defi-hacks-thefts.htm"&gt;Read More: US DOJ Ramps Up Efforts to Crack Down on DeFi Hacks and Thefts&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-doj-ramps-up-efforts-crack-down-defi-hacks-thefts.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113965/275633/judge-g05518a54a-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185047"/></item><item><title>As Metaverse Unfolds, Facebook Showcases Its AI Advances</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-metaverse-unfolds-facebook-showcases-its-ai-advances.htm</link><description>Around Two years ago, on October 28, 2021, the social media platform Facebook solidified its entry into the metaverse. &lt;br /&gt;
In a significant move, Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg renamed the company as "Meta Platforms Inc," underscoring its dedication to the development of the metaverse. &lt;br /&gt;
Meta described the metaverse as the “integrated environment that links all the company’s products and services” ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/as-metaverse-unfolds-facebook-showcases-its-ai-advances.htm"&gt;Read More: As Metaverse Unfolds, Facebook Showcases Its AI Advances&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-metaverse-unfolds-facebook-showcases-its-ai-advances.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113950/275624/artificial-intelligence-g.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="337783"/></item><item><title>G-7 Unpacks Crypto Regulation and CBDCs in Latest Meeting</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/g-7-unpacks-crypto-regulation-and-cbdcs-in-latest-meeting-over-the-weekend.htm</link><description>Finance ministers representing some of the world’s seven most influential economies discussed their commitment to regulating crypto-assets and exploring central bank digital currencies during a Saturday meeting in Japan. &lt;br /&gt;
The Group of Seven, or G-7, called for regulation, monitoring and oversight of crypto, while supporting innovation, according to a press release from the weekend....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/g-7-unpacks-crypto-regulation-and-cbdcs-in-latest-meeting-over-the-weekend.htm"&gt;Read More: G-7 Unpacks Crypto Regulation and CBDCs in Latest Meeting&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>G7</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Financial Stability Board</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/g-7-unpacks-crypto-regulation-and-cbdcs-in-latest-meeting-over-the-weekend.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113963/275626/earth-ge4b5b581b-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="496588"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Samsung Reportedly Partners with Bank of Korea on Offline CBDC Payments, G7 Discussing Crypto, China to Train 500,000 Blockchain Professionals</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-samsung-reportedly-partners-with-bank-of-korea-on-offline-cbdc-payments-g7-discussing-crypto-china-to-train-500000-blockchain-professionals.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-samsung-reportedly-partners-with-bank-of-korea-on-offline-cbdc-payments-g7-discussing-crypto-china-to-train-500000-blockchain-professionals.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Samsung Reportedly Partners with Bank of Korea on Offline CBDC Payments, G7 Discussing Crypto, China to Train 500,000 Blockchain Professionals&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Samsung</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Japan</category><category>G7</category><category>USA</category><category>DOJ</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SEC</category><category>LBRY</category><category>China</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Gold</category><category>Treasury</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Netherlands</category><category>Norway</category><category>Belgium</category><category>Ireland</category><category>UK</category><category>Germany</category><category>France</category><category>Italy</category><category>KuCoin</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-samsung-reportedly-partners-with-bank-of-korea-on-offline-cbdc-payments-g7-discussing-crypto-china-to-train-500000-blockchain-professionals.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113925/275553/adobestock-arcansel-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="135762"/></item></channel></rss>
