<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:54:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitget Betting Big on AI With $10M Investment in Fetch.ai Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-betting-big-on-ai-with-10m-investment-in-fetch-ai-ecosystem/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248325</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitget.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitget.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto derivatives and copy trading platform Bitget is going all-in on artificial intelligence (AI).]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On April 27, Bitget announced it has pledged $10 million for the development of the Fetch.ai ecosystem.</p>
<p>Bitget plans to provide a range of services to Fetch.ai, including marketing consultations and strategic directions.</p>
<p>Fetch.ai provides a service automation infrastructure that is powered by an AI agent network. These autonomous agents perform various tasks, including data analysis and complex financial modeling.</p>
<p>The move is the latest to latch on to an AI boom driven by platforms such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chatgpt-answers-cryptos-biggest-questions-bitcoin-or-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">ChatGPT</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">&#8220;BitGet Pledges $10 million to Foster <a href="https://t.co/kJ9URVpOul" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/kJ9URVpOul</a> Ecosystem&#8221;</p>
<p>Exciting news! A strategic partnership has been struck between <a href="https://t.co/kJ9URVpOul" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/kJ9URVpOul</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/bitgetglobal?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@bitgetglobal</a> with plans to push the <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AI?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#AI</a> ecosystem further <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f440.png" alt="👀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Read more details <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/yYAxgEXjIR" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/yYAxgEXjIR</a> <a href="https://t.co/TcE7kUUf3B" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/TcE7kUUf3B</a></p>
<p>— Fetch.ai (@Fetch_ai) <a href="https://twitter.com/Fetch_ai/status/1651542898490392576?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 27, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Bitget Spending Big</h2>
<p>Bitget Managing Director, Gracy Chen, commented that Fetch.ai already consists of a host of functioning and applicable technological AI solutions before adding:</p>
<blockquote><p>“That is the main reason we have decided to pledge our support to this promising startup and will continue to do so as we identify others in need of assistance from our dedicated fund.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Humayun Sheikh, Fetch.ai founder and CEO, said the opportunities for applying blockchain to AI are limitless.</p>
<p>Fetch.ai uses decentralized machine learning algorithms to provide its users with various innovative software solutions.</p>
<p>On April 10, Bitget announced a $100 million venture fund with a focus on investing in primarily Asian Web3 and crypto projects.</p>
<blockquote><p>The aim is to “foster a positive attitude towards the digital currencies economy and support the development of the web3 environment,” stated the firm at the time.</p></blockquote>
<p>Seychelles-based Bitget was established in 2018 and is currently ranked 8<sup>th</sup> for trust score, <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/exchanges/bitget" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to CoinGecko. The exchange handles $735 million in daily trade volume, offers 548 crypto trading pairs, and claims to have 8 million users.</p>
<p>The exchange’s native token, BGB, jumped by over 4% after the news was out. There has been little movement for the Fetch.ai FET token, which was changing hands for $0.347.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan Harnesses ChatGPT</h2>
<p>Wall Street banking giant <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jpmorgan-survey-paints-mixed-picture-for-crypto-sentiment-in-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">JPMorgan</a> is also keen on AI solutions. On April 27, it was <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-04-26/jpmorgan-s-ai-puts-25-years-of-federal-reserve-talk-into-a-hawk-dove-score?sref=323RPL5z" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reported</a> that the bank had developed an AI tool based on ChatGPT that can analyze Federal Reserve policy statements.</p>
<p>The tool derives a “Hawk-Dove Score,” which enables bank analysts to detect potential trading signals.</p>
<p>The system can predict central bank monetary policy tightening and is predominantly hawkish at the moment. The Fed is expected to raise interest rates by 0.25 basis points next week as it battles with high inflation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-betting-big-on-ai-with-10m-investment-in-fetch-ai-ecosystem/" rel="nofollow">Bitget Betting Big on AI With $10M Investment in Fetch.ai Ecosystem</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Avalanche Transactions Mooned During USDC&#8217;s Temporary De-Peg in Q1 2023: Nansen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-transactions-mooned-during-usdcs-temporary-de-peg-in-q1-2023-nansen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 20:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248536</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Avalanche-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Avalanche-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The brief depeg of USDC stablecoin triggered a surge in transactions and active users on Avalanche.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Avalanche&#8217;s fourth-quarter report shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, data and analytics platform Nansen reported a heavily volatile daily transaction count on the Avalanche C-Chain.</p>
<p>The Avalanche C-Chain is essentially short for contract chain &#8211; which is the default smart contract blockchain on Avalanche. It allows the creation of any Ethereum-compatible smart contracts and runs complementary to the X-Chain, which is used to send and receive funds in the form of AVAX tokens.</p>
<h2>Avalanche On-Chain Q1 2023</h2>
<p>The number of transactions on the network kept oscillating between ~90k and 200k. However, a sharp spike over this range to 290k was seen on March 11, driven by Trader Joe, USDC, and two unlabelled addresses. It was found that the latter were two bots that recorded high activities suggesting multiple players took advantage of the market panic caused by USDC&#8217;s de-peg on that day.</p>
<p>There has been a significant increase in the number of unique addresses transacting on the network as well. Specifically, on March 10 and 11, the daily active addresses experienced a spike, recording over 120k on each day. The average gas paid, on the other hand, followed a similar pattern to the transactions, except for January 1, where it exceeded 40,000 despite no notable increase in the transaction count.</p>
<p>In the first quarter, the average daily gas paid on Avalanche C-Chain was significantly lower when compared with Ethereum. For context, the lowest daily gas paid on Ethereum stood at $2.43 on January 8. This is in stark contrast to the highest gas paid on Avalanche, which was $16 on March 11. Avalanche C-Chain users only shelled out between $0.07 to $0.32 for gas.</p>
<p>Nansen&#8217;s data suggested that despite the sudden spike in transactions on both chains on March 11, the average gas paid on Avalanche C-Chain is still 76 times lower than Ethereum.</p>
<p>Mega Septiandara, Research Analyst at Nansen, said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Even as the Web3 ecosystem rebounds from yet another event that undermined trust in the industry, Avalanche marked a successful start to the year with significant gains combined with multiple product releases and partnerships aimed at powering adoption and reinstating faith in the sector. With a strong focus on driving innovation, Avalanche is undoubtedly poised for marked growth as it enters the second quarter.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>AVAX Price Trajectory</h2>
<p>In addition to substantial growth in overall transactions, and active addresses, Avalanche&#8217;s native token &#8211; AVAX- charted impressive gains.</p>
<p>After <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-skyrockets-14-bitcoin-calm-at-23k-weekend-watch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">starting</a> the year at $10.9, AVAX gained 60% in terms of YTD and was currently trading at $17.55.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-transactions-mooned-during-usdcs-temporary-de-peg-in-q1-2023-nansen/" rel="nofollow">Avalanche Transactions Mooned During USDC&#8217;s Temporary De-Peg in Q1 2023: Nansen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK Treasury Will Consult on DeFi Taxation: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-treasury-will-consult-on-defi-taxation-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248440</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/London-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/London-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The proposed regulatory changes aim to reduce the "administrative burden" for taxpayers.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United Kingdom is gearing up for tax treatment of lending and borrowing on decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols. The country&#8217;s taxation division &#8211; HM Revenue and Customs &#8211; released a consultation document seeking views on modifying the tax treatment of DeFi lending and staking.</p>
<p>The final decision on whether to proceed with legislative changes will be made after the consultation. This is the second stage of a five-step process and will be followed by drafting legislation, implementing and monitoring, and ultimately, reviewing and evaluating the change.</p>
<h2>Taxation for DeFi</h2>
<p>The main aim of the consultation is to create a regime that aligns the taxation of crypto assets used in DeFi lending and staking transactions with the underlying economic substance while bringing down the administrative burden on users, the official<a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/consultations/the-taxation-of-decentralised-finance-involving-the-lending-and-staking-of-cryptoassets/the-taxation-of-decentralised-finance-defi-involving-the-lending-and-staking-of-cryptoassets--2" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> press release</a> stated.</p>
<p>The government aims to establish clear tax and regulatory treatment of the field to position the country &#8220;at the forefront of safe, sustainable, and rapid innovation in crypto assets and blockchain technologies.&#8221;</p>
<p>As such, the tax authority has called on investors, professionals, and firms engaged in DeFi activities, including technology and financial service firms; trade associations and representative bodies; academic institutions and think tanks; and legal, accountancy, and tax advisory firms to submit their views on the matter by 22 June 2023.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The government is inviting answers to the questions below on a potential legislative solution which aims at better aligning the taxation of crypto assets used in DeFi transactions with the underlying economic substance. In addition to the specific questions posed, a more general comment on the issues discussed is welcome&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The proposed legislative modifications state that the crypto used in DeFi transactions would no longer be treated as a disposal for tax. Instead, Capital Gains Tax (CGT) would apply in addition to tax disposal when the crypto assets are economically disposed of in a non-DeFi transaction.</p>
<h2>Crypto Regulation in the UK</h2>
<p>Economic Secretary to the UK Treasury, Andrew Griffith, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-regulations-coming-within-a-year-in-the-uk-andrew-griffith-says/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> last week that the authorities are planning to impose a regulatory framework on the crypto industry in the next 12 months.</p>
<p>The lawmaker asserted that the upcoming regulation will foster the development of the asset class and is aimed at turning the Kingdom into a global cryptocurrency hub.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-treasury-will-consult-on-defi-taxation-report/" rel="nofollow">UK Treasury Will Consult on DeFi Taxation: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Stuck in Limbo, Will $0.5 Fall Soon or is Another Crash Coming? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-stuck-in-limbo-will-0-5-fall-soon-or-is-another-crash-coming-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248643</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple failed to breach the $0.55 resistance region and experienced a significant plunge of 26%, arriving at the crucial support level of the 100-day moving average. However, the price is likely to consolidate within this range, encountering significant support. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart On the daily chart, following Ripple&#8217;s rejection from the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple failed to breach the $0.55 resistance region and experienced a significant plunge of 26%, arriving at the crucial support level of the 100-day moving average. However, the price is likely to consolidate within this range, encountering significant support.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, following Ripple&#8217;s rejection from the $0.58 level, its price suffered a massive decline, experiencing a whopping 26% drop. However, XRP is currently confronting significant support regions consisting of the 100-day moving average at $0.43 and the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level at $0.44.</p>
<p>Considering the strength of these support levels, the price seems likely to enter a consolidation phase followed by high volatility. However, if selling pressure on Ripple pushes the price below the 100-day moving average, another drop could occur, which may flush out many long positions from the derivatives market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_248645" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-248645" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-248645 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_3004231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-Daily-5-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-248645" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, the price has formed a descending price channel. The recent rejection caused XRP to drop below the minor support level of $0.48 and consolidate without a clear direction. Presently, it faces two crucial levels: the $0.48 minor resistance zone and the lower trendline of the channel, which is approximately $0.415.</p>
<p>Based on Ripple&#8217;s recent behavior, the market appears to have entered a consolidation stage between $0.415 and $0.48 until a breakout from this range occurs.</p>
<figure id="attachment_248644" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-248644" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-248644 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_3004232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/XRP-4H-4-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-248644" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-stuck-in-limbo-will-0-5-fall-soon-or-is-another-crash-coming-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Stuck in Limbo, Will $0.5 Fall Soon or is Another Crash Coming? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard Teams Up With Aptos, Polygon, Avalanche, Solana to Strengthen Web3 Foothold</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mastercard-teams-up-with-aptos-polygon-avalanche-solana-to-strengthen-web3-foothold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 14:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248546</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mastercard_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/mastercard_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The solution aims to offer different consumer and business verification needs based on market and compliance requirements. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US payment giant Mastercard has dispatched a new Web3 solution that seeks to bring more trust to blockchain transactions.</p>
<p>Dubbed &#8216;Mastercard Crypto Credential,&#8217; the offering will establish a set of common standards and infrastructure that will &#8220;help attest to trusted interactions among consumers and businesses using blockchain networks.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Mastercard Crypto Credential</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/bringing-more-trust-to-blockchain-transactions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post</a> published on April 28th, Mastercard highlighted the need for trusted, compliant, and verifiable interactions to take place on public blockchain networks. To that extent, Mastercard Crypto Credential is designed to help ensure that the players interested in interacting across Web3 meet certain defined standards while engaging in any type of activity.</p>
<p>In addition to defining verification standards and levels, Mastercard Crypto Credential will also provide necessary enabling technology to target more use cases.</p>
<p>Mastercard said that the focus will be on providing easy-to-remember, straightforward aliases to help consumers share wallet addresses with one another, ramping up the consumer experience alongside reducing the potential for errors.</p>
<p>Bringing richer information to blockchain transactions through metadata is yet another aspect that the new offering will target, along with defining attributes of a wallet to help ensure that transactions are completed as intended.</p>
<p>Additionally, the company has tapped into CipherTrace’s suite of services to verify addresses and support Travel Rule compliance for cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>For this initiative, the company has teamed up with prominent blockchain entities such as Aptos Labs, Ava Labs, Polygon Labs, and The Solana Foundation. These partners are tasked with assisting the company in bringing Mastercard Crypto Credential to the application developers in their ecosystems.</p>
<p>The collaboration aims to enhance verification in NFTs, ticketing, enterprise, and other payment solutions.</p>
<h2>Mastercard Upping its Web3 Exposure</h2>
<p>Mastercard has been engaged in several initiatives in the Web3 space. Last October, it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mastercard-launches-program-to-help-banks-offer-crypto-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a program to help traditional financial institutions offer cryptocurrency trading to their clients. The payments firm <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-taps-mastercard-to-introduce-crypto-prepaid-card-in-brazil-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">teamed up</a> with Binance to roll out crypto prepaid cards in Brazil.</p>
<p>More recently, Mastercard <a href="https://www.mastercard.com/news/perspectives/2023/why-we-re-dropping-an-nft-to-help-emerging-musicians/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">outlined</a> its plans to release NFT to help Web3 musicians access resources to boost their careers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mastercard-teams-up-with-aptos-polygon-avalanche-solana-to-strengthen-web3-foothold/" rel="nofollow">Mastercard Teams Up With Aptos, Polygon, Avalanche, Solana to Strengthen Web3 Foothold</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitulation? NFT Trading Volumes and Prices Plummet in the Last 30 Days</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/capitulation-nft-trading-volumes-and-prices-plummet-in-the-last-30-days/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 11:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248553</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/NFT_Crash.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/NFT_Crash.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The NFT market experienced a decline in trading volumes and prices in the past month, with some major collections plummeting significantly.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past 30 days have seen a decline in trading volumes and prices of most non-fungible token (NFT) projects, likely due to the prolonged bear market of 2022 and the first quarter of 2023.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/insights/nft/analytics/all-collections" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from blockchain analytics firm IntoTheBlock, only six of the top 20 NFT collections by market capitalization recorded increased trading volumes over the last 30 days. The remaining collections experienced a significant decrease, ranging from 20% to 99%.</p>
<h2>NFT Trading Volume Capitulates</h2>
<p>The trading volume for the popular NFT collection <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptopunks-guide/" data-wpel-link="internal">CryptoPunks</a>, which is the second-largest by market cap, plunged by 60.30% within the past month. Other top digital collectibles, such as Mutant Ape Yacht Club, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/baycs-otherside-land-sale-everything-you-need-to-know/" data-wpel-link="internal">Otherdeed</a>, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-moonbirds-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">Moonbirds</a>, and Doodles, also tanked by 20.16%, 53.09%, 73.57%, and 63.55%, respectively.</p>
<p>Additionally, the ninth-largest collection by market cap, Sewer Pass, which was launched by NFT company Yuga Labs, witnessed a staggering drop of 99.16% in its trading volume.</p>
<p>In contrast, Captainz&#8217;s NFT collection recorded the highest surge in trading volume at 53.81%, while Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC), the largest NFT collection by market cap, saw a 24.67% increase in trading volume. Other projects such as Azuki, Autoglyphs, and Meebits also saw an increase in their trading volumes by 24.49%, 14.70%, and 2.48%, respectively.</p>
<p>While some NFT projects recorded increased trading volume, only four out of 20 collections saw a price surge during the same period. The prices of Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) and Meebits dropped by 16.42% and 24.18%, respectively, despite their trading volumes going up. In contrast, CryptoPunks&#8217; price increased by 2.37% despite a decline in trading volume.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Azuki, Autoglyphs, and Captainz were the only collections that saw growth in all aspects, with price gains of 5.29%, 1.44%, and 36.60%, respectively, accompanied by the surge in their trading volumes.</p>
<h2>NFT Market Still Growing</h2>
<p>Despite the recent poor performance, the non-fungible token (NFT) industry has continued to grow and evolve. As reported by <em>CryptoPotato</em> earlier this month, the digital collectibles market has had a solid start to the year.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-market-hit-4-7b-in-sales-in-q1-dappradar/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a>, Q1 2023 was the best quarter since Q2 2022, with NFT trading volume increasing by 137% to $4.7 billion. Additionally, NFT sales for the last quarter amounted to 19.4 million, representing an increase of 8.56% from Q4 2022.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/capitulation-nft-trading-volumes-and-prices-plummet-in-the-last-30-days/" rel="nofollow">Capitulation? NFT Trading Volumes and Prices Plummet in the Last 30 Days</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Extends Dominance Over Alts as BTC Stable Above $29K: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-extends-dominance-over-alts-as-btc-stable-above-29k-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 08:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248609</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Green_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Green_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As the week and the month come to an end, BTC stands above $29,000, while ETH is at $1,900.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few days of April did not bring any substantial price moves in either direction for bitcoin, which remains north of $29,000.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also calm during the weekend as the trading volume has disappeared. On a weekly scale, though, BTC&#8217;s dominance has risen by over a percentage.</p>
<h2>BTC Maintains $29K During Weekend</h2>
<p>This weekend resembles the previous one in terms of lack of volatility, aside from BTC&#8217;s highest price point. Last Monday began with bitcoin jumping to $28,000, but that was short-lived, and the asset returned to $27,000.</p>
<p>It wasn&#8217;t until late Tuesday, when the cryptocurrency began its ascend, that drove it to $30,000 just hours later. Yet, the rejection at that point, albeit driven by fake news, drove it south hard by $3,000, and BTC returned to its previous price position.</p>
<p>The US banking issues, though, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-rollercoaster-at-30k-millions-in-liquidations-first-republic-turmoil-this-weeks-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">pushed</a> it back north, and bitcoin found itself knocking on $30,000&#8217;s door but to no avail once again. Since then, the asset has remained<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/injective-inj-up-17-weekly-bitcoin-btc-stable-above-29k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal"> relatively stable</a> at over $29,000, and the past two days were no exception.</p>
<p>As such, BTC&#8217;s market cap has touched $570 billion, while its dominance over the altcoins has recovered over 1% since last week and is above 47% now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_248611" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-248611" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-248611" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="818" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS-300x134.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS-1024x457.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS-768x343.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS-1536x685.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUDS-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-248611" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Alts Sit Calmly</h2>
<p>The trading volumes during the past few weekends have been lacking, and this one is no exception. As such, most of the alternative coins have failed to produce any notable price movements in either direction.</p>
<p>ETH remains at $1,900 after going above $2,000 and under $1,800 earlier this week. Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, Shiba Inu, and Avalanche are slightly in the red.</p>
<p>In contrast, Dogecoin, Solana, Polkadot, Litecoin, and Tron have all marked insignificant daily gains.</p>
<p>HBAR is the only substantial gainer from the top 50 alts, with a 4.5% daily increase.</p>
<p>Overall, though, even the lower cap alts sit quietly today, which has resulted in no movements for the total market cap. The metric stands inches above $1.2 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_248612" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-248612" style="width: 1884px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-248612" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1884" height="793" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19.jpg 1884w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19-1024x431.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19-768x323.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19-1536x647.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Allcoins-19-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1884px) 100vw, 1884px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-248612" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-extends-dominance-over-alts-as-btc-stable-above-29k-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Extends Dominance Over Alts as BTC Stable Above $29K: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ojamu Announces “Alphie” Launch &#8211; AI-driven Smart Tool for the Blockchain Industry Integrated with ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248593</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ojamu.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Ojamu.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, April 28th, 2023] “Alphie” bot currently specializes in the hot ZK &#38; Optimistic Rollup sectors, with more to come Ojamu, the AI &#38; Blockchain-powered intelligence platform geared towards providing insights into the blockchain &#38; Web3 economy, announced its latest product today, with the launch of its ChatGPT integrated bot “Alphie”, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, April 28th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><em>“Alphie” bot currently specializes in the hot ZK &amp; Optimistic Rollup sectors, with more to come</em></p>
<p>Ojamu, the AI &amp; Blockchain-powered intelligence platform geared towards providing insights into the blockchain &amp; Web3 economy, announced its latest product today, with the launch of its ChatGPT integrated bot “Alphie”, available in both mobile and desktop versions.</p>
<p>Alphie is an advanced, AI-driven &#8216;Alpha Finder,&#8217; providing valuable insights and in-depth analysis in the most cutting-edge areas of the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p>Ojamu CEO and Founder Hal Bame commented, “The bot’s name comes from ‘Alpha’, which in many industries is seen as ‘hard-to-find’ or essential information. Alphie initially focuses on the incredibly popular and fast-moving ZK/Optimistic Rollup space, with leading chains such as Polygon &amp; Arbitrum incredibly acitve, helping users understand complex concepts and terminologies that might otherwise be difficult to grasp and find necessary information on, as well as associated projects.”</p>
<p>Alphie’s capability goes beyond ‘lookups.’ For example, it can break down whitepapers into more digestible information, in order to accelerate users’ research and help them to make better-informed decisions, find specifics on various technologies and understand how those projects differentiate from others.</p>
<p>Key groups within the crypto/blockchain ecosystem will benefit from Alphie:</p>
<p>● Traders gain insights on project fundamentals, technology, and team credentials to make informed decisions and improve trading outcomes.</p>
<p>● Investors can make better investment choices based on solid evaluation of projects’ long-term potential by analyzing tokenomics, use cases, and market trends.</p>
<p>● Developers can easily assess complex emerging technologies like ZK/Optimistic Rollup scaling solutions to decide which is best suited to integrate into their projects.</p>
<p>● Crypto enthusiasts can expand their knowledge of the ZK/Optimistic Rollup space and stay up-to-date with the latest trends and developments thanks to Alphie’s ability to simply explain complex concepts.</p>
<p>Alphie leverages ChatGPT AI technology and fine-tuning AI smart toolsets, as well as Ojamu’s own proprietary AI and data methodology, in order to provide as complete and up-to-date information as possible.</p>
<p>Alphie demystifies ZK/Optimistic Rollups and other advanced blockchain technologies, making it easier for users to comprehend their advantages, limitations, and potential use cases. The bot can provide a comprehensive understanding of these two technologies, their underlying principles, benefits, and drawbacks. It can explain how these Layer 2 scaling solutions work, how they differ from each other, and how they can help address the transaction throughput challenges faced by various blockchain networks. Alphie can also delve into the potential risks and trade-offs associated with implementing these technologies, such as security and data availability concerns.</p>
<p>Ojamu’s future product plans include expanding Alphie&#8217;s coverage to encompass all crypto categories and provide more advanced research and insights based on further technical and fundamental analysis. GPT-4 research and integration are already underway for enhanced AI performance and datasets, as well as improved natural language understanding capabilities, ensuring that Alphie remains at the cutting edge of AI-driven chatbot technology.</p>
<p>For more information, visit: <a href="http://www.ojamuai.com" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">www.ojamuai.com</a></p>
<h2>About Ojamu</h2>
<p><a href="http://ojamu.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Alphie</a> is the second product offering in Ojamu’s suite of AI-driven smart toolsets and is the first of its B2C product offerings. Ojamu is continually is looking to enhance and expand the Alphie suite of products, increasing its offerings both within the crypto/blockchain space and beyond.</p>
<p>Ojamu’s first product, The Ojamu Intelligence Platform (OIP) continues development and focuses on the B2B space, providing brands the actionable intelligence that they need to succeed in the Web 3.0 economy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ojamu-announces-alphie-launch-ai-driven-smart-tool-for-the-blockchain-industry-integrated-with-chatgpt/" rel="nofollow">Ojamu Announces “Alphie” Launch &#8211; AI-driven Smart Tool for the Blockchain Industry Integrated with ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Google Cloud Introduces New Web3 Startup Program</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/google-cloud-introduces-new-web3-startup-program/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Google]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247887</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Google.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Google.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The initiative includes collaboration with a slew of Web3 firms, such as Alchemy, Nansen, and Solana.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Google Cloud announced plans to assist Web3 startups and projects to build and scale faster and more securely.</p>
<p>The new offering expands on the existing initiative called &#8211; &#8220;Google for Startups Cloud Program&#8221; by including additional Web3-specific benefits.</p>
<h2>The Initiative</h2>
<p>According to the official<a href="https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/startups/introducing-google-clouds-new-web3-startup-benefits" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> press release</a>, eligible Web3 technology projects and startups from pre-seed to Series A will be able to apply for the Google for Startups Cloud Program. Projects can also opt-in to Google Cloud&#8217;s Web3-specific benefits which include up to $200,000 over two years in Google Cloud credits and technical and collaboration support.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our goal is to enable Web3 builders to focus on what really matters &#8211; speed-to-market and innovation. This means giving startups the ability to build on our fully managed, serverless platform at no cost, as well as the resources and community to be successful.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, access to a set of grants from ​​Aptos, Celo, Flow, the HBAR Foundation, Near, and the Solana Foundation will also be made available. Each of the founding partners will be offering exclusive grants of up to $1 million to help accelerate Web3 startup growth, in addition to resources to support development.</p>
<p>The program will offer access to up to $3 million in investments from the Polygon Ventures Ecosystem Fund, priority review from the Ventures Team as well as all Polygon Venture benefits. Some of the other perks by Google Cloud include priority review for the Base Ecosystem Fund and access to testnet, discount on Nansen products and engagement fees, credits for Alchemy, and priority access to Alchemy University.</p>
<h2>Google Cloud and Web3</h2>
<p>Google Cloud&#8217;s tryst with Web3 dates back to 2018 when it added datasets for Bitcoin. Since then, the cloud computing giant has forged partnerships with several industry leaders, including Coinbase.</p>
<p>It <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/google-cloud-partners-with-bnb-chain-to-provide-web-3-startup-infrastructure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with BNB Chain last year to offer Web3 startup infrastructure. Earlier this month, the Celo Foundation also <a href="https://blog.celo.org/celo-foundation-announces-collaboration-with-google-cloud-to-help-sustainability-focused-startups-3428ac562a1f" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announced</a> collaborating with Google Cloud to expand the early adoption of the latter&#8217;s services alongside Celo&#8217;s blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/google-cloud-introduces-new-web3-startup-program/" rel="nofollow">Google Cloud Introduces New Web3 Startup Program</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Investor Committed Suicide After Losing Money on Bitcoin (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/indian-investor-committed-suicide-after-losing-money-on-bitcoin-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 20:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=248205</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The man's body was found floating in a river ten days after he had gone missing.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A 49-year-old resident of Kolkata, India, reportedly drowned in the Hooghly River. The primary autopsy found no evidence of violence, suggesting he committed suicide. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The man supposedly invested in shares and bitcoin, hinting that a potential loss on his investment could be one reason behind his unnatural death.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Indian Jumping off a Bridge</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent coverage </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/city/kolkata/bitcoin-investor-in-debt-found-dead-in-river/articleshow/99801686.cms" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">informed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the Indian police found the body floating in the Hooghly River, several miles north of Kolkata. The individual, whose name was not disclosed, had gone missing on April 16. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A close relative of the man told law enforcement agents that the victim did not seem to have any major issues. He lived with his wife and son in a flat on Roy Bahadur Road &#8211; one of Kolkata&#8217;s best areas. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A further investigation, though, estimated that he might have invested some funds in stocks and bitcoin, whereas a downturn in those investments could have pushed him to end his life.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A local police officer thinks it is too early to arrive at the conclusion that dealing with BTC might have played a role in the tragedy. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;He was in service, but we don&#8217;t know anything about his investments, leave alone investments in Bitcoin. We also don&#8217;t know why he went near the river. We would request all not to jump to a conclusion,&#8221; the policeman added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The victim&#8217;s family has not filed a complaint against a possible murder. A thorough investigation will try to determine the motive behind the potential suicide. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The police of Kolkata had to cope with another similar case earlier this month when a 23-year-old man </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-man-tried-to-jump-off-bridge-after-suffering-losses-in-crypto-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tried</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to jump off a river bridge. The individual explained he wanted to commit suicide because he suffered severe losses from investing in cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Suicide in Lucknow</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Investing in digital currencies hides its risks, and people should allocate only as much as they are ready to lose. As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-student-committed-suicide-after-becoming-a-victim-to-a-bitcoin-scam-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in March, a second-year B.Com student from the Indian city Lucknow did not follow that guidance and hanged himself after parting with a $4,200 BTC investment. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The boy was caught in a crypto scam that promised high returns. Nonetheless, he did not receive any yield, while the scheme&#8217;s representatives he was in touch with ceased communication with him. The victim felt depressed and took his life shortly after realizing the fraud. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The body was sent for post-mortem. Its report confirmed death due to suicide… According to the preliminary investigation, the boy hanged himself after losing money,&#8221; the police stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/indian-investor-committed-suicide-after-losing-money-on-bitcoin-report/" rel="nofollow">Indian Investor Committed Suicide After Losing Money on Bitcoin (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
