<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:14:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Massively Outperforms Crypto Hedge Funds in 2023: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-massively-outperforms-crypto-hedge-funds-in-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Institutions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264561</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/institutions_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/institutions_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto hedge funds have underperformed and faced an array of issues this year according to new research.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to data from Switzerland-based investment adviser 21e6 Capital AG, around 13% of crypto hedge funds have shut down so far this year. The reasons for the closures were weak performance and difficulties in accessing banking services.</p>
<p>Furthermore, crypto funds generated, on average, around 15% returns in the first half of 2023. They have been underperforming Bitcoin, which gained 77% over the same period.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Crypto hedge funds suffer from lagging performance to Bitcoin and a set of operational difficulties, such as accessing banking services.</p>
<p>About 13% of them shut down this year, according to data tracked by 21e6 Capital. 1/<a href="https://t.co/L7ozmXW1G4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/L7ozmXW1G4</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/crypto?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@crypto</a></p>
<p>— Yueqi Yang (@Yueqi_Yang) <a href="https://twitter.com/Yueqi_Yang/status/1687489607007358976?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 4, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>Crypto Hedge Funds Lagging</h2>
<p>Despite <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/two-thirds-of-worlds-largest-banks-are-crypto-friendly-research/" data-wpel-link="internal">reports</a> to the contrary claiming that the majority of banks are crypto-friendly, the reality is very different for many crypto hedge funds.</p>
<p>21e6 <a href="https://assets.21e6.io/blog/half-year-review-2023" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reported</a> that many funds held larger-than-normal cash positions following industry turmoil in 2022. As a result, they missed out on Bitcoin’s big moves earlier that year.</p>
<p>Head of marketing and sales at 21e6, Maximilian Bruckner, said many funds are “still struggling to find new partners” for banking services. Banking problems were compounded by the collapses of crypto-friendly banks Silvergate Capital and Signature Bank earlier this year.</p>
<p>Regulatory pressure and America’s SEC-led war on crypto haven’t helped their causes.</p>
<p>97 of the 700 crypto hedge funds tracked by the firm have closed in 2023, it stated. Several closed following the fallout of the FTX collapse, where many had stored their funds.</p>
<p>Those with “market-neutral strategies” performed the worst, generating only a 6.8% return for the first half of this year. The report concluded:</p>
<blockquote><p>“All crypto fund strategies achieved positive results this year. But relative to Bitcoin, they underperformed, especially those with significant exposure to altcoins, to futures, or those strongly dependent on momentum signals.”</p></blockquote>
<p>“Investor confidence improved slightly, but fund inflows and fund launches are not yet signaling a full recovery in sentiment,” it added.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>Digital assets remain flat this weekend with very little movement in total capitalization, which remains at $1.2 trillion at the time of writing.</p>
<p>There has been a slight retreat for BTC and ETH this week, with both dropping a couple of percents but remaining with their respective range-bound channels.</p>
<p>Trading volumes and volatility are currently at historical lows in this, the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-you-know-this-is-the-longest-crypto-bear-market-ever-as-altcoins-languish-regulation-looms-and-tradfi-encroaches/" data-wpel-link="internal">longest-ever</a> crypto winter in industry history.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-massively-outperforms-crypto-hedge-funds-in-2023-report/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Massively Outperforms Crypto Hedge Funds in 2023: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Block&#8217;s BTC Revenue Rises by Over 30% in Q2</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blocks-btc-revenue-rises-by-over-30-in-q2/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 20:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Square CashApp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264369</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["The year-over-year increase in bitcoin revenue and gross profit was driven by an increase in the quantity of bitcoin sold to customers," the firm said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The payment technology firm Block (formerly known as Square) revealed that its bitcoin revenue for the second quarter was approximately 34% more than the figure reported in Q2, 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company, spearheaded by Twitter&#8217;s former CEO Jack Dorsey, is a main player on the crypto scene, owning over 8,000 BTC. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Q2&#8217;s Solid Numbers</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Block </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://s29.q4cdn.com/628966176/files/doc_financials/2023/q2/2Q23_Block_Shareholder-Letter.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that its mobile application that enables monetary transfers &#8211; Cash App &#8211; generated a bitcoin revenue of $2.39 billion in Q2, 2023. The sum is approximately 34% higher than the nearly $1.8 billion registered in the second quarter of last year. Cash App&#8217;s BTC gross profit equaled $44 million, up 7% year-over-year.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The year-over-year increase in bitcoin revenue and gross profit was driven by an increase in the quantity of bitcoin sold to customers, partially offset by a decrease in the average market price of bitcoin compared to the prior-year period,&#8221; the firm stated. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Block disclosed that it had not recognized a bitcoin impairment loss during that time frame. As of the end of June 2023, its BTC investment was worth $245 million. Due to the slight price decrease of the primary digital asset in the following weeks, though, the company&#8217;s 8,027 BTC stash is currently worth approximately $234 million. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization is among the top 10 largest corporate holders of bitcoin (according to CoinGecko&#8217;s data). The leader is MicroStrategy which recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-another-420-btc-for-14-4-million/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">purchased</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> another 420 BTC, bringing its total to 152,800 BTC. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Block&#8217;s overall financial results (excluding bitcoin revenue) were also positive. However, the price of its shares failed to head north. SQ </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/SQ/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">stood</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at over $73 when the market closed on August 3, whereas it is now approximately 6% down in after-hours trading. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Reverse Situation Last Year</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The technology conglomerate </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blocks-shares-jumped-7-despite-declining-q4-bitcoin-revenue/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">disclosed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $1.83 billion of bitcoin revenue generated from its Cash App payment service in Q4 2022, 8.5% less than the Q4, 2021 figures. It explained that the disappointing number resulted from the market crash last year that dwindled investors&#8217; interest in the primary cryptocurrency. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The year-over-year decline in revenue was driven by a decrease in the total dollar amount of bitcoin sold to customers, which we recognize as bitcoin revenue, and bitcoin gross profit was 2% of bitcoin revenue in the quarter,&#8221; Block stated at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the shrunk figure, Block&#8217;s shares spiked by around 7% following the company&#8217;s much better overall financial results. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blocks-btc-revenue-rises-by-over-30-in-q2/" rel="nofollow">Block&#8217;s BTC Revenue Rises by Over 30% in Q2</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Love Hurts: Minnesota Man Loses Over $9 Million in a Crypto Romance Scam: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/love-hurts-minnesota-man-loses-over-9-million-in-a-crypto-romance-scam-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 18:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264437</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/broken_heart_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/broken_heart_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Instead of leaving his wife and getting rich overnight via investing in a suspicious crypto project, the victim ended up losing $9.2 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A resident of Eden Prairie, Minnesota, whose name was undisclosed, has reportedly parted with $9.2 million after falling prey in a typical cryptocurrency romance fraud. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The local police said it has never investigated a crypto-related scam where individuals have lost such a substantial sum.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Multi-Million Scheme</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.startribune.com/in-unprecedented-minnesota-fraud-case-crypto-scheme-bilks-eden-prairie-couple-out-of-9-million/600294214/?refresh=true" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Star Tribune, the man started chatting with a mysterious woman on LinkedIn who urged him to invest in a dubious cryptocurrency project called &#8220;Coinrule-web3.&#8221; She lured him that the investment would make him rich in a short period of time, whereas the generated funds could help the man abandon his wife and run off with his new &#8220;lover.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Blinded by her promises, he ended up distributing $9.2 million between December 2022 and June 2023 via 21 transactions. The man was encouraged by the high return on his investment which he observed on the suspicious platform. However, he was requested to pay millions of dollars upon withdrawing his funds.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite being kept in the dark, it was the man&#8217;s wife who assumed that there might be something wrong with the scheme. She informed the local police in mid-June that her husband had been liquidating their investment accounts for the past half a year. He also called &#8220;in panic,&#8221; urging her to withdraw all their savings to pay the fee so he could cash in his crypto funds. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Law enforcement agents launched an immediate investigation and found out that &#8220;Coinrule-web3&#8221; has been tied to multiple romance scams. They also determined that one of the banks that obtained some of the deposits was connected to previous money laundering cases. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Eden Prairie police disclosed they had investigated four such frauds so far this year. However, none of them could be compared to the most recent case.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;No one in the office has heard of a crypto fraud case as big. In fact, their eyes popped when I told them the amount,&#8221; John Stiles &#8211; spokesman for Minnesota Attorney General Keith Ellison, said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The inspectors also discovered that the mysterious woman embezzled the amount and transferred it into encrypted crypto wallets that no one besides the scammer could access.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The police officers have not revealed whether they have a suspect behind the crime or whether they will proceed with any arrests. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Romance Scams Have Become Highly Popular</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The aforementioned fraud is hardly the only example of a cryptocurrency romance fraud where people fall in love with an unknown individual who later drains their savings via a scheme involving digital assets. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/romance-crypto-scams-on-the-rise-accounted-for-185m-in-losses-for-americans/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, $185 million in losses for American victims parted with $185 million between January 2021 and March 2022 due to scams of this type. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that such fraudsters are active not only in the USA. A British man </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/love-hurts-british-man-loses-200k-in-a-bitcoin-romance-scam-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> $200,000 worth of bitcoin at the beginning of 2022, whereas an elderly resident of Nottinghamshire </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-woman-lost-over-200k-in-a-crypto-romance-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">transferred</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an even higher amount to a wrongdoer who introduced himself as a US Army surgeon.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/love-hurts-minnesota-man-loses-over-9-million-in-a-crypto-romance-scam-report/" rel="nofollow">Love Hurts: Minnesota Man Loses Over $9 Million in a Crypto Romance Scam: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>AI Investments Could Soar to $200 Billion by 2025 According to Goldman Sachs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ai-investments-could-soar-to-200-billion-by-2025-according-to-goldman-sachs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264544</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/goldman_ai_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/goldman_ai_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["AI-related investment could peak as high as 2.5 to 4% of GDP in the US and 1.5 to 2.5% of GDP in other major AI leaders," the experts suggested.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>According to Goldman Sachs&#8217; economists Joseph Briggs and Devesh Kodnani, investments related to Artificial Intelligence (AI) could climb to the astonishing $200 billion by 2025.</p>
<p>They also argued that the United States of America is well-positioned to become the global center of that technology.</p>
<h2>AI Could Impact the Economy</h2>
<p>Goldman Sachs Research, conducted by Briggs and Kodnani, <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/intelligence/pages/ai-investment-forecast-to-approach-200-billion-globally-by-2025.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">estimated</a> that Artificial intelligence has &#8220;enormous economic potential&#8221; and could potentially aid global labor productivity. The economists suggested that a large-scale transformation could happen once businesses invest in physical, digital, and human capital to implement new technologies and reshape their work processes.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Those investments, which could amount to around $200 billion globally by 2025, will probably happen before adoption and efficiency gains start driving major gains in productivity,&#8221; the analysis reads.</p></blockquote>
<p>Briggs and Kodnani think AI-focused investments could account for up to 4% of the US GDP in the future and up to 2.5% of the GDP of other nations. In their view, the world&#8217;s largest economy has the best chance to emerge as a global hub for such technology and could comprise around 50% of the total investments. China, on the other hand, could become the main rival in the field.</p>
<p>The research also determined that market interest in Artificial Intelligence has rapidly increased over the past several months. Approximately every sixth company in the Russell 3000 list has mentioned AI in its earning calls lately. In comparison, just 1% of the firms did so in 2016.</p>
<figure id="attachment_264550" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264550" style="width: 641px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-264550" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman.png" alt="Market Interest in AI" width="641" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman.png 1026w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman-300x187.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman-1024x639.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman-768x479.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Goldman-50x31.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 641px) 100vw, 641px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-264550" class="wp-caption-text">Market Interest in AI, Source: Goldman Sachs</figcaption></figure>
<p>A survey conducted among CEOs of Fortune 500 organizations (shared by Goldman Sachs) revealed that most bosses don&#8217;t think AI will impact their businesses or lower their labor needs in the next year. Nonetheless, the estimations are much different when observing a five-year period, with over 60% of executives expecting headcount amendments due to the technology&#8217;s advancement.</p>
<h2>Some of the Giants Dived in</h2>
<p>Artificial Intelligence has already grabbed the attention of some of the biggest corporations, such as Amazon Web Services (AWS) – the cloud unit of the e-commerce giant. Its CEO Adam Selipsky recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amazon-doubles-down-on-ai-by-investing-100-million/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that the entity will distribute $100 million to design a special &#8220;program&#8221; that could help businesses employ generative AI.</p>
<p>Microsoft and Google are other behemoths who dipped their toes into the field. The former <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-01-23/microsoft-makes-multibillion-dollar-investment-in-openai" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">invested</a> $10 billion into OpenAI, while the latter <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/583ead66-467c-4bd5-84d0-ed5df7b5bf9c" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">put</a> $300 million into Anthropic.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ai-investments-could-soar-to-200-billion-by-2025-according-to-goldman-sachs/" rel="nofollow">AI Investments Could Soar to $200 Billion by 2025 According to Goldman Sachs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bizarre FTX 2.0 Exchange Reboot Plans Are Unreal (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bizarre-ftx-2-0-exchange-reboot-plans-are-unreal-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264548</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_End.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_End.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A coalition of FTX international creditors / customers are behind a push by FTX's CEO to revive the non-US FTX exchange. It's a pretty bizarre idea given how damaged the brand is.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>But it&#8217;s also understandable that FTX creditors are looking for a less stinky exit. The FTX 2.0 reboot proposal is in the reorganization plan <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-reboot-proposal-presented-as-part-of-reorganization-efforts-ftt-jumped-10-overnight/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed Monday</a>, July 31.</p>
<h2>FTX 2.0 Exchange Plans Have High Hopes</h2>
<p>News of the filing caused FTT tokens to spike from $1.34 to 1.55. But soon after, they settled even lower than before. Anyone holding FTT tokens and scanning like a hawk for the opportunity had a brief window to sell with some cushion.</p>
<p>As it turns out, the idea has several downsides. To begin with, it would be like bringing back Enron, or the Exxon Valdez, or Lehman Brothers.</p>
<p>What is the point of that instead of starting from scratch like the Kraken CEO suggested?</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;FTX 2.0 would be worse than starting from scratch. No team, no tech, no licenses, no banking, tarnished brand.&#8221; -Kraken CEO Jesse Powell, <a href="https://twitter.com/jespow/status/1686610969454342144" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Aug 2</a></p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, it&#8217;s an overly-complicated scheme for crypto investors.</p>
<h2>What Investor Would Buy FTT vs. BTC and ETH?</h2>
<p>They&#8217;re just going to sell FTT tokens to newbs who have never heard of FTX or SBF. Then, they&#8217;ll use their money to buy bitcoin and ether. Meanwhile, they&#8217;ll raise funds to pay the bills during the bear market.</p>
<p>Then, as crypto rallies over the long-term cyclical growth channel, they&#8217;ll buy back or burn just enough FTT tokens to keep it pumping along while keeping any extra profits from their BTC and ETH.</p>
<p>A revived FTX might offer yield-bearing accounts instead of focusing on the tokens. But the scheme would be the same. They would pay yields out with VC funding during the bear market, then BTC and ETH gains during the bull run, and keep what&#8217;s left as profits.</p>
<p>This is exactly what SBF did and mismanaged, letting it fall into insolvency. Why would anyone other than the least educated, most vulnerable new crypto retail investor even bother using FTX 2.0 as a middleman custodian for their <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">BTC</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">ETH</a>?</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bizarre-ftx-2-0-exchange-reboot-plans-are-unreal-opinion/" rel="nofollow">Bizarre FTX 2.0 Exchange Reboot Plans Are Unreal (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase to Judge: Crypto is Baseball Cards, not Stocks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-judge-crypto-is-baseball-cards-not-stocks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 14:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264620</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrencies_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrencies_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase found a pretty based way to explain crypto to U.S. Courts for the SEC: Instead of thinking of cryptocurrencies as stocks, think of them like baseball cards.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lawyers for Coinbase Global <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-to-the-rescue-coinbase-cites-ripple-ruling-seeks-to-end-sec-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">asked a</a> U.S. judge Friday to dismiss a suit by the Securities and Exchange Commission. They brought the arguments to back up their request.</p>
<h2>Coinbase lawyers ask judge to dismiss SEC lawsuit</h2>
<p>The SEC lawsuit filed June 6, alleges the crypto exchange is an unregistered securities broker and exchange. In <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/7eaTxSOvCLrGR2frvCqS3Q/b98f952657b7bc821b218d1f601b9161/CoinbasevSEC12_c_Motion.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">the motion</a> to dismiss the suit, Coinbase says:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The SEC misreads Howey in asserting that a &#8216;scheme&#8217; without a contractual undertaking will suffice.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Moreover:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Recent crypto cases do not support the SEC’s efforts to use &#8216;scheme&#8217; as an escape hatch from statutory text.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>And furthermore:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The SEC’s effort to portray a simple asset sale as a security is an unprecedented stretch.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Then, the motion goes on to absolutely pulverize the SEC&#8217;s allegations with a simple analogy to baseball cards.</p>
<h2>Why crypto is like baseball cards, not stocks</h2>
<p>To clearly illustrate what they mean, Coinbase&#8217;s lawyers make the following devastating critique of the Gensler SEC&#8217;s view of cryptocurrencies:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;So for example: one can invest in a baseball or other trading card company, through an instrument that imposes obligations on the company, and that will be a security. Or one can buy baseball cards on the open market, hoping they appreciate in value, and one will have bought a commodity. That remains true even if the company makes representations about plans to create a premier card trading platform, to drive up the value of the cards it sells. Those representations can’t turn baseball cards into securities. Baseball cards are not &#8216;shares in the [baseball card] enterprise.'&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The attorneys for Coinbase continued later on in the motion to delineate crypto exchanges from the stock market:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There is an asset sale. That’s it. It is akin to the sale of a parcel of land, the value of which may fluctuate after the sale. Or a condo in a new development. Or an American Girl Doll, or a Beanie Baby, or a baseball card.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>This is not a far-fetched case at all when the first major exchange to sell bitcoin <a href="https://www.wired.com/2014/03/bitcoin-exchange/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">was Mt. Gox</a> (an acronym for Magic: The Gathering Exchange, yes, the collectible card game).</p>
<p>Coinbase&#8217;s argument here isn&#8217;t any shoe-horned in theorizing. It has a real basis in the historical development of the market for digital assets and tokens.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-to-judge-crypto-is-baseball-cards-not-stocks/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase to Judge: Crypto is Baseball Cards, not Stocks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s the Cost to Mine 1 BTC for Top Bitcoin Miners? Bernstein Clarifies</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/whats-the-cost-to-mine-1-btc-for-top-bitcoin-miners-bernstein-clarifies/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 11:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264459</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Should the market experience favorable momentum due to Bitcoin ETF approvals and increased engagement from institutional players, miners would attain sufficient "margin room" for the 2024 halving, Bernstein outlined. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin miners have had a rocky start in 2023 after being battered by a severe market downturn the previous year. But as prices recovered over the last several months, they have been at significant capacity, according to Bernstein.</p>
<p>The brokerage firm&#8217;s latest report weighs in on how large miners are poised to reap substantial benefits from such a growing trend.</p>
<h2>Where do Miners Stand Ahead of Bitcoin Halving?</h2>
<p>The report suggests that the 16 largest publicly listed mining firms collectively contributed to 16% of the overall mined BTC. The collective mining capacity of the companies was found to be at 72 exahashes per second (EH/s) and is expected to amplify the capacity by 182% within the upcoming 2-3 years.</p>
<p>According to Bernstein analyst Gautam Chhugani, the larger miners with low cost of production and low debt are poised to be &#8220;the big beneficiaries of the expansion, with greater capacity,&#8221; to be resilient in the event of high volatility and cost surges resulting from the upcoming Bitcoin halving that is slated for April 2024.</p>
<p>With Bitcoin currently hovering near $29,000, 15 of the aforementioned Bitcoin miners have production costs below $15,000 per BTC, according to Bernstein&#8217;s estimation.</p>
<p>The analyst leading the <a href="https://www.bernstein.com/home.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With the upcoming halving, that would double the cost of production, and would push a few miners to break even, assuming no price increase from here.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Approval of Bitcoin ETFs Could be a Silver Lining</h2>
<p>On the bright side, the approval of the Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) could come as a relief for miners. Bernstein&#8217;s report argued that the market could witness a &#8220;positive momentum&#8221; from the subsequent increased institutional participation in case the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deviates from its rigid stance.</p>
<p>In such a case, miners would enjoy enough &#8220;margin room&#8221; for the 2024 halving event since the &#8220;lower the cost of production, better the miner positioning for the<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/breakdown-of-btcs-price-performance-after-previous-halvings-will-history-repeat/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"> bitcoin halving</a> impact.&#8221;</p>
<p>It is also important to note that three of the aforementioned miners have a debt-to-equity ratio of over 1, which reduces their ability to hold the line against depressed Bitcoin prices. Four prominent Bitcoin mining companies &#8211; Riot (RIOT), Marathon Digital (MARA), Hut 8 (HUT), and Hive Digital (HIVE) &#8211; retain the crypto in their financial portfolio. This strategic choice empowers them to wait for more favorable prices before engaging in sales. Such a move ultimately leads to amplified realized profits from the BTC they have extracted, according to the report.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-the-cost-to-mine-1-btc-for-top-bitcoin-miners-bernstein-clarifies/" rel="nofollow">What&#8217;s the Cost to Mine 1 BTC for Top Bitcoin Miners? Bernstein Clarifies</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s the Cheapest Day of the Week to Buy Bitcoin? We Asked Google Bard</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/whats-the-cheapest-day-of-the-week-to-buy-bitcoin-we-asked-google-bard/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264605</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/bitcoin_binary_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[We asked Alphabet's chatbot, Google Bard, the best day of the week to buy Bitcoin. Then we checked the Google AI's answer against Yahoo Finance data to make sure Bard wasn't playing fool the journalist.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin price has cautiously ratcheted upward since Jan. A rising trend channel from $16,600 to $30,000 almost doubled the spot price of BTC in H1.</p>
<p>The price changed in three phases, with blistering rallies that happened in January, March, and June.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s what large language model chatbot Google Bard has to say about the best day of the week to buy cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Ripple.</p>
<h2>Cheapest Day of the Week to Buy Crypto?</h2>
<p>There&#8217;s no telling for sure if markets will cool down for now or soar higher in the short term.</p>
<p>Investors looking to accumulate crypto in regular small increments for the long term, however, might consider making Saturdays their go-to weekday for <em>stacking sats</em>.</p>
<p>Buying a set amount of crypto or stocks on a weekly schedule is a classic investing strategy called <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/should-i-buy-bitcoin-now-is-it-now-a-good-price-for-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">dollar cost averaging</a>.</p>
<p>Google Bard says Saturdays are the second-best day of the week to buy crypto. But if you&#8217;re looking for the cheapest prices, the best day of all to buy crypto, according to Bard, is Sunday.</p>
<h2>Here was Google Bard&#8217;s entire answer</h2>
<p>Question: &#8220;Bard, what is the best day of the week to buy cryptocurrency?&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p><em>&#8220;According to historical market data, the best day of the week to buy cryptocurrency is Sunday. The second best day is Saturday. After that, prices rise with Friday being the most expensive day to buy cryptocurrency.</em></p>
<p>Here are some of the reasons why Sunday is considered the best day to buy cryptocurrency:</p>
<ul>
<li>Trading volumes are typically lower on weekends, which can lead to lower prices.</li>
<li>There is less news and volatility on weekends, which can also lead to lower prices.</li>
<li>Some investors may be taking profits on Friday, which can drive prices down on Saturday and Sunday.</li>
</ul>
<p>Of course, there is no guarantee that the price of cryptocurrency will be lower on Sunday. The market is volatile and prices can go up or down at any time. However, if you are looking to buy cryptocurrency at a relatively low price, Sunday is a good day to start your search.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Here&#8217;s a look at what the numbers say to back up Bard&#8217;s answer:</p>
<h2>Psst: Bitcoin price goes on sale 1% Sundays</h2>
<p>Bitcoin price averaged lower from Saturdays through Mondays over the last year of trading. An <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/BTC-USD/history/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">analysis</a> of the historical daily price data suggests Fridays through Mondays are the best days to buy crypto.</p>
<p>Tuesdays and Wednesdays are the best days to sell, the data suggest.</p>
<p>The lowest average daily high price for any day of the week for Bitcoin from Aug 5, 2022 &#8211; Aug 3, 2023, was on Sundays. Over this time period, BTC&#8217;s average intraday high price on Sundays was $23,595. On Saturdays, it was $23,480. The highest average was on Wednesdays: $23,850.</p>
<p>If an investor reaped the entire benefit of these figures, it would mean buying their BTC 1% cheaper each week.</p>
<p>Not bad, Bard.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/whats-the-cheapest-day-of-the-week-to-buy-bitcoin-we-asked-google-bard/" rel="nofollow">What&#8217;s the Cheapest Day of the Week to Buy Bitcoin? We Asked Google Bard</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Squeezing at $29K as Shiba Inu (SHIB) Weekly Gains Top 12%: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-squeezing-at-29k-as-shiba-inu-shib-weekly-gains-top-12-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264631</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_btc_mu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shib_btc_mu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin's price escape this narrow range around $29K soon? The market's volatility is currenty non-existent. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s the weekend, and, let&#8217;s be honest &#8211; nobody is expecting a lot of action. And while there are some weekends that defy this sentiment&#8230; this one is not among them.</p>
<p>In fact, the vast majority of the major cryptocurrencies have failed to move, charting incredibly insignificant differences in their price compared to 24 hours ago. Let&#8217;s take a look.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Getting Squeezed at $29K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been tremendously calm throughout the past week, and it&#8217;s been trading around $29,000 for a while now. This is a very narrow range for a cryptocurrency that&#8217;s as volatile as BTC.</p>
<p>But that volatility seems to have disappeared lately and on a 5-day weighted average, BTC has been less volatile compared to even gold.</p>
<figure id="attachment_264632" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264632" style="width: 1531px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-264632" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0608231" width="1531" height="860" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231.jpg 1531w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231-1024x575.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231-768x431.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0608231-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1531px) 100vw, 1531px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-264632" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance via TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>As you can see in the above 1-hour chart, there&#8217;s literally nothing going on with Bitcoin&#8217;s price, which is completely stuck at the $29K level.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s worth noting that these periods of calmness are not very typical for the cryptocurrency market and tend to be a precursor to a larger move.</p>
<p>We just have to wait and see which direction BTC will take when it inevitably spikes.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Also Flatline</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s not just the Bitcoin price that&#8217;s experiencing a volume draught. It&#8217;s also the altcoin market.</p>
<p>In fact, the total traded volume across the entire industry for the past 24 hours, according to CoinGecko, sits at $23 billion. The good news is that the market is trending upward today, albeit ever so slightly, as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_264633" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-264633" style="width: 1495px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-264633" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231" width="1495" height="773" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231.jpg 1495w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231-300x155.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231-1024x529.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231-768x397.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_heatmap_0608231-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1495px) 100vw, 1495px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-264633" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The most impressive thing is that Shiba Inu (SHIB) continues to chart gains of more than 5% and remains the absolute best performer from the major coins by means of total market cap.</p>
<p>In fact, SHIB&#8217;s weekly gains now top 12%, which, amid a stagnating market like this, is worth noting.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, FLEX Coin is the best-performer from the top 100 with 14% gains, followed by GALA with 8.7%, and ApeCoin (APE) by 8%.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-squeezing-at-29k-as-shiba-inu-shib-weekly-gains-top-12-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Squeezing at $29K as Shiba Inu (SHIB) Weekly Gains Top 12%: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentralized Hedge Fund VC Spectra Reports Strong Demand for Its Presale</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-hedge-fund-vc-spectra-reports-strong-demand-for-its-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264576</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/png_20230620_224536_0000_1024x603_1691150442Cs2WGZ4mMD.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/png_20230620_224536_0000_1024x603_1691150442Cs2WGZ4mMD.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; London, United Kingdom, August 5th, 2023] Decentralized hedge fund VC Spectra has reported strong demand for its Stage 2 presale. The token sale has drawn considerable interest from early investors and underlined VC Spectra&#8217;s potential to redefine the crypto industry. Priding itself on democratizing access to investment opportunities, VC Spectra has carved [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; London, United Kingdom, August 5th, 2023]</strong></p>
<h1><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/td__eRaRvu85SBLZOm5vv3KCdN4fGjAFVrm0f1yYLqNRRlQ53_1691236547uANOPhjXfO.jpeg" /></h1>
<p>Decentralized hedge fund VC Spectra has reported strong demand for its Stage 2 presale. The token sale has drawn considerable interest from early investors and underlined VC Spectra&#8217;s potential to redefine the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Priding itself on democratizing access to investment opportunities, <a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VC Spectra</a> has carved a distinct niche for itself. The on-chain hedge fund extends the availability of early-stage investments to non-accredited investors, thereby bridging a significant market gap.</p>
<p>Investors opting for the SPCT token can leverage an array of unique benefits. These perks include quarterly dividends and buybacks, voting rights, and early access to initial coin offerings (ICOs).</p>
<p>The SPCT token, developed on the Bitcoin blockchain using the BRC-20 standard, provides a robust mechanism for decentralized trading, asset management, and transaction facilitation within the Spectra platform. The Spectra Token (SPCT) is the main currency within the Spectra ecosystem, enabling access to different services on the platform.</p>
<p>By implementing a deflationary model featuring a burn mechanism for the SPCT token, the decentralized hedge fund aims to decrease token circulation gradually. When coupled with <a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VC Spectra&#8217;s</a> unique investment offerings, this novel approach further solidifies SPCT &#8216;s standing in the crypto market.</p>
<p>The Vc Spectra public presale is currently in Stage 2 and has already seen robust demand. The <a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">SPCT token</a>, which started at $0.008 during Stage 1, increased to $0.011 in Stage 2. In the upcoming Stage 3, the token price will increase to $0.025. This is an increase of 213% from the initial token price. Currently, <a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">VC Spectra (SPCT)</a> is offering a 25% bonus for all investor deposits.</p>
<p><strong>About VC Spectra</strong></p>
<p>Spectra is a leading firm driving innovation in Fintech and blockchain through strategic investments and ICOs, empowering financial growth by harnessing cutting-edge technologies.</p>
<p>Spectra VC is a venture capital fund that invests in blockchain and technology-based projects with the goal of generating returns for investors.</p>
<p>Find out more about the VC Spectra presale here:</p>
<p><a href="https://invest.vcspectra.io/login" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Presale</a> | <a href="https://vcspectra.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a>  | <a href="https://t.me/VCSpectra" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/spectravcfund" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/decentralized-hedge-fund-vc-spectra-reports-strong-demand-for-its-presale/" rel="nofollow">Decentralized Hedge Fund VC Spectra Reports Strong Demand for Its Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
