<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Crypto Fraud Scheme Organizers Face Legal Action by CFTC in Florida, Louisiana, and Arkansas</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-fraud-scheme-organizers-face-legal-action-by-cftc-florida-louisiana-arkansas.htm</link><description>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has taken legal action against four individuals and their organization, Fundsz, for their involvement in a fraudulent scheme related to cryptocurrencies and precious metals trading. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-fraud-scheme-organizers-face-legal-action-by-cftc-florida-louisiana-arkansas.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Fraud Scheme Organizers Face Legal Action by CFTC in Florida, Louisiana, and Arkansas&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Fundsz</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 08:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-fraud-scheme-organizers-face-legal-action-by-cftc-florida-louisiana-arkansas.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122298/323563/adobestock-541845522-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="97124"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Spikes Up 2% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-2-24-hours-time-buy.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's recent price surge of 2% within a 24-hour period has prompted speculation about its potential implications for investors.  &lt;br /&gt;
As market dynamics continue to evolve, the question arises: Is this surge signaling an opportune moment to consider buying Bitcoin? Let's find out. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent podcast interview, Michael Saylor, CEO of MicroStrategy, highlighted his perspective on the growing trend of large corporations embracing and centralizing Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-2-24-hours-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Spikes Up 2% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-spikes-up-2-24-hours-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122293/323556/13-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="534339"/></item><item><title>Binance Seeks Registration in Taiwan Under Money Laundering Control Act and FSC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-registration-taiwan-under-money-laundering-control-act-fsc-1.htm</link><description>Binance, the global leader in cryptocurrency exchange by trading volume, has submitted an application for registration in Taiwan according to the Money Laundering Control Act and the Financial Supervisory Commission (FSC). &lt;br /&gt;
During a private meeting on Tuesday, Taiwan's Financial Supervisory Commission informed numerous local crypto service providers that Binance is seeking Anti-Money Laundering (AML) compliance. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-registration-taiwan-under-money-laundering-control-act-fsc-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Seeks Registration in Taiwan Under Money Laundering Control Act and FSC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Taiwan</category><category>FSC</category><category>VASPs</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-seeks-registration-taiwan-under-money-laundering-control-act-fsc-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122270/323548/getpaidstock-com-64d80d66.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="274105"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Legal Battles Continue to Shape its Trajectory – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-legal-battles-continue-shape-its-trajectory-heres-latest.htm</link><description>The ongoing legal wrangle between Ripple Labs and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to cast a shadow over the trajectory of XRP's price.  &lt;br /&gt;
With each twist and turn in the courtroom, the cryptocurrency market responds, causing palpable shifts in XRP's valuation. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-legal-battles-continue-shape-its-trajectory-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Legal Battles Continue to Shape its Trajectory – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-legal-battles-continue-shape-its-trajectory-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122288/323543/chart-xrpusd-jpeg.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1249454"/></item><item><title>Researchers Deploy AI to Uncover Crypto Giveaway Scam Schemes on Twitter</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-deploy-ai-uncover-crypto-giveaway-scam-schemes-twitter.htm</link><description>Researchers at San Diego State University have developed an artificial intelligence (AI) system to detect and expose cryptocurrency giveaway scams on Twitter.  &lt;br /&gt;
Dubbed GiveawayScamHunter, the automated system has identified a staggering 95,111 scam lists created by 87,617 accounts on the social media platform between June 2022 and June 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-deploy-ai-uncover-crypto-giveaway-scam-schemes-twitter.htm"&gt;Read More: Researchers Deploy AI to Uncover Crypto Giveaway Scam Schemes on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Technology News</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Scam</category><category>Crypto Scam</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-deploy-ai-uncover-crypto-giveaway-scam-schemes-twitter.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122275/323512/scam-7503834-1280-media-l.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="128592"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu, Pepe Pump 8%, Which Meme Coins Are Next - Trader Price Predictions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-pepe-price-pump-which-meme-coins-next-trader-price-predictions.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu and Pepe are both up 8% in the past 24 hours, outperforming the wider crypto market which is slightly in the red after news broke yesterday of the SEC delaying its decision on the Ark Bitcoin ETF. &lt;br /&gt;
Some prominent analysts have noted that ten to twelve months prior to the last Bitcoin halving, BTC dominance peaked and altcoin dominance bottomed. If that pattern repeats, it may be a good time to scale into altcoins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-pepe-price-pump-which-meme-coins-next-trader-price-predictions.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu, Pepe Pump 8%, Which Meme Coins Are Next - Trader Price Predictions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-pepe-price-pump-which-meme-coins-next-trader-price-predictions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122278/323524/pepe-coin-dogecoin-shiba-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260917"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Bases, PayPal Stablecoins, Binance Exchanges and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/coinbase-bases-paypal-stablecoins-binance-exchanges-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/coinbase-bases-paypal-stablecoins-binance-exchanges-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Bases, PayPal Stablecoins, Binance Exchanges and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/coinbase-bases-paypal-stablecoins-binance-exchanges-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122082/323379/7-naiive-twitter.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="86233"/></item><item><title>Lil Tay Crypto Token 'LilTay' Emerges on BNB Chain Amidst False Reports on Rapper's Death</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lil-tay-crypto-token-liltay-emerges-bnb-chain-amidst-false-reports-rappers-death.htm</link><description>False reports about the death of internet-famous 14-year-old rapper Lil Tay have triggered the emergence of an unofficial crypto token named "LilTay" on the BNB Chain.  &lt;br /&gt;
The launch of the token coincides with the development of an Ethereum-based "Liltay Token" by her ex-manager, Harry Tsang.  &lt;br /&gt;
The BNB Chain version of the LilTay token has a limited supply of just over 100 tokens and has yet to be traded. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lil-tay-crypto-token-liltay-emerges-bnb-chain-amidst-false-reports-rappers-death.htm"&gt;Read More: Lil Tay Crypto Token 'LilTay' Emerges on BNB Chain Amidst False Reports on Rapper's Death&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lil-tay-crypto-token-liltay-emerges-bnb-chain-amidst-false-reports-rappers-death.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122268/323500/lil-tay-dead-080923-tout-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="134494"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Halving Event in 2024 Sparks Bullish Sentiments – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm</link><description>The BTC/USD is currently witnessing a decline of nearly 0.50%, with its value standing at $29,400.  &lt;br /&gt;
As the cryptocurrency market navigates this shift, Bitcoin faces intensified price pressure in anticipation of the Bitcoin halving event in 2024 and a crucial decision by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regarding an ETF application.  &lt;br /&gt;
Moreover, releasing US inflation data adds an additional layer of uncertainty to the market's trajectory. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Halving Event in 2024 Sparks Bullish Sentiments – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-halving-event-2024-sparks-bullish-sentiments-time-buy-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122264/323494/12-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="533850"/></item><item><title>S Korean Prosecutors Want to Jail $651m ‘Crypto Scammers’ for 12-15 Years</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm</link><description>South Korean prosecutors say they hope to jail executives thought to be behind a $651 million crypto scam to prison for up to 15 years. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Asia Kyungjae, the alleged scam saw 8,000 people left out of pocket. &lt;br /&gt;
The scammers allegedly offered individuals “payouts” if they paid their utilities bills using cryptoassets via a dedicated platform named OnNetworks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm"&gt;Read More: S Korean Prosecutors Want to Jail $651m ‘Crypto Scammers’ for 12-15 Years&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Scam</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-prosecutors-want-to-jail-651m-crypto-scammers-for-12-15-years.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122205/323369/skor-1108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="539716"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 August – Fantom, Rocket Pool, Sui</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has opted to postpone its decision on Ark Invest's proposal for a Bitcoin ETF, continuing a longstanding challenge for cryptocurrency assets seeking inclusion on mainstream U.S. financial platforms. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC announced on Friday its move to solicit public opinion regarding a particular amendment in the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF application, potentially prolonging the decision-making process into 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 August – Fantom, Rocket Pool, Sui&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Fantom</category><category>Shibie</category><category>Rocket Pool</category><category>Chimpanzee</category><category>SUI</category><category>Sui Price</category><category>FTM Price</category><category>FTM</category><category>RPL</category><category>Rpl Price</category><category>CHMPZ</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Cryptos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Barbie</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>US SEC</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Staking</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFTs</category><category>Chatbots</category><category>Telegram</category><category>Chatbot</category><category>Merchandise</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-august-fantom-rocket-pool-sui.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122258/323481/bctbt-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260398"/></item><item><title>AI Crypto Signals Made Easy for Newcomers with New Crypto Startup yPredict – $3.4 Million Raised So Far</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm</link><description>Financial markets have always been unpredictable. Investors have traditionally sought assistance from experts, charts, and algorithms to make informed decisions. But the rise of technology, particularly artificial intelligence, has brought about tools that are changing the face of trading.  &lt;br /&gt;
With crypto signals becoming increasingly popular, traders are also searching for reliable platforms offering these essential cues....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Crypto Signals Made Easy for Newcomers with New Crypto Startup yPredict – $3.4 Million Raised So Far&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Price Predictions</category><category>Best Utility Coin</category><category>Ypredict Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-made-easy-for-newcomers-with-new-crypto-startup-ypredict-34-million-raised-so-far.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122228/323480/f3q1xjexiaazdtv.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="112896"/></item><item><title>Bank of America Says PayPal’s Stablecoin Will Not Record Significant Adoption In The Coming Months</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm</link><description>A new report by the Bank of America suggests that PayPal’s new stablecoin, PYUSD  will not record the projected adoption in the near term citing tougher competition and indifference of investors. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the report, the launch of the new stablecoin by the financial giant is great for the digital asset community and the company itself but it will struggle going head to head against USD Tether (USDT) and USD Coin (USDC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm"&gt;Read More: Bank of America Says PayPal’s Stablecoin Will Not Record Significant Adoption In The Coming Months&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>PayPal</category><category>Bank of America</category><category>PYUSD</category><category>Stablecoin</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bank-of-america-says-paypals-stablecoin-will-not-record-significant-adoption-coming-months.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122256/323479/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103256"/></item><item><title>Sam Bankman-Fried is Heading Back to Jail For Witness Tampering After Judge Ruling</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm</link><description>Disgraced former FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is being sent back to jail over alleged witness tampering. &lt;br /&gt;
US District Judge Lewis Kaplan stated that there is probable cause to believe that the defendant attempted to tamper with witnesses on at least two occasions. &lt;br /&gt;
Bankman-Fried had been staying at his parents' house in California on a $250 million bail....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Bankman-Fried is Heading Back to Jail For Witness Tampering After Judge Ruling&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>People In Crypto</category><category>FTX</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/sam-bankman-fried-is-heading-back-to-jail-for-witness-tampering-after-judge-ruling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122257/323477/adobestock-544467568-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2842826"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Alternative BTC20 Price Ready to Pump as Buybacks Kick in and 54% of Supply Staked</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm</link><description>Launched on Uniswap decentralized exchange yesterday, 'Bitcoin on Ethereum' coin BTC20 is proving an excellent advert for staking, with 54% of tokens now deposited into the smart contract.  &lt;br /&gt;
At the time of writing, $3,303,345 has been staked at a current annual percentage yield of 79.47%, according to the latest BTC20 website real-time dashboard data. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Alternative BTC20 Price Ready to Pump as Buybacks Kick in and 54% of Supply Staked&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-alternative-btc20-price-ready-pump-as-buy-backs-kick-54-of-supply-staked.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122252/323471/btc20-usd-uni-dextools-io.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="281168"/></item><item><title>Coinbase's New Base Blockchain Draws $10 Million Inflows Day After Launch – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Base, a new Ethereum layer 2 blockchain that has been developed by crypto exchange Coinbase, saw inflows worth just over $10 million on its first day after launch. &lt;br /&gt;
According to data from Dune Analytics, the $10 million were transferred to the network by over the course of 24 hours on Thursday, one day after its launch. &lt;br /&gt;
A little more than 15,000 new users joined Base on Thursday, and the day saw 40% fewer transactions than on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase's New Base Blockchain Draws $10 Million Inflows Day After Launch – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Base</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbases-new-base-blockchain-draws-10-million-inflows-day-after-launch-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122249/323462/coinbase-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="708345"/></item><item><title>Venture Firm a16z Dives into ZK Technology Research with 'Jolt' and 'Lasso' Projects</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm</link><description>Prominent VC firm Andreessen Horowitz (a16z) has unveiled two open-source software projects focused on zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs. &lt;br /&gt;
These projects aim to accelerate the core technology behind ZK proofs, a promising type of cryptography that can help scale blockchains by increasing transaction throughput, reducing costs, and enhancing privacy, the firm said in a recent announcement. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm"&gt;Read More: Venture Firm a16z Dives into ZK Technology Research with 'Jolt' and 'Lasso' Projects&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>a16z crypto</category><category>a16z</category><category>zkSnarks</category><category>Scaling</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/venture-firm-a16z-dives-into-zk-technology-research-with-jolt-lasso-projects.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122245/323456/fugqgvnwaaq-yqs-media-lib.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="58061"/></item><item><title>Binance Labs Supports Curve DAO Token with $5 Million Investment, Plans BNB Chain Deployment</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Binance’s investment arm, Binance Labs, has announced a $5 million investment in Curve DAO Token (CRV) in a display of support for Curve and decentralized finance (DeFi) at large. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Labs Supports Curve DAO Token with $5 Million Investment, Plans BNB Chain Deployment&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-supports-curve-dao-token-with-5-million-investment-plans-bnb-chain-deployment.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122243/323455/adobestock-286536391-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="124988"/></item><item><title>DCG and Barry Silbert Seek Dismissal of Lawsuit by Gemini Trust Company Over Alleged Misrepresentations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm</link><description>Digital Currency Group (DCG) has filed a motion to dismiss Gemini's lawsuit, claiming fraud by the company and its founder, Barry Silbert, through DCG's subsidiary, Genesis, which held funds for Gemini's Earn program. &lt;br /&gt;
On July 7, Gemini and its founders, Cameron, and Tyler Winklevoss, filed a lawsuit alleging that DCG and Barry Silbert provided false information about the financial status of their lending subsidiary, Genesis....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm"&gt;Read More: DCG and Barry Silbert Seek Dismissal of Lawsuit by Gemini Trust Company Over Alleged Misrepresentations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DCG</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Genesis</category><category>FTX</category><category>Winklevoss</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcg-barry-silbert-seek-dismissal-of-lawsuit-by-gemini-trust-company-over-alleged-misrepresentations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122237/323454/digital-currency-group-1-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="66296"/></item><item><title>Argentina Becomes Latest Country to Conduct Probe Into Iris-Scanning Worldcoin's Privacy Issues</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm</link><description>Argentina has joined the list of jurisdictions investigating the recently launched AI-meets-crypto project Worldcoin and its privacy practices that stirred endless controversies. &lt;br /&gt;
The Argentinian Agency for Access to Public Information (AAIP) published a notice on Aug. 8, which will conduct an investigation into the processing of personal data carried out by the Worldcoin Foundation in Argentina....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Becomes Latest Country to Conduct Probe Into Iris-Scanning Worldcoin's Privacy Issues&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-becomes-latest-country-to-conduct-probe-into-iris-scanning-worldcoins-privacy-issues.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122239/323447/eye-1132531-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="211900"/></item></channel></rss>
