<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 01:44:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Short-Term Bitcoin Investors Are Taking Profit After the Pump: Glassnode</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/short-term-bitcoin-investors-are-taking-profit-after-the-pump-glassnode/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 01:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234765</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Full_Circle.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Full_Circle.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Short-term holders are selling into the Bitcoin rally to take profit while they can, on-chain analysis shows. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Certain Bitcoin investors are selling while they can after the primary cryptocurrency reclaimed $23,000 earlier this month, according to Glassnode. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The blockchain intelligence provider’s latest report reviews recent on-chain behavioral patterns exhibited by both short and long-term holders. </span></p>
<h2>Exiting While They Can</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The </span><a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-04-2023/?utm_campaign=woc_04_2023&amp;utm_medium=woc_newsletter&amp;utm_source=email" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">newsletter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, posted on Monday, begins by examining Bitcoin’s price, which have reclaimed “multiple on-chain pricing models.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">One model includes the investor price – which reflects the average acquisition price for all coins spent and distributed by Bitcoin miners. Having overcome this model at $17,400, the average miner has returned to a position of profitability.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The move has also returned many people’s Bitcoin back into the profit zone, with Percent Supply in Profit surging from 55% at $16,000 to 67% at $23,100. This was one of the sharpest spikes for Bitcoin profitability during a bear market that has ever occurred. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Glassnode stated that movements in this metric can be useful for identifying when a market recovery may be underway. That said, movements of this size also incentivize Bitcoin holders who have returned to profit to start realizing some of their gains. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In particular, the Percentage of Short-Term Holder Supply in Profit has returned above 97.5% – at which point investors “tend to seize the opportunity and exit at break-even or profit.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Given this substantial spike in profitability, the probability of sell pressure sourced from short term holders is likely to grow accordingly,” said Glassnode. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The data is already bearing this out: trading volume among short term Bitcoin holders (those whose coins last move less than 6 months ago) has skyrocketed well past its long term declining trend. </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-difficulty-surges-10-to-new-ath-as-miners-return/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Miners</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, too, have sold into the rally. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Therefore, the sustainability of the current rally can be considered a balance between inflowing and newly deployed demand, meeting the supply drawn out of investor wallets by these higher prices,” Glassnode continued.</span></p>
<h2>Long Term Holders</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">While short-term holders are selling off, the number coins that haven’t moved for over 6 months is growing at a rate of 100,000 BTC per month. That means that HODLer conviction remains strong, even amidst a market rally. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">At current prices, the average long-term holder is at roughly a break-even basis, meaning their coins are at the same price they bought in at. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last week, Glassnode </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-yearly-start-may-signal-an-incoming-bull-market-glassnode/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">noted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that Bitcoin’s surge in volatility this month could signal the beginning of a cyclical bull market. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/short-term-bitcoin-investors-are-taking-profit-after-the-pump-glassnode/" rel="nofollow">Short-Term Bitcoin Investors Are Taking Profit After the Pump: Glassnode</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Companies Should Separate Clients&#8217; Crypto Assets From Their Own: NYDFS</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/companies-should-separate-clients-crypto-assets-from-their-own-nydfs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234674</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/NYDFS_Crypto.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/NYDFS_Crypto.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The regulator claimed the guidance is intended to offer "greater clarity regarding standards and practices."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) urged firms to set apart customers&#8217; cryptocurrency holdings from their own assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The watchdog argued that co-mingling funds could trigger a significant financial loss for investors.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The NYDFS&#8217; Recommendation</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">New York&#8217;s financial watchdog </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.dfs.ny.gov/industry_guidance/industry_letters/il20230123_guidance_custodial_structures" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">issued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> guidance to state-regulated companies on how they should better protect clients in the event of potential insolvency. It outlined the increasing interest in cryptocurrencies over the past few years and insisted that entities should maintain enhanced control of their customers&#8217; holdings. The agency also believes the market needs to function under an appropriate regulatory framework:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;As stewards of others&#8217; assets, virtual currency entities (VCE) that act as custodians play an important role in the financial system and, therefore, a comprehensive and safe regulatory framework is vital to protecting customers and preserving trust.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The NYDFS urged organizations to keep consumers&#8217; crypto possessions separate from other assets. &#8220;It is expected that a VCE Custodian will not co-mingle customer virtual currency with any of the VCE Custodian&#8217;s own virtual currency or with any other non-customer virtual currency,&#8221; the department added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">They should also release records and maintain a &#8220;clear internal audit trail&#8221; to identify people about any transactions involving their ownings. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The regulator said custodians should not use users&#8217; crypto assets to settle separate financial services, such as guaranteeing an obligation or extending credit. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, they must &#8220;clearly disclose&#8221; to clients the general terms and conditions under which they keep their stash. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Further, the department expects a VCE Custodian to make its standard disclosures and customer agreement readily accessible to customers on its website, in a manner consistent with New York laws and regulations,&#8221; the guidance concluded.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Such Measures Should Have Existed Before FTX&#8217;s Meltdown</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Adrienne Harris &#8211; the superintendent of NYDFS &#8211; opined that the aforementioned guidance could positively impact the cryptocurrency industry and prevent future collapses. However, she believes the regulator should have acted before </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the demise of FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-and-alameda-file-for-bankruptcy-sbf-resigns-as-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for bankruptcy in November last year after failing to honor customer withdrawal requests. One of the accusations against its former CEO &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) &#8211; is that his firm co-mingled users&#8217; funds with Alameda Research, which eventually harmed numerous investors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 30-year-old American has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> not guilty to the charges against him. A trial set for October 2, 2023, will determine whether he played a role in the fallout.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/companies-should-separate-clients-crypto-assets-from-their-own-nydfs/" rel="nofollow">Companies Should Separate Clients&#8217; Crypto Assets From Their Own: NYDFS</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockstream Raises $125 Million to Expand Institutional Bitcoin Mining Services</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockstream-raises-125-million-to-expand-institutional-bitcoin-mining-services/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 23:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234755</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Blockstream raised $125m to expand institutional bitcoin mining services; CEO Adam Back vowed to adopt decentralized structures.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockstream, a leading bitcoin infrastructure provider, announced on January 24 that it had raised $125 million in funding to expand its institutional bitcoin mining services.</p>
<p>This fundraising round was led by Kingsway Capital, a UK-based private equity fund, and included participation from other investors such as Fulgur Ventures and Cohen &amp; Company Capital Markets.</p>
<p>This is the first fundraising for Blockstream since its <a href="https://blog.blockstream.com/en-blockstream-secures-210m-series-b-financing/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">2021 Series B round</a>, where the company raised $210 million to accelerate the construction of enterprise-class mining facilities with hosting capabilities for institutional clients. Following that round of financing, Blockstream reached a $3.2 billion valuation.</p>
<h2>Blockstream Points to Institutional Bitcoin Mining Services.</h2>
<p>The company has seen increased demand for its hosting services due to its strong track record and substantial scale, as well as an industry-wide shortage of available power capacity. This hosting service has remained a resilient market segment compared to &#8220;prop&#8221; miners, who have seen their operations impacted by bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility and the crypto market.</p>
<p>Erik Svenson, Blockstream&#8217;s President &amp; CFO, <a href="https://www.prweb.com/releases/2023/1/prweb19127332.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> that this new fundraising would allow the company to accelerate its YoY revenue growth and continue building better infrastructure that contributes to the economic future of Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Svenson emphasized the company&#8217;s focus on &#8220;reducing risk for institutional miners&#8221; by building high-value use cases on the most secure blockchain on the planet, bitcoin.</p>
<h2>2022: The Year We Learn Not to Rely on Centralized Projects</h2>
<p>Adam Back, CEO of Blockstream, said that 2022 was a learning year for the market, referencing the numerous project failures and scams that caused massive money losses and the closure of multiple crypto companies. He believes these bad experiences should serve as a learning opportunity to &#8220;reduce the need for reliance on third parties.&#8221;</p>
<p>He encouraged players in the crypto ecosystem to move to decentralized structures and non-custodian bitcoin-based architectures, such as Liquid&#8217;s simple contracts, in order to have full custody of their funds.</p>
<p>Back also highlighted that Liquid&#8217;s simple contracts enable self-custody for active traders via offline limit orders, non-custodial options, and collateralized loans, all from the security of the trader&#8217;s own hardware wallet protected by their own keys. This technology is compatible with both decentralized and centralized order-book exchanges.</p>
<p>Additionally, the recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-700-million-liquidated-as-terra-luna-crashes-below-1/" data-wpel-link="internal">market failures</a> and scams remind the importance of decentralization and self-custody in the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>While 2022 was a year full of bad experiences for many enthusiasts in the crypto ecosystem, it undoubtedly served as a learning experience for the crypto community to understand that there will always be <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lazarus-group-suspected-as-culprits-for-100-million-harmony-bridge-hack/" data-wpel-link="internal">malicious actors</a> lurking to take advantage of innocent —<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-losing-coins-bitcoin-core-dev-starts-to-doubt-self-custody/" data-wpel-link="internal">and experienced</a>— people.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockstream-raises-125-million-to-expand-institutional-bitcoin-mining-services/" rel="nofollow">Blockstream Raises $125 Million to Expand Institutional Bitcoin Mining Services</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Despite Embracing Bitcoin, El Salvador Repaid its $800 Million Bond</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/despite-embracing-bitcoin-el-salvador-repaid-its-800-million-bond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 22:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234625</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/PresidentSalvador.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[President Bukele and Finance Minister Zelaya disclosed that El Salvador paid its $800 million bond plus interest. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nayib Bukele &#8211; the President of El Salvador &#8211; revealed that the government repaid its $800 million bond plus interest the same day it was set to mature.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Settling the bond comes despite the pessimistic views that the nation will experience financial challenges due to its bitcoin forays.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;We Just Paid in Full&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">El Salvador&#8217;s political leader, who is among the biggest proponents of bitcoin, announced the news on Twitter, regretting that most international media outlets did not spread the information. At the same time, they were among the first to doubt whether the country would be able to repay the $800 million bond that matured on January 23. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">In the past year, almost every legacy international news outlet said that because of our “<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Bitcoin</a> bet”, El Salvador was going to default on its debt by January 2023 (since we had an 800 million dollar bond maturing today).</p>
<p>Literally, hundreds of articles <a href="https://t.co/rEiK7K13U4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/rEiK7K13U4</a></p>
<p>— Nayib Bukele (@nayibbukele) <a href="https://twitter.com/nayibbukele/status/1617695406812721156?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">January 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He specifically referred to The New York Times, which </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/07/05/world/americas/el-salvador-bitcoin-national-currency.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in July last year that El Salvador&#8217;s decision to purchase bitcoin on a macroeconomic level could harm its monetary network and prevent it from paying its debt. Bukele further stated that the bond was settled without having to ink a deal with the International Monetary Fund (IMF).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Changpeng Zhao (CZ) &#8211; CEO of the world&#8217;s leading crypto exchange, Binance &#8211; congratulated El Salvador for meeting its financial obligations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The nation&#8217;s Minister of Finance &#8211; Alejandro Zelaya &#8211; also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/AlejandroZelay9/status/1617710130673467397" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">confirmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the multi-million bond payment:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Unfortunately, for the disinformation campaign of some national and international media, we announce that on this day, we have completed the payment of the 2023 bond for $800 million, plus interest.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The presidency&#8217;s press office reportedly </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/el-salvador-says-it-has-repaid-800-million-bond-maturing-january-2023-01-24/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">told</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Reuters that the government recently paid $604.1 million and interest of $23.4 million, as well as carrying out another two transactions in 2022.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">El Salvador: the Land of Bitcoin</span></h2>
<p>El Salvador <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-months-later-bitcoin-now-officially-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">legalized</a> bitcoin in September 2021, and its authorities have remained supportive even through the prolonged bear market.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">El Salvador has also used the challenging macroeconomic situation as an opportunity to purchase more amounts of the digital asset. Latest data shows that it holds 2,381 BTC, but the number could be higher since President Bukele </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-to-start-buying-1-bitcoin-per-day-says-bukele/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the government will buy one bitcoin per day in mid-November. However, there is no information on whether the buying spree goes as promised. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The nation currently sits on significant paper losses due to the depreciation of the cryptocurrency market. El Salvador spent over $103 million to accumulate its stash over the years, which is worth nearly two times less as of now.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-embracing-bitcoin-el-salvador-repaid-its-800-million-bond/" rel="nofollow">Despite Embracing Bitcoin, El Salvador Repaid its $800 Million Bond</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genesis Sues Roger Ver for $20 Million for Failing to Settle Crypto Options</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-sues-roger-ver-for-20-million-for-failing-to-settle-crypto-options/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 22:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Roger Ver]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234746</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Roger_Ver.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Roger_Ver.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As insolvency drama rages on, Roger Ver has found himself in legal trouble with another embattled crypto firm. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The so-called “Bitcoin Jesus,” Roger Ver, has been summoned to repay over $20 million in damages to Genesis after failing to settle certain cryptocurrency options transactions before the payment deadline. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The investor has been given 20 days to answer the summons, after which he will be forced to pay reparations by default.</span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://www.offshorealert.com/crypto-investor-roger-ver-sued-for-20m-by-bvi-affiliate-of-insolvent-crypto-lender-genesis/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Offshore Alert, the filing was submitted by a British Virgin Islands-domiciled affiliate of Genesis, which designated New York Country as the place of trial. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The filing states that the options transactions in question expired on December 30. Failing to answer the summons will require Ver to repay at least $20,869,788, alongside Genesis’s costs, expenses, and attorney’s fees. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">This isn’t the first time Ver has gotten into legal trouble this crypto winter. In July, the Seychelles-based crypto exchange CoinFlex sued Ver for $84 million for failing to repay his margin debt.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">CoinFlex had made a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/roger-vers-debt-part-of-the-reason-for-coinflexs-collapse-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">special arrangement</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> for Ver in which it agreed not to liquidate the collateral on his trade when it reached the regular limit, due to trust in him as a counterparty. The company filed for restructuring in August. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Genesis, too, has filed for bankruptcy, after going down as the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-has-226-million-in-claims-against-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">largest unsecured creditor</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in FTX’s bankruptcy. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">A Genesis lawyer recently told a Manhattan court that an agreement could be reached with creditors within a week. Filings show that the company still has $1.6 billion worth of assets more than liabilities. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Ver is a longtime member of the crypto space, and a loud proponent of Bitcoin Cash (BCH) – a Bitcoin hard fork with an increased block size limit to facilitate faster transactions. His margin loan with CoinFlex was against BCH, which is down 53% over the last year.  </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/genesis-sues-roger-ver-for-20-million-for-failing-to-settle-crypto-options/" rel="nofollow">Genesis Sues Roger Ver for $20 Million for Failing to Settle Crypto Options</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Will Be the Foundation of Crypto’s Next Cycle: Pantera Capital</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defi-will-be-the-foundation-of-cryptos-next-cycle-pantera-capital/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 20:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234727</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Pantera sees the popularity of Defi surging as scaling solutions and usability continue to improve. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Pantera Capital – a blockchain-focused institutional asset manager – has released a report reviewing the state of the blockchain industry in 2022, and what to expect on the technological and adoption front going forward.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The report predicted that crypto has already bottomed and that the next market cycle will be defined by greater adoption of decentralized finance (Defi). </span></p>
<h2>The Era of Defi</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Pantera’s co-Chief Investment Officer (CIO) Joey Krug, the crypto industry has been trending toward self-custody and trust minimization since the fall of Mt. Gox in 2013. Today, wallet providers like Trezor and Ledger – alongside smart contract protocols like Uniswap and 0x – are helping mitigate issues related to centralization and mismanagement. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“It seems fairly evident that the historical arc of the world’s financial rails will end up as blockchain-based systems using smart contracts,&#8221; wrote Krug in the </span><a href="https://panteracapital.com/blockchain-letter/the-year-ahead/#joey-section" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">report</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. He cited scaling solutions enabling sub-ten cent transaction fees coupled with ease of writing smart contract-based systems as drivers of such adoption. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Much like crypto market prices, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-bullish-and-2-bearish-cases-for-defi-going-into-2023-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Defi</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> activity fell substantially throughout 2022, with </span><a href="https://defillama.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">total value locked</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> (TVL) across all protocols now just $47 billion – down from roughly $180 billion in late 2021. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Pantera’s report also reflects a substantial decline in venture capital investment in crypto during that time. According to Pantera general partner Paul Veradittakit, global funding for VC-backed crypto startups fell from $9.8 billion in Q4 2021 to $2.4 billion in Q4 2022. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, from the money that remained in crypto last year, Defi investment alone took a 42% share of the pie, with the rest going to sectors like gaming, consumer crypto, and dev infrastructure.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We believe this is a tremendous time to start a company in the blockchain space,” said Veradittakit. “Talent is more educated and passionate about the industry than in previous cycles. A plethora of capital has been raised and is awaiting deployment.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2>The Significance of the Merge</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Pantera’s investment analyst, Will Reid, called the Ethereum </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-history-from-whitepaper-to-hardforks-and-the-eth-merge/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Merge</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> “one of the most technically impressive software updates ever performed.&#8221; The upgrade, which took place in September, reduced the ETH’s inflation rate while transitioning the network to a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, Ethereum still has many drastic upgrades ahead of it, including The Surge, The Scourge, The Verge, The Purge, and The Splurge, as coined by the network’s co-founder Vitalik Buterin. Reid predicted these upgrades will take Ethereum on a path toward greater speed, usability, and decentralization.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Higher bandwidth, more secure, and more user-friendly blockchains should allow for a similar Cambrian explosion of applications and use cases in Web3,” he said.<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400"><span style="color: #2b2b2b;font-size: 16px">Ethereum is the primary network for Defi, accounting for over 50% of TVL across the entire industry.</span><br />
</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-will-be-the-foundation-of-cryptos-next-cycle-pantera-capital/" rel="nofollow">DeFi Will Be the Foundation of Crypto’s Next Cycle: Pantera Capital</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clear Upward Trend in Addresses as Ethereum Rallies Past $1.6K: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/clear-upward-trend-in-addresses-as-ethereum-rallies-past-1-6k-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 19:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234702</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ethereum_mining.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ethereum_mining.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum has made a remarkable recovery since the FTX contagion hit the crypto market.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The year started on a bullish note which aided the world&#8217;s largest altcoin to sprint towards its pre-FTX market cap levels.</p>
<p>Days after struggling to overcome $1,600, Ethereum finally climbed past the resistance level on Tuesday amidst a broader market rally. Even as certain group of investors looking to pocket quick gains began offloading the token, this has not affected the growing appeal of the network.</p>
<h2>Ethereum Ownership</h2>
<p>According to the latest <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1617869037035487233" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> by IntoTheBlock, there is a clear upward trend in addresses with balances of all sizes. Except for one cohort of Ether holders with 0.10 ETH to 1 ETH, which started decreasing in size with the start of the bear market, all the other cohorts have been on a steady rise.</p>
<p>With the most recent increase in Ethereum&#8217;s price, some bigger holders have resorted to offloading their assets in a bid to rake in quick gains. Despite this, ITB noted an increase in addresses with larger balances in terms of USD valuations.</p>
<p>This trend depicted an enhanced market sentiment after a brutal year of an incessant downtrend.</p>
<p>A drill down further at the ownership revealed that six addresses held a total of 22.65% of the ETH supply, and these addresses have been active. In terms of the overall distribution, ITB&#8217;s data suggested that whales hold most of the tokens in circulation. The retail players, on the other hand, held a relatively small percentage of the supply.</p>
<h2>Shanghai Mainnet</h2>
<p>Staking activity on the Ethereum network has continued its uptrend as the total value staked in ETH 2.0 deposit contract <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnodealerts/status/1614446200916156416" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reached</a> yet another ATH earlier this month. A prominent uptick in value was seen after January 6th, coinciding with the developers announcing that the Shanghai Upgrade that seeks to enable the withdrawal of staked ETH.</p>
<p>Touted as the first major update since Ethereum’s historic Merge in September, Shanghai is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-shanghai-public-testnet-to-hit-the-floor-in-february-end/" data-wpel-link="internal">slated to go live</a> in March 2023.</p>
<p>More recently, the first shadow fork designed to test the readiness of ETH staking withdrawal capability was deployed successfully. The release is expected to have a significant impact on crypto markets and usher in the emergence of new participants entering the network.</p>
<p>JP Morgan analysts predicted 95% of retail investors on Coinbase could participate in staking Ethereum after the fork, ramping up the exchange&#8217;s revenue between $225 million and $545 million per year.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Ethereum continued to see the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-and-cardano-record-highest-level-of-developer-activity-in-2022-dappradar/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">highest</a> level of developer activity in 2022 despite the market slump.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/clear-upward-trend-in-addresses-as-ethereum-rallies-past-1-6k-data/" rel="nofollow">Clear Upward Trend in Addresses as Ethereum Rallies Past $1.6K: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Surges Past $23K, Is the Rally Sustainable? (Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-surges-past-23k-is-the-rally-sustainable-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234675</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The ongoing rally will not zoom back to fresh all-time highs, but it could be different. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has been moving higher as the equity markets fetched more gains. The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization climbed over $23,000 on Tuesday. Since the beginning of the year, both Bitcoin and Ethereum added 40% surges to their trajectory, retracting the entire post-FTX dump.</p>
<p>Needless to say, the ongoing rally has sparked concerns over its sustainability on the backdrop of last year&#8217;s bloodbath, as well as subsequent numerous fake-out rallies. However, the latest Bankless <a href="https://newsletter.banklesshq.com/p/why-this-rally-is-different-c80" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a> suggests that &#8220;there are reasons to believe that this rally could have legs.&#8221;</p>
<h2>&#8216;Bears Out of Skies&#8217;</h2>
<p>One of the major reasons pointed out by Bankless is that there is little to suggest that the market is over-leveraged. 2022 saw a major de-leveraging event as centralized infrastructures came crumbling down, which flushed out a gigantic portion of leverage.</p>
<p>Open interest on perpetual futures also saw a significant drawdown.</p>
<p>DeFi whales, for one, were &#8220;not particularly over-leveraged.&#8221; To trigger another event of cascading liquidation similar to that of FTX and COVID would, hence, require an &#8220;exogenous shock&#8221; as there is only $164 million of liquidatable ETH positions above $1,000 across lending protocols such as Maker, Aave, Compound, Euler, and Liquity.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Although battered players like DCG remain, there is little to suggest that the market is over-leveraged. Given the massive amount of short liquidations YTD, it appears as though it’s bears, not bulls, who are out over their skies.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Gauging Further</h2>
<p>The positioning of investors and traders also suggests that the rally could be sustainable. Upon gauging further, it was found that investors are holding a large portion of their assets in cash. Meanwhile, data from Nansen <a href="https://www.nansen.ai/post/smart-money-stablecoin-index-updates" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">shows</a> that the percentage of large whale portfolios that are held in cash stands at 25%. Even as the value fell from its peak of 40%, the report stated that it is still at a &#8220;historically elevated level.&#8221;</p>
<p>Such a range was indicative that investors are nowhere near fully allocated, with &#8220;plenty of ammo remaining on the sidelines&#8221; to push the prices higher.</p>
<p>A chunk of liquidity has left the market as stablecoin declined over 4% from $142 billion to $136 billion. But it appears that the remaining capital still has a significant amount of dry powder.</p>
<p>Moreover, the asset class being highly sensitive to liquidity in the wider financial market, any loosening financial conditions could act as a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-bitcoins-rally-this-is-the-next-major-target-for-btc-price-analysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">bullish</a> nod to the crypto prices.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-surges-past-23k-is-the-rally-sustainable-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Surges Past $23K, Is the Rally Sustainable? (Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Short Squeeze or Temporary Decline, What&#8217;s Next for XRP? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/short-squeeze-or-temporary-decline-whats-next-for-xrp-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234533</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple is aiming for higher price levels as the market experienced another uptrend over the previous week. The trend&#8217;s momentum looks promising, yet the price must first surpass the crucial resistance level of $0.43. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart After a short-term consolidation at the $0.39 level, the price finally broke the 100-day [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple is aiming for higher price levels as the market experienced another uptrend over the previous week. The trend&#8217;s momentum looks promising, yet the price must first surpass the crucial resistance level of $0.43.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>After a short-term consolidation at the $0.39 level, the price finally broke the 100-day and 200-day moving average lines with significant momentum and continues to spike.</p>
<p>A breakout from the 200-day moving average is considered a substantial bullish sign in terms of price action and impacts the whole sentiment of the market.</p>
<p>However, the price faces a crucial resistance region consisting of the static resistance zone of $0.41-$0.43 and the channel&#8217;s middle boundary. This means there is a war going on between buyers and sellers.</p>
<p>The upcoming price action will determine XRP&#8217;s short-term path, and if the bulls achieve dominance and the price surpasses the mentioned level, another spike will be anticipated.</p>
<p>On the contrary, if the price fails to break out, a decline will possibly occur, followed by short-term fluctuations.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234534" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234534" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234534 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2401231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-Daily-1-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234534" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour timeframe, the abovementioned resistance zone of $0.41-$0.43 is more apparent as it has recently rejected the price in late November. Currently, the price faces the yellow descending trendline at the same level, which makes it a more powerful resistance zone.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, a solid bearish divergence between the price and the RSI indicator has formed and could reverse the current trend, resulting in a slight decline. As a result, the odds are against Ripple in terms of price action, and a short-term rejection looks imminent.</p>
<p>Still, the market may surprise participants with a short-squeeze event and impulsively break above this resistance region.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234535" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234535" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234535 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_2401232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Xrp-4H-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234535" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/short-squeeze-or-temporary-decline-whats-next-for-xrp-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Short Squeeze or Temporary Decline, What&#8217;s Next for XRP? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Breaks Past $1.6K But is a Short-Term Correction Imminent? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-breaks-past-1-6k-but-is-a-short-term-correction-imminent-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234537</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-23-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-23-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price has been on the rise for quite a while now after breaking above the $1300 resistance level. While the positive trend remains on higher timeframes, some signs are suggesting that at least a short-term correction is quite probable. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the daily timeframe, the price is constantly [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has been on the rise for quite a while now after breaking above the $1300 resistance level. While the positive trend remains on higher timeframes, some signs are suggesting that at least a short-term correction is quite probable.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price is constantly climbing higher and could reach the $1800 level soon. However, a short-term pullback seems imminent as the RSI indicator has been in overbought conditions over the past few days.</p>
<p>In case of a correction, the 200-day moving average located around the $1400 mark could be the first turning point, with the 50-day moving average located around the $1300 support zone being the second major support. Still, the price could first test the $1800 level before a pullback or reversal.</p>
<p>In the less probable event of a bullish breakout from the $1800 resistance level on the first try, ETH could rally towards the significant $2000 level aggressively.</p>
<p>Overall, this scenario seems unlikely in the short term, as a pullback seems a lot more possible.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234709" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234709" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234709 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2401232" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/1-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234709" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour timeframe, the price has reached the $1650 resistance area but is struggling to break higher at the moment.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator is also showing some worrying signs in this timeframe, as a clear bearish divergence has been forming between the last two price highs, with the RSI demonstrating a lower high. This classic reversal pattern could point to a probable rejection from the $1800 level in the short term.</p>
<p>From a classical price action consideration, the $1350 support area could continue holding in case of a deep correction. A valid breakout above the $1800 level would invalidate this scenario, but it does not seem very likely at the moment.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234710" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234710" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-234710" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2401231" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/2-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234710" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<h3>ETH Open Interest</h3>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has been on the rise over the last couple of weeks after an exhausting consolidation above the $1000 mark. Meanwhile, the exchange reserve metric&#8217;s decline has come to a halt after a massive drop since the FTX bankruptcy.</p>
<p>It is likely that the recent rally is a result of the significant decrease in exchange reserve, as many investors have withdrawn their coins from exchanges and stored them in their personal wallets, fearing that the same thing that happened to FTX could happen to their preferred exchange. Therefore, the subsequent supply shock could be one of the key factors leading to the current price rally.</p>
<p>However, the Exchange Reserve metric has currently stopped falling, which is pointing to the fact that while many holders are withdrawing ETH, others are depositing their coins to sell them at a profit or a smaller loss, as the price has risen relatively higher.</p>
<p>To conclude, this metric should be monitored closely in the short term as an increase in the reserve could lead to a surge in selling pressure, resulting in a bearish reversal.</p>
<figure id="attachment_234540" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-234540" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-234540 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_reserves_on_exchanges_chart_2401231" width="2560" height="1614" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-1536x969.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-2048x1292.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Exchange-Reserve-Jan-23-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-234540" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-breaks-past-1-6k-but-is-a-short-term-correction-imminent-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Breaks Past $1.6K But is a Short-Term Correction Imminent? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
