<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Push BTC Above $23,000 – How High Can BTC Go?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23000-how-high-can-btc-go.htm</link><description>On January 29, Bitcoin price has surged over 2.5%, with the leading cryptocurrency reaching a price of over $23,500. The surge in bitcoin’s price has been fueled by institutional buying and the expectation of further adoption.  &lt;br /&gt;
The technical outlook is suggesting bullish predictions for BTC’s future, but it remains unclear how high the asset will go. In this article, we explore how far BTC could climb in the near future and what factors will influence its path....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23000-how-high-can-btc-go.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Push BTC Above $23,000 – How High Can BTC Go?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-above-23000-how-high-can-btc-go.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102990/253755/market-roundup-night-29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="517320"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction – Can XRP Go to $5 This Year?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-can-xrp-go-5-year.htm</link><description>XRP is the sixth-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization and has been on a roller coaster ride in the past year. With its price going up and down, many investors are wondering what the XRP price prediction will be and if can it reach the $5 mark this year.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this article, we will look at the factors that could affect XRP's price and make a prediction of whether it can reach $5 or not....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-can-xrp-go-5-year.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction – Can XRP Go to $5 This Year?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-can-xrp-go-5-year.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102948/253724/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="839709"/></item><item><title>New York State Takes a Step Toward Cryptocurrency Adoption with New Bill</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-york-state-takes-step-toward-cryptocurrency-adoption-with-new-bill.htm</link><description>The state of New York has announced a new bill that would allow agencies to accept cryptocurrency as a form of payment for fines, civil penalties, taxes, fees, and other payments charged by the state. &lt;br /&gt;
Introduced on January 26 by Democratic Assembly Member Clyde Vanel, the New York State Assembly Bill A523 legislation suggests changes to the state’s current financial law to allow for the use of cryptocurrencies in payments to state agencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-york-state-takes-step-toward-cryptocurrency-adoption-with-new-bill.htm"&gt;Read More: New York State Takes a Step Toward Cryptocurrency Adoption with New Bill&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>New York</category><category>Adoption</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Payment</category><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-york-state-takes-step-toward-cryptocurrency-adoption-with-new-bill.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102953/253715/statue-of-liberty-gc0edba4fc-1920-media-library-original-1920-1079.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="377080"/></item><item><title>White House Unveils Plan to Tackle Cryptocurrency Risks, Calls for Increased Enforcement</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/white-house-unveils-plan-tackle-cryptocurrency-risks-calls-for-increased-enforcement.htm</link><description>The White House has published a roadmap asking authorities to increase enforcement and ramp up efforts to regulate the crypto sector. &lt;br /&gt;
In an official blog on Friday, the Biden Administration detailed its plans to address potential risks from cryptocurrencies in a roadmap that calls for authorities to “ramp up enforcement where appropriate” and Congress “to step up its efforts” to regulate the industry. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/white-house-unveils-plan-tackle-cryptocurrency-risks-calls-for-increased-enforcement.htm"&gt;Read More: White House Unveils Plan to Tackle Cryptocurrency Risks, Calls for Increased Enforcement&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>The White House</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Regulations</category><category>Congress</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/white-house-unveils-plan-tackle-cryptocurrency-risks-calls-for-increased-enforcement.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102950/253714/adobestock-joe-gough-1-media-library-original-895-597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="123162"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Prices and Ethereum Prediction; The Factors That Could Propel BTC and ETH To New Heights</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-factors-that-could-propel-btc-eth-new-heights.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and Ethereum have been two of the most popular digital assets in the world, with their prices having seen a huge surge since their inception. As more and more people become interested in cryptocurrencies, it is important to understand what factors could propel Bitcoin and Ethereum to new heights.  &lt;br /&gt;
This article will discuss the various factors that could affect the prices of these two popular digital currencies, including fundamental and technical analysis. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-factors-that-could-propel-btc-eth-new-heights.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Prices and Ethereum Prediction; The Factors That Could Propel BTC and ETH To New Heights&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-factors-that-could-propel-btc-eth-new-heights.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102945/253712/market-roundup-day-29.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="549539"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as $35 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Can BTC Hit a New All-Time High in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-35-billion-trading-volume-comes-in-can-btc-hit-a-new-all-time-high-in-2023.htm</link><description>In the past week, Bitcoin has seen a 10% rise in its value, leading many to believe that a bull market is arriving. The price of Bitcoin can be unpredictable, however there are certain factors to consider when predicting its potential future performance. &lt;br /&gt;
On January 28, the BTC/USD market opened at $23,067.00 and has since gained 0.07% in 24 hours to reach a current price of $22,971.00. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-35-billion-trading-volume-comes-in-can-btc-hit-a-new-all-time-high-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as $35 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Can BTC Hit a New All-Time High in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-35-billion-trading-volume-comes-in-can-btc-hit-a-new-all-time-high-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102933/253692/market-roundup-night-28.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="517831"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Hit $3 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-2023.htm</link><description>LUNC, a token worth roughly over $1 billion on the Terra Classic protocol, is edging closer to a 17.54% move that could propel it to $0.00021. Meanwhile, the 50th largest cryptocurrency’s value increased by 6.5% in 24 hours and is trading at $0.0001775 at the time of writing. &lt;br /&gt;
Investors are preparing for the expected outcome by taking up new positions in LUNC, according to data from CoinMarketCap, showing a 48% spike in the 24-hour trading volume to $100 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Hit $3 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Classic</category><category>Terra Luna</category><category>Terra</category><category>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction</category><category>LUNC</category><category>LUNC/USD</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102932/253674/luncusd-2023-01-28-14-51-49.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="356249"/></item><item><title>California DMV to Use Blockchain Technology for Record Keeping</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/california-dmv-use-blockchain-technology-for-record-keeping.htm</link><description>The Department of Motor Vehicles in California plans to use blockchain technology for record keeping, including the issuance of car ownership and simplifying transfers of such ownership. &lt;br /&gt;
The DMV has tapped a private fork of the Tezos blockchain, an open-source blockchain that can execute peer-to-peer transactions and serve as a platform for deploying smart contracts, according to a recent report by Fortune. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/california-dmv-use-blockchain-technology-for-record-keeping.htm"&gt;Read More: California DMV to Use Blockchain Technology for Record Keeping&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>California</category><category>Department of Motor Vehicles</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/california-dmv-use-blockchain-technology-for-record-keeping.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102931/253671/istock-1297506770-dmv.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="903156"/></item><item><title>Shining Bitcoin Towers, Waking ETH Whales, Commingled Customer Funds and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shining-bitcoin-towers-waking-eth-whales-commingled-customer-funds-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shining-bitcoin-towers-waking-eth-whales-commingled-customer-funds-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Shining Bitcoin Towers, Waking ETH Whales, Commingled Customer Funds and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/shining-bitcoin-towers-waking-eth-whales-commingled-customer-funds-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102656/253314/huobiglobal-twitter.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="48746"/></item><item><title>US Judge: Sam Bankman-Fried Attempted to Influence Witness via Encrypted Messenger App</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-judge-sam-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness-via-encrypted-messenger-app.htm</link><description>Sam Bankman-Fried, the disgraced founder of cryptocurrency exchange FTX, has allegedly tried to influence some potential witnesses of his trial via encrypted messaging software Signal. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-judge-sam-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness-via-encrypted-messenger-app.htm"&gt;Read More: US Judge: Sam Bankman-Fried Attempted to Influence Witness via Encrypted Messenger App&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><category>FTX</category><category>Ftx Trial</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-judge-sam-bankman-fried-attempted-to-influence-witness-via-encrypted-messenger-app.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102926/253670/screenshot-2023-01-26-at-15-36-23-media-library-original-1200-603.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="46766"/></item><item><title>How to Buy a Tom Brady NFT: A Beginner's Guide</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/how-buy-tom-brady-nft.htm</link><description>Are you a fan of Tom Brady and looking to add one of his rare NFTs to your collection? Look no further! Read on to discover a comprehensive guide on how to buy a Tom Brady NFT, including information on who Tom Brady is, what the Tom Brady NFT collection consists of, how much you can expect to pay, and more....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/how-buy-tom-brady-nft.htm"&gt;Read More: How to Buy a Tom Brady NFT: A Beginner's Guide&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/how-buy-tom-brady-nft.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102123/252037/tom-brady-nfts.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="942335"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Prices and Ethereum Prediction; Could The Weekend See BTC &amp; ETH Breakout?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-could-weekend-see-btc-eth-breakout.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and Ethereum prices have been steady despite experiencing significant volatility in the past few weeks. Bitcoin is maintaining a narrow range between $22,350 and $23,350, while Ethereum is trading choppily within a tight range of $1,550 to $1,630.  &lt;br /&gt;
As we enter the weekend, many investors are wondering if this could be the time for a breakout....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-could-weekend-see-btc-eth-breakout.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Prices and Ethereum Prediction; Could The Weekend See BTC &amp; ETH Breakout?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-prices-ethereum-prediction-could-weekend-see-btc-eth-breakout.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102922/253669/market-roundup-day-28.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="550323"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Option Markets Keep Sending Bullish Signals – Here’s the Implications for BTC Price</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm</link><description>Bitcoin options markets continue to signal that investors are anticipating further upside in the BTC price. According to a chart on The Block, the widely followed Bitcoin 25% delta skew has remained above zero since the middle of January and recently hit its highest since Q4 2021 at close to 6.0....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Option Markets Keep Sending Bullish Signals – Here’s the Implications for BTC Price&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Options</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Bull market</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-option-markets-keep-sending-bullish-signals-heres-implications-for-btc-price.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102917/253660/bitcoin-3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6331437"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Mining Network Hits New Record Hash Rate Above 300 EH/s</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm</link><description>According to Bitcoin mining data tracking website MiningPoolStats, Bitcoin’s hash rate hit a new record high earlier this week. According to the website, the network reached the milestone of computing three hundred quintillion (300,000,000,000,000,000,000) hashes per second (300 EH/s)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Mining Network Hits New Record Hash Rate Above 300 EH/s&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Mining</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-mining-network-hits-new-record-hash-rate-above-300-ehs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102916/253651/bitcoin-miner.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2105861"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 27 January – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, CCHG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrencies are becoming increasingly popular as a way for investors to diversify their portfolios. With so many different coins and tokens available, it can be difficult to know which ones to buy.  &lt;br /&gt;
In this article, we will look at five of the best cryptos to buy today – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, and CCHG. We will discuss each coin's features and use cases in detail so that you can make an informed decision about which one is the right fit for your portfolio....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 27 January – MEMAG, FTM, FGHT, MATIC, CCHG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-27-january-memag-ftm-fght-matic-cchg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102902/253601/best-crypto-27-jan.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="331639"/></item><item><title>Formula 1 Racing Team Secures $100 Million Sponsorship from Crypto Casino – Is The Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>The crypto gambling platform based in Australia, Stake.com, has entered a partnership worth $100 million with the Alfa Romeo Racing team, indicating a comeback in crypto-related sponsorships. &lt;br /&gt;
This event marks one of the first and biggest sponsorship programs following the catastrophic collapse of FTX exchange which became known for its high-level and wide-reaching sponsorships....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Formula 1 Racing Team Secures $100 Million Sponsorship from Crypto Casino – Is The Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/formula-1-racing-team-secures-100-million-sponsorship-from-crypto-casino-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/102907/253600/adobestock-110861591.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1816993"/></item></channel></rss>
