<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 23:51:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin or Ethereum? DeFi Dev Explains Which Is Better For Building</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-or-ethereum-defi-dev-explains-which-is-better-for-building/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 23:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267213</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/EthereumBitcoin-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/EthereumBitcoin-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin development is sharply focused, whereas Ethereum development is more accessible and better funded, according to Atomic Finance CEO Tony Cai.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Bitcoin or Ethereum a better protocol for developers? A closer look reveals the answer may not be so obvious.</p>
<p>Tony Cai – CEO of Bitcoin-based DeFi platform Atomic Finance and former Ethereum builder – published a Twitter thread on Wednesday explaining the different experiences of building apps on both networks, including the strengths and weaknesses of each.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Advantage: Security and Focus</h2>
<p>According to Cai, Bitcoin’s <a href="https://twitter.com/TonyCai_/status/1691919517616689362" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">first advantage</a> is the security of its programming language. The original crypto network’s Discrete Log Contracts (DLCs) boast fewer attack services than Ethereum’s smart contracts, which have lost users hundreds of millions of dollars due to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-weaknesses-of-ethereum-vs-modern-blockchains-interview-with-radix/" data-wpel-link="internal">coding mistakes</a> and exploits over the past few years.</p>
<blockquote><p>“In ETH, one tiny mistake (like 1-2 lines of code being written in the wrong order) can lead to millions lost,” wrote Cai.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Having spent time building on ETH first before pivoting to building on BTC, I&#39;ve seen the best and worst parts of both communities.</p>
<p>I&#39;m probably gonna get some hate for this, but screw it&#8230;</p>
<p>BTC vs ETH: An Honest Reflection from a Builder. </p>
<p>Here are 6 things I noticed:<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/3sBZKrZlRn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/3sBZKrZlRn</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Tony Cai <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/269b.png" alt="⚛" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> #SoundFinance (@TonyCai_) <a href="https://twitter.com/TonyCai_/status/1691919517616689362?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The Bitcoin development experience also benefits from “laser focus” – clarity and emphasis specifically on innovation. According to Cai, the ETH community “moves fast” and ushers in new developments every week, making it easy for builders to get lost with “shiny object syndrome.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“Bitcoin&#8217;s scripting language and capabilities are intentionally limited to ensure its primary function remains robust,” said Cai to CryptoPotato via DM. “Ethereum, on the other hand, was designed as a platform for decentralized applications, making it more flexible and versatile.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Ethereum has famously boasted both NFTs and tokenization for years – technologies that have only <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-non-profit-to-support-bitcoin-nft-developers/" data-wpel-link="internal">begun</a> to emerge on Bitcoin. This limited capability keeps developers focused on securing product-market fit, rather than conjuring complex tokenomics and “rationalizations” as to why their projects need a token at all.</p>
<h2>Ethereum’s Advantage: Expressiveness and Dev Infrastructure</h2>
<p>Naturally, Bitcoin’s strict scripting language leaves it with some tradeoffs. Not only is development more technically limited, but more developers naturally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitmex-explains-why-ethereum-has-more-dapps-than-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">gravitate</a> toward’s Ethereum’s more welcoming programming language – Solidity.</p>
<p>“Programming on Solidity is simple for anyone who understands the basics of Javascript. Which most programmers do these days,” said Cai. It also has far greater developer infrastructure through tools like Truffle Suite and Infura, and more hackathon events for creating new tools.</p>
<p>Cai believes the fewer hackathons in Bitcoin may boil down to its relative lack of tokenization, which has led to less funding and sponsorships for the network’s developers. “BTC startups don’t have the luxury of massive treasuries funded by a token drop / ICO,” he explained.</p>
<p>Though firms like Blockstream and Chaincode Labs have stepped in to help fund the ecosystem, Cai said Ethereum has always had a more “structured” approach to funding thanks to its ICO, and the Ethereum Foundation.</p>
<p>Developer culture within both camps also widely differs. Whereas Bitcoiners make changes “cautiously” with a focus on “preserving the integrity of the network,” Ethereum development can be more of a “free for all” where devs are constantly “exploring new use cases.”</p>
<p>The contrast has created a clear rift where Bitcoin’s “podcasters” and “content creators” often take the public spotlight, rather than its developers. It’s also limited the creativity of Bitcoin applications and startups to four basic categories: lightning network micropayments, fiat on-ramps, multisig providers, and bitcoin rewards.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Bitcoin&#8217;s grassroots, decentralized approach to funding and development has its merits, as does Ethereum&#8217;s more structured approach,” concluded Cai.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-or-ethereum-defi-dev-explains-which-is-better-for-building/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin or Ethereum? DeFi Dev Explains Which Is Better For Building</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Custodian BitGo Raises $100 Million in Series C Funding, Valued at $1.75 Billion</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-custodian-bitgo-raises-100-million-in-series-c-funding-valued-at-1-75-billion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266892</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BitGo_Funding.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BitGo_Funding.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital previously scrapped acquisition of BitGo. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>California-based crypto custodian BitGo announced securing $100 million in a Series C funding round, bringing its valuation to $1.75 billion. The freshly injected funds will be deployed to make strategic acquisitions and expand its regulated custody, wallet, and infrastructure solutions globally.</p>
<p>Both new and outside strategic investors have participated in the funding round.</p>
<ul>
<li>In a <a href="https://www.prweb.com/releases/bitgo-secures-100m-series-c-funding-at-1-75b-valuation-301901731.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a>, BitGo CEO Mike Belshe highlighted the growing demand for regulated custody solutions both in the US as well as across the world.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Not only are we seeing growing demand for regulated custody solutions in the US, but we&#8217;re also seeing the demand on a global scale. We are very pleased to announce our $100M Series C for the purpose of meeting this growing need and to provide institutions, brands, coin foundations, and others with secure and seamless participation in the digital asset ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>According to the platform&#8217;s analysis, BitGo witnessed a 60% increase in newly onboarded clients since the beginning of the year, a 20% jump in AUC, a 200% surge in fiat custody, and 40x growth in staked assets.</li>
<li>Mike Novogratz’s cryptocurrency investment firm Galaxy Digital previously announced plans to purchase BitGo for $1.2 billion.</li>
<li>The agreement was, however, canceled, with Galaxy blaming the inability of the crypto custody company to provide audited financial statements for 2021 as stipulated in the agreement.</li>
<li>This prompted the digital asset custodian to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitgo-confirms-filing-lawsuit-against-galaxy-digital-seeks-100m-in-damages/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">file</a> a lawsuit against Galaxy seeking damages in excess of $100 million, citing &#8220;improper repudiation and intentional breach of its merger agreement.&#8221;</li>
<li>Meanwhile, BitGo <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitgo-discontinues-acquisition-of-prime-trust/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> it will not be acquiring Prime Trust, which later <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-linked-crypto-custodian-prime-trust-files-for-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in Delaware.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-custodian-bitgo-raises-100-million-in-series-c-funding-valued-at-1-75-billion/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Custodian BitGo Raises $100 Million in Series C Funding, Valued at $1.75 Billion</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plummets To $25k Triggering $1 Billion In Liquidations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-to-25k-triggering-1-million-in-liquidations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:10:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267219</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/BitcoinCrash.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/BitcoinCrash.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin hasn't seen such lows since mid-June, after two of the industry's biggest exchanges were sued by regulators. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price plummeted on Thursday to $25,300, touching lows the asset has not seen in the past two months.</p>
<p>The event triggered nearly $1 billion in liquidations across the entire crypto market.</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin slightly rebounded after the crash, trading for $26,386 at writing time.</li>
<li>The last time Bitcoin traded this low was in mid-June, shortly after Binance and Coinbase were sued by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), and shortly before BlackRock announced its bid for a Bitcoin spot ETF.</li>
<li>According to <a href="https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Coinglass</a>, over $788 million in liquidations have occurred in the past 24 hours, including over $812 million in the last hour alone. Roughly half of the liquidations were on Bitcoin trades, with another $245 million on ETH trades.</li>
<li>The largest single liquidation took place on an ETH-BUSD trade on Binance, clearing out a trader for a whopping $55.92 million. The total number of liquidations surpassed 164,000.</li>
<li>The news arrives shortly after the Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/behind-the-curtain-of-elon-musks-secretive-spacex-revenue-growth-and-rising-costs-2c828e2b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> that Elon Musk&#8217;s SpaceX had sold the remainder of its Bitcoin holdings, writing down its value from last year by $373 million.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_267220" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267220" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-267220 size-large" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-1024x560.png" alt="" width="1024" height="560" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-1024x560.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-300x164.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-768x420.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-1536x840.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14-50x27.png 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTCUSD_2023-08-17_17-57-14.png 1574w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267220" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin / USD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-to-25k-triggering-1-million-in-liquidations/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Plummets To $25k Triggering $1 Billion In Liquidations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore Police Arrest 10 Foreigners for Alleged Money Laundering and Forgery Offenses</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-police-arrest-10-foreigners-for-alleged-money-laundering-and-forgery-offenses/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 20:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266996</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/PoliceArrest-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/PoliceArrest-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Singapore has seized over $736M worth of properties, cash, and assets including crypto, in one of its major money laundering crackdowns.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Singapore authorities have arrested 10 foreign nationals suspected to be involved in money laundering and forgery, among other illicit activities, and have seized or frozen cash, assets, and crypto worth over S$1 billion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While eight other suspects are on the run, the case could be considered one of Singapore&#8217;s largest money laundering crackdowns.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Singapore Seizes Over $1B in Cash, Properties, and Assets</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Singapore Police Force (SPF), in a <a href="https://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=680376724131024&amp;id=100064761068356&amp;mibextid=Nif5oz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Facebook post</a> on August 16, revealed that over 400 law enforcement officers from the Commercial Affairs Department (CAD), the Special Operations Command, the Police Intelligence Department, and the Criminal Investigation Department, simultaneously raided the residence of the suspects, who lived in places such as condominiums and Good Class Bungalows (GCB).</p>
<p dir="ltr">The raid happened on August 15, with the SPF stating that authorities acted based on information that the arrested individuals allegedly used fake documents to substantiate their source of funds in Singapore bank accounts.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the Police, none of the 10 individuals are citizens of or permanent residents in Singapore. Instead, the suspects, with an age range between 31 and 44 years, are Cypriot, Turkish, Cambodian, Ni-Vanuatu, and Chinese nationals, with seven out of the 10 non-Chinese nationals said to possess other foreign passports issued by China.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Following the crackdown, authorities seized over 35 bank accounts holding an estimated balance of more than $110 million, S$23 million cash, including foreign currencies, and issued a prohibition of disposal orders against 94 properties and 50 vehicles with an estimated worth of S$815 million.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Other assets confiscated include over 270 pieces of jewelry, 250 luxury bags and watches, two gold bars, and 11 documents on information on crypto, bringing the total value of cash and assets seized or frozen to over S$1 billion ($736.5 million).</p>
<p dir="ltr">With further investigations ongoing, eight other people are currently at large and wanted by the police, with the SPF stating that 12 other individuals are helping with the case.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Aiming to Be a Vibrant Crypto Hub in Asia</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/news/media-releases/2023/mas-will-not-tolerate-the-abuse-of-our-financial-system-for-illicit-activities" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">separate announcement</a>, the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) said that local financial institutions filed suspicious transaction reports (STRs) after they noticed red flags such as dubious documentation of source of wealth, notable inconsistencies in information provided, and suspicious fund flows.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to a statement by the Deputy Managing Director (Financial Supervision), MAS, Ho Hern Shin:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;This case has highlighted that vigilance and prompt filing of STRs by our FIs have helped law enforcement authorities to identify those suspected of carrying out illicit activities. But it has also highlighted that as a global  financial hub, Singapore remains vulnerable to transnational ML/TF risks and that MAS and FIs need to continue to work together to strengthen our defenses against these risks.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">Singapore, striving to be Asia&#8217;s financial hub, has seen an influx of foreign businesses due to its advanced infrastructure and stable regulatory framework. The city-state is also positioning itself as a major center for digital currencies, with crypto firms such as Gemini, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-receives-in-principle-singapore-payments-license-us-crypto-exodus-continues/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, Coinbase, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" data-wpel-link="internal">Blockchain.com</a>, and Circle securing regulatory licenses in Singapore.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Recently, MAS <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-central-bank-unveils-stablecoin-regulation-as-global-trailblazer/" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> a new regulation for single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore dollar or any G10 currency issued in the city-state.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-police-arrest-10-foreigners-for-alleged-money-laundering-and-forgery-offenses/" rel="nofollow">Singapore Police Arrest 10 Foreigners for Alleged Money Laundering and Forgery Offenses</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Just Axed USDT Support For These 3 Blockchains</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-just-axed-usdt-support-for-these-3-blockchains/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 19:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267204</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tether.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Tether.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether will no longer mint USDT on Omni – the first protocol ever to support USDT.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoin giant Tether announced on Thursday that it has discontinued USDT support for three blockchains, on which the token “lacks significant traction.”</p>
<p>Those chains include Bitcoin’s Omni Layer, Bitcoin Cash’s Simple Ledger Protocol (SLP), and Kusama.</p>
<h2>No Signs Of Omni Adoption</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://tether.to/en/tether-makes-strategic-transition-to-meet-community-demands-and-foster-innovation/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">explained</a> on Tether’s website on Thursday, community interest is a “key factor” in deciding whether or not the company will bring USDT to a particular network.</p>
<p>“If a blockchain lacks significant traction over an extended period and shows no signs of recovery in usage indicators, maintaining support becomes inefficient and may jeopardize security and oversight,” wrote Tether.</p>
<p>To the firm’s dismay, this appears to be the case with Omni – a smart contract layer built on top of Bitcoin to enable smart contracts and tokenization on the network roughly a decade ago. In 2014, Omni became the “first transport layer” for Tether, playing a “crucial role” in the company’s early journey.</p>
<p>“Over the years, the Omni Layer faced challenges due to the lack of popular tokens and the availability of USD₮ on other blockchains,” Tether wrote. Crypto exchanges, for example, have favored other layers such as Ethereum and Tron, making USDT transfers even less popular on Omni.</p>
<p>Tether said it would reconsider launching USDT on Omni if there was “increased utilization” of its decentralized exchange and token issuance protocol in the future.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin’s Future With Stablecoins</h2>
<p>Tether hasn’t given up on Bitcoin, however: it now plans to issue USDT on RGB, an alternative smart contracts system that leverages Bitcoin’s base layer and lightning network for “unparalleled scalability.”</p>
<p>“We firmly believe that RGB will usher in a new era for digital assets, smart contracts, and digital rights, garnering comprehensive support from major players in our industry,” said Tether.</p>
<p>While USDT mints end as of today, holders of USDT on these chains will still be able to redeem their tokens for the next 12 months. They may also trade their tokens on exchanges, like Bitfiniex, for assets on other chains.</p>
<p>Though Omni has failed to gain adoption, numerous other initiatives for Bitcoin-based stablecoins have been launched in recent years. In May, Stably <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stably-launches-bitcoins-first-brc-20-stablecoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> the first stablecoin on Bitcoin’s base layer using the BRC-20 token standard, which was developed using Ordinals technology.</p>
<p>The creator of BRC-20 has himself promoted <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-aims-to-bitcoinize-the-dollar-with-taros-alpha-release/" data-wpel-link="internal">Taro</a> – a developing protocol for issuing assets on Bitcoin’s lightning network.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-just-axed-usdt-support-for-these-3-blockchains/" rel="nofollow">Tether Just Axed USDT Support For These 3 Blockchains</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>These Meme Coins Are Trending Today But Not For the Good Reasons</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/these-meme-coins-are-trending-today-but-not-for-the-good-reasons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267197</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/memecoins_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/memecoins_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[These meme coins are in the trending section but not for the right reason. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB), Pepe (PEPE), and Bone Shibaswap (BONE) are among the top five trending coins in the market today. Interestingly, none of them is making the headlines for a good reason.</p>
<ul>
<li>Data from CoinMarketCap indicates the three meme coins are currently all <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-shiba-inu-shib-crashing-despite-shibarium-launch-2-possible-reasons/" data-wpel-link="internal">in the red</a>. BONE is down 12.83% in the last 24 hours, and more than 20% over the last seven days.</li>
<li>On its part, Shiba Inu is currently 8.16% below its price from the previous day and 10.5% over the week. At 2.15%, PEPE has lost the least value among the three in the last 24 hours. However, it has fared worse than SHIB and BONE over 30 days, dropping as much as 19% from its price over that period.</li>
<li>Market watchers believe the bad performances of SHIB and BONE could be down to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">controversy</a> surrounding Shiba Inu’s new layer-2 network, Shibarium.</li>
<li>The blockchain went live on Aug. 16 after months of anticipation. Shortly after, reports started surfacing regarding issues with the network, with on-chain data apparently showing transactions had stalled for as long as five hours.</li>
<li>Some analysts also claimed there was something wrong with Shibarium’s <a href="https://www.shibrpc.com/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">remote procedure call</a> (RCP), with crypto sleuth ZachXBT referring to it as “dead.”</li>
<li>Worse yet, purported screenshots of an internal Telegram conversation between Shibarium developers are doing the rounds on social media, with one showing lead developer Shytoshi saying the team was unable to recover assets connected to the Shibarium network.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-meme-coins-are-trending-today-but-not-for-the-good-reasons/" rel="nofollow">These Meme Coins Are Trending Today But Not For the Good Reasons</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Growing Short Positions Lead to Bullish Opportunities for Crypto Investors: Santiment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/growing-short-positions-lead-to-bullish-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-santiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 17:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267089</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/BearVsBullBitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/BearVsBullBitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Santiment said traders have doubled down on their short positions due to the market's current downturn.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain analytics platform Santiment revealed that the increased short positions in the crypto market provide an opportunity for bullish investors to position themselves for an uptick in prices.</p>
<p>In a recent tweet, Santiment said traders have doubled down on their short positions due to the market&#8217;s current downturn.</p>
<h2>Traders Bet Against Crypto Markets</h2>
<p>With many traders <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/big-shorts-michael-burry-bets-big-on-stock-crash-will-bitcoin-follow/" data-wpel-link="internal">betting against</a> the market, the likelihood of liquidation increases and, possibly, the prices of assets too. The platform disclosed that the current signal is one that many bullish investors have been waiting for as they prepare for a rise in prices.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f9d0.png" alt="🧐" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Traders are shorting now as <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/crypto?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#crypto</a> market caps continue their downturn. When the crowd begins to bet against markets, it increases the likelihood of <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/liquidations?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#liquidations</a>, causing prices to rise. For many <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bullish?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#bullish</a> investors out there, this is the signal that many are waiting for. <a href="https://t.co/JiKqUBruMn" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/JiKqUBruMn</a></p>
<p>— Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1691919694062862531?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The market downturn is evident in the total crypto market cap, which has plunged by more than 1.8% to $1.13 trillion in the past 24 hours, per data from CoinMarketCap. The prices of bitcoin and ether (ETH) have also <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">declined</a> by over 2% within the same time frame to levels around the $28,500 and $1,700 regions, respectively.</p>
<p>The altcoins have suffered even more, with losses of up to 10% on a daily scale.</p>
<h2>The Right Time to Buy?</h2>
<p>Santiment&#8217;s analysis aligns with that of another from on-chain intelligence firm CryptoQuant, which <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/64db830782e8484d4172bd67-Recent-open-interest-in-the-Ethereum-futures-market-shows-the-same-pattern" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noted</a> a rapid spike in Ethereum&#8217;s open interest in the past couple of days. Open interest is a metric that counts short and long contracts in futures markets currently open on all derivative exchanges.</p>
<p>While the open interest indicator keeps track of both short and long contracts, previous occurrences have shown that the metric rises when the prices of crypto assets are down. As it surged in the same period that ETH declined, it is a strong suggestion that the new positions on the futures market are from short traders.</p>
<p>Different patterns over the past month have shown that the spike in open interest is usually followed by a bounce that shoots the crypto asset&#8217;s price upward and, in turn, the open interest downward. As Santiment stated, bullish investors see such signals as positive as they believe the current plunge is the right time to buy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/growing-short-positions-lead-to-bullish-opportunities-for-crypto-investors-santiment/" rel="nofollow">Growing Short Positions Lead to Bullish Opportunities for Crypto Investors: Santiment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bankrupt Crypto Entities Genesis and FTX Reach Agreement on $175 Million Claim</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-entities-genesis-and-ftx-reach-agreement-on-175-million-claim/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267103</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Genesis_Resolve.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This settlement marks a notable decrease from FTX's initial demand of nearly $4 billion.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FTX&#8217;s sister trading firm, Alameda Research, will be allowed a general unsecured claim of $175 million against Genesis. The disgraced crypto exchange led by Sam Bankman-Fried previously sought to claw back $4 billion from DCG-owned lender Genesis which also filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy.</p>
<p>However, the latest court filing suggests that FTX and Genesis have reached an agreement, with the former having to settle for $3.825 billion less than originally demanded. The deal also entails waiving Genesis&#8217; corresponding claims against FTX.</p>
<ul>
<li>Genesis lawyers <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/genesis/Home-DocketInfo" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">highlighted</a> that the settlement will greatly streamline the process of confirming the Chapter 11 reorganization plan without incurring the expenses associated with prolonged litigation.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The agreement will, among various outcomes, notably facilitate the approval process for the Genesis Debtors&#8217; chapter 11 reorganization plan (referred to as the &#8220;Genesis Plan&#8221;). Additionally, it will eliminate the potential drawbacks, costs, and unpredictability linked to extended legal disputes involving the FTX Debtors, Genesis Debtors, and GGCI.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In a corresponding submission to the court, FTX&#8217;s chief restructuring officer, John J. Ray III, maintained that the deal is &#8220;fair&#8221; and in the &#8220;best interest&#8221; of all the parties engaged.</li>
<li>The intention behind this <a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DocketInfo" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">arrangement</a>, as stated by legal representatives, is to facilitate the orderly resolution of matters for both companies and the reimbursement of funds to customers.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, the FTX 2.0 Coalition <a href="https://twitter.com/AFTXcreditor/status/1692092064027086890" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">expressed</a> its dissatisfaction, arguing that the agreement is notably unfavorable, especially given the ongoing Department of Justice (DOJ) investigation into DCG and Genesis.</li>
<li>The group anticipates that the Unsecured Creditors&#8217; Committee (UCC) will raise objections to this settlement, citing that Genesis had been reimbursed by Alameda using substantial amounts from FTX customer funds in 2022.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bankrupt-crypto-entities-genesis-and-ftx-reach-agreement-on-175-million-claim/" rel="nofollow">Bankrupt Crypto Entities Genesis and FTX Reach Agreement on $175 Million Claim</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Analyst Forecasts Over 44% Rally for Shiba Inu (SHIB): Find Out the Targets</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/analyst-forecasts-over-44-rally-for-shiba-inu-shib-find-out-the-targets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267137</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_up_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_up_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the ongoing hiccups around Shibarium, leading analyst believes there's still a room for major SHIB rally.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well-known cryptocurrency market analyst, Michael van de Poppe, anticipated a strong surge in Shiba Inu (SHIB) price, exceeding 44% in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>This bullish outlook relies on SHIB holding on to three key support levels long enough to reestablish an upward trajectory.</p>
<p>In stark contrast to the current crypto market demeanor, which remains predominantly devoid of action, SHIB, currently ranked 15th by market cap, has been on-and-off with its price action recently.</p>
<figure id="attachment_267138" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267138" style="width: 468px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-267138 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="468" height="458" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24.jpg 468w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24-300x294.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-24-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267138" class="wp-caption-text">SHIB 90-day price chart. Source: Coingecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>An analysis of the past 30 days indicates that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inu-lead-dev-all-is-well-no-bridge-issue-this-caused-the-shibarium-issues/" data-wpel-link="internal">SHIB</a> rallied by about 16%, moving from a low of $0.0000077 to the current $0.000009. 90-day charts paint a similar picture of gains, with SHIB rallying 12.5% from a low of $0.000008.</li>
<li>Both these mid-term charts imply that SHIB has been on an upward trajectory.</li>
<li>However, 24-hour and 7-day charts show 10% and 7.9% price declines, respectively.</li>
<li>This change in direction prompted new analysis, with an expert <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1691431293341384704" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noting</a> that if SHIB holds onto support levels at $0.00000941$, $0.00000870, and $0.00000808, the coin could change direction and record a surge to $0.000013.</li>
<li>Considering the prevailing price, such a move means a gain of over 44%.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_267139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-267139" style="width: 443px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-267139" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1-3.jpg" alt="1" width="443" height="339" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1-3.jpg 443w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1-3-300x230.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1-3-50x38.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 443px) 100vw, 443px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-267139" class="wp-caption-text">Source: X</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>With the coin trading below the first support level, the next pivot price target remains at $0.000087, which could lead to a new bull session for <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-shibarium-experiences-major-issues-on-day-1-details/" data-wpel-link="internal">SHIB</a>.</li>
<li>Barchart’s analytics suggest that the most critical resistance levels for SHIB are at $0.00001, $0.0000105, and $0.0000108. However, these resistance levels might not be extremely hard to beat since less than 48 hours ago, SHIB was trading at $0.000011 before it took a nose dive to current levels.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/analyst-forecasts-over-44-rally-for-shiba-inu-shib-find-out-the-targets/" rel="nofollow">Analyst Forecasts Over 44% Rally for Shiba Inu (SHIB): Find Out the Targets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are Bitcoin ETFs Sell-The-News Events? BTC Down $1.5K Since Europe&#8217;s First Spot One</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/are-bitcoin-etfs-sell-the-news-events-btc-down-1-5k-since-europes-first-spot-one/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=267135</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[If this theory is true, imagine what could happened if the US ever greenlights a spot BTC ETF.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Europe saw the launch of the first spot Bitcoin ETF on Tuesday, but it turned out to be a sell-the-news moment since the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price plummeted in the following days to multi-month lows.</p>
<p>Interestingly, something similar happened back in 2021 after the launch of the futures Bitcoin ETFs in the States, leading to speculations on whether these products are actually benefiting the crypto industry.</p>
<h2>BTC Down After First European ETF</h2>
<p>Going under the ticker BCOIN, the Jacobi FT Wilshire Bitcoin ETF <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-spot-bitcoin-etf-goes-live-in-europe-with-interesting-twist/" data-wpel-link="internal">went live</a> earlier this week on the Euronext Amsterdam exchange, marking the launch of the first spot BTC exchange-traded fund in the European Union.</p>
<p>Moreover, the two entities behind it &#8211; Jacobi Asset Management and Wilshire Indexes &#8211; claimed that the ETF contains a &#8220;verifiable built-in Renewable Energy Certificate (REC) solution which allows institutional investors to access the benefits of Bitcoin whilst also meeting ESG goals.”</p>
<p>This product came at a time when the words &#8220;spot Bitcoin ETF&#8221; are particularly hot, so one could expect that its launch would be regarded as a highly bullish development for the entire industry.</p>
<p>Well, this hasn&#8217;t been the case, at least yet. Instead of a hype-driven price rally, BTC&#8217;s price performance has been quite underwhelming, with the asset slumping by roughly a grand and a half since its weekly peak at $29,700 (on Bitstamp).</p>
<p>Moreover, bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-lost-40b-in-2-days-as-btc-plummets-toward-28k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">dropped</a> to $28,300 earlier on August 17 and marked its lowest price position in about two months.</p>
<h2>Not The First</h2>
<p>2021 was perhaps the most bullish and favorable year for bitcoin, at least in recent times, as the cryptocurrency charted new peaks frequently, resulting in an all-time high of $69,000 in November. In fact, that ATH came just a few weeks after the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-futures-etf-is-live-generates-around-500m-volume-in-its-first-hour-of-trading/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of the first BTC-related exchange-traded fund in the States, albeit being a futures one.</p>
<p>What followed, though, was not all that bullish. Instead of heading toward $100,000 as many in the community expected back then (remember the laser eyes?), BTC plummeted by approximately $20,000 by the end of the year. Less than a month later, the asset was down to $33,000.</p>
<p>And that was before the war in Ukraine started, the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-valuable-lessons-from-terras-collapse-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash of Terra</a>, the subsequent bankruptcies, and the FTX implosion that happened later that year, all of which further dragged BTC&#8217;s price south.</p>
<p>So maybe the BTC ETFs are not so good for the industry after all? Or maybe their negative impact is just momentary.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it would be interesting to follow what would or could happen to BTC and the entire market if the SEC finally decides to greenlight a spot Bitcoin ETF in the States. According to the agency&#8217;s latest on the matter, though, that would be in 2024, the earliest, as it delayed making a final decision on the recent filings.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/are-bitcoin-etfs-sell-the-news-events-btc-down-1-5k-since-europes-first-spot-one/" rel="nofollow">Are Bitcoin ETFs Sell-The-News Events? BTC Down $1.5K Since Europe&#8217;s First Spot One</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
