<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:43:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Week Following Stablecoin Introduction, PayPal Appoints New CEO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/a-week-following-stablecoin-introduction-paypal-appoints-new-ceo/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 23:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266469</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/paypal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/paypal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dan Schulman will step down from the CEO position at the end of September and depart PayPal's board of directors in May 2024.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Board of Directors of PayPal disclosed that the new Chief Executive Officer of the payment processor giant will be Alex Chriss (an executive who runs Small Businesses and Self-Employed Group at Intuit). He will enter the new role on September 27, replacing Dan Schulman.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The amendment comes a week after PayPal doubled down on its crypto efforts by launching a stablecoin pegged to the valuation of the US dollar. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">PayPal With a New Boss</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/paypal-names-alex-chriss-as-next-president-and-ceo-301899740.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement</a> states that the Board of Directors was looking for a new CEO for months. The appointment of Chriss (who will also serve as President of PayPal) seems to have complied with the requirements of finding an individual with extensive global payments, product, and technology experience, who could lead the company toward new achievements in the future. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;With his depth of experience in product development, his passion for serving customers and his longstanding commitment to empowering and enabling small businesses, and his proven track record of developing and inspiring his team, Alex is the perfect leader to take PayPal forward and accelerate the company&#8217;s growth opportunities,&#8221; said John Donahoe, Chair of the PayPal Board of Directors.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also thanked Dan Schulman for his &#8220;outstanding leadership&#8221; over the past eight years, during which he helped the firm set up a solid foundation for the future. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Speaking on the matter was also Chriss, who described PayPal as an &#8220;extraordinary company that plays a critical role in the lives of consumers and merchants all over the world.&#8221;<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_266485" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266485" style="width: 533px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266485" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss.jpg" alt="Alex Chriss" width="533" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss-300x225.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss-768x576.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Alex-Chriss-50x38.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 533px) 100vw, 533px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266485" class="wp-caption-text">Alex Chriss, Source: Bloomberg</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Schulman will remain on the board of the firm until the next annual meeting of stockholders in May 2024. Under his reign, PayPal introduced several cryptocurrency offerings, and he displayed himself as a keen proponent of the industry. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Schulman, who admitted in 2019 that he holds bitcoin, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-will-redefine-the-financial-world-paypals-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> that the combination of digital assets, central bank digital currencies, stablecoins, and digital wallets could reshape the financial system.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Continuing PayPal&#8217;s Crypto Forays</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides holding crypto on its balance sheet and enabling a variety of cryptocurrency services for users, PayPal recently made the headlines by </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">launching</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a stablecoin called PYUSD. The monetary product is fixed to the value of the American dollar and issued by Paxos Trust Co.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">PayPal said it will gradually introduce PYUSD to clients in the USA: a move indicating the firm&#8217;s determination to remain part of the digital asset sector despite the regulatory uncertainty in the world&#8217;s largest economy.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Alex Chriss&#8217; background in Intuit includes helping individuals and small businesses have better access to financial services and more control over their funds. As such, his appointment could align with PayPal&#8217;s crypto mission.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-week-following-stablecoin-introduction-paypal-appoints-new-ceo/" rel="nofollow">A Week Following Stablecoin Introduction, PayPal Appoints New CEO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Unveils Stablecoin Regulation as Global Trailblazer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-central-bank-unveils-stablecoin-regulation-as-global-trailblazer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 21:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266463</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Singapore.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Singapore.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Stablecoins that meet all the criteria set by Singapore's central bank will be labeled as MAS-regulated stablecoins. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following last year&#8217;s stablecoin implosion, international leaders have emphasized the importance of setting up global regulations and norms for this sector. Despite such calls, only a few have taken concrete steps to enact these measures.</p>
<p>In contrast, Singapore&#8217;s central bank has taken a proactive approach by introducing a structured framework, outlining various prerequisites, aiming to bring transparency to stablecoin issuers and their operations.</p>
<h2>Singapore&#8217;s Stablecoin Regulation</h2>
<p>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced features of a new regulatory framework to ensure a high degree of value stability for stablecoins regulated in the city-state.</p>
<p>The regulatory framework has been shaped by incorporating input received during the October 2022 public consultation and will be relevant to single-currency stablecoins (SCS) pegged to the Singapore Dollar or any other G10 currency issued within Singapore.</p>
<p>As such, there are certain requirements that the SCS needs to comply with.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Value Stability:</strong> The reserve assets of SCS will be subject to specifications concerning their constitution, valuation, safekeeping, and audit. These measures aim to ensure a substantial level of confidence in maintaining value stability.</li>
<li><strong>Capital: </strong>To mitigate the risks of insolvency and facilitate orderly shutting down of business (if necessary), stablecoin issuers must uphold a minimum base capital and maintain liquid assets.</li>
<li><strong>Redemption at Par:</strong> Issuers must refund the par value of SCS to holders within a span of five business days from a redemption request.</li>
<li><strong>Disclosure:</strong> Issuers are required to furnish users with necessary disclosures, including details about the value-stabilizing mechanism of the SCS, the rights of SCS holders, as well as the results of audits performed on the reserve assets.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stablecoins that meet all the criteria will be labeled as MAS-regulated ones, thereby setting them apart from the ones that lack oversight.</p>
<p>With the latest move, Singapore is among the world&#8217;s first jurisdictions to have adopted regulatory measures for stablecoins. Commenting on the development, MAS&#8217;s Deputy Managing Director (Financial Supervision) Ho Hern Shin <a href="https://www.mas.gov.sg/news/media-releases/2023/mas-finalises-stablecoin-regulatory-framework" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;MAS’ stablecoin regulatory framework aims to facilitate the use of stablecoins as a credible digital medium of exchange, and as a bridge between the fiat and digital asset ecosystems. We encourage SCS issuers who would like their stablecoins recognized as &#8216;MAS regulated stablecoins&#8217; to make early preparations for compliance.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Singapore&#8217;s Crypto Advancement</h2>
<p>Singapore is slowly establishing itself as a hub for digital currencies. To that extent, the regulators in the region are actively seeking to attract international companies, especially in light of critiques from the crypto sector regarding the regulatory framework in the US.</p>
<p>Several crypto platforms, such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Blockchain.com,</a> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Crypto.com,</a> Gemini, Circle, Paxos, and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-receives-in-principle-singapore-payments-license-us-crypto-exodus-continues/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ripple</a>, have secured authorization in Singapore over the past several months.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-central-bank-unveils-stablecoin-regulation-as-global-trailblazer/" rel="nofollow">Singapore&#8217;s Central Bank Unveils Stablecoin Regulation as Global Trailblazer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Web3 Domain Platform Ethereum Name Service (ENS) Clocked in $235k in Daily Fees: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/web3-domain-platform-ethereum-name-service-ens-clocked-in-235k-in-daily-fees-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 19:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266341</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ENS raked in $235,000 in daily fees, the highest in nearly a year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Web3 decentralized domains service provider &#8211; Ethereum Name Service (ENS) &#8211; raked in $235,000 in fees on August 13. The figure is the highest since September 11, 2022.</p>
<p>Over the past couple of years, ENS has stood as a mainstay within the Web3 realm, enabling individuals to generate easily understandable domain names and wallet addresses for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to data from Arkham Intelligence&#8217;s dashboard, ENS DAO (<a href="https://platform.arkhamintelligence.com/explorer/address/0xFe89cc7aBB2C4183683ab71653C4cdc9B02D44b7" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">0xFe…44b7</a>) holds more than $132.4 million in assets, including 10 million ENS (worth $90.63 million), 15,000 ETH (worth $27.72 million), and 14.13 million in USDC stablecoin.</li>
<li>The total active ENS names have also <a href="https://dune.com/ethereumnameservice/ens" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">exceeded</a> 2.6 million as of August 14th across nearly 740,000 unique addresses.</li>
<li>The latest development comes a little over a month after the &#8220;distributed, open, and extensible naming system&#8221; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-gears-up-for-layer-2-expansion/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to tap layer-2 in a bid to enhance scalability and cut costs.</li>
<li>Earlier this year, ENS also launched a new fiat on-ramp for domain registrations via Web3 fiat payment gateway MoonPay.</li>
<li>Its rival, Unstoppable Domains, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/web3-domain-provider-unstoppable-domains-expands-support-to-eth-domains/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">extended</a> support to &#8220;.eth&#8221; domains in July, allowing users to purchase via the official website.</li>
<li>With the move, Unstoppable Domains seeks to engage with a fresh audience since the platform typically offers domain endings such as .crypto, .blockchain, .nft, etc., while ENS is the only venue where Ethereum enthusiasts were able to purchase the .eth domain names.</li>
<li>In order to prevent &#8220;naming collisions,&#8221; each .eth domain obtained via Unstoppable&#8217;s website will be recorded through the ENS smart contract with the same full functionality as other .eth domains.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/web3-domain-platform-ethereum-name-service-ens-clocked-in-235k-in-daily-fees-data/" rel="nofollow">Web3 Domain Platform Ethereum Name Service (ENS) Clocked in $235k in Daily Fees: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Requests Protective Order, Accuses SEC of Conducting &#8216;Fishing Expedition&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-requests-protective-order-accuses-sec-of-conducting-fishing-expedition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 18:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266432</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance previously roped in a former prosecutor at the US DOJ to represent the firm in the legal battle against the SEC. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance filed a motion requesting a protective order against the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), claiming the regulator is conducting a &#8220;fishing expedition&#8221; instead of seeking the narrow and &#8220;limited&#8221; discovery authorized by the Consent Order to ensure the security and availability of customer assets.</p>
<p>The motion asserts that Binance has already provided the SEC with the necessary information.</p>
<h2>Binance Sees Protective Order Against SEC</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/67474542/95/securities-and-exchange-commission-v-binance-holdings-limited/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a>, Binance called the SEC’s approach &#8220;troubling and inappropriate,&#8221; arguing that BAM&#8217;s asset custody practices have &#8220;nothing to do&#8221; with the underlying claims in this case.</p>
<p>This is in reference to the communications dating back to November 2022 that the SEC has demanded to be produced in court. For the uninitiated, BAM Trading is the holding company of Binance.US and BAM Management.</p>
<p>Binance claimed that BAM implemented numerous measures in accordance with the Consent Order to further ensure that customer assets are secure and have already produced necessary information about customer assets to the SEC.</p>
<p>Pointing to the SEC&#8217;s failure to uncover any trace of evidence indicating any misuse or mishandling of BAM customer assets, Binance urged the court to grant a protective order to restrict the regulator from conducting a maximum of four depositions of BAM employees.</p>
<p>As part of the order, Binance is seeking a ban on the SEC from raising questions during these depositions that fall beyond the boundaries defined by the Consent Order.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the filing also said the depositions of BAM&#8217;s CEO and CFO should be disallowed, along with any requests for communications about different subjects.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;BAM has worked in good faith, but the SEC has been steadfast in its belief that the Consent Order gives it carte blanche to investigate every aspect of BAM’s asset custody practices without any discernible limitation whatsoever.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Binance vs. SEC</h2>
<p>Current US regulations do not accommodate digital assets, which has led the SEC to use its own interpretations to oversee the sector. The approach was met with severe backlash. The US regulators sued Binance and CEO Changpeng &#8216;CZ&#8217; Zhao in June this year for allegedly operating a &#8220;web of deception.&#8221;</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Allegations</a> against the cryptocurrency exchange include actions like inflating trading volumes artificially, redirecting customer funds, neglecting to prevent US customers from using the platform, and providing false information to investors regarding its market surveillance measures.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-requests-protective-order-accuses-sec-of-conducting-fishing-expedition/" rel="nofollow">Binance Requests Protective Order, Accuses SEC of Conducting &#8216;Fishing Expedition&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Explodes to New ATH in Argentina</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-explodes-to-new-ath-in-argentina/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266666</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin_Argentina.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Bitcoin_Argentina.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is erupting in Argentina after a pro-Bitcoin, anti-peso presidential candidate won the nation’s primary elections.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has tapped a new all-time high against the Argentine peso, shortly after a Bitcoin-supportive presidential candidate came first in the nation’s primary elections.</p>
<p>The asset now trades for $10,258,244.60 ARS, up 21% over the past 5 days.</p>
<h2>Pressure on the Peso</h2>
<p>Compared to the US dollar, Bitcoin has performed remarkably well against the peso over time given that the latter currency’s persistently high inflation.</p>
<p>Last month, the nation’s annual inflation rate skyrocketed to 115% up from 98% in January. Meanwhile, as BTC is up 76% year to date in USD terms, its risen 249% against the peso in that same timeframe.</p>
<p>Yet a large portion of those gains came only after Argentina’s primary elections over the weekend, which saw Javier Milei – leader of La Libertad Avanza (Freedom Advances) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-supporter-javier-milei-wins-primary-presidential-elections-in-argentina/" data-wpel-link="internal">score</a> over 30% of the vote.</p>
<p>A keen critic of inflation, Milei wants to entirely abolish Argentina’s central bank, replacing the peso with the dollar. He’s also pitched solving some of Argentina’s inflationary issues using Bitcoin, which proponents praise as a potential inflation hedge due to its fixed supply of 21 million coins.</p>
<blockquote><p>“What Bitcoin is representing is the return of money to its original creator: the private sector,” the politician has stated in previous interviews.</p>
<p>“Bitcoin has an algorithm that one day it will reach a certain amount, and there is no more, and it can compete with other currencies,” he added.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/argentina-approves-btc-index-futures-contracts-on-matba-rofex-exchange-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Argentina</a> is currently one of the top 20 countries for crypto adoption worldwide, according to data from both Statista and <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-global-crypto-adoption-index/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Chainalysis</a>.</p>
<h2>Can Argentina Eradicate the Peso?</h2>
<p>Shortly after Milei’s surprise success on Sunday, the Argentine government opted to devalue the peso by another 20% early on Monday – roughly the same amount by which Bitcoin has risen against it since that time.</p>
<p>A devaluing peso only makes life more difficult for locals, who witness the purchasing power of their savings erode in real time.</p>
<p>&#8220;The more the dollar rises, the more expensive things become,&#8221; said Marta Gisela Barrera, a 29-year-old recycler struggling to buy food for her children, to the <a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/world/argentine-peso-plunges-after-rightist-who-admires-trump-comes-first-in-primary-vote-1.6517879" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Associated Press</a> Monday morning. &#8220;I don&#8217;t know what&#8217;s going to happen anymore.&#8221;</p>
<p>Were Milei to become President following October’s election, he would still need approval from Congress to entirely replace the peso. Alternatively, he’s suggested having a referendum or “non-binding popular vote” on the matter, though it’s still unclear if this would be enough without lawmakers’ support.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-explodes-to-new-ath-in-argentina/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Explodes to New ATH in Argentina</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did You Know? XRP Marks 16 Consecutive Weeks of Institutional Inflows</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/did-you-know-xrp-marks-16-consecutive-weeks-of-institutional-inflows/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266552</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ripple_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ripple_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinShares found that digital asset investment products saw inflows of $29 million following three weeks of outflows.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investment products for XRP, the native crypto asset of the Ripple network, have recorded the 16th consecutive week of institutional inflows since the start of 2023.</p>
<p>According to data <a href="https://blog.coinshares.com/volume-144-digital-asset-fund-flows-weekly-report-7d29c8c04df5" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">analyzed</a> by CoinShares in its latest Digital Asset Fund Flows Weekly Report, XRP saw $0.5 million in inflows during the past week.</p>
<h2>XRP Sees Inflows for the 16th Week</h2>
<p>CoinShares found that digital asset investment products saw inflows of $29 million following three weeks of outflows. Bitcoin <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-funds-soak-in-27-million-inflows-following-positive-inflation-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">recorded</a> the highest influx of $27 million, with its short funds experiencing outflows of $2.7 million.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s dominance was followed by Ethereum’s, which led altcoins with inflows of $2.5 million, Uniswap with $0.7 million, XRP with $0.5 million, and Solana with $0.4 million. XRP’s inflows represent 12% of its assets under management (AUM). The asset’s AUM has spiked by 127% since the beginning of the year.</p>
<p>In terms of regional activity, Canada saw the most inflows of $24 million, followed by Switzerland with $8 million and the United States with $0.9 million. Despite Canada’s notable growth, the country is behind others from a year-to-date perspective.</p>
<p>CoinShares deduced that the improved investor sentiment was due to the recent U.S. inflation data, which fell slightly below expectations, raising suspicions that a September rate hike would not happen. The data also suggests that the broader crypto market remains supportive despite low trading volumes.</p>
<h2>XRP Gains Market Dominance</h2>
<p>While XRP records constant inflows, the digital asset is also gaining significant popularity in the crypto space. <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-poised-to-surpass-btc-eth-and-ada-as-the-leading-payment-cryptocurrency/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that a CryptoCompare study found the XRP Ledger (XRPL) to be the fastest and most cost-effective blockchain network for payments, making it a more sustainable choice for businesses seeking quick and affordable payment solutions.</p>
<p>Compared to Bitcoin’s average transaction processing time of 10 minutes, the XRPL handles transactions in 3.3 seconds with a cost of $0.00003. This is also significantly better than Ethereum’s 15 seconds and Cardano’s 20 seconds.</p>
<p>Data from CoinMarketCap <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/xrp/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> that XRP has gained market dominance and is currently the fifth-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, a feat the digital asset attained since Ripple Labs <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/has-ripple-xrp-won-or-will-the-sec-appeal-what-will-happen-next/" data-wpel-link="internal">won</a> a partial victory in a three-year-long legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-you-know-xrp-marks-16-consecutive-weeks-of-institutional-inflows/" rel="nofollow">Did You Know? XRP Marks 16 Consecutive Weeks of Institutional Inflows</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana Price Keeps Rising, While Launchpad XYZ Raises $1.2 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/solana-price-keeps-rising-while-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-2-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 15:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266524</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchpad_solana_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/launchpad_solana_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto market continues to surprise investors, with Solana ($SOL) being the latest token to experience significant upside. $SOL has soared 11% in the past week, putting the price just below the crucial $25 level. However, $SOL isn&#8217;t the only cryptocurrency gaining ground – the new Web3 project Launchpad XYZ ($LPX) is also making waves [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market continues to surprise investors, with Solana ($SOL) being the latest token to experience significant upside.</p>
<p>$SOL has soared 11% in the past week, putting the price just below the crucial $25 level.</p>
<p>However, $SOL isn&#8217;t the only cryptocurrency gaining ground – the new Web3 project Launchpad XYZ ($LPX) is also making waves as its presale phase hits the $1.2 million milestone.</p>
<h2>Bulls Regain Control as $SOL Price Surges</h2>
<p>Solana has posted a bullish close in six of the last seven days, showcasing a level of consistency not seen since mid-June.</p>
<p>After dropping 30% from July’s peak, $SOL has bounced back, with the bulls seemingly in control.</p>
<p>Price has climbed above the 20-day and 50-Day Exponential Moving Averages (EMAs) on the daily time frame, indicating that the short and medium-term trends have flipped bullish.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266570" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-19.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="284" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-19.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-19-300x142.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-19-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Additionally, <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from CoinMarketCap</a> shows that $375 million worth of $SOL was traded in the past 24 hours – making it the eighth largest cryptocurrency globally, as measured by trading volume.</p>
<p>This surge in trading activity shows that interest in Solana remains high among market participants.</p>
<p>Coupled with the positive sentiment in the crypto market as a whole, sentiment remains optimistic among many investors about $SOL’s growth trajectory for the remainder of 2023.</p>
<h2>Solana’s Thriving NFT Sector Fuels Token Growth</h2>
<p>One of the main factors contributing to Solana’s recent price rise is the platform’s expanding NFT capabilities.</p>
<p>Solana has become a go-to blockchain for launching new NFT collections, with <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/blockchains" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">data from CryptoSlam</a> showing that it is now only behind Ethereum in terms of daily sales.</p>
<p>Over 890,000 NFT transactions occurred on Solana in the past 30 days, leading to a total sales volume of $75.4 million.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-20.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266568" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-20.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="164" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-20.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-20-300x82.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-20-50x14.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Leading projects like Gruuvies, Tensorians, and Solcasino.io have also chosen Solana due to its speed, low fees, and growing user base – and this influx of activity has prompted additional interest in the network.</p>
<p>Naturally, the more NFT activity on Solana, the higher the demand for $SOL, helping drive the token&#8217;s recent price increase.</p>
<p>As such, the thriving NFT sector on Solana looks poised to fuel further growth for $SOL in the second half of 2023.</p>
<h2>Launchpad XYZ Presale Heating Up &amp; Raises $1.2 Million Ahead of Exchange Listings</h2>
<p>While Solana’s price keeps rising, another crypto asset gaining momentum is <a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=solana-price-keeps-rising-while-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-2-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ ($LPX)</a>, which recently crossed $1.2 million raised in its ongoing presale.</p>
<p>This ambitious project aims to drive mainstream adoption of Web3 assets by simplifying access to cryptocurrencies, NFTs, blockchain gaming, and the metaverse.</p>
<p>During Launchpad XYZ’s ongoing presale, investors can purchase $LPX, the platform’s native token, for just $0.0445 ahead of the planned exchange listings for later this year.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266567" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-14.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="339" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-14.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-14-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture4-14-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Many believe this decision could prove fruitful, given the comprehensive nature of the Launchpad XYZ platform.</p>
<p>As outlined in the <a href="https://launchpad.xyz/assets/documents/LaunchpadXYZ_Whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">project’s whitepaper</a>, Launchpad XYZ will offer an advanced trading terminal, trading signals, educational materials, and a “Launchpad Quotient” score for ranking digital assets.</p>
<p>The platform will even have an AI-powered assistant called “Apollo” that provides data-driven insights and setups from experienced traders.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-8.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-266563" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-8.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="235" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-8.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-8-300x117.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-8-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>There are also built-in incentives to hold $LPX tokens long-term, including discounted fees, NFT whitelist access, and exclusive entry to cryptocurrency presales.</p>
<p>Members of the <a href="https://t.me/Launchpad_Official_Channel" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Launchpad XYZ Telegram channel</a> are also discussing the project’s roadmap, which notes plans for a decentralized exchange (DEX) and NFT directory.</p>
<p>With an experienced founding team and $1.2 million already raised, Launchpad XYZ looks like a project to watch closely ahead of its upcoming exchange listing.</p>
<p><a href="https://shrt.care/11df4205?referrer=solana-price-keeps-rising-while-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-2-million" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Launchpad XYZ Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer.</a></em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-price-keeps-rising-while-launchpad-xyz-raises-1-2-million/" rel="nofollow">Solana Price Keeps Rising, While Launchpad XYZ Raises $1.2 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why is Logan Paul Facing Massive Criticism on His $1M Bet for Danis Match?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-logan-paul-facing-massive-criticism-on-his-1m-bet-for-danis-match/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266607</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/logan_paul_v_danis_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/logan_paul_v_danis_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Logan Paul, a multifaceted entertainer and crypto enthusiast, has received criticism from various quarters regarding his recent $1m bet proposition.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Logan Paul is gearing up for his next event, a boxing match against Brazilian Dillon Danis scheduled for October 14 in Manchester, England.</p>
<p>Danis, widely recognized as an MMA fighter and Conor McGregor&#8217;s training partner, will be coached by the Irishman for the upcoming fight.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266608" style="width: 443px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-266608" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412.jpg" alt="Screenshot 2023-08-15 172412" width="443" height="445" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412.jpg 443w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Screenshot-2023-08-15-172412-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 443px) 100vw, 443px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266608" class="wp-caption-text">Source: X</figcaption></figure>
<p>Upon learning about this, Paul launched an explicit rant, accompanied by insults, while offering a one million dollar bet on the match.</p>
<h2>Logan Paul Faces Criticism</h2>
<p>This move has drawn heavy criticism from the crypto community, mainly due to Paul&#8217;s failure to reimburse victims of his CryptoZoo (ZOO) project.</p>
<p>Launched in 2021, CryptoZoo promised a cryptocurrency game featuring the ZOO token and NFTs. Despite initial hype during the bull market, the project has failed to meet expectations. Earlier this year, Paul <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/change-of-heart-logan-paul-apologizes-to-coffeezilla-amidst-fallout-over-nft-project/" data-wpel-link="internal">pledged</a> to rectify the situation for affected investors, but this has yet to materialize. He is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/logan-paul-faces-class-action-lawsuit-over-alleged-cryptozoo-nft-rug-pull/" data-wpel-link="internal">facing</a> a class-action lawsuit associated with regard to the above.</p>
<p>Consequently, his willingness to wager $1 million on a match outcome has left many unamused. In response to Paul&#8217;s outburst, Danis took to Twitter, highlighting that Paul may have money to bet, but has failed to pay off those he scammed.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-logan-paul-facing-massive-criticism-on-his-1m-bet-for-danis-match/" rel="nofollow">Why is Logan Paul Facing Massive Criticism on His $1M Bet for Danis Match?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shibarium Nearly Complete, Shiba Inu With a New Major Announcement</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shibarium-nearly-complete-shiba-inu-with-a-new-major-announcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 14:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266592</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_exclam_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_exclam_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kusama has confirmed that Shibarium is nearly complete, while also revealing another important partnership.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu has shared yet another announcement with its community.</p>
<p>The ecosystem&#8217;s marketing strategist took it to Twitter (now known as X) to reveal that the SHIB Doggy DAO has partnered with a leading digital asset advisory and investment firm.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266593" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266593" style="width: 537px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_img.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266593 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_img.jpg" alt="shiba_inu_img" width="537" height="429" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_img.jpg 537w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_img-300x240.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_img-50x40.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 537px) 100vw, 537px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266593" class="wp-caption-text">Source: X</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SHIB Doggy DAO Shakes Hands with ATH</h2>
<p>The new partnership is struck between Alpha Transform Holdings (ATH) and SHIB Doggy DAO. The latter is the decentralized autonomous organization that&#8217;s governed by holders of the SHIB token and funds the projects that are now built on Shibarium.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, ATH is a digital asset advisory and investment firm that&#8217;s comprised of a team of veteran leaders from heavyweights like Nasdaq, News Crop, and Disney and has advised projects like Tether and even Ethereum, per the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2023/08/14/2724869/0/en/Alpha-Transform-Holdings-Joins-SHIB-Doggy-DAO-Foundation-as-Advisor.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>.</p>
<p>Commenting on the matter was Chief Investment Officer and CEO at Alpha Transform Holdings, Enzo Villani, who said:</p>
<blockquote><p>“SHIB continues the incredible trajectory. Shibarium has already seen great momentum. With over 21 million wallets and over 250,000 smart contracts written to their Layer 2 blockchain testnet, there are many brands in entertainment, media, and finance that will be interested in engaging with this vibrant community.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Shibarium Nearly Complete</h2>
<p>In a comment on the partnership, the lead developer behind the Shiba Inu ecosystem &#8211; Shytoshi Kusama &#8211; said that Shibarium is &#8220;nearly complete.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Now that Shibarium is nearly complete, and our full structure placed at the feet of the world, we couldn&#8217;t ask for a better partner to help shepherd this next phase of the Shiba global phenomenon. [&#8230;] We look forward to Alpha Transform helping our Foundation swiftly and effectively chart the best course possible for the future of the Shiba Inu ecosystem.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The SHIB price hasn&#8217;t yet reacted to the news, trading 2% down in the past 24 hours but 11% up for the day, following an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shib-rallies-14-weekly-but-warning-signs-flash-3-things-to-watch-this-week-shiba-inu-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">impressive weekly rally.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shibarium-nearly-complete-shiba-inu-with-a-new-major-announcement/" rel="nofollow">Shibarium Nearly Complete, Shiba Inu With a New Major Announcement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu&#8217;s LEASH Explodes Following Listing on Major Exchange</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-leash-explodes-following-listing-on-major-exchange/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wayne Jones]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto Bits]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=266574</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_leash_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/shiba_inu_leash_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LEASH, one of Shiba Inu's ecosystem tokens, has achieved another milestone with its recent listing on the renowned cryptocurrency exchange crypto.com.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In an exciting announcement, the Crypto.com exchange has made LEASH (Doge Killer) accessible on their platform, providing users with seamless trading and swapping capabilities with other cryptocurrencies available on the exchange.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266575" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266575" style="width: 527px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_img1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-266575" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_img1.jpg" alt="leash_img1" width="527" height="678" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_img1.jpg 527w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_img1-233x300.jpg 233w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_img1-39x50.jpg 39w" sizes="(max-width: 527px) 100vw, 527px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266575" class="wp-caption-text">Source: <a href="https://twitter.com/Cryptocom_Insto/status/1691381761681305600" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">X</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>This development has garnered attention and celebration from the official Shiba Inu Twitter account, which shared the news with the SHIBARMY, emphasizing the significance of this listing on Crypto.com as a considerable achievement for the ecosystem.</p>
<h2>LEASH Price Reaction Amid Announcement</h2>
<p>Furthermore, recent <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/doge-killer" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">data</a> from CoinGecko highlights the impressive performance of the Shiba Inu ecosystem tokens SHIB, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-shiba-inus-leash-skyrocket-this-week-lead-developer-teases-big-updates-heres-when/" data-wpel-link="internal">LEASH</a>, and BONE over the past 7 days.</p>
<p>As of the time of writing, LEASH is being traded at $667.40, showcasing an impressive 15.2% increase in value in the past 24 hours. These gains reflect the growing interest and confidence in the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<figure id="attachment_266576" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-266576" style="width: 819px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-266576 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1.jpg" alt="leash_price_chart" width="819" height="544" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1.jpg 819w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1-300x199.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1-768x510.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/leash_price_chart-1-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 819px) 100vw, 819px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-266576" class="wp-caption-text">LEASH price chart. Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>LEASH&#8217;s listing on the Crypto.com exchange, coupled with its price surge, bodes well for the Shiba Inu ecosystem.</p>
<p>This development has captured the attention of cryptocurrency enthusiasts and investors, generating increased interest and participation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/shiba-inus-leash-explodes-following-listing-on-major-exchange/" rel="nofollow">Shiba Inu&#8217;s LEASH Explodes Following Listing on Major Exchange</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
