<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Coinbase Was Dismissed by the US SEC After Months of Figuring Out How To Register, Chief Legal Officer Says</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-was-dismissed-by-us-sec-after-months-of-figuring-out-how-register-chief-legal-officer-says.htm</link><description>Coinbase was dismissed by the US Securities and Exchange Commission with no response after months of discussing how to register with the agency, the crypto exchange’s chief legal officer told lawmakers on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Paul Grewal, chief legal officer at Coinbase, faced lawmakers hours after the exchange was charged by the SEC for not registering with it. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-was-dismissed-by-us-sec-after-months-of-figuring-out-how-register-chief-legal-officer-says.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Was Dismissed by the US SEC After Months of Figuring Out How To Register, Chief Legal Officer Says&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>House Agriculture</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-was-dismissed-by-us-sec-after-months-of-figuring-out-how-register-chief-legal-officer-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116093/311800/adobestock-521876474-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="389077"/></item><item><title>Japanese Megabank Mitsubishi UFJ to Launch Stablecoin Issuance Platform in 2024</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-megabank-mitsubishi-ufj-launch-stablecoin-issuance-platform-2024.htm</link><description>The Japanese banking giant Mitsubishi UFJ says it will launch a cross-chain stablecoin issuance and interoperability platform next year. &lt;br /&gt;
In an official Mitsubishi UFJ announcement, the firm stated that it would work with a Tokyo-based company named Datachain to “build cross-chain infrastructure for stablecoins.” &lt;br /&gt;
Mitsubishi UFJ began piloting the project back in March....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-megabank-mitsubishi-ufj-launch-stablecoin-issuance-platform-2024.htm"&gt;Read More: Japanese Megabank Mitsubishi UFJ to Launch Stablecoin Issuance Platform in 2024&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Mitsubishi UFJ</category><category>Japan</category><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/japanese-megabank-mitsubishi-ufj-launch-stablecoin-issuance-platform-2024.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116002/311652/japan-0606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="592844"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 6 June – Bitget, Quant, Kava</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-6-june-bitget-quant-kava.htm</link><description>Coinbase, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges globally, faces a lawsuit from US regulators, hot on the heels of similar legal action against Binance, another industry heavyweight. &lt;br /&gt;
The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) accused Coinbase of operating illegally without prior registration, a mandatory requirement for securities trading firms in the US. &lt;br /&gt;
Considering this recent macroeconomic development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-6-june-bitget-quant-kava.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 6 June – Bitget, Quant, Kava&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>WSM</category><category>BGB</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>QNT</category><category>YPRED</category><category>KAVA</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Bitget token</category><category>Quant</category><category>yPredict</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Web3</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Binance</category><category>CZ</category><category>US SEC</category><category>SEC</category><category>US</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-6-june-bitget-quant-kava.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116096/311819/best-crypto-6-june.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="241305"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy Pepe Coin? PEPE Coin Price Plummets 15% in 7 Days as Launchpad Approaches $1 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-plummets-15-7-days-as-launchpad-approaches-1-million.htm</link><description>Despite an incredible surge of over 50,000% between April 15 and May 5, Pepe Coin (PEPE) is experiencing a significant decline of more than 60% from its peak, with 15% of the drop occurring in the past week. &lt;br /&gt;
Uncertainty looms over the meme coin's future potential, causing market participants to question how much further the crypto prices may fall....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-plummets-15-7-days-as-launchpad-approaches-1-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy Pepe Coin? PEPE Coin Price Plummets 15% in 7 Days as Launchpad Approaches $1 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Pepe Price</category><category>Pepe Coin Price</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Crypto Presale 2023</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>Web3</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Crypto Wallet</category><category>Crypto Gaming</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFTs</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-pepe-coin-pepe-price-plummets-15-7-days-as-launchpad-approaches-1-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116070/311799/trent-pepe-frog-falling-t.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1001869"/></item><item><title>US CFTC Chair Says Claim That the Agency Is a ‘Light Touch Regulator’ Could Not Be ‘Farther From the Truth’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-pushes-back-light-touch-regulation-views-gives-timeline-for-potential-new-rules.htm</link><description>US Commodity Futures Trading Commission Chair Rostin Behnam pushed back on assertions that his agency would be a “light touch regulator” for cryptocurrency, following an eventful week and as lawmakers contemplate legislation to regulate the industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
Behnam was asked on Tuesday during a House Agriculture Committee hearing on opinions that the CFTC is seen as taking a lighter touch when it comes to regulating the crypto industry. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-pushes-back-light-touch-regulation-views-gives-timeline-for-potential-new-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: US CFTC Chair Says Claim That the Agency Is a ‘Light Touch Regulator’ Could Not Be ‘Farther From the Truth’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-pushes-back-light-touch-regulation-views-gives-timeline-for-potential-new-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116084/311783/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="426841"/></item><item><title>Judge Rules Against FTX in Genesis Bankruptcy Mediation Case</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-against-ftx-genesis-bankruptcy-mediation-case.htm</link><description>FTX will not be allowed to join in the mediation between now-bankrupt crypto lender Genesis Global and its parent company, Barry Silbert’s crypto conglomerate Digital Currency Group (DCG), a judge has ruled. &lt;br /&gt;
In the ruling, US Bankruptcy Judge Sean Lane decided against FTX's inclusion in the settlement talks, where Genesis and its major creditors, along with DCG, aim to develop a revised payout proposal, Bloomberg reported on Monday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-against-ftx-genesis-bankruptcy-mediation-case.htm"&gt;Read More: Judge Rules Against FTX in Genesis Bankruptcy Mediation Case&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Genesis</category><category>FTX</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/judge-rules-against-ftx-genesis-bankruptcy-mediation-case.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116026/311694/genesis-global.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="65424"/></item><item><title>AI Deepfakes Becoming Tool of Choice in Cyber Extortion, Says FBI – How is Crypto Being Used in the Process?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-deepfakes-becoming-tool-of-choice-cyber-extortion-says-fbi-how-crypto-being-used-process.htm</link><description>The Federal Bureau of Investigation has issued a stark warning about the growing threat of "deepfakes" being used in cyber extortion.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent report, the FBI said that malicious actors are using deepfakes to manipulate photographs or videos, often obtained from social media accounts or the open internet, and create sexually-themed images that appear authentic....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-deepfakes-becoming-tool-of-choice-cyber-extortion-says-fbi-how-crypto-being-used-process.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Deepfakes Becoming Tool of Choice in Cyber Extortion, Says FBI – How is Crypto Being Used in the Process?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Technology News</category><category>Deepfake</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Elon Musk</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-deepfakes-becoming-tool-of-choice-cyber-extortion-says-fbi-how-crypto-being-used-process.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116080/311780/istockphoto-532253660-612x612.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="29372"/></item><item><title>El Salvador’s Bitcoin Mining Industry Sees Tether Join its $1 Billion Venture</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-mining-industry-sees-tether-join-its-1-billion-venture.htm</link><description>After the massive losses that followed the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX, users lost confidence in lending, custody, and cryptocurrency service providers.  &lt;br /&gt;
The fear of losing assets, as with FTX, plagues people's minds after the commotion.  &lt;br /&gt;
Some experts believe it will take a while for fear, uncertainty, and doubt (FUD) to clear from people's minds. &lt;br /&gt;
It is a critical time for crypto firms as many are experiencing the effects of the FUD caused by the FTX collapse. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-mining-industry-sees-tether-join-its-1-billion-venture.htm"&gt;Read More: El Salvador’s Bitcoin Mining Industry Sees Tether Join its $1 Billion Venture&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/el-salvadors-bitcoin-mining-industry-sees-tether-join-its-1-billion-venture.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116081/311781/bitcoin-gc67e33bda-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="450348"/></item><item><title>Former Minnesota Vikings Co-Owner Convicted in $700 Million Cryptocurrency Scam</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-minnesota-vikings-co-owner-convicted-in-700-million-cryptocurrency-scam.htm</link><description>The Manhattan federal court has convicted the former co-owner of the Minnesota Vikings, Reginald Fowler, for a $700 million crypto scam.  &lt;br /&gt;
Washington Post reported that Fowler, aged 64, defrauded the Alliance of American Football (AAF), a now-shut-down professional football league, in a fraudulent crypto investment. &lt;br /&gt;
The sentence announced by the US Attorney’s Office in New York noted that the Arizona-based businessman would serve a 75-month jail term. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/former-minnesota-vikings-co-owner-convicted-in-700-million-cryptocurrency-scam.htm"&gt;Read More: Former Minnesota Vikings Co-Owner Convicted in $700 Million Cryptocurrency Scam&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/former-minnesota-vikings-co-owner-convicted-in-700-million-cryptocurrency-scam.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116079/311779/scam-gd888d0c41-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="313065"/></item><item><title>New Shiba Inu, China-Japan INU Meme Coin Price Explodes 40,000%, Wall St Memes Pumps to $4.5m</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-shiba-inu-china-japan-inu-coin-price-explodes-40000-wall-st-memes-pumps-to-45m.htm</link><description>The latest meme coin to challenge for the Shiba Inu crown by grabbing buyers’ dollars is $INU, which launched two days ago and has risen 40,000%. &lt;br /&gt;
$INU is trading at $0.000000008840 and reached a high yesterday of $0.000000009831, according to Dextools price data. &lt;br /&gt;
24-hour volume is around $20 million and the market cap is a little over $8 million. &lt;br /&gt;
The token’s DEX liquidity is $1.29 million. When it launched on June 4, total liquidity was just 20 ETH....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-shiba-inu-china-japan-inu-coin-price-explodes-40000-wall-st-memes-pumps-to-45m.htm"&gt;Read More: New Shiba Inu, China-Japan INU Meme Coin Price Explodes 40,000%, Wall St Memes Pumps to $4.5m&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-shiba-inu-china-japan-inu-coin-price-explodes-40000-wall-st-memes-pumps-to-45m.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116073/311775/inuusdt-2023-06-06-17-55-45.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="759511"/></item><item><title>AI Crypto Signals and Trading Alpha Made Easy with This New Crypto Platform – Best Low Cap Gem?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-trading-alpha-made-easy-with-new-crypto-platform-best-low-cap-gem.htm</link><description>Step into the future of trading with yPredict, a new crypto platform that combines the power of AI with the dynamism of the blockchain.  &lt;br /&gt;
With its native $YPRED token, yPredict is spear-heading an innovation revolution in the crypto market. &lt;br /&gt;
Brought to life by elite Machine Learning minds, yPredict employs a high-tech combination of AI and data analytics, providing retail traders with a competitive edge previously reserved for VC analytics....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-trading-alpha-made-easy-with-new-crypto-platform-best-low-cap-gem.htm"&gt;Read More: AI Crypto Signals and Trading Alpha Made Easy with This New Crypto Platform – Best Low Cap Gem?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ai-crypto-signals-trading-alpha-made-easy-with-new-crypto-platform-best-low-cap-gem.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116067/311769/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="869401"/></item><item><title>Crypto Prices Rising Again After Regulatory FUD: Bitcoin, Ethereum &amp; Meme Coins Bounce After Escaping SEC Wrath</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-rising-again-after-regulatory-fud-bitcoin-ethereum-meme-coins-bounce-after-escaping-sec-wrath.htm</link><description>Despite a new round of regulatory FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in wake of their just-announced lawsuit against Coinbase, crypto prices are rising again. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH) and a number of meme coins like Dogecoin (DOGE) and Shiba Inu (SHIB) were all trading in the green on Tuesday. &lt;br /&gt;
BTC was last in the $26,000, ETH in the $1,840 area, DOGE just under $0.07 and SHIB near $0.000008, all sharply up from Monday’s lows....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-rising-again-after-regulatory-fud-bitcoin-ethereum-meme-coins-bounce-after-escaping-sec-wrath.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Prices Rising Again After Regulatory FUD: Bitcoin, Ethereum &amp; Meme Coins Bounce After Escaping SEC Wrath&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ether</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-rising-again-after-regulatory-fud-bitcoin-ethereum-meme-coins-bounce-after-escaping-sec-wrath.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116068/311765/sec.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="9814734"/></item><item><title>As Crypto Prices Crash, Whales are Accumulating $WSM Before it Lists on Exchanges – What Do They Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-crypto-prices-crash-whales-are-accumulating-wsm-before-it-lists-exchanges-what-do-they-know.htm</link><description>In an increasingly unpredictable cryptocurrency market, meme coins are establishing their foothold. &lt;br /&gt;
One such coin garnering attention before its listing on exchanges is Wall Street Memes ($WSM). &lt;br /&gt;
With a dedicated community and a performance-driven track record, $WSM has accumulated over $4.5 million in its ongoing pre-sale stage (ranking it among the biggest crypto presales of 2023)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/as-crypto-prices-crash-whales-are-accumulating-wsm-before-it-lists-exchanges-what-do-they-know.htm"&gt;Read More: As Crypto Prices Crash, Whales are Accumulating $WSM Before it Lists on Exchanges – What Do They Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-crypto-prices-crash-whales-are-accumulating-wsm-before-it-lists-exchanges-what-do-they-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116066/311761/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="252153"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as SOL is Deemed a Security by the SEC – Will the Charges Send SOL Lower?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-deemed-security-by-sec-will-charges-send-sol-lower.htm</link><description>SOL, the cryptocurrency that powers the smart-contract-enabled, high-performance Solana layer-1 blockchain protocol, has just been deemed as a security by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). &lt;br /&gt;
In the past two days, the SEC has sued both Binance and Coinbase, two of the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges in terms of trading volumes, for operating as unlicensed securities exchanges within the US....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-deemed-security-by-sec-will-charges-send-sol-lower.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as SOL is Deemed a Security by the SEC – Will the Charges Send SOL Lower?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-sol-deemed-security-by-sec-will-charges-send-sol-lower.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116063/311760/sol.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="405982"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price is Going to Zero After the SEC Says ADA is a Security While Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Blasts to New Highs – 100x Potential in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-is-going-to-zero-after-the-sec-says-ada-is-a-security-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-blasts-to-new-highs-100x-potential-in-2023.htm</link><description>The crypto market experienced a shockwave as the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) recently filed a lawsuit against Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, naming Cardano (ADA) as an unregistered security - shifting the Cardano price prediction over night....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-is-going-to-zero-after-the-sec-says-ada-is-a-security-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-blasts-to-new-highs-100x-potential-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price is Going to Zero After the SEC Says ADA is a Security While Eco-Friendly Crypto Ecoterra Blasts to New Highs – 100x Potential in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-is-going-to-zero-after-the-sec-says-ada-is-a-security-while-eco-friendly-crypto-ecoterra-blasts-to-new-highs-100x-potential-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116054/311753/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1385787"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Two US Representatives Demand Crypto Tax Regulations, Atomic Wallet Stolen Funds Traced to N.Korean Hackers, OKX Partners with Custody Service Provider Komainu, Zodia Custody Joins Hands with Blockdaemon</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-two-us-representatives-demand-crypto-tax-regulations-atomic-wallet-stolen-funds-traced-to-nkorean-hackers-okx-partners-with-custody-service-provider-komainu-zodia-custody-joins-hands-with-blockdaemon.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today's crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-two-us-representatives-demand-crypto-tax-regulations-atomic-wallet-stolen-funds-traced-to-nkorean-hackers-okx-partners-with-custody-service-provider-komainu-zodia-custody-joins-hands-with-blockdaemon.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Two US Representatives Demand Crypto Tax Regulations, Atomic Wallet Stolen Funds Traced to N.Korean Hackers, OKX Partners with Custody Service Provider Komainu, Zodia Custody Joins Hands with Blockdaemon&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>USA</category><category>CFTC</category><category>CBOE</category><category>Tax</category><category>Treasury</category><category>IRS</category><category>Security</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Hack</category><category>North Korea</category><category>OKX</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Investment</category><category>Binance</category><category>Career</category><category>Staking</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-two-us-representatives-demand-crypto-tax-regulations-atomic-wallet-stolen-funds-traced-to-nkorean-hackers-okx-partners-with-custody-service-provider-komainu-zodia-custody-joins-hands-with-blockdaemon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116023/311703/adobestock-unshu-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="126274"/></item><item><title>SEC Chair Gary Gensler Calls for Crypto Firms To Register Following Binance, Coinbase Charges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-calls-for-crypto-firms-register-following-binance-coinbase-charges.htm</link><description>Conversations with crypto firms have been constructive, but they also need to be compliant with securities laws, said US Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler. &lt;br /&gt;
Gensler spoke to CNBC Squawk Box on Tuesday morning, a mere hour or so after the agency announced charges against the largest US based crypto exchange Coinbase.  &lt;br /&gt;
Gensler was asked about conversations the agency had with Coinbase before the complaint was filed. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-calls-for-crypto-firms-register-following-binance-coinbase-charges.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Chair Gary Gensler Calls for Crypto Firms To Register Following Binance, Coinbase Charges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-chair-gary-gensler-calls-for-crypto-firms-register-following-binance-coinbase-charges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116056/311734/chair-gary-gensler-01-2022.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="46920"/></item><item><title>Harsh Rajat, Co-Founder of Push Protocol, on Creating a Web3 Communication Network, and AI | Ep. 236</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/harsh-rajat-co-founder-of-push-protocol-on-creating-a-web3-communication-network-and-ai-ep-236.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Harsh Rajat, Co-Founder &amp; Project Lead of Push Protocol, talks about centralized communication platforms, native communication between wallets, and creating a web3 communication network....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/harsh-rajat-co-founder-of-push-protocol-on-creating-a-web3-communication-network-and-ai-ep-236.htm"&gt;Read More: Harsh Rajat, Co-Founder of Push Protocol, on Creating a Web3 Communication Network, and AI | Ep. 236&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/harsh-rajat-co-founder-of-push-protocol-on-creating-a-web3-communication-network-and-ai-ep-236.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116048/311714/harsh-rajat-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="134715"/></item><item><title>The Rise of Cryptocurrencies in Arab Countries: Understanding Saudi Arabia's Latest Move</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-of-cryptocurrencies-arab-countries-understanding-saudi-arabias-latest-move.htm</link><description>With cryptocurrencies increasingly gaining a foothold across the Arab world, some industry analysts are examining how Saudi Arabia’s plan to join China’s New Development Bank, also known as the BRICS bank, could impact on diversifying the kingdom’s financial environment. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-of-cryptocurrencies-arab-countries-understanding-saudi-arabias-latest-move.htm"&gt;Read More: The Rise of Cryptocurrencies in Arab Countries: Understanding Saudi Arabia's Latest Move&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Saudi Arabia</category><category>BRICS</category><category>NDB</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rise-of-cryptocurrencies-arab-countries-understanding-saudi-arabias-latest-move.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116041/311708/263e19fdf3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="30756"/></item><item><title>Coinbase COIN Stock Drops 10% Following SEC's Lawsuit Against Binance</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-coin-stock-drops-10-following-secs-lawsuit-against-binance.htm</link><description>Shares of major US-based cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase plunged 10% after the US Securities and Exchange Commission announced charges against Binance and its founder Changpeng Zhao. &lt;br /&gt;
Coinbase stock ended the last trading day on Monday trading at $58.71, down by 9.05%, according to data by Yahoo Finance. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-coin-stock-drops-10-following-secs-lawsuit-against-binance.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase COIN Stock Drops 10% Following SEC's Lawsuit Against Binance&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-coin-stock-drops-10-following-secs-lawsuit-against-binance.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116032/311705/coinbase-media-library-or.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="189673"/></item></channel></rss>
