<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:26:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Cloud Joins Chainlink As Node Operator]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/coinbase-cloud-joins-chainlink-as-node-operator</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-cloud-x-chainlink-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-cloud-x-chainlink-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-cloud-x-chainlink-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/coinbase-cloud-joins-chainlink-as-node-operator</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud, the crypto exchange's cloud services arm, recently announced a partnership with Chainlink Network to expand its presence in the decentralized sphere.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As part of the collaboration, Coinbase Cloud will serve as a node operator, contributing its extensive experience and infrastructure to the Chainlink Network. This strategic partnership is expected to boost the multi-chain ecosystem by delivering high-quality data for Web3 applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Chainlink Network is renowned as a leading oracle solution and Web3 services platform. It forms a crucial bridge between blockchain-based smart contracts and external data and systems, seamlessly connecting the evolving Web3 and the traditional Web2 worlds. Chainlink's decentralized oracle networks (DONs) source, format, and deliver real-world data to smart contracts, thereby significantly enhancing the transparency and efficiency of on-chain economies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To date, the Chainlink Network has been a key enabler of a significant amount of economic activity, with over $7T in transaction value facilitated and more than 7.4 billion data points delivered on-chain. The services offered by Chainlink are broad-ranging and include Price Feeds, VRF, Proof of Reserve, Automation, Functions, and CCIP. By deciding to join as a node operator, Coinbase Cloud is poised to contribute towards maintaining the security and reliability of these services provided by Chainlink.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud is a secure and robust blockchain infrastructure platform that empowers developers with the necessary tools and services to create, deploy, and scale their blockchain applications. The platform offers a vast range of features. It provides staking services for individual investors, enterprises, and institutions, facilitating users to earn rewards for offering security and services to Proof of Stake networks. The platform's Wallet as a Service (WaaS) is a turnkey solution for building and managing secure crypto wallets, featuring essential components like key management, hot/cold storage, and multi-factor authentication. Developers also have access to the Coinbase Pay SDK, simplifying the integration of crypto payments into their applications and supporting a broad array of cryptocurrencies and payment methods.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud also offers a scalable Node solution for running nodes on various blockchain networks, a crucial element for participation in these networks. It also includes Coinbase Commerce, a payment solution facilitating businesses to accept crypto payments, characterized by easy setup, fraud and chargeback protection, and reporting features. On the infrastructure side, Coinbase also operates Base, a comprehensive developer platform, grants developers access to Coinbase's APIs, documentation, and support, making it an invaluable resource for both seasoned developers and those just starting out with Coinbase Cloud. Backed by Coinbase's extensive expertise and experience in the blockchain sector, Coinbase Cloud serves as a robust platform for developing and deploying secure and dependable blockchain applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The crypto exchange's cloud services division will move to launch a Chainlink node to leverage its robust multi-region, multi-cloud infrastructure. It brings to the table its substantial background in managing blockchain data for high-throughput networks, including Aptos, Solana, Ethereum, Algorand, and Flow. This also means that such a collaboration will benefit from Coinbase Cloud's enterprise-grade security, which will help maintain the quality and reliability of the data provided.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kai Zhao, Group Product Manager at Coinbase Cloud, shares:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[through the process of] building decentralized Oracles, we are helping to create a more decentralized and trustworthy future for blockchain technology. We believe onchain is the next online, and we look forward to working with Chainlink to further this future."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Echoing the enthusiasm, William Reilly, Global Head of CeFi, Sales &amp; Strategy at Chainlink Labs, notes that Coinbase Cloud's "extensive experience, robust infrastructure, and commitment to security" are compelling factors that "make [Coinbase Cloud] an invaluable addition to the Chainlink ecosystem."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This partnership represents a substantial development in the Web3 and blockchain industry. With Coinbase Cloud's extensive infrastructure and Chainlink's oracle solution coming together, the provision of high-quality data for Web3 applications is set to improve. This move can be seen as part of a broader trend towards promoting further decentralization and enhancing the integrity of the blockchain industry. The two firms previously collaborated to work on an integration for off-chain feeds.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud, the crypto exchange's cloud services arm, recently announced a partnership with Chainlink Network to expand its presence in the decentralized sphere.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As part of the collaboration, Coinbase Cloud will serve as a node operator, contributing its extensive experience and infrastructure to the Chainlink Network. This strategic partnership is expected to boost the multi-chain ecosystem by delivering high-quality data for Web3 applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Chainlink Network is renowned as a leading oracle solution and Web3 services platform. It forms a crucial bridge between blockchain-based smart contracts and external data and systems, seamlessly connecting the evolving Web3 and the traditional Web2 worlds. Chainlink's decentralized oracle networks (DONs) source, format, and deliver real-world data to smart contracts, thereby significantly enhancing the transparency and efficiency of on-chain economies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">To date, the Chainlink Network has been a key enabler of a significant amount of economic activity, with over $7T in transaction value facilitated and more than 7.4 billion data points delivered on-chain. The services offered by Chainlink are broad-ranging and include Price Feeds, VRF, Proof of Reserve, Automation, Functions, and CCIP. By deciding to join as a node operator, Coinbase Cloud is poised to contribute towards maintaining the security and reliability of these services provided by Chainlink.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud is a secure and robust blockchain infrastructure platform that empowers developers with the necessary tools and services to create, deploy, and scale their blockchain applications. The platform offers a vast range of features. It provides staking services for individual investors, enterprises, and institutions, facilitating users to earn rewards for offering security and services to Proof of Stake networks. The platform's Wallet as a Service (WaaS) is a turnkey solution for building and managing secure crypto wallets, featuring essential components like key management, hot/cold storage, and multi-factor authentication. Developers also have access to the Coinbase Pay SDK, simplifying the integration of crypto payments into their applications and supporting a broad array of cryptocurrencies and payment methods.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Cloud also offers a scalable Node solution for running nodes on various blockchain networks, a crucial element for participation in these networks. It also includes Coinbase Commerce, a payment solution facilitating businesses to accept crypto payments, characterized by easy setup, fraud and chargeback protection, and reporting features. On the infrastructure side, Coinbase also operates Base, a comprehensive developer platform, grants developers access to Coinbase's APIs, documentation, and support, making it an invaluable resource for both seasoned developers and those just starting out with Coinbase Cloud. Backed by Coinbase's extensive expertise and experience in the blockchain sector, Coinbase Cloud serves as a robust platform for developing and deploying secure and dependable blockchain applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The crypto exchange's cloud services division will move to launch a Chainlink node to leverage its robust multi-region, multi-cloud infrastructure. It brings to the table its substantial background in managing blockchain data for high-throughput networks, including Aptos, Solana, Ethereum, Algorand, and Flow. This also means that such a collaboration will benefit from Coinbase Cloud's enterprise-grade security, which will help maintain the quality and reliability of the data provided.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kai Zhao, Group Product Manager at Coinbase Cloud, shares:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[through the process of] building decentralized Oracles, we are helping to create a more decentralized and trustworthy future for blockchain technology. We believe onchain is the next online, and we look forward to working with Chainlink to further this future."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Echoing the enthusiasm, William Reilly, Global Head of CeFi, Sales &amp; Strategy at Chainlink Labs, notes that Coinbase Cloud's "extensive experience, robust infrastructure, and commitment to security" are compelling factors that "make [Coinbase Cloud] an invaluable addition to the Chainlink ecosystem."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This partnership represents a substantial development in the Web3 and blockchain industry. With Coinbase Cloud's extensive infrastructure and Chainlink's oracle solution coming together, the provision of high-quality data for Web3 applications is set to improve. This move can be seen as part of a broader trend towards promoting further decentralization and enhancing the integrity of the blockchain industry. The two firms previously collaborated to work on an integration for off-chain feeds.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Receive 100% Rewards with DogeMiyagi, Binance Coin and Polkadot!]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/receive-100-rewards-with-dogemiyagi-binance-coin-and-polkadot</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-76.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-76.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-76.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 01:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/receive-100-rewards-with-dogemiyagi-binance-coin-and-polkadot</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the world of cryptocurrencies, staking has emerged as a compelling way to receive more tokens while securing the blockchain network. DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI), Binance Coin (BNB), and Polkadot (DOT) are among the tokens that offer staking programs with enticing benefits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By actively participating in these programs, users have the opportunity to earn commissions on token purchases in MIYAGI, enjoy a 3.5% APY with BNB, and delve into the dynamic Polkadot staking system. These opportunities provide a pathway for users to engage with the crypto ecosystem and capitalize on the potential rewards of staking.</p>
<p>The New Presale Meme Coin Fostering Growth Through Referrals!</p>
<p>The DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) team has recently unveiled their plans for an upcoming Token Referral Program&mdash;a new initiative aimed at rewarding community members for their active involvement. This captivating program allows users to connect their wallets and generate unique referral codes, which they can then share with friends, family, and digital acquaintances.</p>
<p>By using these codes, individuals can earn a generous 10% commission on every purchase of MIYAGI tokens, effectively acknowledging their contributions. This straightforward opportunity not only allows users to bolster their MIYAGI holdings but also plays a role in driving the overall success of the token's ecosystem.</p>
<p>BNB Offers Stakers a 3.5% APY!&nbsp;</p>
<p>Supporting the Binance blockchain network with their staked BNB, users not only play a crucial role in fortifying the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) network's security but also enjoy the benefits of a 3.5% APY. By loaning their tokens to the exchange, users enable the network to validate transactions tirelessly, fuel decentralized governance, and enhance overall robustness.</p>
<p>In return for their trust, stakers are handsomely rewarded with tokens, serving as an enticing incentive to keep their tokens staked for the long haul. The beauty of staking BNB lies in the myriad variations and possibilities it offers, each presenting a unique twist to this clever game.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Discovering the Dynamic Realm of Polkadot</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT), a sophisticated NPoS blockchain, relies on these validators to verify transactions and safeguard its network. With a more distributed and decentralized network, the chances of successful attacks by hackers are greatly reduced!</p>
<p>DOT holders have a variety of ways to engage with the Polkadot staking system. Whether you join a nomination pool to share rewards and penalties, become a nominator to handpick reliable validators, or even run your own nomination pool with competent validators, the options are plenty. And if you simply want to stake your cryptocurrency and join in on the action, that's an option too.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Staking in the world of cryptocurrencies offers a great opportunity to unlock rewards and enhance holdings. DogeMiyagi, Binance Coin, and Polkadot stand out as tokens that provide enticing staking programs with unique benefits. By actively participating in these programs, users can earn an incredible selection of high-value commissions. These avenues not only allow users to capitalize on the potential rewards but also contribute to the growth and success of the respective ecosystems.</p>
<p>For More Information on DogeMiyagi, Click the Links Below!</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of cryptocurrencies, staking has emerged as a compelling way to receive more tokens while securing the blockchain network. DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI), Binance Coin (BNB), and Polkadot (DOT) are among the tokens that offer staking programs with enticing benefits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By actively participating in these programs, users have the opportunity to earn commissions on token purchases in MIYAGI, enjoy a 3.5% APY with BNB, and delve into the dynamic Polkadot staking system. These opportunities provide a pathway for users to engage with the crypto ecosystem and capitalize on the potential rewards of staking.</p>
<p>The New Presale Meme Coin Fostering Growth Through Referrals!</p>
<p>The DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) team has recently unveiled their plans for an upcoming Token Referral Program&mdash;a new initiative aimed at rewarding community members for their active involvement. This captivating program allows users to connect their wallets and generate unique referral codes, which they can then share with friends, family, and digital acquaintances.</p>
<p>By using these codes, individuals can earn a generous 10% commission on every purchase of MIYAGI tokens, effectively acknowledging their contributions. This straightforward opportunity not only allows users to bolster their MIYAGI holdings but also plays a role in driving the overall success of the token's ecosystem.</p>
<p>BNB Offers Stakers a 3.5% APY!&nbsp;</p>
<p>Supporting the Binance blockchain network with their staked BNB, users not only play a crucial role in fortifying the Proof-of-Stake (PoS) network's security but also enjoy the benefits of a 3.5% APY. By loaning their tokens to the exchange, users enable the network to validate transactions tirelessly, fuel decentralized governance, and enhance overall robustness.</p>
<p>In return for their trust, stakers are handsomely rewarded with tokens, serving as an enticing incentive to keep their tokens staked for the long haul. The beauty of staking BNB lies in the myriad variations and possibilities it offers, each presenting a unique twist to this clever game.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Discovering the Dynamic Realm of Polkadot</p>
<p>Polkadot (DOT), a sophisticated NPoS blockchain, relies on these validators to verify transactions and safeguard its network. With a more distributed and decentralized network, the chances of successful attacks by hackers are greatly reduced!</p>
<p>DOT holders have a variety of ways to engage with the Polkadot staking system. Whether you join a nomination pool to share rewards and penalties, become a nominator to handpick reliable validators, or even run your own nomination pool with competent validators, the options are plenty. And if you simply want to stake your cryptocurrency and join in on the action, that's an option too.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Staking in the world of cryptocurrencies offers a great opportunity to unlock rewards and enhance holdings. DogeMiyagi, Binance Coin, and Polkadot stand out as tokens that provide enticing staking programs with unique benefits. By actively participating in these programs, users can earn an incredible selection of high-value commissions. These avenues not only allow users to capitalize on the potential rewards but also contribute to the growth and success of the respective ecosystems.</p>
<p>For More Information on DogeMiyagi, Click the Links Below!</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Get Ready To Gamble With Big Eyes Coin's Casino: Exclusively For BIG Token Holders]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/get-ready-to-gamble-with-big-eyes-coins-casino-exclusively-for-big-token-holders</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-593.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-593.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-593.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 01:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/get-ready-to-gamble-with-big-eyes-coins-casino-exclusively-for-big-token-holders</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Are you a cat lover and a crypto enthusiast? Look no further than Big Eyes Coin (BIG) - the first and only cat-themed meme coin in the market, launched by the BIG team in late 2022. With its unique feline-inspired design and innovative features, Big Eyes Coin offers a perfect investment opportunity for those looking to join the cat crew and potentially earn a significant amount of money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Purrfect Opportunity for Cat Lovers</p>
<p>With big sparkling eyes, Big Eyes Coin hit the crypto presale market on 20th August 2022. The excitement surrounding its native currency, BIG, has been palpable in the crypto world for the past 8 months. To date, Big Eyes Coin has completed 12 stages of presale and raised more than $35.5 million. In the current 13th stage, a BIG token costs $0.00053, which is a remarkable increase of over 400% from its initial stage.</p>
<p>But the excitement doesn't stop there. The Big Eyes Coin team has recently issued Loot Boxes at varying affordable prices. These boxes contain BIG tokens worth up to $1 million and unique NFT cards that can be minted and traded. The distinctive feature of these loot boxes is that they are designed in a way not to cause any financial loss to the investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the Big Eyes Coin presale is quickly approaching its end on June 3rd, the team has announced a 300% bonus to investors who use the END300 code, further enhancing the deal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Roadmap to Success&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recently, the project team made a BIG announcement revealing the launch date of the BIG tokens. According to that, the BIG tokens will be launched on the Uniswap crypto exchange platform on June 15. Additionally, the BIG team has plans to list the tokens on 13 other exchanges to increase the accessibility and visibility of the BIG tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Casino With 4000+ Games&nbsp;</p>
<p>To drive up excitement before the launch on June 15, the BIG team has announced the launch of a casino with more than 4,000 games. The Casino will become fully operational on 29th August and feature exclusive Play to Earn (P2E) games. Participation in the gaming and betting services will be limited to BIG token holders, which is expected to drive demand for and increase the value of the BIG Eyes Coin post-launch.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Big Eyes Coin team plans to expand its presence beyond cryptocurrencies by developing innovative and exclusive NFTs. The BIG team has outlined plans for the creation of Spurr Store, which will enable users to buy and sell digital assets, helping to make Big Eyes Coin a top virtual marketplace.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Success Mantra&nbsp;</p>
<p>The success of Big Eyes Coin can be attributed to the unwavering support of its community, which has been a top priority for the team from the beginning of the project.&nbsp; By involving the community in the development and promotion of the project, the team has been able to create a strong and loyal following. To achieve this, Big Eyes Coin has hosted 17 games and gifted valuable prizes to its community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The team has also pledged 5% of its total supply to save the oceans and has already donated nearly $16,000 to charities, demonstrating its social responsibility. Last but not least, to retain this hard-earned loyal community, the Big Eyes Coin team is using a no-fee, no-tax policy policy approach.</p>
<p>Therefore, if you are looking for a business opportunity where you can invest less and earn a significant amount of money, then Big Eyes Coin is an ideal option for you.</p>
<p>Click the links below to know more about Big Eyes Coin (BIG) and its six-month Exchange Roadmap here:&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL&nbsp;</p>
<p>OpenSea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you a cat lover and a crypto enthusiast? Look no further than Big Eyes Coin (BIG) - the first and only cat-themed meme coin in the market, launched by the BIG team in late 2022. With its unique feline-inspired design and innovative features, Big Eyes Coin offers a perfect investment opportunity for those looking to join the cat crew and potentially earn a significant amount of money.&nbsp;</p>
<p>A Purrfect Opportunity for Cat Lovers</p>
<p>With big sparkling eyes, Big Eyes Coin hit the crypto presale market on 20th August 2022. The excitement surrounding its native currency, BIG, has been palpable in the crypto world for the past 8 months. To date, Big Eyes Coin has completed 12 stages of presale and raised more than $35.5 million. In the current 13th stage, a BIG token costs $0.00053, which is a remarkable increase of over 400% from its initial stage.</p>
<p>But the excitement doesn't stop there. The Big Eyes Coin team has recently issued Loot Boxes at varying affordable prices. These boxes contain BIG tokens worth up to $1 million and unique NFT cards that can be minted and traded. The distinctive feature of these loot boxes is that they are designed in a way not to cause any financial loss to the investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As the Big Eyes Coin presale is quickly approaching its end on June 3rd, the team has announced a 300% bonus to investors who use the END300 code, further enhancing the deal.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Roadmap to Success&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recently, the project team made a BIG announcement revealing the launch date of the BIG tokens. According to that, the BIG tokens will be launched on the Uniswap crypto exchange platform on June 15. Additionally, the BIG team has plans to list the tokens on 13 other exchanges to increase the accessibility and visibility of the BIG tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Casino With 4000+ Games&nbsp;</p>
<p>To drive up excitement before the launch on June 15, the BIG team has announced the launch of a casino with more than 4,000 games. The Casino will become fully operational on 29th August and feature exclusive Play to Earn (P2E) games. Participation in the gaming and betting services will be limited to BIG token holders, which is expected to drive demand for and increase the value of the BIG Eyes Coin post-launch.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the Big Eyes Coin team plans to expand its presence beyond cryptocurrencies by developing innovative and exclusive NFTs. The BIG team has outlined plans for the creation of Spurr Store, which will enable users to buy and sell digital assets, helping to make Big Eyes Coin a top virtual marketplace.</p>
<p></p>
<p>The Success Mantra&nbsp;</p>
<p>The success of Big Eyes Coin can be attributed to the unwavering support of its community, which has been a top priority for the team from the beginning of the project.&nbsp; By involving the community in the development and promotion of the project, the team has been able to create a strong and loyal following. To achieve this, Big Eyes Coin has hosted 17 games and gifted valuable prizes to its community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The team has also pledged 5% of its total supply to save the oceans and has already donated nearly $16,000 to charities, demonstrating its social responsibility. Last but not least, to retain this hard-earned loyal community, the Big Eyes Coin team is using a no-fee, no-tax policy policy approach.</p>
<p>Therefore, if you are looking for a business opportunity where you can invest less and earn a significant amount of money, then Big Eyes Coin is an ideal option for you.</p>
<p>Click the links below to know more about Big Eyes Coin (BIG) and its six-month Exchange Roadmap here:&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL&nbsp;</p>
<p>OpenSea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Seen Below 25974 - 19 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-seen-below-25974-19-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-may-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-may-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-17-may-2023-240-1920-1080-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-seen-below-25974-19-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Eye 26093:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 19 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained exposed to additional downside risk early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 26763.44 area, a retracement level associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 29850 area.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 26523.85 level during a pullback, representing the 61.8% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25810 to 27678.73.&nbsp; Stops were also recently elected below the 26886.35 level during the depreciation, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that strengthened around the 27295 area.&nbsp; Following recent selling pressure, related downside price objectives include the 26396, 26308, 26093, 25885, and 25604 levels.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives related to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27158.01 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27035.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bears Eye 26093:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 19 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained exposed to additional downside risk early in the Asian session as the pair continued to orbit the 26763.44 area, a retracement level associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 29850 area.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 26523.85 level during a pullback, representing the 61.8% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25810 to 27678.73.&nbsp; Stops were also recently elected below the 26886.35 level during the depreciation, a downside price objective linked to selling pressure that strengthened around the 27295 area.&nbsp; Following recent selling pressure, related downside price objectives include the 26396, 26308, 26093, 25885, and 25604 levels.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives related to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27158.01 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27035.23.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[New Meme Kings : TOADS and PEPE look to end the dominance of DOGE and SHIB]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/new-meme-kings-toads-and-pepe-look-to-end-the-dominance-of-doge-and-shib</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153734.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153734.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153734.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/new-meme-kings-toads-and-pepe-look-to-end-the-dominance-of-doge-and-shib</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto markets operate remarkably differently from mainstream financial markets. On the one hand, coins like Bitcoin have serious underpinning in seeking to decentralize the global financial system and whatnot. On the other hand, memecoins operate as literal jokes that utilize internet meme popularity. Well, at least that was the case for the first one to break out, DogeCoin. </p>
<p>Due to Dogecoin's success, many memecoins have emerged with varying degrees of success. DigiToads (TOADS) and Pepe token are new entrants to the scene, fast getting on the radar of crypto enthusiasts. The fact that there are now multiple memecoin options also speaks volumes about the dynamism of this industry. </p>
<p>DigiToads and PEPE Are Dominating</p>
<p>These memecoins are different standard-bearers of this subsector. DigiToads seeks to add utility to the memecoin scene by operating as a play-to-earn (P2E) gaming token. The game revolves around a nature-themed metaverse swamp that is full of adventure. DigiToads has only recently launched its token sale and has already raised over $3.2 million.</p>
<p>A metaverse gaming ecosystem adds more dynamism to the concept of a memecoin. In line with the name, the game is based on toad avatars as they seek to battle for their precious swamp habitat. The project also has NFT collectibles to tap into another popular aspect of crypto gaming. These in-game collectibles increase engagement and can be collected as players navigate the game and nurture their toads.</p>
<p>The Pepe the Frog meme is one of the most famous memes online, especially in right wing circles. It features a picture of a frog that is sometimes skeptical or nonchalant, with different meme inscriptions on the image. Well, there is now a Pepecoin inspired by this famous token, and it is quickly gaining traction in cryptocurrency circles. </p>
<p>DigiToads is keen on building its utility aspect as compared to other memecoins. There is much to work with in the gaming sector, where the blockchain has yet to achieve its potential fully. By combining the hype of a memecoin and the enduring popularity of a quality game, its creators are looking to build a more stable platform.</p>
<p>The fact that these projects, based on funny-looking amphibians, are now some of the most popular memecoins speaks to the dynamism of this sector. Memecoin popularity is based on the notoriety of memes in popular culture. It is noteworthy that DigiToads is trying to implement a virtual metaverse gaming ecosystem over and above its memecoin essence. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>DOGE Rose But TOADS Has More Upsides</p>
<p>Memecoins take inspiration from internet memes and the viral humor they carry. Amid Bitcoin's rise as a scarce transformative asset with solid principles, Dogecoin was more of a parody coin whose creators had little intention of having it as a major cryptocurrency. A decade later, Dogecoin and other meme coins are an established component of the crypto sector, with several coins with a combined market capitalization of hundreds of billions of dollars. </p>
<p>The astronomical rise of Dogecoin came after a seemingly humorous tweet by Elon Musk in 2019 and several times in the next few years. Musk already had tens of millions of followers on Twitter with significant name recognition on Twitter. He would use phrases like 'one word: Doge' or post the Dogecoin logo, a Shiba Inu dog, as an unstoppable sandstorm. Without a doubt, Elon's promotional activity has been a focal point in Dogecoin's popularity. </p>
<p>Crypto enthusiasts carried the joke, and Dogecoin soon became one of the most popular cryptocurrencies out there. The coin appreciated more than 1000% in the middle of a crypto rally of 2020-2021 before tapering off. Shiba Inu coin piggybacked on the popularity of Dogecoin, and the two have since become the notable memecoins of this crypto era. Shiba </p>
<p>Nowadays, a memecoin refers to coins that fall under the broad umbrella of projects with a humorous or fun tinge. Many projects with the memecoin label have serious development teams behind them. &nbsp;DigiToads is an example of this approach by building on what DogeCoin and SHIB achieved but with the advantage of utility. DOGE may still be the biggest stablecoin, but TOADS could have more upside, given its actual use cases. </p>
<p>TOADS: The Upcoming Meme King? </p>
<p>The role of memecoins in the cryptocurrency industry is mixed. Some look at them as a hilarious spin on established crypto names like Bitcoin and Ethereum. For memecoin traders, they represent legitimate investment opportunities. Famous personalities like Elon Musk can instantly change the price of a memecoin with a tweet. </p>
<p>Some memecoins have tried to strike a balance between the two polar ends of crypto development. That's where the likes of TOADS come in. TOADS is a memecoin but provides the utility of a P2E gaming token with a vibrant gaming ecosystem in tow. The beauty of this industry is that it has something for just about everyone. </p>
<p class="s14">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto markets operate remarkably differently from mainstream financial markets. On the one hand, coins like Bitcoin have serious underpinning in seeking to decentralize the global financial system and whatnot. On the other hand, memecoins operate as literal jokes that utilize internet meme popularity. Well, at least that was the case for the first one to break out, DogeCoin. </p>
<p>Due to Dogecoin's success, many memecoins have emerged with varying degrees of success. DigiToads (TOADS) and Pepe token are new entrants to the scene, fast getting on the radar of crypto enthusiasts. The fact that there are now multiple memecoin options also speaks volumes about the dynamism of this industry. </p>
<p>DigiToads and PEPE Are Dominating</p>
<p>These memecoins are different standard-bearers of this subsector. DigiToads seeks to add utility to the memecoin scene by operating as a play-to-earn (P2E) gaming token. The game revolves around a nature-themed metaverse swamp that is full of adventure. DigiToads has only recently launched its token sale and has already raised over $3.2 million.</p>
<p>A metaverse gaming ecosystem adds more dynamism to the concept of a memecoin. In line with the name, the game is based on toad avatars as they seek to battle for their precious swamp habitat. The project also has NFT collectibles to tap into another popular aspect of crypto gaming. These in-game collectibles increase engagement and can be collected as players navigate the game and nurture their toads.</p>
<p>The Pepe the Frog meme is one of the most famous memes online, especially in right wing circles. It features a picture of a frog that is sometimes skeptical or nonchalant, with different meme inscriptions on the image. Well, there is now a Pepecoin inspired by this famous token, and it is quickly gaining traction in cryptocurrency circles. </p>
<p>DigiToads is keen on building its utility aspect as compared to other memecoins. There is much to work with in the gaming sector, where the blockchain has yet to achieve its potential fully. By combining the hype of a memecoin and the enduring popularity of a quality game, its creators are looking to build a more stable platform.</p>
<p>The fact that these projects, based on funny-looking amphibians, are now some of the most popular memecoins speaks to the dynamism of this sector. Memecoin popularity is based on the notoriety of memes in popular culture. It is noteworthy that DigiToads is trying to implement a virtual metaverse gaming ecosystem over and above its memecoin essence. </p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>DOGE Rose But TOADS Has More Upsides</p>
<p>Memecoins take inspiration from internet memes and the viral humor they carry. Amid Bitcoin's rise as a scarce transformative asset with solid principles, Dogecoin was more of a parody coin whose creators had little intention of having it as a major cryptocurrency. A decade later, Dogecoin and other meme coins are an established component of the crypto sector, with several coins with a combined market capitalization of hundreds of billions of dollars. </p>
<p>The astronomical rise of Dogecoin came after a seemingly humorous tweet by Elon Musk in 2019 and several times in the next few years. Musk already had tens of millions of followers on Twitter with significant name recognition on Twitter. He would use phrases like 'one word: Doge' or post the Dogecoin logo, a Shiba Inu dog, as an unstoppable sandstorm. Without a doubt, Elon's promotional activity has been a focal point in Dogecoin's popularity. </p>
<p>Crypto enthusiasts carried the joke, and Dogecoin soon became one of the most popular cryptocurrencies out there. The coin appreciated more than 1000% in the middle of a crypto rally of 2020-2021 before tapering off. Shiba Inu coin piggybacked on the popularity of Dogecoin, and the two have since become the notable memecoins of this crypto era. Shiba </p>
<p>Nowadays, a memecoin refers to coins that fall under the broad umbrella of projects with a humorous or fun tinge. Many projects with the memecoin label have serious development teams behind them. &nbsp;DigiToads is an example of this approach by building on what DogeCoin and SHIB achieved but with the advantage of utility. DOGE may still be the biggest stablecoin, but TOADS could have more upside, given its actual use cases. </p>
<p>TOADS: The Upcoming Meme King? </p>
<p>The role of memecoins in the cryptocurrency industry is mixed. Some look at them as a hilarious spin on established crypto names like Bitcoin and Ethereum. For memecoin traders, they represent legitimate investment opportunities. Famous personalities like Elon Musk can instantly change the price of a memecoin with a tweet. </p>
<p>Some memecoins have tried to strike a balance between the two polar ends of crypto development. That's where the likes of TOADS come in. TOADS is a memecoin but provides the utility of a P2E gaming token with a vibrant gaming ecosystem in tow. The beauty of this industry is that it has something for just about everyone. </p>
<p class="s14">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sparklo (SPRK): Ignites The Future Of Investments, Leaving Unus Sed Leo (LEO) And Stellar (XLM) At Bay]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-ignites-the-future-of-investments-leaving-unus-sed-leo-leo-and-stellar-xlm-at-bay</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153517.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153517.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-153517.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-ignites-the-future-of-investments-leaving-unus-sed-leo-leo-and-stellar-xlm-at-bay</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The realm of digital currency is a thrilling landscape, as it is constantly transforming and brimming with fresh innovators presenting novel solutions. The spotlight has recently been directed toward a groundbreaking project called - Sparklo.</p>
<p>Utilizing blockchain technology and NFTs in an imaginative way, Sparklo is poised to become the platform of countless enthusiasts. While esteemed cryptocurrencies such as Unus Sed Leo (LEO) and Stellar (XLM) are facing bullish resistance and staggering stability.</p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo (SPRK): unleashing the power of precious metals for new investors</p>
<p>Sparklo presents a groundbreaking alternative-investment platform that's set to revolutionize the way we trade and invest in precious metals. With Sparklo, anyone can now easily access and invest in the timeless allure of gold, silver and platinum through fractional or whole investments in NFTs. </p>
<p>As Sparklo enters its second presale phase ending, the opportunity to join this golden revolution is now more enticing than ever. Secure your Sparklo tokens at the incredible price of just $0.022per token. The Sparklo project also underwent an audit by the InterFi network and its liquidity will be locked for a total of 100 years. The team also completed their KYC verification, enhancing the overall trust and security within the project.</p>
<p>No more hassle of buying, storing, or exchanging precious metals, Sparklo brings together a global community of traders and investors. Breaking down various walls and unleashing a world of possibilities. Be part of the Sparklo movement, where accessibility, safety and cost-effectiveness merge to redefine the landscape of precious metal investments.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s7">Unus Sed Leo (LEO): embrace stability and slight profit potential in the crypto market</p>
<p>Unus Sed Leo (LEO) is making waves in the cryptocurrency market due to its low volatility and strong position against price manipulation. The Risk/Reward Gauge of Unus Sed Leo (LEO) indicates that the token has a relatively stable price, providing investors with a sense of security. Looking ahead, Unus Sed Leo (LEO) price is well-positioned with support near $3.48 and resistance set at $3.51. </p>
<p>This means that the token has room to grow before facing any significant selling pressure. Investors looking for stability, profit potential and a promising investment in the crypto market should consider adding Sparklo to their portfolio. While some investors may see Unus Sed Leo (LEO) as a promising investment option due to its unique features and current price positioning, it's important to consider the potential risks and downsides before jumping in.</p>
<p class="s7">Stellar (XLM) price hits roadblocks as bulls face resistance </p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) has been on an upward trajectory this year, 2023, with an impressive breakthrough in January that shattered a descending resistance line, signaling a potential end to the correction phase. The price of Stellar (XLM) surged toward the long-standing resistance level at an average of $0.105, raising hopes for a major breakout. </p>
<p>However, Stellar (XLM) faced strong opposition, leading to a bearish engulfing candlestick formation. This recent rejection has temporarily halted the ascent of the Stellar (XLM) price. As a lot of charts are showing bearish signs for Stellar (XLM), now is a good time to stay away from Stellar (XTM) as it shows bearish signs. </p>
<p class="s11">Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
 Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance
 Website: https://sparklo.finance
 Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance
 Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The realm of digital currency is a thrilling landscape, as it is constantly transforming and brimming with fresh innovators presenting novel solutions. The spotlight has recently been directed toward a groundbreaking project called - Sparklo.</p>
<p>Utilizing blockchain technology and NFTs in an imaginative way, Sparklo is poised to become the platform of countless enthusiasts. While esteemed cryptocurrencies such as Unus Sed Leo (LEO) and Stellar (XLM) are facing bullish resistance and staggering stability.</p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo (SPRK): unleashing the power of precious metals for new investors</p>
<p>Sparklo presents a groundbreaking alternative-investment platform that's set to revolutionize the way we trade and invest in precious metals. With Sparklo, anyone can now easily access and invest in the timeless allure of gold, silver and platinum through fractional or whole investments in NFTs. </p>
<p>As Sparklo enters its second presale phase ending, the opportunity to join this golden revolution is now more enticing than ever. Secure your Sparklo tokens at the incredible price of just $0.022per token. The Sparklo project also underwent an audit by the InterFi network and its liquidity will be locked for a total of 100 years. The team also completed their KYC verification, enhancing the overall trust and security within the project.</p>
<p>No more hassle of buying, storing, or exchanging precious metals, Sparklo brings together a global community of traders and investors. Breaking down various walls and unleashing a world of possibilities. Be part of the Sparklo movement, where accessibility, safety and cost-effectiveness merge to redefine the landscape of precious metal investments.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s7">Unus Sed Leo (LEO): embrace stability and slight profit potential in the crypto market</p>
<p>Unus Sed Leo (LEO) is making waves in the cryptocurrency market due to its low volatility and strong position against price manipulation. The Risk/Reward Gauge of Unus Sed Leo (LEO) indicates that the token has a relatively stable price, providing investors with a sense of security. Looking ahead, Unus Sed Leo (LEO) price is well-positioned with support near $3.48 and resistance set at $3.51. </p>
<p>This means that the token has room to grow before facing any significant selling pressure. Investors looking for stability, profit potential and a promising investment in the crypto market should consider adding Sparklo to their portfolio. While some investors may see Unus Sed Leo (LEO) as a promising investment option due to its unique features and current price positioning, it's important to consider the potential risks and downsides before jumping in.</p>
<p class="s7">Stellar (XLM) price hits roadblocks as bulls face resistance </p>
<p>Stellar (XLM) has been on an upward trajectory this year, 2023, with an impressive breakthrough in January that shattered a descending resistance line, signaling a potential end to the correction phase. The price of Stellar (XLM) surged toward the long-standing resistance level at an average of $0.105, raising hopes for a major breakout. </p>
<p>However, Stellar (XLM) faced strong opposition, leading to a bearish engulfing candlestick formation. This recent rejection has temporarily halted the ascent of the Stellar (XLM) price. As a lot of charts are showing bearish signs for Stellar (XLM), now is a good time to stay away from Stellar (XTM) as it shows bearish signs. </p>
<p class="s11">Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
 Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance
 Website: https://sparklo.finance
 Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance
 Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Signature Banks Demise Due to Crypto Exposure: FDIC Chair]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/signature-banks-demise-due-to-crypto-exposure-fdic-chair</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sig-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sig-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/sig-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/signature-banks-demise-due-to-crypto-exposure-fdic-chair</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Gruenberg, chairman of the FDIC, blamed Signature Bank&rsquo;s involvement in the crypto industry for its ultimate collapse. </p>
<p>In a recent speech before the House Committee on Financial Services, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) chairman blamed Signature Bank&rsquo;s reliance on uninsured deposits from the crypto industry and its exposure to the events that took place in 2022 for its demise.</p>
<p>Martin Gruenberg acknowledged the FDIC&rsquo;s bank supervision could have been more substantial. He conceded the agency did not act fast enough to prevent crisis from spreading through Signature&rsquo;s operations.</p>
<p>Chairman Gruenberg added that Signature&rsquo;s lack of risk management procedures and poor governance put the bank in a position where it could not manage liquidity in a crisis, making it unable to meet large withdrawal requests. Withdrawals were triggered by fears about Signature Bank&rsquo;s solvency and involvement in the volatile crypto sector.</p>
<p>Some bank executives tried to blame rising interest rates as the reason for its collapse, but Gruenberg argued that no bank could survive a run of such speed and magnitude.</p>
Signature&rsquo;s Closure Unrelated to Crypto: NYDFS
<p>In March, the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) announced that its decision to shut down the bank was not influenced by its involvement in the crypto industry. Signature worked extensively with several crypto firms, with an estimated 30% of its deposits originating from the industry.</p>
<p>Signature came under scrutiny during the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX when it emerged the exchange held accounts with the bank. At the time, Signature said these accounts represented less than 0.1% of its overall deposits, adding that it planned to reduce around $10 billion in deposits emanating from digital asset clients.</p>
<p>The bank said by reducing its ties with digital asset clients; it would bring its crypto-related deposits down to between 15-20% of its total.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Martin Gruenberg, chairman of the FDIC, blamed Signature Bank&rsquo;s involvement in the crypto industry for its ultimate collapse. </p>
<p>In a recent speech before the House Committee on Financial Services, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) chairman blamed Signature Bank&rsquo;s reliance on uninsured deposits from the crypto industry and its exposure to the events that took place in 2022 for its demise.</p>
<p>Martin Gruenberg acknowledged the FDIC&rsquo;s bank supervision could have been more substantial. He conceded the agency did not act fast enough to prevent crisis from spreading through Signature&rsquo;s operations.</p>
<p>Chairman Gruenberg added that Signature&rsquo;s lack of risk management procedures and poor governance put the bank in a position where it could not manage liquidity in a crisis, making it unable to meet large withdrawal requests. Withdrawals were triggered by fears about Signature Bank&rsquo;s solvency and involvement in the volatile crypto sector.</p>
<p>Some bank executives tried to blame rising interest rates as the reason for its collapse, but Gruenberg argued that no bank could survive a run of such speed and magnitude.</p>
Signature&rsquo;s Closure Unrelated to Crypto: NYDFS
<p>In March, the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) announced that its decision to shut down the bank was not influenced by its involvement in the crypto industry. Signature worked extensively with several crypto firms, with an estimated 30% of its deposits originating from the industry.</p>
<p>Signature came under scrutiny during the collapse of the crypto exchange FTX when it emerged the exchange held accounts with the bank. At the time, Signature said these accounts represented less than 0.1% of its overall deposits, adding that it planned to reduce around $10 billion in deposits emanating from digital asset clients.</p>
<p>The bank said by reducing its ties with digital asset clients; it would bring its crypto-related deposits down to between 15-20% of its total.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Hosts Global Celebrations in Honor of  Bitcoin Pizza Day]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-hosts-global-celebrations-in-honor-of-bitcoin-pizza-day</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-18_12-51-36_1684415752Es1SOfD0Eo.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-18_12-51-36_1684415752Es1SOfD0Eo.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-18_12-51-36_1684415752Es1SOfD0Eo.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:30:53 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/binance-hosts-global-celebrations-in-honor-of-bitcoin-pizza-day</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">From Binance-style super meet-ups to online contests, the crypto exchange is celebrating Bitcoin&rsquo;s famous first purchase</p><p>Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, is celebrating the thirteenth anniversary of Bitcoin Pizza Day, the historic day in 2010 that a purchase of two pizzas was made in return for 10,000 BTC.</p><p>To celebrate this monumental day in crypto and the revolution it marks for the industry, Binance will be hosting in-person community meet-ups around the world. The celebrations will kick off in the birthplace of pizza, Naples, Italy, on May 21 and continue with local pizzeria and pizza van takeovers in ten countries, including Brazil, Bahrain, Pakistan, Vietnam, Sri Lanka, Cambodia, Uruguay, Mexico, Argentina, and New Zealand.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>The community is also invited to celebrate Pizza Day on social media and the Binance app. Participants who share their Binance-themed pizzas using #BinancePizza or complete tasks to collect all the Pizza Flavours on the Binance app have a chance to win the crypto equivalent of a year&amp;apos;s supply of pizza. Online celebrations will continue as Binance hosts a virtual live meet-up&nbsp;with the attendance of CZ on May 22 at 12:00 PM UTC, featuring discussions on the meaning of Bitcoin Pizza Day with prominent Binance Feed creators.</p><p>"Bitcoin Pizza Day is a testament to the power of community and the growing acceptance of BTC as part of our daily lives," said Yi He, Binance co-founder and Chief Marketing Officer. "At Binance, we believe in the importance of mass adoption, and we are committed to creating more and more use cases for crypto in everyday situations. As more people recognize the value and potential of blockchain and crypto, our community grows stronger, and we continue to build our industry."</p><p>The global Pizza Day meet-ups will offer fun activities with the chance to win swag and rewards, and of course, free pizza. Events vary by city, for example in Naples, the first 500 users to register for the event will be able to claim free "Binance style" pizza and drinks and take part in a pizza-making contest for Binance prizes. For more information on events near you, visit our blog.&nbsp;</p><p>Bitcoin Pizza Day stands as a pivotal milestone for the crypto industry, signifying its remarkable exponential growth and paving the path for widespread adoption of digital currencies over the past 13 years. As ever, Binance continues to move towards its goal of increasing the freedom of money and believes that growing crypto adoption will create even further opportunities for financial freedom. Therefore, once again this year, Binance is proud to celebrate this momentous day with our deserving and empowering community.</p><p>About Binance&nbsp;</p><p>Binance is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain ecosystem and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider with a financial product suite that includes the largest digital asset exchange by volume. Trusted by millions worldwide, the Binance platform is dedicated to increasing the freedom of money for users, and features an unmatched portfolio of crypto products and offerings, including: trading and finance, education, data and research, social good, investment and incubation, decentralization and infrastructure solutions, and more. For more information, visit:&nbsp;https://www.binance.com</p>ContactMarina Zibarevapr@binance.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, UAE, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-center">From Binance-style super meet-ups to online contests, the crypto exchange is celebrating Bitcoin&rsquo;s famous first purchase</p><p>Binance, the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, is celebrating the thirteenth anniversary of Bitcoin Pizza Day, the historic day in 2010 that a purchase of two pizzas was made in return for 10,000 BTC.</p><p>To celebrate this monumental day in crypto and the revolution it marks for the industry, Binance will be hosting in-person community meet-ups around the world. The celebrations will kick off in the birthplace of pizza, Naples, Italy, on May 21 and continue with local pizzeria and pizza van takeovers in ten countries, including Brazil, Bahrain, Pakistan, Vietnam, Sri Lanka, Cambodia, Uruguay, Mexico, Argentina, and New Zealand.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>The community is also invited to celebrate Pizza Day on social media and the Binance app. Participants who share their Binance-themed pizzas using #BinancePizza or complete tasks to collect all the Pizza Flavours on the Binance app have a chance to win the crypto equivalent of a year&amp;apos;s supply of pizza. Online celebrations will continue as Binance hosts a virtual live meet-up&nbsp;with the attendance of CZ on May 22 at 12:00 PM UTC, featuring discussions on the meaning of Bitcoin Pizza Day with prominent Binance Feed creators.</p><p>"Bitcoin Pizza Day is a testament to the power of community and the growing acceptance of BTC as part of our daily lives," said Yi He, Binance co-founder and Chief Marketing Officer. "At Binance, we believe in the importance of mass adoption, and we are committed to creating more and more use cases for crypto in everyday situations. As more people recognize the value and potential of blockchain and crypto, our community grows stronger, and we continue to build our industry."</p><p>The global Pizza Day meet-ups will offer fun activities with the chance to win swag and rewards, and of course, free pizza. Events vary by city, for example in Naples, the first 500 users to register for the event will be able to claim free "Binance style" pizza and drinks and take part in a pizza-making contest for Binance prizes. For more information on events near you, visit our blog.&nbsp;</p><p>Bitcoin Pizza Day stands as a pivotal milestone for the crypto industry, signifying its remarkable exponential growth and paving the path for widespread adoption of digital currencies over the past 13 years. As ever, Binance continues to move towards its goal of increasing the freedom of money and believes that growing crypto adoption will create even further opportunities for financial freedom. Therefore, once again this year, Binance is proud to celebrate this momentous day with our deserving and empowering community.</p><p>About Binance&nbsp;</p><p>Binance is the world&rsquo;s leading blockchain ecosystem and cryptocurrency infrastructure provider with a financial product suite that includes the largest digital asset exchange by volume. Trusted by millions worldwide, the Binance platform is dedicated to increasing the freedom of money for users, and features an unmatched portfolio of crypto products and offerings, including: trading and finance, education, data and research, social good, investment and incubation, decentralization and infrastructure solutions, and more. For more information, visit:&nbsp;https://www.binance.com</p>ContactMarina Zibarevapr@binance.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bankruptcy Court Approves Voyager Repayment Plan]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bankruptcy-court-approves-voyager-repayment-plan</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/voyager-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bankruptcy-court-approves-voyager-repayment-plan</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The third iteration of the Voyager bankruptcy plan has finally been approved by the court. According to the terms, affected customers can expect to recover up to 35% of their claims.</p>
Voyager Liquidating To Refund Customers
<p>In a significant development for users affected by the Voyager Digital Ltd. bankruptcy case, the court has approved a plan that allows customers to recoup a substantial portion of their frozen funds. According to the latest reports, users may be able to recover up to 35.7% of their initial claims, providing some much-needed relief for those impacted by the unfortunate situation.</p>
<p>This marks a positive turning point for Voyager Digital, a crypto brokerage platform that experienced financial difficulties leading to the freezing of customer accounts.&nbsp;</p>
Attempt No.1: The FTX Debacle
<p>The defunct company has had two failed attempts in the past to refund its customers. Back in September 2022, FTX had placed a winning bid of $1.4 billion on the bankrupt company&rsquo;s assets. However, with FTX also going under soon, the deal fell through. Reportedly, if the deal had been fully realized and FTX had not collapsed, creditors would have been able to reclaim 72% of their account values.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto exchange even went as far as to sue Voyager for $445.8 million in January 2023, alleging that loan repayments made by Voyager in 2022 are subject to clawback due to their timing, occurring right before FTX's bankruptcy.</p>
Attempt No.2: Binance Backs Out
<p>The second chance at redemption came Voyager&rsquo;s way with Binance.US and a $1 billion acquisition deal. However, there was significant legal pushback on this plan from the bankruptcy court, and after a lot of back and forth, the deal finally fell through in late April, resulting in Voyager looking into liquidation options.&nbsp;</p>
Attempt No.3: Finally Approved
<p>The bankrupt crypto brokerage firm finally got lucky on its third try when Judge Michael Wiles of the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York approved its bankruptcy plan to liquidate on May 17.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under the terms of the plan, Voyager will begin repaying customers' frozen accounts in the near future. The approved proposal ensures that 35.7% of the initial claims will be distributed to the affected users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Voyager has stated that as of May 8, it held $1.33 billion in recoverable assets, with $629.8 million being immediately available for recovery while facing claims totaling $1.8 billion. There is also a possibility that the firm may recover its funds frozen in the also-bankrupt crypto hedge fund, Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The third iteration of the Voyager bankruptcy plan has finally been approved by the court. According to the terms, affected customers can expect to recover up to 35% of their claims.</p>
Voyager Liquidating To Refund Customers
<p>In a significant development for users affected by the Voyager Digital Ltd. bankruptcy case, the court has approved a plan that allows customers to recoup a substantial portion of their frozen funds. According to the latest reports, users may be able to recover up to 35.7% of their initial claims, providing some much-needed relief for those impacted by the unfortunate situation.</p>
<p>This marks a positive turning point for Voyager Digital, a crypto brokerage platform that experienced financial difficulties leading to the freezing of customer accounts.&nbsp;</p>
Attempt No.1: The FTX Debacle
<p>The defunct company has had two failed attempts in the past to refund its customers. Back in September 2022, FTX had placed a winning bid of $1.4 billion on the bankrupt company&rsquo;s assets. However, with FTX also going under soon, the deal fell through. Reportedly, if the deal had been fully realized and FTX had not collapsed, creditors would have been able to reclaim 72% of their account values.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto exchange even went as far as to sue Voyager for $445.8 million in January 2023, alleging that loan repayments made by Voyager in 2022 are subject to clawback due to their timing, occurring right before FTX's bankruptcy.</p>
Attempt No.2: Binance Backs Out
<p>The second chance at redemption came Voyager&rsquo;s way with Binance.US and a $1 billion acquisition deal. However, there was significant legal pushback on this plan from the bankruptcy court, and after a lot of back and forth, the deal finally fell through in late April, resulting in Voyager looking into liquidation options.&nbsp;</p>
Attempt No.3: Finally Approved
<p>The bankrupt crypto brokerage firm finally got lucky on its third try when Judge Michael Wiles of the United States Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of New York approved its bankruptcy plan to liquidate on May 17.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Under the terms of the plan, Voyager will begin repaying customers' frozen accounts in the near future. The approved proposal ensures that 35.7% of the initial claims will be distributed to the affected users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Voyager has stated that as of May 8, it held $1.33 billion in recoverable assets, with $629.8 million being immediately available for recovery while facing claims totaling $1.8 billion. There is also a possibility that the firm may recover its funds frozen in the also-bankrupt crypto hedge fund, Three Arrows Capital.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The Multichain Hypothesis: Why Coexistence is Key for Web3's Future]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-multichain-hypothesis-why-coexistence-is-key-for-web3s-future</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-130815.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-130815.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-18-at-130815.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-multichain-hypothesis-why-coexistence-is-key-for-web3s-future</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Web3, the next epoch of the internet, is built upon revolutionary technology called blockchain. As this new era unfolds, an important debate has emerged within the crypto industry: Will there be a winner-take-all scenario among blockchains, or can multiple blockchains coexist? This ongoing discussion, known as the multichain hypothesis, has profound implications for the future of Web3. In this thought leadership article, we will delve into the significance of blockchain coexistence and explore how Poly Network, a leading interoperability solution, is playing a pivotal role in enabling the benefits of multichain synergy.</p>
<p>Diversifying Blockchain Infrastructure In recent years, the blockchain landscape has witnessed the development of diverse infrastructure layers, adding richness and variety to the previous Ethereum layer-1 (L1) monopoly. This expansion has unlocked unique benefits for different blockchain communities. From scalability solutions to specialized functionalities, each infrastructure layer offers distinct advantages that cater to specific needs and use cases. The proliferation of these offerings has led to increased diversity within the blockchain ecosystem, presenting users with an array of choices and opportunities.</p>
<p>Unlocking Synergy through Interoperability</p>
<p>While diversity among blockchains is crucial, the true power of Web3 lies in the ability to unlock the synergy between different chains. This is where interoperability becomes paramount. By seamlessly connecting disparate blockchains, interoperability solutions like Poly Network enable the aggregation of benefits across ecosystems. Through the establishment of secure and efficient bridges, users can seamlessly transfer assets, data, and value across multiple chains, unleashing the true potential of interconnectedness.</p>
<p>Maximizing Synergy and Empowering Users</p>
<p>The multichain hypothesis holds the key to the future of Web3. The coexistence of diverse blockchains, facilitated by interoperability solutions, allows for the maximization of synergistic value. Each blockchain can leverage its unique strengths, fostering collaboration and innovation within the ecosystem. Users benefit from a broader range of options and opportunities, enabling them to tailor their experiences to their specific needs. With Poly Network's cutting-edge interoperability solutions, users gain unprecedented control and ownership over their digital assets and data, which transcends the limitations of individual chains.</p>
<p>Maximizing Web3 Potential: Multichain Synergies with Poly Network</p>
<p>Poly Network stands at the forefront of the multichain revolution, empowering the future of Web3 through its groundbreaking interoperability solutions. By seamlessly connecting blockchains, Poly Network enables users to unlock the full potential of decentralized finance, decentralized applications, and beyond. Through secure and trustless bridges, users can harness the benefits of diverse blockchains while maintaining control and ownership of their assets. Poly Network's commitment to interoperability paves the way for a more inclusive, interconnected, and user-centric Web3.</p>
<p>The multichain hypothesis highlights the importance of coexistence among blockchains in the Web3 era. As the crypto industry continues to evolve, diversity and interoperability become the driving forces behind innovation and user empowerment. Poly Network's groundbreaking solutions play a pivotal role in enabling the aggregation of benefits and maximizing synergy between different chains. By embracing the multichain future, we can unlock a new paradigm of possibilities and shape a more vibrant and inclusive Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Web3, the next epoch of the internet, is built upon revolutionary technology called blockchain. As this new era unfolds, an important debate has emerged within the crypto industry: Will there be a winner-take-all scenario among blockchains, or can multiple blockchains coexist? This ongoing discussion, known as the multichain hypothesis, has profound implications for the future of Web3. In this thought leadership article, we will delve into the significance of blockchain coexistence and explore how Poly Network, a leading interoperability solution, is playing a pivotal role in enabling the benefits of multichain synergy.</p>
<p>Diversifying Blockchain Infrastructure In recent years, the blockchain landscape has witnessed the development of diverse infrastructure layers, adding richness and variety to the previous Ethereum layer-1 (L1) monopoly. This expansion has unlocked unique benefits for different blockchain communities. From scalability solutions to specialized functionalities, each infrastructure layer offers distinct advantages that cater to specific needs and use cases. The proliferation of these offerings has led to increased diversity within the blockchain ecosystem, presenting users with an array of choices and opportunities.</p>
<p>Unlocking Synergy through Interoperability</p>
<p>While diversity among blockchains is crucial, the true power of Web3 lies in the ability to unlock the synergy between different chains. This is where interoperability becomes paramount. By seamlessly connecting disparate blockchains, interoperability solutions like Poly Network enable the aggregation of benefits across ecosystems. Through the establishment of secure and efficient bridges, users can seamlessly transfer assets, data, and value across multiple chains, unleashing the true potential of interconnectedness.</p>
<p>Maximizing Synergy and Empowering Users</p>
<p>The multichain hypothesis holds the key to the future of Web3. The coexistence of diverse blockchains, facilitated by interoperability solutions, allows for the maximization of synergistic value. Each blockchain can leverage its unique strengths, fostering collaboration and innovation within the ecosystem. Users benefit from a broader range of options and opportunities, enabling them to tailor their experiences to their specific needs. With Poly Network's cutting-edge interoperability solutions, users gain unprecedented control and ownership over their digital assets and data, which transcends the limitations of individual chains.</p>
<p>Maximizing Web3 Potential: Multichain Synergies with Poly Network</p>
<p>Poly Network stands at the forefront of the multichain revolution, empowering the future of Web3 through its groundbreaking interoperability solutions. By seamlessly connecting blockchains, Poly Network enables users to unlock the full potential of decentralized finance, decentralized applications, and beyond. Through secure and trustless bridges, users can harness the benefits of diverse blockchains while maintaining control and ownership of their assets. Poly Network's commitment to interoperability paves the way for a more inclusive, interconnected, and user-centric Web3.</p>
<p>The multichain hypothesis highlights the importance of coexistence among blockchains in the Web3 era. As the crypto industry continues to evolve, diversity and interoperability become the driving forces behind innovation and user empowerment. Poly Network's groundbreaking solutions play a pivotal role in enabling the aggregation of benefits and maximizing synergy between different chains. By embracing the multichain future, we can unlock a new paradigm of possibilities and shape a more vibrant and inclusive Web3 ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Leading Crypto Teams and Investors Launch $50M Cross-Chain Fund powered by Wormhole]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/leading-crypto-teams-and-investors-launch-50m-cross-chain-fund-powered-by-wormhole</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Logos_Borderless_CrossChain_Fund_1_1684352691OziQFIxFjj.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Logos_Borderless_CrossChain_Fund_1_1684352691OziQFIxFjj.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Logos_Borderless_CrossChain_Fund_1_1684352691OziQFIxFjj.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 13:00:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/leading-crypto-teams-and-investors-launch-50m-cross-chain-fund-powered-by-wormhole</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Miami, FL, United States, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Borderless Capital is the manager behind this new fund. Investors include Jump Crypto, Aptos Labs, Polygon Ventures, Solana Foundation, Algorand Foundation, GSR, Arrington Capital&nbsp;among other institutions&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Over twenty blockchain teams and venture funds have teamed up to launch a $50 million Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund focused on backing and growing new startups that leverage the Wormhole cross-chain messaging protocol. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund is being managed and operated by Borderless Capital, a leading venture capital firm in the Web3 space. Backed by top blockchain protocols, infrastructure providers, and institutional investors, the fund aims to support cross-chain innovations that will drive the growth and adoption of the Web3 industry. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund is backed by Jump Crypto, Polygon Ventures, Aptos Labs, Solana Foundation, Sei Foundation, Algorand Foundation, CLabs (the company behind the Celo Blockchain), the Moonbeam Foundation, Optimism, Circle, MultiCoin GP&rsquo;s Tushar Jain and Kyle Samani, Arrington Capital, GSR, Floating Point Group, Chainlayer, Chainode Tech, 01Node, Staking Fund, Moonlet.io, Forbole Ventures, Syncnode, Inotel, Triton One, Strangelove, Securitize&rsquo;s CEO Carlos Domingo, OtterSec among others.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Navigating the Web3 landscape is becoming increasingly challenging due to the proliferation of numerous layer-1 blockchains, layer-2 scaling solutions, and specialized appchains with unique purposes and parameters. This complexity poses difficulties for users and alienates developers who are restricted from accessing a single ecosystem, hindering their growth. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund seeks to unlock the full potential of a cross-chain future, aiming to redefine users' experiences and establish Wormhole as the cross-chain standard for builders to transcend the limitations of individual ecosystems.&nbsp;This innovation prioritizes aggregation, security, scalability, compatibility, and composability.</p>"We believe in a borderless Web3 future and are thrilled to have the support of our partners and investors who share our vision. In the same way that in Web2 the value was created through aggregating the relationship with the users we believe that in Web3 this is the natural next step" said David Garcia, CEO &amp; Managing Partner of Borderless Capital. "Our goal is to empower builders to transcend the limitations of individual ecosystems, paving the way for blockchain applications and protocols to realize their full potential."<p class="ql-align-justify">Wormhole, the technological focus of the Fund, is a foundational protocol that enables cross-chain messaging of value and data across more than 23 high-value chains, already leveraged by influential protocols and companies like Uniswap, Circle and Base from Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Crypto is still a nascent industry with essentially limitless growth opportunity, and we should be doing nothing but working together, regardless of which specific networks individuals may be more passionate about. It&rsquo;s really exciting to see so many ecosystems come together with leading venture funds to unite on solving the interoperability challenge by supporting startups that integrate Wormhole&rsquo;s cross-chain messaging standard,&rdquo; said Dan Reecer, Head of Operations at Wormhole Foundation.<p class="ql-align-justify">Builders, founders and developers looking to reach across ecosystems can apply to the Cross-Chain Ecosystem fund at wormhole.com/programs. Applications will be reviewed by the fund manager, Borderless Capital, starting this month.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Borderless</p><p>Borderless is a leading investment management firm focused on Web3 technology, dedicated to supporting the next generation of innovators who are driving the development of groundbreaking technologies that will enable the creation of value without borders. Borderless comprises a team of builders, partners, and investors who adopt a long-term perspective and strive to unleash the full potential of open, community-driven networks. Since 2018, Borderless has invested in 200+ protocols/companies across infrastructure, business applications, and nascent cryptographic protocols, and has played an integral role in the development of some of the most significant and innovative Web3 communities. For more information, please visit their website.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Wormhole</p><p>Wormhole is the industry standard cross-chain messaging protocol powering applications across Web3. Wormhole provides developers access to liquidity and users on over 20 of the leading blockchain networks, enabling use cases that span DeFi, NFTs, governance, and more. Wormhole enables a growing suite of products to build on its messaging layer. Wormhole Connect is an in-app bridging widget that can be integrated in as few as 3 lines of code. The wider Wormhole network is trusted and used by teams like Circle (USDC) and Uniswap, and to date, the platform has facilitated the transfer of over 35 billion dollars through hundreds of millions of cross-chain messages.</p>ContactBorderless Teammedia@borderlesscapital.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miami, FL, United States, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Borderless Capital is the manager behind this new fund. Investors include Jump Crypto, Aptos Labs, Polygon Ventures, Solana Foundation, Algorand Foundation, GSR, Arrington Capital&nbsp;among other institutions&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Over twenty blockchain teams and venture funds have teamed up to launch a $50 million Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund focused on backing and growing new startups that leverage the Wormhole cross-chain messaging protocol. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund is being managed and operated by Borderless Capital, a leading venture capital firm in the Web3 space. Backed by top blockchain protocols, infrastructure providers, and institutional investors, the fund aims to support cross-chain innovations that will drive the growth and adoption of the Web3 industry. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund is backed by Jump Crypto, Polygon Ventures, Aptos Labs, Solana Foundation, Sei Foundation, Algorand Foundation, CLabs (the company behind the Celo Blockchain), the Moonbeam Foundation, Optimism, Circle, MultiCoin GP&rsquo;s Tushar Jain and Kyle Samani, Arrington Capital, GSR, Floating Point Group, Chainlayer, Chainode Tech, 01Node, Staking Fund, Moonlet.io, Forbole Ventures, Syncnode, Inotel, Triton One, Strangelove, Securitize&rsquo;s CEO Carlos Domingo, OtterSec among others.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Navigating the Web3 landscape is becoming increasingly challenging due to the proliferation of numerous layer-1 blockchains, layer-2 scaling solutions, and specialized appchains with unique purposes and parameters. This complexity poses difficulties for users and alienates developers who are restricted from accessing a single ecosystem, hindering their growth. The Cross-Chain Ecosystem Fund seeks to unlock the full potential of a cross-chain future, aiming to redefine users' experiences and establish Wormhole as the cross-chain standard for builders to transcend the limitations of individual ecosystems.&nbsp;This innovation prioritizes aggregation, security, scalability, compatibility, and composability.</p>"We believe in a borderless Web3 future and are thrilled to have the support of our partners and investors who share our vision. In the same way that in Web2 the value was created through aggregating the relationship with the users we believe that in Web3 this is the natural next step" said David Garcia, CEO &amp; Managing Partner of Borderless Capital. "Our goal is to empower builders to transcend the limitations of individual ecosystems, paving the way for blockchain applications and protocols to realize their full potential."<p class="ql-align-justify">Wormhole, the technological focus of the Fund, is a foundational protocol that enables cross-chain messaging of value and data across more than 23 high-value chains, already leveraged by influential protocols and companies like Uniswap, Circle and Base from Coinbase.&nbsp;</p>&ldquo;Crypto is still a nascent industry with essentially limitless growth opportunity, and we should be doing nothing but working together, regardless of which specific networks individuals may be more passionate about. It&rsquo;s really exciting to see so many ecosystems come together with leading venture funds to unite on solving the interoperability challenge by supporting startups that integrate Wormhole&rsquo;s cross-chain messaging standard,&rdquo; said Dan Reecer, Head of Operations at Wormhole Foundation.<p class="ql-align-justify">Builders, founders and developers looking to reach across ecosystems can apply to the Cross-Chain Ecosystem fund at wormhole.com/programs. Applications will be reviewed by the fund manager, Borderless Capital, starting this month.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Borderless</p><p>Borderless is a leading investment management firm focused on Web3 technology, dedicated to supporting the next generation of innovators who are driving the development of groundbreaking technologies that will enable the creation of value without borders. Borderless comprises a team of builders, partners, and investors who adopt a long-term perspective and strive to unleash the full potential of open, community-driven networks. Since 2018, Borderless has invested in 200+ protocols/companies across infrastructure, business applications, and nascent cryptographic protocols, and has played an integral role in the development of some of the most significant and innovative Web3 communities. For more information, please visit their website.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Wormhole</p><p>Wormhole is the industry standard cross-chain messaging protocol powering applications across Web3. Wormhole provides developers access to liquidity and users on over 20 of the leading blockchain networks, enabling use cases that span DeFi, NFTs, governance, and more. Wormhole enables a growing suite of products to build on its messaging layer. Wormhole Connect is an in-app bridging widget that can be integrated in as few as 3 lines of code. The wider Wormhole network is trusted and used by teams like Circle (USDC) and Uniswap, and to date, the platform has facilitated the transfer of over 35 billion dollars through hundreds of millions of cross-chain messages.</p>ContactBorderless Teammedia@borderlesscapital.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[NFT Show Europe Invites Exhibitors to the Major Blockchain and Digital Art Conference]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nft-show-europe-invites-exhibitors-to-the-major-blockchain-and-digital-art-conference</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/NFTSE_July_2023_1684326924Saf1Rk1u4Y.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/NFTSE_July_2023_1684326924Saf1Rk1u4Y.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/NFTSE_July_2023_1684326924Saf1Rk1u4Y.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:22:08 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nft-show-europe-invites-exhibitors-to-the-major-blockchain-and-digital-art-conference</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Valencia, Spain, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>NFT Show Europe, the leading conference for the blockchain, metaverse, and digital art industries, is inviting exhibitors to sign up for its forthcoming event. As an exhibitor at NFT Show Europe 2023, companies will have the opportunity to showcase their innovative solutions to potential investors, clients, and industry partners who are eager to discover the next big thing.&nbsp;</p><p>NFT Show Europe, set to run from July 14-15, 2023, provides a lucrative opportunity for businesses to exhibit their solutions and stand out in the digital arena. Trailblazing companies in the blockchain, web3, metaverse, tokenization, DeFi, and gaming industries can now sign up for an exhibition spot at #NFTSE. Participants will be immersed in a high-energy web3 business and networking atmosphere in the Spanish coastal city of Valencia.</p><p>At #NFTSE, participants will have the opportunity to rub shoulders with leaders from Alpine F1, Activision Blizzard, Epic Games, and Crypto. Page, Decentraland, SKI Federation, Joyn, Lama, Navi Studio, United Nations, UNICEF, Odos, Polkadot, and Zepeto among other companies and visitors from 55+ countries.</p><p>At NFT Show Europe, business exhibitors will have an opportunity to elevate their brand presence, generate leads, and forge powerful partnerships that will catapult their growth to new heights.</p><p>Exhibitor spaces are now available for the European conference but spaces are selling fast. Interested parties are encouraged to reserve their spot now to ensure their company's presence at the major event. Exhibitors can sign up at https://www.nftshoweurope.com/exhibitors/.</p><p>NFT Show Europe is one of the world&rsquo;s leading meeting points for web3, blockchain, metaverse, and digital art pioneers.t. It provides an international meeting point for experts to share their insights on the next era of the internet in a futuristic business-art atmosphere.</p><p>#NFTSE 2023 Official Trailer: https://youtu.be/Rf9jazG1yE0</p><p>Website: https://nftshoweurope.com/</p><p>Twitter: @nftshoweurope</p><p></p>ContactMedia and Communications ManagerIbon EscaladaNFT Show Europeibon@nftshoweurope.comTelegram: @IbonRdL]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Valencia, Spain, May 18th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>NFT Show Europe, the leading conference for the blockchain, metaverse, and digital art industries, is inviting exhibitors to sign up for its forthcoming event. As an exhibitor at NFT Show Europe 2023, companies will have the opportunity to showcase their innovative solutions to potential investors, clients, and industry partners who are eager to discover the next big thing.&nbsp;</p><p>NFT Show Europe, set to run from July 14-15, 2023, provides a lucrative opportunity for businesses to exhibit their solutions and stand out in the digital arena. Trailblazing companies in the blockchain, web3, metaverse, tokenization, DeFi, and gaming industries can now sign up for an exhibition spot at #NFTSE. Participants will be immersed in a high-energy web3 business and networking atmosphere in the Spanish coastal city of Valencia.</p><p>At #NFTSE, participants will have the opportunity to rub shoulders with leaders from Alpine F1, Activision Blizzard, Epic Games, and Crypto. Page, Decentraland, SKI Federation, Joyn, Lama, Navi Studio, United Nations, UNICEF, Odos, Polkadot, and Zepeto among other companies and visitors from 55+ countries.</p><p>At NFT Show Europe, business exhibitors will have an opportunity to elevate their brand presence, generate leads, and forge powerful partnerships that will catapult their growth to new heights.</p><p>Exhibitor spaces are now available for the European conference but spaces are selling fast. Interested parties are encouraged to reserve their spot now to ensure their company's presence at the major event. Exhibitors can sign up at https://www.nftshoweurope.com/exhibitors/.</p><p>NFT Show Europe is one of the world&rsquo;s leading meeting points for web3, blockchain, metaverse, and digital art pioneers.t. It provides an international meeting point for experts to share their insights on the next era of the internet in a futuristic business-art atmosphere.</p><p>#NFTSE 2023 Official Trailer: https://youtu.be/Rf9jazG1yE0</p><p>Website: https://nftshoweurope.com/</p><p>Twitter: @nftshoweurope</p><p></p>ContactMedia and Communications ManagerIbon EscaladaNFT Show Europeibon@nftshoweurope.comTelegram: @IbonRdL]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Litecoin wakes up as its halving approaches]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/litcoin-wakes-up-as-its-halving-approaches</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lite-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lite-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/lite-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/litcoin-wakes-up-as-its-halving-approaches</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Touted as digital silver to Bitcoin&rsquo;s gold, Litecoin has suddenly awakened, putting on nearly 20% in 4 days.</p>
<p>Like a blast from the past Litecoin has perhaps put itself into the reckoning again after a short, sharp rally. Like Bitcoin, Litecoin has a halving where the block rewards for miners are cut in half. This halving event is now on the horizon, and is expected to take place in July or August of this year.</p>
<p>Litecoin's recent surge of 20% exemplifies the growing interest in diversifying cryptocurrency portfolios. As investors become more sophisticated, they recognize the need to explore beyond Bitcoin's dominance and explore other avenues.&nbsp;</p>
Faster and more efficient than Bitcoin
<p>One of Litecoin's key differentiators lies in its technology. Created by Charlie Lee, a former Google engineer, Litecoin boasts faster block generation times and a more efficient mining algorithm compared to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This distinction makes Litecoin capable of processing transactions four times faster, offering increased scalability and improved transaction speeds. These features position Litecoin as a possible solution for everyday transactions, where speed and efficiency are paramount.</p>
<p>Litecoin's resilience owes much to its community, which has weathered the challenges of the last few years, fostering a dedicated network of enthusiasts who actively promote and develop the currency.&nbsp;</p>
The Litecoin price history
<p>The Litecoin price is currently sitting at $92.60. This is a strong area of resistance, and should $LTC manage to flip this into support, we could see a sustained run that could take the token a lot higher.</p>
<p>Back in 2017 at the height of that crypto bull run, $LTC rose as high as $373 before sinking into the ensuing awful bear market that saw the token plumb the depths to around $21.</p>
<p>A rally into mid 2019 saw Litecoin get back to $145, before the bears took over once again and Litecoin sank again to its lowest point at $20. From here it began its most glorious ascent yet, reaching $413 in May 2021.</p>
<p>This was the first top for this particular bull run, and where Bitcoin surpassed this, Litecoin was only able to hit $295 for its second top at the end of the bull run in November of 2021.</p>
<p>Whether Litecoin is able to see such glory days again is a moot point. However, with its halving approaching it could potentially see some strong gains.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Touted as digital silver to Bitcoin&rsquo;s gold, Litecoin has suddenly awakened, putting on nearly 20% in 4 days.</p>
<p>Like a blast from the past Litecoin has perhaps put itself into the reckoning again after a short, sharp rally. Like Bitcoin, Litecoin has a halving where the block rewards for miners are cut in half. This halving event is now on the horizon, and is expected to take place in July or August of this year.</p>
<p>Litecoin's recent surge of 20% exemplifies the growing interest in diversifying cryptocurrency portfolios. As investors become more sophisticated, they recognize the need to explore beyond Bitcoin's dominance and explore other avenues.&nbsp;</p>
Faster and more efficient than Bitcoin
<p>One of Litecoin's key differentiators lies in its technology. Created by Charlie Lee, a former Google engineer, Litecoin boasts faster block generation times and a more efficient mining algorithm compared to Bitcoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This distinction makes Litecoin capable of processing transactions four times faster, offering increased scalability and improved transaction speeds. These features position Litecoin as a possible solution for everyday transactions, where speed and efficiency are paramount.</p>
<p>Litecoin's resilience owes much to its community, which has weathered the challenges of the last few years, fostering a dedicated network of enthusiasts who actively promote and develop the currency.&nbsp;</p>
The Litecoin price history
<p>The Litecoin price is currently sitting at $92.60. This is a strong area of resistance, and should $LTC manage to flip this into support, we could see a sustained run that could take the token a lot higher.</p>
<p>Back in 2017 at the height of that crypto bull run, $LTC rose as high as $373 before sinking into the ensuing awful bear market that saw the token plumb the depths to around $21.</p>
<p>A rally into mid 2019 saw Litecoin get back to $145, before the bears took over once again and Litecoin sank again to its lowest point at $20. From here it began its most glorious ascent yet, reaching $413 in May 2021.</p>
<p>This was the first top for this particular bull run, and where Bitcoin surpassed this, Litecoin was only able to hit $295 for its second top at the end of the bull run in November of 2021.</p>
<p>Whether Litecoin is able to see such glory days again is a moot point. However, with its halving approaching it could potentially see some strong gains.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[XRP Up After Latest Court Ruling, Crypto Daily TV 18/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/xrp-up-after-latest-court-ruling-crypto-daily-tv-18-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-xrp-up.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-xrp-up.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-xrp-up.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 10:56:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/xrp-up-after-latest-court-ruling-crypto-daily-tv-18-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>SEC asks Grayscale to withdraw FIL trust application</p>
<p>The SEC asked Grayscale to withdraw its application to launch a Filecoin trust product, the asset manager revealed. Grayscale said in a press release that it had received a comment letter from the federal securities regulator saying FIL "meets the definition of a security."</p>
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP goes up after latest court ruling</p>
<p>XRP, the native token of Ripple Labs Inc.&rsquo;s blockchain ecosystem, jumped the most in about seven weeks after investors interpreted a court ruling as favorable for the crypto payments company.</p>
<p>Tether will buy Bitcoin for reserves </p>
<p>Stablecoin issuer Tether will regularly buy bitcoin for its stablecoin reserves using a portion of its profits starting this month as part of a new investment strategy focused on the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, the firm announced.</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.9% in the last session.
<p>Bitcoin gained 0.9% against the Dollar in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 26674.6667 and resistance is at 27502.6667.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD remained largely unchanged in the last session.
<p>Ethereum-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1784.7967 and resistance is at 1849.5367.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD rose 0.5% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair gained 0.5% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.4106 and resistance is at 0.4587.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 4.6% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 4.6% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 84.6267 and resistance is at 93.0267.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Initial Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Initial Jobless Claims measure the number of people filing first-time claims for state unemployment insurance. The US Initial Jobless Claims will be released at 12:30 GMT, the US Continuing Jobless Claims at 12:30 GMT, and Japan's National Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Continuing Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Counting Jobless Claims measures the number of individuals who are unemployed and are currently receiving unemployment benefits.</p>
<p>JP National Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The National Consumer Price Index measures price movements obtained by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>UK GfK Consumer Confidence</p>
<p>The GfK Group Consumer Confidence is a leading index that measures the level of consumer confidence in economic activity. The UK's GfK Consumer Confidence will be released at 23:01 GMT, Australia's Employment Change at 01:30 GMT, and Australia's Unemployment Rate at 01:30 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Employment Change</p>
<p>The Employment Change is a measure of the change in the number of employed people, which in turn shows the strength of the Labour market.</p>
<p>AU Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>SEC asks Grayscale to withdraw FIL trust application</p>
<p>The SEC asked Grayscale to withdraw its application to launch a Filecoin trust product, the asset manager revealed. Grayscale said in a press release that it had received a comment letter from the federal securities regulator saying FIL "meets the definition of a security."</p>
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP goes up after latest court ruling</p>
<p>XRP, the native token of Ripple Labs Inc.&rsquo;s blockchain ecosystem, jumped the most in about seven weeks after investors interpreted a court ruling as favorable for the crypto payments company.</p>
<p>Tether will buy Bitcoin for reserves </p>
<p>Stablecoin issuer Tether will regularly buy bitcoin for its stablecoin reserves using a portion of its profits starting this month as part of a new investment strategy focused on the largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization, the firm announced.</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.9% in the last session.
<p>Bitcoin gained 0.9% against the Dollar in the last session. The ROC is giving a negative signal. Support is at 26674.6667 and resistance is at 27502.6667.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD remained largely unchanged in the last session.
<p>Ethereum-Dollar price remained largely unchanged in the last session. The MACD is giving a negative signal. Support is at 1784.7967 and resistance is at 1849.5367.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD rose 0.5% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair gained 0.5% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 0.4106 and resistance is at 0.4587.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 4.6% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 4.6% in the last session. The ROC is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 84.6267 and resistance is at 93.0267.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Initial Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Initial Jobless Claims measure the number of people filing first-time claims for state unemployment insurance. The US Initial Jobless Claims will be released at 12:30 GMT, the US Continuing Jobless Claims at 12:30 GMT, and Japan's National Consumer Price Index at 23:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US Continuing Jobless Claims</p>
<p>The Counting Jobless Claims measures the number of individuals who are unemployed and are currently receiving unemployment benefits.</p>
<p>JP National Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The National Consumer Price Index measures price movements obtained by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services.</p>
<p>UK GfK Consumer Confidence</p>
<p>The GfK Group Consumer Confidence is a leading index that measures the level of consumer confidence in economic activity. The UK's GfK Consumer Confidence will be released at 23:01 GMT, Australia's Employment Change at 01:30 GMT, and Australia's Unemployment Rate at 01:30 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Employment Change</p>
<p>The Employment Change is a measure of the change in the number of employed people, which in turn shows the strength of the Labour market.</p>
<p>AU Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Indian Crypto Industry Urges Govt, RBI To Restore UPI Access]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/indian-crypto-industry-urges-govt-rbi-to-restore-upi-access</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/india-1920-3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/india-1920-3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/india-1920-3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 10:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/indian-crypto-industry-urges-govt-rbi-to-restore-upi-access</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Indian cryptocurrency industry has petitioned the government and the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to restore its access to the hugely popular Unified Payments Interface (UPI) for cryptocurrency-related services and activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto exchanges and their users based in India lost access to UPI after it was suspended in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Major Push By Crypto Stakeholders&nbsp;
<p>Two separate proposals were made to the Indian government and the Reserve Bank of India, asking for the restoration of access to UPI. UPI is a real-time payment system that the crypto space lost access to in 2022. The requests were made by an Indian cryptocurrency exchange and a policy advisory firm, Black Dot. Furthermore, there is a third proposal in the pipeline, which will be made in the next few weeks. This proposal will be made by a new crypto policy advocacy group called the Bharat Web3 Association (BWA).&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposals are not related or coordinated with one another. However, they represent the first significant push by those in the crypto space to argue for policy changes governing the industry that has been left in limbo thanks to the ongoing crypto winter, a series of harsh taxes, and a shadow ban. As a result of the shadow ban, Indian banks, and payment processors cut off access to banking services for cryptocurrency exchanges. Following this, exchanges also lost access to UPI services shortly after.&nbsp;</p>
India&rsquo;s Burgeoning UPI Ecosystem&nbsp;
<p>Following the Covid-19 pandemic, India has seen a staggering adoption of UPI by its growing and tech-savvy population. In 2022, the UPI interface processed 74 billion UPI transactions worth over $1.5 trillion. Citizens using UPI can pay for groceries and nearly all services through a QR code linked to their bank account. The UPI system is used nationally by merchants and is hugely popular because merchants are not charged a fee to accept UPI payments.&nbsp;</p>
The Trigger For The Setback&nbsp;
<p>So why did Indian cryptocurrency exchanges lose access to UPI? The trigger for the crisis can be traced to the launch of Coinbase in India. Coinbase launched its operations in India on the 7th of April, 2022, with executives going out of their way to highlight how easy trading on the company app would be with UPI processing all payments. Shortly after the event, the governing entity of UPI, the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI), tweeted that it was not aware of crypto exchanges using UPI services. The NPCI works under the Reserve Bank of India (RBI).&nbsp;</p>
The Proposals In Question&nbsp;
<p>An Indian cryptocurrency exchange made the first proposal to restore UPI access. However, the exchange requested not to be identified as the matter had not been made public as yet. The exchange noted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have submitted a representation with the NPCI, seeking the removal of restrictions on the use of UPI services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The exchange made the proposal shortly after India added crypto to the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA). This made cryptocurrency exchanges, NFT marketplaces, and custody wallet service providers legally responsible for monitoring and reporting any suspicious financial activities. Some believed that this would give regulators more teeth in dealing with the industry, while others believed this would give more legitimacy to the growing crypto sector in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The second proposal was made in tranches, both before and after India made crypto subject to anti-money laundering rules governed by different authorities. This proposal was made by the public policy advisory firm Black Dot. Black Dot has previously collaborated with the Indian Government. The Black Dot proposal states UPI&rsquo;s seamless user experience ensures that all transactions are on-shore, giving regulators and relevant authorities a clear trail of transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Black Dot cited a report stating that since the closure of UPI access, over 80% of transactions were conducted on a peer-to-peer basis. The proposal further added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Arbitrarily denying a class of investors from accessing instruments of their choice via UPI when another group of investors has access to their choice (e.g., IPO) may also violate Article 14 (equality before the law).&rdquo;</p>

<p>As of now, it remains to be seen if the Indian government or the Reserve Bank of India are moved by these proposals. However, the Indian crypto space is unanimous in its view that restoring UPI access would lend the space a significant amount of credibility.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Indian cryptocurrency industry has petitioned the government and the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to restore its access to the hugely popular Unified Payments Interface (UPI) for cryptocurrency-related services and activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto exchanges and their users based in India lost access to UPI after it was suspended in 2022.&nbsp;</p>
Major Push By Crypto Stakeholders&nbsp;
<p>Two separate proposals were made to the Indian government and the Reserve Bank of India, asking for the restoration of access to UPI. UPI is a real-time payment system that the crypto space lost access to in 2022. The requests were made by an Indian cryptocurrency exchange and a policy advisory firm, Black Dot. Furthermore, there is a third proposal in the pipeline, which will be made in the next few weeks. This proposal will be made by a new crypto policy advocacy group called the Bharat Web3 Association (BWA).&nbsp;</p>
<p>The proposals are not related or coordinated with one another. However, they represent the first significant push by those in the crypto space to argue for policy changes governing the industry that has been left in limbo thanks to the ongoing crypto winter, a series of harsh taxes, and a shadow ban. As a result of the shadow ban, Indian banks, and payment processors cut off access to banking services for cryptocurrency exchanges. Following this, exchanges also lost access to UPI services shortly after.&nbsp;</p>
India&rsquo;s Burgeoning UPI Ecosystem&nbsp;
<p>Following the Covid-19 pandemic, India has seen a staggering adoption of UPI by its growing and tech-savvy population. In 2022, the UPI interface processed 74 billion UPI transactions worth over $1.5 trillion. Citizens using UPI can pay for groceries and nearly all services through a QR code linked to their bank account. The UPI system is used nationally by merchants and is hugely popular because merchants are not charged a fee to accept UPI payments.&nbsp;</p>
The Trigger For The Setback&nbsp;
<p>So why did Indian cryptocurrency exchanges lose access to UPI? The trigger for the crisis can be traced to the launch of Coinbase in India. Coinbase launched its operations in India on the 7th of April, 2022, with executives going out of their way to highlight how easy trading on the company app would be with UPI processing all payments. Shortly after the event, the governing entity of UPI, the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI), tweeted that it was not aware of crypto exchanges using UPI services. The NPCI works under the Reserve Bank of India (RBI).&nbsp;</p>
The Proposals In Question&nbsp;
<p>An Indian cryptocurrency exchange made the first proposal to restore UPI access. However, the exchange requested not to be identified as the matter had not been made public as yet. The exchange noted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have submitted a representation with the NPCI, seeking the removal of restrictions on the use of UPI services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The exchange made the proposal shortly after India added crypto to the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA). This made cryptocurrency exchanges, NFT marketplaces, and custody wallet service providers legally responsible for monitoring and reporting any suspicious financial activities. Some believed that this would give regulators more teeth in dealing with the industry, while others believed this would give more legitimacy to the growing crypto sector in the country.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The second proposal was made in tranches, both before and after India made crypto subject to anti-money laundering rules governed by different authorities. This proposal was made by the public policy advisory firm Black Dot. Black Dot has previously collaborated with the Indian Government. The Black Dot proposal states UPI&rsquo;s seamless user experience ensures that all transactions are on-shore, giving regulators and relevant authorities a clear trail of transactions.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Black Dot cited a report stating that since the closure of UPI access, over 80% of transactions were conducted on a peer-to-peer basis. The proposal further added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Arbitrarily denying a class of investors from accessing instruments of their choice via UPI when another group of investors has access to their choice (e.g., IPO) may also violate Article 14 (equality before the law).&rdquo;</p>

<p>As of now, it remains to be seen if the Indian government or the Reserve Bank of India are moved by these proposals. However, the Indian crypto space is unanimous in its view that restoring UPI access would lend the space a significant amount of credibility.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tether To Use Net Profits To Buy Bitcoin And Shore Up Reserves]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-to-use-net-profits-to-buy-bitcoin-and-shore-up-reserves</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-to-use-net-profits-to-buy-bitcoin-and-shore-up-reserves</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The entity behind the USDT stablecoin, Tether, has announced that it will use a portion of its profits and purchase Bitcoin (BTC) in an effort to shore up its stablecoin reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tether had revealed a net profit of $1.48 billion in Q1 2023 and also revealed it had around $1.5 billion in BTC holdings.&nbsp;</p>
Tether To Shore Up Reserves Using New Investment Strategy&nbsp;
<p>According to a statement by the company, it plans to invest around 15% of its net profits to help diversify the assets backing the USDT stablecoin. USDT is the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, maintaining a 1:1 peg with the US dollar. According to the numbers, this would mean Tether would devote around $222 million to purchasing Bitcoin and add the token to its reserve surplus. Tether stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Starting this month, Tether will regularly allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits towards purchasing Bitcoin (BTC). Tether anticipates that the current and future BTC holdings in its reserves will not exceed the Shareholder Capital Cushion and will further strengthen and diversify the reserves.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, the company added that it would custody the BTC independently and refrain from using third-party custodians.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;While it is common practice among many institutional investors to third-party custody their Bitcoin, Tether believes in the philosophy &ldquo;Not your keys, not your bitcoin&rdquo; and takes possession of the private keys associated with all of its Bitcoin holdings.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether&rsquo;s moves to accumulate Bitcoin would make the company one of the biggest holders of the asset, joining other notable investors such as MicroStrategy boss Michael Saylor and Paul Tudor Jones.&nbsp;</p>
Capitalizing On Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Tether revealed in its Q1 2023 Assurance Report that it held around $1.5 billion worth of BTC in its reserves, along with $3.4 billion worth of gold. Additionally, 85% of its reserves are held in cash or cash-like assets such as US Treasury Bonds. Tether&rsquo;s pivot towards Bitcoin aims to help strengthen and diversify its stablecoin reserves and also capitalize on its price investment as an investment. Chief Technology Officer at Tether, Paolo Ardiono, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The decision to invest in Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset. Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Our investment in bitcoin is not only a way to enhance the performance of our portfolio, but it is also a method of aligning ourselves with a transformative technology.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The company added that it plans to use only its realized profits from investment operations to purchase Bitcoin. This means the firm would consider only the tangible gains from its operations which consist of the difference between the purchase price and the net proceeds from an asset sale. Alternatively, in the case of maturing assets such as Treasury Bills, the difference between the purchase price and the reimbursement amount. The company added that it was also focusing on developing energy and bitcoin mining infrastructure and communication systems, among other investments.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Problem With Transparency&nbsp;
<p>Tether has come under heavy criticism within the crypto space and from authorities thanks to a lack of transparency about its reserves and several controversial investment decisions. There have also been concerns about the quality of reserve assets backing its USDT stablecoin. However, despite these concerns, the USDT stablecoin has emerged as a safe haven for investors. This was outlined in March 2023 when the US banking crisis hit USDC, the second-largest stablecoin in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>USDC was severely impacted due to the sudden implosion of Silicon Valley Bank (SVB), which left a chunk of USDC&rsquo;s reserves frozen for a weekend. As a result, several stablecoins lost their dollar peg as a domino effect played out in the market. However, Tether was able to maintain its price stability thanks to a perceived disconnection and isolation from US Banks, thanks to it being incorporated in the British Virgin Islands and Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The entity behind the USDT stablecoin, Tether, has announced that it will use a portion of its profits and purchase Bitcoin (BTC) in an effort to shore up its stablecoin reserves.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tether had revealed a net profit of $1.48 billion in Q1 2023 and also revealed it had around $1.5 billion in BTC holdings.&nbsp;</p>
Tether To Shore Up Reserves Using New Investment Strategy&nbsp;
<p>According to a statement by the company, it plans to invest around 15% of its net profits to help diversify the assets backing the USDT stablecoin. USDT is the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, maintaining a 1:1 peg with the US dollar. According to the numbers, this would mean Tether would devote around $222 million to purchasing Bitcoin and add the token to its reserve surplus. Tether stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Starting this month, Tether will regularly allocate up to 15% of its net realized operating profits towards purchasing Bitcoin (BTC). Tether anticipates that the current and future BTC holdings in its reserves will not exceed the Shareholder Capital Cushion and will further strengthen and diversify the reserves.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Furthermore, the company added that it would custody the BTC independently and refrain from using third-party custodians.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;While it is common practice among many institutional investors to third-party custody their Bitcoin, Tether believes in the philosophy &ldquo;Not your keys, not your bitcoin&rdquo; and takes possession of the private keys associated with all of its Bitcoin holdings.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether&rsquo;s moves to accumulate Bitcoin would make the company one of the biggest holders of the asset, joining other notable investors such as MicroStrategy boss Michael Saylor and Paul Tudor Jones.&nbsp;</p>
Capitalizing On Bitcoin&nbsp;
<p>Tether revealed in its Q1 2023 Assurance Report that it held around $1.5 billion worth of BTC in its reserves, along with $3.4 billion worth of gold. Additionally, 85% of its reserves are held in cash or cash-like assets such as US Treasury Bonds. Tether&rsquo;s pivot towards Bitcoin aims to help strengthen and diversify its stablecoin reserves and also capitalize on its price investment as an investment. Chief Technology Officer at Tether, Paolo Ardiono, added,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The decision to invest in Bitcoin, the world&rsquo;s first and largest cryptocurrency, is underpinned by its strength and potential as an investment asset. Bitcoin has continually proven its resilience and has emerged as a long-term store of value with substantial growth potential. Our investment in bitcoin is not only a way to enhance the performance of our portfolio, but it is also a method of aligning ourselves with a transformative technology.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The company added that it plans to use only its realized profits from investment operations to purchase Bitcoin. This means the firm would consider only the tangible gains from its operations which consist of the difference between the purchase price and the net proceeds from an asset sale. Alternatively, in the case of maturing assets such as Treasury Bills, the difference between the purchase price and the reimbursement amount. The company added that it was also focusing on developing energy and bitcoin mining infrastructure and communication systems, among other investments.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Problem With Transparency&nbsp;
<p>Tether has come under heavy criticism within the crypto space and from authorities thanks to a lack of transparency about its reserves and several controversial investment decisions. There have also been concerns about the quality of reserve assets backing its USDT stablecoin. However, despite these concerns, the USDT stablecoin has emerged as a safe haven for investors. This was outlined in March 2023 when the US banking crisis hit USDC, the second-largest stablecoin in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>USDC was severely impacted due to the sudden implosion of Silicon Valley Bank (SVB), which left a chunk of USDC&rsquo;s reserves frozen for a weekend. As a result, several stablecoins lost their dollar peg as a domino effect played out in the market. However, Tether was able to maintain its price stability thanks to a perceived disconnection and isolation from US Banks, thanks to it being incorporated in the British Virgin Islands and Hong Kong.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Uniswap Eyes Deployment On Moonbeam Parachain]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/uniswap-eyes-deployment-on-moonbeam-parachain</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-x-moonbeam-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-x-moonbeam-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uniswap-x-moonbeam-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/uniswap-eyes-deployment-on-moonbeam-parachain</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Premier decentralized exchange platform Uniswap is set to launch on Polkadot's Moonbeam parachain, with the integrations tabled through its decentralized governance platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's plans for a more diversified offering have gained traction with its proposed launch on Moonbeam, Polkadot's parachain. This move, unanimously approved on Uniswap's governance forum, is set to thrust the DEX into a promising decentralized environment that emulates Ethereum's functionality, fostering app portability. Smart contracts for the exchange are already on Moonbeam; only front-end integration and auto router updates are yet to to be implemented.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ @Uniswap - the most popular decentralized exchange by daily traded volume - is coming to Polkadot via the @MoonbeamNetwork parachain, increasing volume &amp; liquidity across the ecosystem! pic.twitter.com/lKaceLv6ce</p>
&mdash; Polkadot (@Polkadot) May 17, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Moonbeam, concentrating on a developer-friendly atmosphere similar to Ethereum, makes it seamless for developers to move their Ethereum applications over to the Polkadot network, an interconnected web of blockchains referred to as parachains. Polkadot's relay chain ensures that these parachains share security. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's current emphasis is on managing initial liquidity issues for the new platform. The proposal cautions about temporary liquidity bootstrapping absences due to market instability. As a solution, contributors to the proposed implementation are considering applying for a Moonbeam grant to expedite liquidity provision, implying the funds, if approved, would be governed by Uniswap's decentralized autonomous organization (DAO).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Omar Elassar, business development executive at Polkadot developer Parity Technologies, echoed the positive sentiments in an accompanying announcement. Elassar claims that the new integration would enhance the speed and security for Uniswap users:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Polkadot is a strong fit for Uniswap, whose users can discover everything the network&rsquo;s parachains offer, such as high performance, scalability, security, and interoperability."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polkadot is composed of intricate network of interconnected blockchain networks or "parachains", offers shared security through the Polkadot relay chain. The Moonbeam parachain, a component of this network, is strategically designed to emulate the Ethereum developer environment. This design seeks to simplify the process for developers looking to transition their Ethereum applications into the Polkadot ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap remains as the world's largest decentralized exchange by trading volume, averaging at roughly $550 million in daily movement, according to CoinMarketCap data. Born within the Ethereum network, Uniswap has been consistently extending its reach into other networks. A testament to this drive includes the launch of a BNB Chain version and its a deployment to Polygon zkEVm. Uniswap also has an iOS app version, which was met with some restriction by Apple.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The news of this integration also coincides with a related proposal on Uniswap's governance forum, where contributors she256, Michigan Blockchain, and GFX Labs proposed a Uniswap V3 integration with Coinbase's Layer 2 blockchain infrastructure, Base.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This is still subject to an on-chain governance vote, but will eventually be considered if it receives enough approval. If approved, GFX Labs manage the contracts' technical implementation on Base, following the proposal's approval. Base's potential benefits are already drawing interest from key players like Uniswap's founder Hayden Adams, who has expressed anticipation for deploying the DEX on the network via the native canonical bridge, supervised by Base's core developers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Premier decentralized exchange platform Uniswap is set to launch on Polkadot's Moonbeam parachain, with the integrations tabled through its decentralized governance platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's plans for a more diversified offering have gained traction with its proposed launch on Moonbeam, Polkadot's parachain. This move, unanimously approved on Uniswap's governance forum, is set to thrust the DEX into a promising decentralized environment that emulates Ethereum's functionality, fostering app portability. Smart contracts for the exchange are already on Moonbeam; only front-end integration and auto router updates are yet to to be implemented.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">1/ @Uniswap - the most popular decentralized exchange by daily traded volume - is coming to Polkadot via the @MoonbeamNetwork parachain, increasing volume &amp; liquidity across the ecosystem! pic.twitter.com/lKaceLv6ce</p>
&mdash; Polkadot (@Polkadot) May 17, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Moonbeam, concentrating on a developer-friendly atmosphere similar to Ethereum, makes it seamless for developers to move their Ethereum applications over to the Polkadot network, an interconnected web of blockchains referred to as parachains. Polkadot's relay chain ensures that these parachains share security. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap's current emphasis is on managing initial liquidity issues for the new platform. The proposal cautions about temporary liquidity bootstrapping absences due to market instability. As a solution, contributors to the proposed implementation are considering applying for a Moonbeam grant to expedite liquidity provision, implying the funds, if approved, would be governed by Uniswap's decentralized autonomous organization (DAO).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Omar Elassar, business development executive at Polkadot developer Parity Technologies, echoed the positive sentiments in an accompanying announcement. Elassar claims that the new integration would enhance the speed and security for Uniswap users:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;Polkadot is a strong fit for Uniswap, whose users can discover everything the network&rsquo;s parachains offer, such as high performance, scalability, security, and interoperability."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polkadot is composed of intricate network of interconnected blockchain networks or "parachains", offers shared security through the Polkadot relay chain. The Moonbeam parachain, a component of this network, is strategically designed to emulate the Ethereum developer environment. This design seeks to simplify the process for developers looking to transition their Ethereum applications into the Polkadot ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Uniswap remains as the world's largest decentralized exchange by trading volume, averaging at roughly $550 million in daily movement, according to CoinMarketCap data. Born within the Ethereum network, Uniswap has been consistently extending its reach into other networks. A testament to this drive includes the launch of a BNB Chain version and its a deployment to Polygon zkEVm. Uniswap also has an iOS app version, which was met with some restriction by Apple.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The news of this integration also coincides with a related proposal on Uniswap's governance forum, where contributors she256, Michigan Blockchain, and GFX Labs proposed a Uniswap V3 integration with Coinbase's Layer 2 blockchain infrastructure, Base.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This is still subject to an on-chain governance vote, but will eventually be considered if it receives enough approval. If approved, GFX Labs manage the contracts' technical implementation on Base, following the proposal's approval. Base's potential benefits are already drawing interest from key players like Uniswap's founder Hayden Adams, who has expressed anticipation for deploying the DEX on the network via the native canonical bridge, supervised by Base's core developers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LayerZero and Immunefi Unveil $15m Bug Bounty]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/layerzero-and-immunefi-unveil-15m-bug-bounty</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/layerzero-x-immunefi-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/layerzero-x-immunefi-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/layerzero-x-immunefi-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/layerzero-and-immunefi-unveil-15m-bug-bounty</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero Labs and Immunefi have announced their collaboration to launch an unprecedented $15 million bug bounty program. The initiative sets a new benchmark in the crypto industry, surpassing the previous record holder, MakerDAO&rsquo;s $10 million bug bounty.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">LayerZero Labs, renowned for its omnichain interoperability protocol LayerZero, and Immunefi, a leader in bug bounty and security services, have partnered to stimulate the work of smart contract information security researchers and white hat hackers in identifying potential vulnerabilities and attack vectors on blockchain protocols such as LayerZero. The sheer size of this bounty sets it apart from LayerZero&rsquo;s previous initiatives and underlines its prioritization of smart contract security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The reward fund is earmarked to come from the equity entity of LayerZero Labs. LayerZero's CEO, Bryan Pellegrino, emphasized the commitment to security over all other facets:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;The security of [a] protocol comes before anything else.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Immunefi, on the other hand, is no stranger to the security challenges of the crypto sector. Providing security services for over $60 billion in user funds across a wide range of crypto-based projects and blockchain firms such as SushiSwap, Optimism, Polygon, Synthetix, and Chainlink, among others, Immunefi has paid out over $75 million in bug bounties to date.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero's recent $120 million Series B funding round has catapulted its valuation to $3 billion. Its distinctive messaging protocol allows for various types of message exchanges between blockchains, eliminating the need for intermediaries. LayerZero currently connects over 30 mainnet blockchains, including two non-Ethereum Virtual Machines (EVMs) and Aptos.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, the crypto world hasn't been without its fair share of financial damages of late. According to Immunefi&rsquo;s Crypto Losses 2022 report, over $3.9 billion was "lost" last year. Notably, this represents a 51.2% reduction compared to 2021's loss figures. Specifically, $3.77 billion of the 2022 losses resulted from 134 hacking incidents, and fraud accounted for another $175 million lost over 34 incidents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero, launched in March 2022, has seen a transaction volume exceeding $15 billion within its first 14 months. Demonstrating its stringent adherence to security measures, LayerZero has not experienced a security exploit or hack since inception. Last year, the blockchain infrastructure firm invested around $5 million in auditing to ensure the security of its code before its release to the public.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the overall crypto market has seen fewer losses recently, the actual amounts involved are still substantial. For instance, in March, a massive $200 million was pilfered from the crypto lending platform, Euler Finance. This exploit, albeit substantial, only ranks among the top 20 in recent crypto history.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Security stands as a paramount concern for anyone involved in the crypto space. As Pellegrino asserts:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;For anyone building in the space, security should be the priority above all else. If you don&rsquo;t have good security, eventually you will be hacked.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The bug bounty program offers a substantial maximum reward of $15 million for the discovery of a high-severity vulnerability. The precise payout is determined based on the Immunefi Vulnerability Severity Classification System, which assesses the impact of the identified vulnerability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bug reports submitted to the program need to include a viable proof-of-concept (PoC) that demonstrates a tangible impact on the scoped assets. The terms explicitly state that theoretical explanations or statements alone cannot be accepted as PoCs &ndash; concrete code is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The program outlines that critical smart contract vulnerabilities found on major blockchains and Layer 2 protocols such as Ethereum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism, and Fantom may garner a reward of either $250,000 or 10% of the endangered asset's value at the time of reporting, whichever is higher. For all other chains, the payout for critical vulnerabilities starts at $25,000. Rewards for non-critical vulnerabilities are evaluated based on internal criteria.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero Labs and Immunefi have announced their collaboration to launch an unprecedented $15 million bug bounty program. The initiative sets a new benchmark in the crypto industry, surpassing the previous record holder, MakerDAO&rsquo;s $10 million bug bounty.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">LayerZero Labs, renowned for its omnichain interoperability protocol LayerZero, and Immunefi, a leader in bug bounty and security services, have partnered to stimulate the work of smart contract information security researchers and white hat hackers in identifying potential vulnerabilities and attack vectors on blockchain protocols such as LayerZero. The sheer size of this bounty sets it apart from LayerZero&rsquo;s previous initiatives and underlines its prioritization of smart contract security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The reward fund is earmarked to come from the equity entity of LayerZero Labs. LayerZero's CEO, Bryan Pellegrino, emphasized the commitment to security over all other facets:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;The security of [a] protocol comes before anything else.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Immunefi, on the other hand, is no stranger to the security challenges of the crypto sector. Providing security services for over $60 billion in user funds across a wide range of crypto-based projects and blockchain firms such as SushiSwap, Optimism, Polygon, Synthetix, and Chainlink, among others, Immunefi has paid out over $75 million in bug bounties to date.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero's recent $120 million Series B funding round has catapulted its valuation to $3 billion. Its distinctive messaging protocol allows for various types of message exchanges between blockchains, eliminating the need for intermediaries. LayerZero currently connects over 30 mainnet blockchains, including two non-Ethereum Virtual Machines (EVMs) and Aptos.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, the crypto world hasn't been without its fair share of financial damages of late. According to Immunefi&rsquo;s Crypto Losses 2022 report, over $3.9 billion was "lost" last year. Notably, this represents a 51.2% reduction compared to 2021's loss figures. Specifically, $3.77 billion of the 2022 losses resulted from 134 hacking incidents, and fraud accounted for another $175 million lost over 34 incidents.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">LayerZero, launched in March 2022, has seen a transaction volume exceeding $15 billion within its first 14 months. Demonstrating its stringent adherence to security measures, LayerZero has not experienced a security exploit or hack since inception. Last year, the blockchain infrastructure firm invested around $5 million in auditing to ensure the security of its code before its release to the public.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the overall crypto market has seen fewer losses recently, the actual amounts involved are still substantial. For instance, in March, a massive $200 million was pilfered from the crypto lending platform, Euler Finance. This exploit, albeit substantial, only ranks among the top 20 in recent crypto history.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Security stands as a paramount concern for anyone involved in the crypto space. As Pellegrino asserts:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;For anyone building in the space, security should be the priority above all else. If you don&rsquo;t have good security, eventually you will be hacked.&rdquo;</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The bug bounty program offers a substantial maximum reward of $15 million for the discovery of a high-severity vulnerability. The precise payout is determined based on the Immunefi Vulnerability Severity Classification System, which assesses the impact of the identified vulnerability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bug reports submitted to the program need to include a viable proof-of-concept (PoC) that demonstrates a tangible impact on the scoped assets. The terms explicitly state that theoretical explanations or statements alone cannot be accepted as PoCs &ndash; concrete code is required.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The program outlines that critical smart contract vulnerabilities found on major blockchains and Layer 2 protocols such as Ethereum, BNB Chain, Avalanche, Polygon, Arbitrum, Optimism, and Fantom may garner a reward of either $250,000 or 10% of the endangered asset's value at the time of reporting, whichever is higher. For all other chains, the payout for critical vulnerabilities starts at $25,000. Rewards for non-critical vulnerabilities are evaluated based on internal criteria.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Crypto Market with TMS Network, DogeMiyagi, and TRON!]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/revolutionizing-crypto-market-with-tms-network-dogemiyagi-and-tron</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-592.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-592.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-592.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/revolutionizing-crypto-market-with-tms-network-dogemiyagi-and-tron</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, all eyes are on DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) and its potential to replicate the success of TMS Network, while updates on ChainLink (LINK) and TRON (TRX) keep investors engaged. Launched in May 2023, DogeMiyagi has swiftly gained momentum, drawing inspiration from "The Karate Kid" and the iconic Doge meme.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With a growing market cap, this meme coin is on the verge of virality, joining the ranks of DOGE and PEPE. But what sets DogeMiyagi apart is its strategic alignment with the Ethereum staking trend and its commitment to community and decentralization. Will MIYAGI unleash its meme coin magic and become the next big sensation in the crypto world?&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Updates on Chainlink and TRON</p>
<p>TRX Sets the Stage for Higher Liquidity:</p>
<p>Tron Stake 2.0 is on the horizon, offering increased staking flexibility and durations. This upgrade could attract more users, leading to higher rewards and liquidity. However, TRX's price action remains limited, consolidating around $0.065.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, Chainlink (LINK) establishes a solid support level, hinting at potential growth with a golden cross formation in sight. However, it's TMS Network (TMSN) that steals the spotlight with its record-breaking presale.</p>
<p>Trading Reinvented</p>
<p>TMS Network (TMSN) has gained momentous levels of popularity as it revolutionizes the trading experience with its decentralized platform, which allows users to trade cryptocurrencies, stocks, CFDs, and Forex seamlessly, all backed by secure and transparent blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>No middlemen mean lower costs and faster transactions. With an intuitive interface and educational resources, TMSN empowers traders of all levels. Users can say goodbye to high fees and welcome instant deposits and withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>From Karate Chops to Crypto Swaps</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) enters the bullish market with a meme coin karate chop! Inspired by "The Karate Kid" and the legendary Doge meme, DogeMiyagi has swiftly gained momentum since its recent launch. With a growing market cap, this coin is on the path to virality, joining the meme coin season rally with SHIB and PEPE!</p>
<p>Nonetheless, what really makes DogeMiyagi stand out is its perfect timing with the Ethereum staking trend. As Ethereum transitions to Proof-of-Stake, staking rewards have reached all-time highs, attracting investors to Ethereum-based projects, including meme coins like DogeMiyagi. Drawing inspiration from the iconic character Mr. Miyagi, DogeMiyagi embodies profound life lessons and has even earned the prestigious Medal of Blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It's not just about the memes but also about embracing a community that believes in decentralization and shared ownership. DogeMiyagi's vibrant ecosystem offers NFTs, crypto discussions flow, and fun side-splitting memes. The meme coin lets holders seamlessly interact with other wallets, all while staying true to sustainability principles.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the cryptocurrency market is undergoing continuous evolution, presenting great potential for DogeMiyagi as it rapidly gains momentum. Furthermore, with TMSN revolutionizing the trading experience, the world of crypto offers traders fresh opportunities. This dynamic and ever-changing realm of finance makes it an exhilarating time to be actively involved!</p>
<p>For more info on DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI):</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, all eyes are on DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) and its potential to replicate the success of TMS Network, while updates on ChainLink (LINK) and TRON (TRX) keep investors engaged. Launched in May 2023, DogeMiyagi has swiftly gained momentum, drawing inspiration from "The Karate Kid" and the iconic Doge meme.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With a growing market cap, this meme coin is on the verge of virality, joining the ranks of DOGE and PEPE. But what sets DogeMiyagi apart is its strategic alignment with the Ethereum staking trend and its commitment to community and decentralization. Will MIYAGI unleash its meme coin magic and become the next big sensation in the crypto world?&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Updates on Chainlink and TRON</p>
<p>TRX Sets the Stage for Higher Liquidity:</p>
<p>Tron Stake 2.0 is on the horizon, offering increased staking flexibility and durations. This upgrade could attract more users, leading to higher rewards and liquidity. However, TRX's price action remains limited, consolidating around $0.065.&nbsp;</p>
<p>On the other hand, Chainlink (LINK) establishes a solid support level, hinting at potential growth with a golden cross formation in sight. However, it's TMS Network (TMSN) that steals the spotlight with its record-breaking presale.</p>
<p>Trading Reinvented</p>
<p>TMS Network (TMSN) has gained momentous levels of popularity as it revolutionizes the trading experience with its decentralized platform, which allows users to trade cryptocurrencies, stocks, CFDs, and Forex seamlessly, all backed by secure and transparent blockchain technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>No middlemen mean lower costs and faster transactions. With an intuitive interface and educational resources, TMSN empowers traders of all levels. Users can say goodbye to high fees and welcome instant deposits and withdrawals.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>From Karate Chops to Crypto Swaps</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) enters the bullish market with a meme coin karate chop! Inspired by "The Karate Kid" and the legendary Doge meme, DogeMiyagi has swiftly gained momentum since its recent launch. With a growing market cap, this coin is on the path to virality, joining the meme coin season rally with SHIB and PEPE!</p>
<p>Nonetheless, what really makes DogeMiyagi stand out is its perfect timing with the Ethereum staking trend. As Ethereum transitions to Proof-of-Stake, staking rewards have reached all-time highs, attracting investors to Ethereum-based projects, including meme coins like DogeMiyagi. Drawing inspiration from the iconic character Mr. Miyagi, DogeMiyagi embodies profound life lessons and has even earned the prestigious Medal of Blockchain.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It's not just about the memes but also about embracing a community that believes in decentralization and shared ownership. DogeMiyagi's vibrant ecosystem offers NFTs, crypto discussions flow, and fun side-splitting memes. The meme coin lets holders seamlessly interact with other wallets, all while staying true to sustainability principles.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the cryptocurrency market is undergoing continuous evolution, presenting great potential for DogeMiyagi as it rapidly gains momentum. Furthermore, with TMSN revolutionizing the trading experience, the world of crypto offers traders fresh opportunities. This dynamic and ever-changing realm of finance makes it an exhilarating time to be actively involved!</p>
<p>For more info on DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI):</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Countdown For Big Eyes Coin Begins: Cryptocurrency Launch, BIG Things Are Coming]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/countdown-for-big-eyes-coin-begins-cryptocurrency-launch-big-things-are-coming</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-590.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-590.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-590.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/countdown-for-big-eyes-coin-begins-cryptocurrency-launch-big-things-are-coming</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has grown in leaps and bounds since it first began. With the induction of the first cryptocurrency, there was an atmosphere of innovation and advancement as it ushered in a pathway and a glimpse into the future of finance.</p>
<p>Since then, we have had many coins rise and fall, some being completely obliterated by the competitive nature of the market. However, the latest innovation in the market is that of meme-coins, like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, which bring about a light-hearted nature to the normally serious demeanor of the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG) has become a force to be reckoned with since last year with its speedy growth, sublime rewards system, and grand community of investors. The platform has shown great potential with everything they have done, and as they prepare to launch in less than a month, the next six months seem like an exciting time for the community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin has a range of products and services in store for investors and loyal users, as well as easily accessible tokens which are to be listed on popular exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New Journey, New Rewards</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin has worked diligently to deliver the best quality products and services to its community of users and investors. During the ongoing presale, the platform has a wide variety of profitable opportunities. From the loot boxes to NFTs to bonuses, Big Eyes Coin did not shy away from rewarding its clientele in the best of ways.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the next six months, Big Eyes Coin community members can look forward to a Big Eyes Coin Casino, which will have over 4,000 games and a variety of Play-to-Earn (P2E) games that come with their rewards. The casino will be fully operational in August, and users can play using only $BIG, which will likely reduce the supply of tokens on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now is a fantastic chance to earn tokens during the current presale and build up your Casino Kitty. Buy your tokens now using the code END300 for a 300% bonus and avoid scarcity!</p>
<p>BIG Plans For Exchanges</p>
<p>When a cryptocurrency is listed on an exchange, it is the same as being picked up by a record label to being starred in a big movie - it brings about recognition and credibility to the brand. This is the next step for Big Eyes Coin because the platform wants to develop a larger community of investors through visibility, authenticity, and accessibility. The best way to do so is through exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin plans to launch on several exchanges, possibly starting with Tier 1 Exchange and Uniswap and including Bitget, CoinEx, BitMart, Deepcoin, and Gate.io, to name a few. This will ensure that Big Eyes Coin maintains a steady level of growth and can gain access to a wider and possibly global market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Altogether, the months following the launch are bound to be some of the most exciting times for both Big Eyes Coin and the community. Although Big Eyes Coin is going to be now on the market, it is speculated to be a solid competitor for Dogecoin and Shiba Inu based on how well it performed during the presale. Once the launch happens, Big Eyes Coin will face an exhilarating phase of growth, one that will be most profitable for both the platform and its investors.</p>
<p>For More on Big Eyes Coin (BIG):</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Opensea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has grown in leaps and bounds since it first began. With the induction of the first cryptocurrency, there was an atmosphere of innovation and advancement as it ushered in a pathway and a glimpse into the future of finance.</p>
<p>Since then, we have had many coins rise and fall, some being completely obliterated by the competitive nature of the market. However, the latest innovation in the market is that of meme-coins, like Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, which bring about a light-hearted nature to the normally serious demeanor of the industry.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG) has become a force to be reckoned with since last year with its speedy growth, sublime rewards system, and grand community of investors. The platform has shown great potential with everything they have done, and as they prepare to launch in less than a month, the next six months seem like an exciting time for the community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin has a range of products and services in store for investors and loyal users, as well as easily accessible tokens which are to be listed on popular exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>New Journey, New Rewards</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin has worked diligently to deliver the best quality products and services to its community of users and investors. During the ongoing presale, the platform has a wide variety of profitable opportunities. From the loot boxes to NFTs to bonuses, Big Eyes Coin did not shy away from rewarding its clientele in the best of ways.&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the next six months, Big Eyes Coin community members can look forward to a Big Eyes Coin Casino, which will have over 4,000 games and a variety of Play-to-Earn (P2E) games that come with their rewards. The casino will be fully operational in August, and users can play using only $BIG, which will likely reduce the supply of tokens on exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Now is a fantastic chance to earn tokens during the current presale and build up your Casino Kitty. Buy your tokens now using the code END300 for a 300% bonus and avoid scarcity!</p>
<p>BIG Plans For Exchanges</p>
<p>When a cryptocurrency is listed on an exchange, it is the same as being picked up by a record label to being starred in a big movie - it brings about recognition and credibility to the brand. This is the next step for Big Eyes Coin because the platform wants to develop a larger community of investors through visibility, authenticity, and accessibility. The best way to do so is through exchanges.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin plans to launch on several exchanges, possibly starting with Tier 1 Exchange and Uniswap and including Bitget, CoinEx, BitMart, Deepcoin, and Gate.io, to name a few. This will ensure that Big Eyes Coin maintains a steady level of growth and can gain access to a wider and possibly global market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Altogether, the months following the launch are bound to be some of the most exciting times for both Big Eyes Coin and the community. Although Big Eyes Coin is going to be now on the market, it is speculated to be a solid competitor for Dogecoin and Shiba Inu based on how well it performed during the presale. Once the launch happens, Big Eyes Coin will face an exhilarating phase of growth, one that will be most profitable for both the platform and its investors.</p>
<p>For More on Big Eyes Coin (BIG):</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Opensea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
