<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:16:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Unveils Capital Connect for VIP Clients</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-unveils-capital-connect-for-vip-clients/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250012</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/BinanceEurope.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/BinanceEurope.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Capital Connect is a "self-service" platform for all Binance VIP users in non-restricted regions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance is rolling out a new platform that seeks to connect institutional investors with crypto investment fund managers.</p>
<p>At launch, the new platform, dubbed &#8216;Capital Connect,&#8217; will be available to Binance VIP-level users including asset and fund managers, brokers, hedge funds, family offices and high net-worth individuals, liquidity providers, and corporations.</p>
<h2>Binance&#8217;s Free Service for VIP Clients</h2>
<p>According to the official <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/vip/binance-vip-and-institutional-launches-capital-connect-connecting-investors-and-investment-managers-4081079031133794475" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post,</a> the service will be free for all existing Binance VIP clients in non-restricted regions. This essentially means that the crypto exchange will not charge any fee or commission. Binance VIP-level users who have completed the verification process may apply for access to the platform as either an Investor or an Investment Manager, or both.</p>
<p>As an Investor, users will be able to browse various funds and diversify their portfolio allocations. They can also pick Investment Managers based on strategies, redemption terms, fees, assets under management (AUM), and Sharpe Ratios.</p>
<p>Investors are the only ones who can initiate connection requests, following which Investment Managers can scan through the investors&#8217; profiles before accepting a connection. Investment Managers are required to provide records of monthly returns verified by reputable fund administrators. This data can assist investors in referencing a fund&#8217;s past performance.</p>
<p>Binance, on the other hand, will not be involved in any discussions between parties after a successful connection has been established. The crypto exchange also said it will not guarantee any investment returns.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;With Capital Connect, one of our goals has been to provide a new way for Investors and Investment Managers to connect. We hope this will also demonstrate our commitment to supporting the growth and adoption of digital assets.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>FUD and Expansion</h2>
<p>The latest offering comes amidst Binance facing massive pressure on the US regulatory front.</p>
<p>Pouring money and resources into global compliance over the past year has helped Binance win approvals across several jurisdictions in Europe, such as France, Italy, Lithuania, Spain, Cyprus, and Poland.</p>
<p>The CZ-led company is also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-when-binance-japan-will-officially-launch/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">planning</a> to reenter the Japanese market after June this year via its acquisition of regulated crypto exchange Sakura Exchange BitCoin.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-unveils-capital-connect-for-vip-clients/" rel="nofollow">Binance Unveils Capital Connect for VIP Clients</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Congress Holds First Joint Committee Hearing on Crypto Legislation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-congress-holds-first-joint-committee-hearing-on-crypto-legislation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250099</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/USCongress.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/USCongress.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Certain congressmen are still unsure whether digital assets deserve unique legislation.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Two committees in the US House of Representatives held the first-ever joint hearing related to crypto on Wednesday, seeking to carve a path forward to legislation on digital assets. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The early stages of the hearing proved combative, with certain Democrats questioning whether crypto-specific legislation should be signed at all. </span></p>
<h2>A Focus On Making Law</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i43Ckphd9vo&amp;ab_channel=GOPFinancialServices" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">hearing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, held by the House Financial Services Committee (HFSC) and the House Agriculture Committee, was titled “The Future of Digital Assets: Measuring the Regulatory Gaps in the Digital Assets Market.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">HFSC chairman Patrick McHenry </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-president-will-sign-crypto-legislation-within-12-months-cynthia-lummis-patrick-mchenry-consensus-2023-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">announced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the hearing would take place this month at Consensus 2023 in April, confirming that it would relate to the market structure surrounding digital assets. In his opening remarks, McHenry stressed to his fellow committee members that “the purpose here is to make law.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“We need to get this right, for a couple of reasons,” he said. “One is to harness innovation and enable consumer protection. The other is the ensure that the CFTC and the Securities and Exchange Commission will work together to ensure that consumers are protected, unlike what is currently happening.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">His counterpart and ranking Democrat within the committee, Maxine Waters, agreed that it was time to get back to drafting </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/democrats-are-not-happy-with-house-committees-draft-stablecoin-bill/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">legislation</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> –citing limits in the Security and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s authority to go after fraudulent crypto firms. “These should be bipartisan concerns, and legislation to address them should have a path to the President’s desk.” </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Stephen Lynch, the senior Democrat on the digital assets subcommittee, wasn’t entirely in agreement, however. He claimed that creating new legislation for digital assets seems “redundant and unnecessary” given that the financial system’s current securities laws have “sustained massive innovation in our financial system for decades.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">His comments were largely in line with those of SEC chairman Gary Gensler, who has repeatedly stated that the laws on the books provide his agency with </span><a href="https://twitter.com/GaryGensler/status/1651624244445421591" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">ample authority</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to regulate crypto. However, the Commodities and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has been at odds with the SEC for years, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cftc-claims-crypto-assets-are-commodities-in-lawsuit-against-ex-deutsche-bank-investment-banker/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">arguing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the CFTC has more authority over crypto than Gensler recognizes. </span></p>
<h2>Crypto’s Future in the United States</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Toward the end of the hearing, Brad Sherman – the Californian Democrat and prominent crypto critic – questioned whether digital assets should even have a future in the United States. He referred to cryptocurrencies as a “hidden money system” that diverts capital investment from useful industries, and whose “announced purpose” is to defeat sanctions and tax laws. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Crypto bros make money literally by making money, and they’ve made over a trillion dollars,” said Sherman during a separate hearing later on Wednesday. “They&#8217;ll accuse the U.S. government of making money out of thin air. Maybe we do, but we&#8217;re the U.S. government.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">HFSC Chair McHenry concluded the hearing by claiming that the SEC’s current approach to disclosure statements and registrations “don’t work for digital assets,” and that the CFTC needs additional authority over the market.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The CFTC and SEC alone can’t do this. Congress must act,” he said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last month, McHenry said he expects that the President will have signed some piece of crypto legislation into law within the next 12 months. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-congress-holds-first-joint-committee-hearing-on-crypto-legislation/" rel="nofollow">US Congress Holds First Joint Committee Hearing on Crypto Legislation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Court Restrains Arthur Hayes from Abusing 3AC Founder Su Zhu: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/court-restrains-arthur-hayes-from-abusing-3ac-founder-su-zhu-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 21:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250031</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/arthur_hayes2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hayes has constantly asked the Three Arrows co-founder and his partner to repay a $6 million debt incurred following 3AC's demise.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Su Zhu, the co-founder of the now-defunct cryptocurrency hedge fund Three Arrows Capital (3AC), has obtained a restraining order from a Singaporean court against Arthur Hayes, the co-founder and former CEO of crypto exchange BitMEX.</p>
<p>According to a court <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/10/three-arrows-founder-su-zhu-obtains-singapore-restraining-order-against-arthur-hayes-over-harassment/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a> seen by CoinDesk, the restraining order prohibits Hayes from using any insulting or abusive communication that would cause Zhu alarm, harassment, or distress.</p>
<h2>Hayes Restrained From Abusing Zhu</h2>
<p>In the past few months, Hayes has constantly asked Zhu and his 3AC partner Kyle Davies to repay a $6 million debt that stemmed from the hedge fund&#8217;s collapse last year.</p>
<p>Recall that Three Arrows Capital was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-arrows-capital-ordered-into-liquidation-by-a-birtish-virgin-islands-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> into liquidation by a British Virgin Islands court in June due to challenges it faced amid the first wave of the 2022 crypto winter caused by the Terra-Luna ecosystem <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-700-million-liquidated-as-terra-luna-crashes-below-1/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse</a>. 3AC&#8217;s demise, which sent ripple effects through the industry, left the hedge fund owing its creditors more than $1 billion.</p>
<p>Zhu and Davies disappeared after 3AC&#8217;s failure, only to surface several months later in a Bloomberg interview announcing the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/opnx-crypto-exchange-formed-by-3ac-founders-goes-live/" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of OPNX, an exchange for trading bankruptcy claims. The duo launched OPNX on April 4, with a planned giveaway of its native token FLEX.</p>
<p>In several tweets, Hayes criticized and mocked the 3AC co-founders&#8217; attempts to raise funds for their new platform. He once <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arthur-hayes-zhu-su-ann-kyle-davies-led-opnx-received-funding-from-bahrain/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that &#8220;a little birdie&#8221; told him that the duo had raised big money from a sovereign wealth fund in Bahrain.</p>
<p>The former BitMEX CEO also diced their interview with Bloomberg while making fun of and criticizing some of their statements. Highlighting a section where Zhu said they failed to realize that Luna could fall to zero in a matter of days and the effect that such would have on the crypto industry, Hayes mocked them for not reading the asset&#8217;s whitepaper.</p>
<h2>No Communication Henceforth</h2>
<p>In the restraining order, Harassment Court Judge Sandra Looi Ai Lin prohibited Hayes from communicating with Zhu by any means and publishing any identity information.</p>
<p>Henceforth, the BitMEX co-founder is banned from using abusive or threatening words on Zhu. Judge Lin also ruled that the order could be served to Hayes via his Twitter account.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/court-restrains-arthur-hayes-from-abusing-3ac-founder-su-zhu-report/" rel="nofollow">Court Restrains Arthur Hayes from Abusing 3AC Founder Su Zhu: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>UK National Pleads Guilty to Stealing $8 Million in Crypto and Hacking Twitter Accounts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uk-national-pleads-guilty-to-stealing-8-million-in-crypto-and-hacking-twitter-accounts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 19:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Twitter]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249964</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TwitterHack.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/TwitterHack.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Prosecutors said he used his sophisticated technological prowess, such as SIM Swap and Cyberstalking, for malicious purposes.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joseph James O&#8217;Connor, a 23-year-old British citizen extradited from Spain to the United States on April 26, pleaded guilty to multiple charges, including hacking the social media platform Twitter in 2020.</p>
<p>O&#8217;Connor, who also uses the online name PlugwalkJoe, has been charged with stealing cryptocurrencies worth $794,000 from a Manhattan-based company through a SIM Swap attack. U.S. prosecutors said O&#8217;Connor would forfeit the funds and pay his victims restitution.</p>
<p>Besides, O’Connor has been indicted for hacking Twitter and Tik Tok accounts and promoting fraudulent schemes. He has pleaded guilty to all these charges, and he may face a maximum sentence of 77 years on all counts of charges.</p>
<h2>Malicious Acts</h2>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Joseph O&#8217;Connor, a/k/a &#8220;PlugwalkJoe,&#8221; used his sophisticated technological abilities for malicious purposes – conducting a complex SIM swap attack to steal large amounts of cryptocurrency, hacking Twitter, conducting computer intrusions to take over social media accounts, and even cyberstalking two victims, including a minor victim,&#8221; U.S. Attorney Damian Williams said in a <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/uk-citizen-extradited-and-pleads-guilty-cybercrime-offenses" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>O&#8217;Connor&#8217;s malicious exploits included hacking of verified Twitter accounts of Tesla CEO Elon Musk and Joe Biden, a presidential candidate at that time. In addition, Reuters <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/uk-citizen-extradited-us-pleads-guilty-2020-twitter-hack-2023-05-09/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> the Twitter accounts of Barack Obama, Bill Gates, Benjamin Netanyahu, Jeff Bezos, Kim Kardashian, Kanye West, and Michael Bloomberg were also affected.</p>
<p>The news agency added that he used these accounts with millions of followers to solicit digital currency, forcing Twitter to stop publishing messages from these profiles for several hours until those were thoroughly sanitized and secured.</p>
<h2>Scams on the Rise</h2>
<p>A recent FBI <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/2-5-billion-stolen-from-us-victims-via-crypto-investment-scams-in-2022-fbi-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> revealed that U.S. citizens lost over $10 billion in online frauds in 2022, out of which $2.57 billion was drained by various crypto investment scams. Hackers often break into famous individuals&#8217; social media accounts, promote fraudulent crypto investment schemes, and prey on unsuspecting investors. In 2021, U.S. citizens lost only $907 million in crypto scams.</p>
<p>Scams through verified Twitter accounts <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/scams-impersonating-vitalik-buterin-mount-amid-the-merge/" data-wpel-link="internal">increased</a> notably ahead of Ethereum Merge. Amid the hype and excitement during the transition, in one instance, malicious entities hacked the official Twitter handle of Go First Airline and changed it to vitalik.eth. The display picture was also replaced with that of Vitalik Buterin. The compromised account then promoted a fake giveaway scam of $100,000 ETH.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uk-national-pleads-guilty-to-stealing-8-million-in-crypto-and-hacking-twitter-accounts/" rel="nofollow">UK National Pleads Guilty to Stealing $8 Million in Crypto and Hacking Twitter Accounts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Held on Exchanges Drops to 5-Year Lows: Santiment</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-held-on-exchanges-drops-to-5-year-lows-santiment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249963</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[More and more HODLers seem to prefer to store their crypto on cold wallets than deal with exchanges.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The crypto analytics platform &#8211; Santiment &#8211; indicated that the amount of bitcoin held on digital asset exchanges has recently plummeted below 6%. The last time the figures were that low was in December 2017.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The decreased trust in centralized platforms intensified shortly after the fallout of FTX (one of the leaders in its field prior to its bankruptcy). Binance has also seen a rise in bitcoin outflows during the past several months, signaling that many users prefer to rely on self-custody over a third-party custodian.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTC Holders Keep Losing Confidence in Exchanges</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1655696154389278721" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">analyzed</a> by Santiment, bitcoin&#8217;s supply held on exchanges has fallen to 5.84% &#8211; the lowest point in the past five and a half years.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249977" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249977" style="width: 778px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249977" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment.png" alt="BTC's Supply on Exchanges" width="778" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment.png 2106w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-300x154.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-1024x527.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-768x395.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-1536x790.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-2048x1053.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Santiment-50x26.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 778px) 100vw, 778px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249977" class="wp-caption-text">BTC&#8217;s Supply on Exchanges, Source: Santiment</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The rapid shift from custodians to self-custody methods started at the beginning of 2022 and continued throughout the following months. A steep decline occurred after November last year when the amount of BTC sitting on centralized platforms dropped under 7%. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX meltdown</a> could be considered a major factor. Back then, many investors lost trust in exchanges considering the shocking collapse of the once-prominent entity that was valued at over $32 billion. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance &#8211; the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; witnessed a massive wave of customer withdrawals in December last year, which (according to CEO Zhao) was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1602905590384181248" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">triggered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by FUD.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CZ assured that his company will remain a solid custodian, suggesting that people should feel protected when storing cryptocurrency holdings there. The rest who have any doubts should feel free to transfer their stash in cold wallets, he added.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance&#8217;s Recent BTC Outflows</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-wallets-see-huge-spikes-in-bitcoin-outflows-suspends-btc-transactions/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> earlier this week, over 160,000 BTC (worth $4.6 billion at the time) </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">left</span><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> one of the platform&#8217;s wallets in what was described as the largest single withdrawal in its history. Analyst Colin Wu shed more light on the move, arguing it is likely that &#8220;the Binance cold wallet was internally adjusted to a new address, and the new address did not transfer out after receiving funds.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that the company temporarily suspended BTC withdrawals a day earlier due to network congestion. The disturbance lasted a few hours, and operations returned back to normal. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange halted transactions once again on May 8 &#8220;due to the large volume of pending transactions.&#8221; CZ remained unfazed, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1655447058864566273" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">using</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his signature number &#8220;4&#8221; to indicate that the issue was not serious. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;There are some FUD about BTC withdrawal issues. Here is why. Bitcoin network fees are fluctuating, 18x in a month,&#8221; he explained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/binance" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sorted out</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the difficulties in the following hours and thanked its users for their patience.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-held-on-exchanges-drops-to-5-year-lows-santiment/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Held on Exchanges Drops to 5-Year Lows: Santiment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Biden Advocates for an End to Tax Loopholes That Benefit &#8216;Wealthy Crypto Investors&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/biden-advocates-for-an-end-to-tax-loopholes-that-benefit-wealthy-crypto-investors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249984</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/JB-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/JB-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The U.S. president believes wealthy crypto investors are benefiting from tax loopholes that should be closed. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>U.S. President Joe Biden is advocating for an end to tax loopholes that benefit what he described as &#8220;wealthy crypto investors.&#8221;</p>
<p>In a Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/POTUS/status/1655988502079602690?t=7l0fpGjfTeZ12KYUimxtig&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post</a> late Tuesday, Biden shared an infographic that read: &#8220;We think Congress should cut tax loopholes that help wealthy crypto investors.&#8221;</p>
<p>According to the post, these loopholes have cost the government around $18 billion in revenue. In his tweet, the president mentioned &#8220;MAGA House Republicans&#8221; as opposers of his tax plans.</p>
<h2>Biden Reprimands Republicans</h2>
<p>Biden stated that while he is calling for these changes, the MAGA House Republicans are in support of the tax loopholes and, in contrast, advocating cutting food safety inspections.</p>
<p>President Biden&#8217;s post sparked a lot of reaction from the crypto community on Twitter, with many wondering what tax loopholes he was referring to.</p>
<figure id="attachment_73003" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-73003" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-73003" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-scaled.jpg" alt="JoeBiden" width="2560" height="1707" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-2048x1365.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/JoeBiden-min-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-73003" class="wp-caption-text">Joe Biden. Source: CNBC</figcaption></figure>
<p>Adam Cochran, a managing partner at digital asset-focused Cinneamhain Ventures, replied to the post, saying that &#8220;crypto actually suffers compared to other assets on how gains are taxed on transfer between asset types.&#8221; He added that he would &#8220;challenge absolutely anyone to cite this supposed loophole.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Biden Proposes Changes to Crypto Taxation</h2>
<p>The latest tax plan is part of Biden&#8217;s recently proposed <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/president-bidens-2024-tax-plan-to-target-crypto-wash-trading-and-capital-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal">fiscal year 2024 budget</a>, which has not received support from Republican opposition in the U.S. House. The budget proposed a change to crypto taxation rules to target wash trading.</p>
<p>The administration noted that crypto assets were not initially subject to the same wash trading rules that apply to stocks and bonds. However, implementing these changes to apply to this emerging asset class could raise $24 billion in revenue.</p>
<p>Biden&#8217;s administration has not been supportive of crypto and has continued to introduce new harsh tax rules for the sector. For instance, the White House&#8217;s Council of Economic Advisers (CEA) is seeking a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal">punitive tax</a> of up to 30% of mining firms&#8217; electricity costs in the U.S. – a move that could negatively impact the profit of such operators.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-advocates-for-an-end-to-tax-loopholes-that-benefit-wealthy-crypto-investors/" rel="nofollow">Biden Advocates for an End to Tax Loopholes That Benefit &#8216;Wealthy Crypto Investors&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Didn’t ETH Dump After Shanghai? Interview With Nansen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-didnt-eth-dump-after-shanghai-interview-with-nansen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain Conferences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum Merge]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249730</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum_Locked.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nansen speaks on how there were surprisingly few ETH withdrawals from its staking contract following Shanghai, and how supposed Binance withdrawals in March were somewhat exaggerated. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The Shapella upgrade last month enabled validators to unstake millions of ETH from the Ethereum 2.0 contract, allowing the funds to potentially be sold on the open market. Despite this, the second-largest cryptocurrency actually increased in value after the upgrade. How come?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">At Consensus 2023, CryptoPotato sat down with representatives from Nansen, a blockchain analytics company, to discuss how things have looked on-chain since the final phase of the Merge. </span></p>
<h2>Shanghai Defies Expectations</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Going into the upgrade, Nansen Content Lead Andrew Thurman </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Blockanalia/status/1647040391911444480" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> he’d predicted that net outflows from Ethereum’s staking contract would be a weeks-long phenomenon. To his surprise, his firm found that withdrawals appeared to have flattened out within a matter of days. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We knew that entities with exposure to US regulatory, for example, Kraken and Coinbase, where there was clear indication that staking as a business was going to undergo some regulatory challenges – we know those people want to unwind their positions</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, so that&#8217;s a big overhang,” said Jason Xu – Senior Product Manager at Nansen – to CryptoPotato in an interview. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This proved true to a degree. Immediately following Shapella, Kraken alone accounted for </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">67%</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> of all principal ETH withdrawals from the staking contract. The firm was fined $30 million by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and forced to shut down its staking service prior to the upgrade. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Coinbase – which has been issued a Wells Notice by the SEC but promised to defend itself in court – was responsible for another 11%, but the withdrawal overhang from both firms has since “flattened out.” Kraken’s and Coinbase’s shares of total ETH principal withdrawals have since changed to 34.9% and 14.1%, respectively, per Nansen’s </span><a href="https://query.nansen.ai/public/dashboards/Hk93n66vsO0uvycfui8ypF2xcpNhpraxfwX5AWZJ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Shanghai dashboard</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249731" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249731" style="width: 928px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249731 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot.png" alt="" width="928" height="381" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot.png 928w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot-300x123.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot-768x315.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/newplot-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 928px) 100vw, 928px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249731" class="wp-caption-text">ETH Principal Withdrawn (All Time). Source: Nansen</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The other hypothesis, according to Xu, was that there likely wouldn&#8217;t be any heightened interest from new retail participants to start staking since they’ve already had access to liquid staking derivatives like </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Lido</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> for a long time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Such services – which provide stakers with a 1:1 convertible liquid token for their locked, staked ETH – are expected to succeed well into the future due to the difficulty for users to stake on their own. “ETH has consistently delivered on their roadmap, the technical roadmap. So I think people are confident in ETH,” he said.</span></p>
<figure style="width: 4032px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/693983534737522688/1101159206213652500/20230426_151031.jpg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><img src="https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/693983534737522688/1101159206213652500/20230426_151031.jpg" alt="" width="4032" height="2268" /></a><figcaption class="wp-caption-text">Jason Xu (Centre); Aurélie Boiteux (Right)</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As of May 8, there is over 19.3 million ETH locked away for staking – more than before Shapella had activated. Xu added that many “smart money” investors in crypto, by Nansen’s standards, are mainly holding “different variants of staked ETH.”</span></p>
<h2>FUD vs. Facts: Binance Withdrawals</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Much was said regarding a supposed </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dex-volume-unaffected-but-btc-outflows-from-binance-increase-post-cftc-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">influx of withdrawal requests</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on Binance back in March, shortly after the global crypto exchange was sued by the Commodities and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">However, when asked if these reports were true, Nansen Ecosystem Growth Manager Aurélie Boiteux said these claims “might be exaggerating a little bit.” In reality, for both Binance in that particular case as well many other large exchange withdrawals, it was really just Binance “sending to another Binance wallet.”</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We saw a lot of drama on Twitter,” she said, “ and people tend to react really too </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">quickly, maybe just for fear, for example, by fear and anything. But so far on-chain, I don&#8217;t recall a really big issue regarding regulatory in that aspect.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">While volume can vary on the exchange from day to day, Boiteux said that volume at Binance didn’t seem to experience any statistically significant change on-chain after the </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-addresses-the-cftc-in-house-trading-allegations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">CFTC lawsuit</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, unlike the FTX debacle in November. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Boiteux refused to provide any specific price predictions for the future. “We do not predict the future, that we try to understand by what&#8217;s happened before, what could be a potential price, what could be a potential bear market or bull market, et cetera,” she said. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Xu, however, remained bullish. “My opinion&#8217;s to the moon,” he said. “ That&#8217;s the politically correct answer I&#8217;m going to give.”</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-didnt-eth-dump-after-shanghai-interview-with-nansen/" rel="nofollow">Why Didn’t ETH Dump After Shanghai? Interview With Nansen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Miners Capitalizing on Ordinals Hype: Daily Revenue Hit 5-Year High at $17M</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:55:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249982</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Bitcoin_Network.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Bitcoin_Network.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin miner revenue has improved tremendously thanks to Ordinals.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For some, the Ordinals craze has wreaked havoc in the Bitcoin ecosystem. BTC&#8217;s price may have, so far, failed to capitalize on it, but that was not the case for the network miners.</p>
<p>In fact, the development has been a blessing in disguise for them.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Miner Revenue Shoots Up</h2>
<p>This month was marked by skyrocketing transaction fees and network congestion as Bitcoin Ordinals reached unprecedented heights. While Bitcoin&#8217;s price is cautiously recovering with modest gains, the network becoming increasingly expensive for transactions is potentially a welcome development for the mining industry, which faced severe battering last year.</p>
<p>In fact, Bitcoin miners earned a total of $17.75 million in revenues on May 8th. According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/n3ocortex/status/1655980326152204289" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> shared by Glassnode CTO Rafael Schultze-Kraft, such a single-day spike in mining revenue is rare.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Happy <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#bitcoin</a> miners.</p>
<p>$17.7 million USD earned through transactions fees – in a single day.</p>
<p><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4ca.png" alt="📊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/HWoFWtrdkz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/HWoFWtrdkz</a> <a href="https://t.co/6Wc4PzDwx7" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/6Wc4PzDwx7</a></p>
<p>— Rafael Schultze-Kraft (@n3ocortex) <a href="https://twitter.com/n3ocortex/status/1655980326152204289?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 9, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Upon gauging further, it was found that the Bitcoin transaction fee for May 8th surged to a whopping $31.14, a level that was last seen in April 2021.</p>
<p>The latest development also coincided with the Ordinals pushing transaction fees above mining rewards for the first time since 2017. As a result, several Bitcoin miners, including Luxor Technologies and AntPool, mined blocks where fees surpassed Bitcoin&#8217;s block subsidy of 6.25 BTC.</p>
<p>As Bitcoin Ordinals kept hitting new milestones, a new achievement came in the form of the number of daily inscriptions that more than doubled in a span of nearly ten days only. <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> that there are now more than 5.1 million Ordinal inscriptions.</p>
<p>Text-type ordinals had the highest market share after taking over their image counterpart.</p>
<p>The surge in Ordinals transactions naturally increased miner activities and subsequent fees even as the price of the flagship cryptocurrency is yet to mirror the enthusiasm.</p>
<p>Recently, one of the most prominent cryptocurrency exchanges, Binance, also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-support-bitcoin-ordinals-in-its-ntf-marketplace/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to list Bitcoin NFTs on its platform.</p>
<h2>Michael Saylor&#8217;s Take on Ordinals</h2>
<p>Not all Bitcoin advocates are happy with the remarkable success that Ordinals had witnessed. However, long-time Bitcoin bull and MicroStrategy co-founder Michael Saylor believes the latest craze could prove to be a catalyst for Bitcoin&#8217;s adoption.</p>
<p>In the PBD <a href="https://twitter.com/udiWertheimer/status/1656059727321739265" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Podcast</a>, Saylor said the development of an application that&#8217;s driving up transaction fees &#8211; at the backdrop of bank failures, hyperinflation, and lack of regulatory clarity that&#8217;s hurting the asset class &#8211; is a catalyst.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miners-capitalizing-on-ordinals-hype-daily-revenue-hit-5-year-high-at-17m/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Miners Capitalizing on Ordinals Hype: Daily Revenue Hit 5-Year High at $17M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Outer Ring MMO Early Access Pre-Alpha Date is Set: June 28</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-outer-ring-mmo-early-access-pre-alpha-date-is-set-june-28/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250046</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[⁣[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] June 28th marks an important day for the Outer Ring community as the highly anticipated MMORPG enters its Early Access Pre-Alpha phase. This version of the game will offer players the chance to create and save their profile within the ecosystem, select from 5 different species, and test character [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>⁣[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>June 28th marks an important day for the <a href="https://outerringmmo.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Outer Ring</a> community as the highly anticipated MMORPG enters its Early Access Pre-Alpha phase. This version of the game will offer players the chance to create and save their profile within the ecosystem, select from 5 different species, and test character customization options.⁣</p>
<p>Players can also expect to learn the fundamental movement mechanics and engage in their first PVP multiplayer battle with the assault rifle and pistol. Additionally, the Pre-Alpha version will feature PVE multiplayer dungeon missions, giving players the opportunity to work together and experience the dangers of the Outer Ring.⁣</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-250050" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring2.jpg" alt="Outer_Ring2" width="512" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring2.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring2-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Outer_Ring2-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>Great Silver City, the capital of Fanet, will provide players with a true MMO experience. It will also be the first time that players can walk through the streets and squares of the city and enter the first buildings constructed by Outer Ring&#8217;s partners, such as Baskonia, Team Heretics, or Kinepolis.⁣</p>
<p>It is important to note that this Early Access Pre-Alpha version is not the complete game, and many features and developments are yet to be implemented until the game&#8217;s official release. The Outer Ring MMO team will be collecting feedback from players during this phase to improve the game further.⁣</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tjQlH4WhSQY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are excited to announce the Early Access Pre-Alpha date for the Outer Ring MMO,&#8221; said Daniel Valdés, CEO of Outer Ring. &#8220;We have been working tirelessly to bring this project to life, and we are grateful for the support of our community and partners. We hope players will enjoy this version of the game and continue to play for years to come.&#8221;⁣</p></blockquote>
<p>Further information on how to access the Early Access Pre-Alpha will be revealed soon, and the Outer Ring MMO team will continue to provide updates on the game&#8217;s progress through their DevUpdates.⁣</p>
<p>For more information, please visit the Outer Ring MMO website and social media channels.⁣</p>
<h2>About the project:</h2>
<p>The Outer Ring MMO is a science fiction MMORPG with a tokenized economy. It is set in a universe inspired by the Outer Ring Saga, a book where 5 species belonging to 4 factions engage in battles to dominate planets and resources. The game&#8217;s economy is player-driven, where players create or earn all the assets. The blockchain technology is used to convert these assets and items into fungible or non-fungible tokens (NFTs). This means that players own the objects and can generate income by selling them, giving value to their time invested.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-outer-ring-mmo-early-access-pre-alpha-date-is-set-june-28/" rel="nofollow">The Outer Ring MMO Early Access Pre-Alpha Date is Set: June 28</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The $12K PEPE Airdrop: Transitioning the Memecoin Hype to Bitcoin Ordinals</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-12k-pepe-airdrop-transitioning-the-memecoin-hype-to-bitcoin-ordinals/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 12:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250001</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_cover_image.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_cover_image.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The PEPE hype is carrying through and becoming multi-chain. Ordinals Wallet airdropped PEPE-themed NFTs to some of its users.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Memecoins are hardwired into Internet culture, and crypto was not spared. From Dogecoin and Shiba Inu (SHIB) to the latest craze surrounding the popular PEPE coin, the industry has long been involved with them.</p>
<p>Now, the PEPE coin mania is also spreading across other protocols, and Bitcoin seems to be well under the radar. But it&#8217;s not exactly what you may think.</p>
<ul>
<li>Ordinals Wallet is a veteran wallet that supports the so-called NFTs on Bitcoin &#8211; Ordinals. While called NFTs, they do have their differences to legacy non-fungible tokens, as most know them on Ethereum.</li>
<li>The team behind it made headlines after it decided to airdrop Pixel Pepe&#8217;s ordinals to users who made a transaction onto their wallet or marketplace before block 777888.</li>
<li>This is essentially within the first week of the creation of Ordinals Wallet.</li>
<li>The interesting part is that the lowest floor price, at the time of the post, was around 0.4 BTC &#8211; close to a whopping $12,000.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Pixel Pepes incoming!<a href="https://twitter.com/ordinalswallet?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@ordinalswallet</a> confirmed that they had airdropped <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PixelPepes?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#PixelPepes</a> to users who made a transaction onto their wallet/marketplace before block 777888.</p>
<p>-&gt; The total supply of Pixel Pepes is 1563, and their current floor price is 0.319999 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$BTC</a> <a href="https://t.co/0iqNHUxRnc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/0iqNHUxRnc</a></p>
<p>— CryptoPotato Official (@Crypto_Potato) <a href="https://twitter.com/Crypto_Potato/status/1656264050030833666?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>Meanwhile, PEPE&#8217;s price has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-pump-and-dump-from-1-8b-market-cap-to-800m-in-4-days-hype-over/" data-wpel-link="internal">lost</a> a major chunk of its recently acquired value, and its market capitalization tumbled toward $800 million after peaking at close to $2 billion a few days ago.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-12k-pepe-airdrop-transitioning-the-memecoin-hype-to-bitcoin-ordinals/" rel="nofollow">The $12K PEPE Airdrop: Transitioning the Memecoin Hype to Bitcoin Ordinals</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
