<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Crypto Custodian Ledger Lets Users Buy Digital Assets In New PayPal Integration</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm</link><description>Crypto hardware wallet, Ledger has announced a new PayPal integration that allows its users to buy Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH).  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a joint announcement by the companies on Aug 16, Ledger Live software become fully integrated with verified PayPal users in the United States with no extra verification....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Custodian Ledger Lets Users Buy Digital Assets In New PayPal Integration&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ledger</category><category>PayPal</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Hardware wallet</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-custodian-ledger-lets-users-buy-digital-assets-new-paypal-integration.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122612/324297/paypal-media-library-orig.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="103701"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Stellar Buys Minority Stake in MoneyGram, Adidas and BAPE Reveal Limited Sneakers Auctioned via NFT Passes, Three Key Silvergate Execs Set to Leave the Company</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Stellar Buys Minority Stake in MoneyGram, Adidas and BAPE Reveal Limited Sneakers Auctioned via NFT Passes, Three Key Silvergate Execs Set to Leave the Company&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Investment</category><category>Stellar</category><category>Moneygram</category><category>NFT</category><category>Silvergate</category><category>SEC</category><category>Uzbekistan</category><category>Banking</category><category>mastercard</category><category>Moonpay</category><category>Payments</category><category>Ireland</category><category>Regulation</category><category>SIX</category><category>SDX</category><category>Security</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-stellar-buys-minority-stake-in-moneygram-adidas-and-bape-reveal-limited-sneakers-auctioned-via-nft-passes-three-key-silvergate-execs-set-to-leave-the-company.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122587/324261/screenshot-2023-08-16-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="319017"/></item><item><title>New Crypto Lobbyist Group Emerges in Washington, Seeks to Allay Misconceptions in the Sector</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency miners are getting a dedicated mining lobbyist group tasked with dispelling fears around the activity among citizens and policymakers. &lt;br /&gt;
The group, the Digital Energy Council was unveiled on Aug 15 and will now open up discussions with policymakers in Washington on the sustainability of crypto mining whilst advancing key policies to spark growth in the sector....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm"&gt;Read More: New Crypto Lobbyist Group Emerges in Washington, Seeks to Allay Misconceptions in the Sector&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Miner</category><category>Lobbyist Group</category><category>Washington</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-crypto-lobbyist-group-emerges-washington-seeks-allay-misconceptions-sector.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122599/324274/bitcoin-gf8a75ed9e-1280-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293858"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Startup Nova Labs Introduces Affordable $5 Phone Plan – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>Blockchain startup Nova Labs has announced the launch of a new phone plan that offers users unlimited text, talk, and data at just $5 per month. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Tuesday press release, Nova Labs said that the plan will initially be available only to residents of Miami or those who have received an invitation to access the product....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Startup Nova Labs Introduces Affordable $5 Phone Plan – Crypto Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Nova Labs</category><category>Telecommunication</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-startup-nova-labs-introduces-affordable-5-phone-plan-crypto-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122588/324240/iphone-500291-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="227848"/></item><item><title>Singapore Court to Adjudicate DeFiance Capital's $140 Million Dispute with 3AC Liquidators</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm</link><description>A judge in Singapore has decided that a $140 million legal dispute between bankrupt crypto hedge fund Three Arrows Capital’s (3AC) liquidators and investment firm DeFiance Capital will be heard in the city-state, against the will of the liquidators. &lt;br /&gt;
The disagreement between the parties center around assets managed by DeFiance Capital, an independently run firm that was within the 3AC corporate structure....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm"&gt;Read More: Singapore Court to Adjudicate DeFiance Capital's $140 Million Dispute with 3AC Liquidators&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Three Arrows Capital</category><category>3AC</category><category>DeFiance Capital</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/singapore-court-adjudicate-defiance-capitals-140-million-dispute-with-3ac-liquidators.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122591/324255/3ac.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="141215"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy THORChain? RUNE Price Blasts Up 60% and LPX Token Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>In a magnificent display, leading decentralized liquidity and trading protocol THORhain (RUNE) has blasted up a shocking +60% - yet, as traders race to get in on the action, many are asking is it too late to buy THORChain? &lt;br /&gt;
The pump comes amid a favourable time in THORchain tokenomics, with large swathes of supply currently in circulation and the slow onset of deflationary dynamics afoot....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy THORChain? RUNE Price Blasts Up 60% and LPX Token Can Find the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 12:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-thorchain-rune-price-blasts-up-60-lpx-token-can-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122589/324254/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="375523"/></item><item><title>Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun's Huobi-Linked Exchange WhiteBIT Raises Concerns Over Its Lending Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm</link><description>An obscure exchange with connections to Justin Sun, WhiteBIT, has sparked concerns after advertising a staggering Annual Percentage Yield (APY) of 24.8% to users depositing Tether (USDT) for a year on its lending platform, Protos reported.  &lt;br /&gt;
This rate is five times higher than the average USD money market rate, a glaring red flag for potential investors. &lt;br /&gt;
WhiteBIT's association with Justin Sun, a well-known figure in the cryptocurrency industry, raises further suspicion. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Billionaire Justin Sun's Huobi-Linked Exchange WhiteBIT Raises Concerns Over Its Lending Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Justin Sun</category><category>Huobi</category><category>USDD</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-billionaire-justin-suns-huobi-linked-exchange-whitebit-raises-concerns-over-its-lending-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122586/324237/justin-sun.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="140116"/></item><item><title>Solana Price Prediction as Tokenized Version of Bitcoin Prepares to Launch on SOL Blockchain – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm</link><description>The price of Solana (SOL) has dived by 6% today, with the altcoin's fall to $23.39 coming as the cryptocurrency market as a whole drops by 1.5% in the past 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;
This means SOL has lost 5% in a week and 15% in a month, with today's selloff largely the result of speculation that the SEC is delay all of its decisions regarding Bitcoin ETF applications until 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price Prediction as Tokenized Version of Bitcoin Prepares to Launch on SOL Blockchain – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-prediction-as-tokenized-version-of-bitcoin-prepares-launch-sol-blockchain-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122581/324236/solana-price-prediction-a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1159021"/></item><item><title>ApeCoin is Going to Zero as APE Price Drops 10% in 24 Hours While New Meme Coin Sonik Goes Viral – How to Buy Early?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm</link><description>As altcoin markets continue to take a hit, ApeCoin (APE) has fallen -10% back below the 20DMA in a tumultuous rejection from trendline resistance, leaving some fearful BAYC bagholders to question whether ApeCoin is going to zero. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes following a catastrophic year for ApeCoin, which has bled-out -93.5% since the all-time high on April 28 2022 - leaving APE price reeling in a tight descendant trading channel since the start of this summer....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm"&gt;Read More: ApeCoin is Going to Zero as APE Price Drops 10% in 24 Hours While New Meme Coin Sonik Goes Viral – How to Buy Early?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/apecoin-going-zero-as-ape-price-drops-10-24-hours-while-new-meme-coin-sonik-goes-viral-how-buy-early.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122578/324232/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="911562"/></item><item><title>PayPal Halts Crypto Sales in U.K. Until 2024 to Comply With New FCA Rules</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm</link><description>Online payment giant PayPal said it will temporarily pause crypto buying services in the UK to comply with the recent new rules for marketing cryptoassets enacted by the UK Financial Conduct Authority (FCA). &lt;br /&gt;
In a message to its customers on Tuesday, PayPal said that the crypto sales would pause effective 1 October 2023 and the service will be re-enabled in early 2024....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm"&gt;Read More: PayPal Halts Crypto Sales in U.K. Until 2024 to Comply With New FCA Rules&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/paypal-halts-crypto-sales-uk-until-2024-comply-with-new-fca-rules.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122557/324183/pexels-brett-jordan-5437587.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="4379393"/></item><item><title>Base and Linea Users Lose $460,000 as SwirlLend Vanishes in Suspected Exit Scam</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/base-linea-users-lose-460000-as-swirllend-vanishes-suspected-exit-scam.htm</link><description>SwirlLend, an Ethereum Layer 2 lending project active on the Base and Linea networks, has reportedly pulled off an exit scam that has resulted in the disappearance of an estimated $460,000 in user deposits. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a comprehensive on-chain analysis conducted by cybersecurity firm PeckShield, the SwirlLend team purportedly withdrew approximately $290,000 from the Base network and around $170,000 from the Linea network, subsequently funneling these assets to the Ethereum blockchain. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/base-linea-users-lose-460000-as-swirllend-vanishes-suspected-exit-scam.htm"&gt;Read More: Base and Linea Users Lose $460,000 as SwirlLend Vanishes in Suspected Exit Scam&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Exit Scam</category><category>Rug Pulls</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/base-linea-users-lose-460000-as-swirllend-vanishes-suspected-exit-scam.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122576/324216/exit-scam.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="179003"/></item><item><title>Major Chinese Filecoin Miner Accused of Orchestrating $83.2 Million Pyramid Scheme</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-chinese-filecoin-miner-accused-of-orchestrating-832-million-pyramid-scheme.htm</link><description>A Chinese local court has started the trial in the case of Shenzhen Shikongyun (Space-Time Cloud) Technology, a major Filecoin mining firm, for an alleged $83.2 million pyramid scheme. &lt;br /&gt;
The ongoing trial in Pingnan County in the Guangxi autonomous region involves the company's four executives, including the founders....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-chinese-filecoin-miner-accused-of-orchestrating-832-million-pyramid-scheme.htm"&gt;Read More: Major Chinese Filecoin Miner Accused of Orchestrating $83.2 Million Pyramid Scheme&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Mining</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>FIL</category><category>China</category><category>Legal</category><category>Court</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-chinese-filecoin-miner-accused-of-orchestrating-832-million-pyramid-scheme.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122559/324210/adobestock-gesrey-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="265437"/></item><item><title>Sei Price Prediction as Binance Listing Sends Price Soaring – New Airdrop Coming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sei-price-prediction-as-binance-listing-sends-price-soaring-new-airdrop-coming.htm</link><description>The Sei price has rocketed by 29% in the past 24 hours, surging to $0.256859 after the new utility token was added to Binance and other major exchanges yesterday. &lt;br /&gt;
The native token of new layer-one blockchain Sei, which is designed to facilitate speedy cross-chain trades and transactions, SEI has also risen by 60% since CoinGecko began tracking it yesterday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sei-price-prediction-as-binance-listing-sends-price-soaring-new-airdrop-coming.htm"&gt;Read More: Sei Price Prediction as Binance Listing Sends Price Soaring – New Airdrop Coming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 10:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sei-price-prediction-as-binance-listing-sends-price-soaring-new-airdrop-coming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122572/324215/sei-price-prediction-as-b.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1175063"/></item><item><title>Cookie Coin Rockets Up 5,000% But Crypto Whales are Accumulating This Other Coin Instead – What Do They Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cookie-coin-rockets-up-5000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-coin-instead-what-do-they-know.htm</link><description>DEX tokens built on Coinbase's new layer-2 blockchain have been witnessing intense price action since BASE launched on August 9, and Cookie Coin (COOKIE) is the latest entrant to undertake a sensational move this on-chain summer. &lt;br /&gt;
With market attention gripped to the BASE launch, recent weeks have seen massive traction for meme coins built using the new blockchain - with coins such as Wall Street Base exploding +1,000%. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cookie-coin-rockets-up-5000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-coin-instead-what-do-they-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Cookie Coin Rockets Up 5,000% But Crypto Whales are Accumulating This Other Coin Instead – What Do They Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cookie-coin-rockets-up-5000-but-crypto-whales-are-accumulating-other-coin-instead-what-do-they-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122565/324209/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="927258"/></item><item><title>Stablecoin Firm Circle's Chief Strategy Officer Urges Legislation Amidst USDC Market Decline</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/stablecoin-firm-circles-chief-strategy-officer-urges-legislation-amidst-usdc-market-decline.htm</link><description>Circle is advocating for federal legislation regarding stablecoins amid the volatility in its USD Coin (USDC) after some bank failures earlier this year.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent interview with Bloomberg, Dante Disparte, Circle's Chief Strategy Officer, spoke out against the lack of regulations in the stablecoin industry, highlighting the risks posed to investors and the broader financial system....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/stablecoin-firm-circles-chief-strategy-officer-urges-legislation-amidst-usdc-market-decline.htm"&gt;Read More: Stablecoin Firm Circle's Chief Strategy Officer Urges Legislation Amidst USDC Market Decline&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Circle</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Regulation</category><category>USDC</category><category>USDT</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/stablecoin-firm-circles-chief-strategy-officer-urges-legislation-amidst-usdc-market-decline.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122573/324193/adobestock-514809399-1-me.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="257762"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as DOGE Falls 5% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-falls-5-24-hours-time-buy-dip.htm</link><description>The Dogecoin price has dropped by 5% in the past 24 hours, falling to $0.070500 as the cryptocurrency market reacts badly to speculation that the SEC has delayed all decisions on recent Bitcoin ETF applications. &lt;br /&gt;
DOGE is now down by 7% in a week and by 8% in a fortnight, with the meme token basically flat since the beginning of the year, in contrast to many major cryptocurrencies (e.g. Bitcoin, Ethereum, XRP) which have gained substantially since January 1....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-falls-5-24-hours-time-buy-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as DOGE Falls 5% in 24 Hours – Time to Buy the Dip?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-doge-falls-5-24-hours-time-buy-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122561/324192/dogecoin-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1202252"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Europe's ETF Launch, BlackRock's SEC Decision &amp; Depot's Growth</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-europes-etf-launch-blackrocks-sec-decision-depots-growth.htm</link><description>In a dynamic period for Bitcoin, the renowned cryptocurrency has seen its value slightly diminish, trading at $29,231—a 0.50% decrease as of Wednesday.  &lt;br /&gt;
Adding to the ever-evolving landscape, Europe has made headlines by launching the very first Bitcoin ETF. &lt;br /&gt;
At the same time, speculations swirl around the US Securities and Exchange Commission, potentially deferring its judgment on BlackRock's submission. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-europes-etf-launch-blackrocks-sec-decision-depots-growth.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Europe's ETF Launch, BlackRock's SEC Decision &amp; Depot's Growth&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-europes-etf-launch-blackrocks-sec-decision-depots-growth.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122551/324182/16-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="490072"/></item><item><title>Binance Connect to Cease Operations on August 16 – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-connect-cease-operations-august-16-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>As confirmed via email from a Binance spokesperson on August 15, Binance Connect, the regulated buy-and-sell crypto arm of the Binance exchange, will shut down on August 16. &lt;br /&gt;
The same day, the decentralized BNB Chain exchange known as Biswap posted a tweet announcing that Binance, a major cryptocurrency exchange, had arrived at a challenging decision....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-connect-cease-operations-august-16-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Connect to Cease Operations on August 16 – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Binance Connect</category><category>Bifinity</category><category>SEC</category><category>CFTC</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-connect-cease-operations-august-16-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122554/324179/adobestock-286536391-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="183170"/></item><item><title>Chamber of Digital Commerce Policy VP Criticizes SEC’s Aggressive Stance on Crypto Industry Regulation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-policy-vp-criticizes-secs-aggressive-stance-crypto-industry-regulation.htm</link><description>During an interview, Cody Carbone, the Vice President of Policy at the Chamber of Digital Commerce, expressed his concerns regarding the regulatory stance the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has adopted toward the cryptocurrency industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
Carbone highlighted that the SEC’s approach towards the digital asset sector has been notably aggressive. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-policy-vp-criticizes-secs-aggressive-stance-crypto-industry-regulation.htm"&gt;Read More: Chamber of Digital Commerce Policy VP Criticizes SEC’s Aggressive Stance on Crypto Industry Regulation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Chamber of Digital Commerce</category><category>CDC</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chamber-of-digital-commerce-policy-vp-criticizes-secs-aggressive-stance-crypto-industry-regulation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122547/324176/q1n6n1n2-1920-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="164779"/></item><item><title>Argentina Set to Become a ‘Bitcoin Haven,’ Politician Claims</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-set-become-bitcoin-haven-politician-claims.htm</link><description>An Argentinian politician has claimed the country will soon become a ‘Bitcoin haven,’ with the nation edging closer to electing a BTC-keen head of state. &lt;br /&gt;
The claims were made by Diana Mondino, an economist, university professor, and former board member of firms such as Pampa Energía, Banco Supervielle, Loma Negra, and Bodegas Bianchi....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-set-become-bitcoin-haven-politician-claims.htm"&gt;Read More: Argentina Set to Become a ‘Bitcoin Haven,’ Politician Claims&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Argentina</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/argentina-set-become-bitcoin-haven-politician-claims.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122525/324097/adobestock-243463317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="464082"/></item></channel></rss>
