<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Chinese Charities Accepting Digital Yuan Donations – More CBDC Firsts to Come?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-charities-accepting-digital-yuan-donations.htm</link><description>Chinese charities are now accepting digital yuan donations, with the nation’s CBDC also breaking new ground in the world of corporate loans. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet WXRB, the coastal province of Jiangsu has welcomed its first “online corporate and personal digital yuan donations platform.” &lt;br /&gt;
At a ceremony held earlier this week, the state-run commercial bank the Agricultural Bank of China made a CBDC donation to the Wuxi Charity Federation....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-charities-accepting-digital-yuan-donations.htm"&gt;Read More: Chinese Charities Accepting Digital Yuan Donations – More CBDC Firsts to Come?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/chinese-charities-accepting-digital-yuan-donations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116386/312281/china-1-0906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="458762"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 9 June – Immutable X, Render, Stacks</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-9-june-immutable-x-render-stacks.htm</link><description>The cryptocurrency industry is in turmoil, with Coinbase and Binance experiencing a massive outflow of over $4 billion in recent days. &lt;br /&gt;
This is due to the allegations by the SEC of federal securities law violations, leading to a significant number of users leaving these exchanges. &lt;br /&gt;
Given these circumstances, how might this impact the selection of the best cryptos to buy now? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-9-june-immutable-x-render-stacks.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 9 June – Immutable X, Render, Stacks&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>WSM</category><category>IMX</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>RNDR</category><category>YPRED</category><category>STX</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Immutable X</category><category>Render Token</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Stacks</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Play To Earn</category><category>Crypto Gaming</category><category>Sustainable Crypto</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>NFT</category><category>Non-fungible token</category><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-9-june-immutable-x-render-stacks.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116488/312434/best-crypto-9j.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="377701"/></item><item><title>New Meme Crypto $MIKE O'Hearn Token Joins Top Trending Coins In DEXTools Hot Pairs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-crypto-mike-ohearn-token-top-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-hot-pairs.htm</link><description>Baby don't rug me? One of the newest meme coins is based on the popular Tiktok and Twitter meme featuring bodybuilder Mike O'Hearn, and it's already a top trending cryptocurrency. &lt;br /&gt;
$MIKE coin is up 70% in the past 24 hours and recently broke into the top ten trending cryptocurrency assets, or 'hot pairs', on DEXTools which tracks tokens on decentralized exchanges....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-crypto-mike-ohearn-token-top-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-hot-pairs.htm"&gt;Read More: New Meme Crypto $MIKE O'Hearn Token Joins Top Trending Coins In DEXTools Hot Pairs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-meme-crypto-mike-ohearn-token-top-trending-crypto-coins-dextools-hot-pairs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116483/312430/mike-ohearn-crypto-token-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="378079"/></item><item><title>US CFTC Wins Precedent Setting Case Against Ooki DAO, Calling It a ‘Wake-Up Call’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-wins-precedent-setting-case-against-ooki-dao-calling-it-a-wake-up-call.htm</link><description>A US district judge ruled in favor of the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission in its litigation against Ooki DAO — which could have further implications for other decentralized autonomous organizations.  &lt;br /&gt;
Judge William H. Orrick entered a default judgment order on Thursday night, which requires Ooki DAO to pay a civil penalty of $643,542, stop operating in the US and ordering it to shut down Ooki DAO’s website....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-wins-precedent-setting-case-against-ooki-dao-calling-it-a-wake-up-call.htm"&gt;Read More: US CFTC Wins Precedent Setting Case Against Ooki DAO, Calling It a ‘Wake-Up Call’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>DAO</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-wins-precedent-setting-case-against-ooki-dao-calling-it-a-wake-up-call.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116484/312418/adobestock-323811126-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="426841"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Prediction as Research and Development Firm Input Output Responds to SEC's Claims that ADA is a Unregistered Security – What Happens Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-research-development-firm-input-output-responds-secs-claims-that-ada-unregistered-security-what-happens-next.htm</link><description>It’s been an ugly few days for ADA, the cryptocurrency that powers the Cardano blockchain, a decentralized smart-contract-enabled layer-1 protocol. &lt;br /&gt;
ADA dropped another near 7% on Friday to hit $0.30 per token and is eyeing a retest of March’s lows. &lt;br /&gt;
Losses on the week now stand at a staggering more than 20%, which would mark the cryptocurrency’s worst week in over two years. &lt;br /&gt;
And Cardano price predictions have suddenly become much more bearish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-research-development-firm-input-output-responds-secs-claims-that-ada-unregistered-security-what-happens-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Prediction as Research and Development Firm Input Output Responds to SEC's Claims that ADA is a Unregistered Security – What Happens Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>ADA</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-research-development-firm-input-output-responds-secs-claims-that-ada-unregistered-security-what-happens-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116480/312413/ada-3.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="190344"/></item><item><title>Jack Dorsey-Backed Nostr Platform Collaborates with Zebedee to Create New Social Media Later – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorsey-backed-nostr-platform-collaborates-with-zebedee-to-create-new-social-media-later-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>A rapidly growing decentralized Twitter competitor, Nostr, is collaborating with Zebedee to design a new social media.  &lt;br /&gt;
This move would enable interoperability between Zebedee's ZBD app and Nostr apps.  &lt;br /&gt;
Zebedee is a New Jersey-based video game payment platform with over one million Bitcoin wallets, supported by a $46.5 million VC fund. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorsey-backed-nostr-platform-collaborates-with-zebedee-to-create-new-social-media-later-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: Jack Dorsey-Backed Nostr Platform Collaborates with Zebedee to Create New Social Media Later – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Finance News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jack-dorsey-backed-nostr-platform-collaborates-with-zebedee-to-create-new-social-media-later-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116473/312409/website-g41b4047df-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1714792"/></item><item><title>Lens Protocol Raises $15 Million to Augment Decentralized Social Media – Next Twitter Competitor?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lens-protocol-raises-15-million-augment-decentralized-social-media-next-twitter-competitor.htm</link><description>Aave’s Lens Protocol, a social layer for web3, has raised $15 million in funding to develop decentralized blockchain-backed social media.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a June 8 blog post, IDEO CoLab Ventures led the funding round alongside other VCs, such as General Catalyst, Variant, Blockchain Capital, and Palm Tree.  &lt;br /&gt;
Other prominent venture capitals, including A. Capital, Seed Club Ventures, Robot Ventures, and DAOs like PUNK DAO and Flamingo DAO, participated in the fundraising....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lens-protocol-raises-15-million-augment-decentralized-social-media-next-twitter-competitor.htm"&gt;Read More: Lens Protocol Raises $15 Million to Augment Decentralized Social Media – Next Twitter Competitor?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lens-protocol-raises-15-million-augment-decentralized-social-media-next-twitter-competitor.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116471/312407/phone-gffbce4ddb-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="388444"/></item><item><title>Polygon Price is Going to Zero as the SEC Begins Clamp Down on Crypto Industry but Sustainable Coin Ecoterra Just Raised $4.9 Million – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/polygon-price-going-zero-as-sec-begins-clamp-down-crypto-industry-but-sustainable-coin-ecoterra-just-raised-49-million-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>It’s been a disastrous week for Polygon. &lt;br /&gt;
The Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution’s native MATIC token has shed nearly 20% of its value since the weekly open, tanking from the upper $0.80s to the low-$0.70s....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/polygon-price-going-zero-as-sec-begins-clamp-down-crypto-industry-but-sustainable-coin-ecoterra-just-raised-49-million-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Polygon Price is Going to Zero as the SEC Begins Clamp Down on Crypto Industry but Sustainable Coin Ecoterra Just Raised $4.9 Million – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Polygon</category><category>MATIC</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Presale</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/polygon-price-going-zero-as-sec-begins-clamp-down-crypto-industry-but-sustainable-coin-ecoterra-just-raised-49-million-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116472/312406/polygon.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1097475"/></item><item><title>SOL is 'Not a Security', Insists Solana Foundation Amid SEC Lawsuits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sol-not-security-insists-solana-foundation-amid-sec-lawsuits.htm</link><description>The Solana network’s native token SOL is “not a security,” despite the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) claiming otherwise, the Solana Foundation has said. &lt;br /&gt;
Commenting on the regulatory status of its token to CoinDesk on Thursday, the Solana Foundation made it clear that it still sees Solana as sufficiently decentralized for its native token to not be considered a security for regulatory purposes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sol-not-security-insists-solana-foundation-amid-sec-lawsuits.htm"&gt;Read More: SOL is 'Not a Security', Insists Solana Foundation Amid SEC Lawsuits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sol-not-security-insists-solana-foundation-amid-sec-lawsuits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116435/312358/solana.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="851712"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Push BTC Up From Recent Bottom at $26,200 – Where is BTC Heading Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-up-from-recent-bottom-at-26200-where-btc-heading-next.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, experienced a recent dip that saw its price reach a bottom at $26,200.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, a surge of bullish activity has propelled BTC back up, raising questions about its future trajectory.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors eagerly await insights into where Bitcoin is headed next. Will its upward momentum continue, or is there potential for a reversal? ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-up-from-recent-bottom-at-26200-where-btc-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Push BTC Up From Recent Bottom at $26,200 – Where is BTC Heading Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-push-btc-up-from-recent-bottom-at-26200-where-btc-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116445/312383/9-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="513816"/></item><item><title>Berenberg Capital Adjusts Coinbase Price Target in Response to SEC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-capital-adjusts-coinbase-price-target-response-sec-lawsuit.htm</link><description>According to a research report by Berenberg Capital, investment bank analyst Mark Palmer believes that Coinbase shares are currently deemed "uninvestable" in the short term due to the ongoing lawsuit filed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). &lt;br /&gt;
Palmer noted in the report that the anticipated decline in second-quarter trading volumes on Coinbase had already been expected prior to the lawsuit. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-capital-adjusts-coinbase-price-target-response-sec-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Berenberg Capital Adjusts Coinbase Price Target in Response to SEC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/berenberg-capital-adjusts-coinbase-price-target-response-sec-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116431/312353/coinbase-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="189852"/></item><item><title>US House Financial Services Committee Republicans Reach Some Compromise With Democrats on Latest Version of a Stablecoin Bill</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-republicans-reach-some-compromise-with-democrats-latest-version-of-stablecoin-bill.htm</link><description>The House Financial Services Committee under its Republican leadership has dropped a new version of its stablecoin bill after receiving feedback from its Democratic members.  &lt;br /&gt;
The bill, which is still a discussion draft, would regulate payment stablecoins specifically, and would allow state regulators to supervise stablecoin issuers, with federal regulators having a primary role by issuing capital and liquidity requirements. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-republicans-reach-some-compromise-with-democrats-latest-version-of-stablecoin-bill.htm"&gt;Read More: US House Financial Services Committee Republicans Reach Some Compromise With Democrats on Latest Version of a Stablecoin Bill&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-republicans-reach-some-compromise-with-democrats-latest-version-of-stablecoin-bill.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116464/312401/adobestock-265746413-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="381661"/></item><item><title>US Justice Department Charges Two Russian Nationals With Stealing Thousands of Bitcoin Linked to Mt. Gox</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-justice-department-charges-two-russian-nationals-with-stealing-thousands-of-bitcoin-linked-mt-gox.htm</link><description>The US Department of Justice unsealed charges against Russian nationals Alexey Bilyuchenko and Aleksandr Verner, for allegedly stealing thousands of bitcoin from the Mt.Gox crypto exchange back in 2011 to 2014.  &lt;br /&gt;
Bilyuchenko, 43, and Verner, 29, were charged on Friday in the Southern District of New York “with conspiring to launder approximately 647,000 bitcoins,” which the department said was the majority of the bitcoins belonging to Mt. Gox’s customers. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-justice-department-charges-two-russian-nationals-with-stealing-thousands-of-bitcoin-linked-mt-gox.htm"&gt;Read More: US Justice Department Charges Two Russian Nationals With Stealing Thousands of Bitcoin Linked to Mt. Gox&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Mt Gox</category><category>Russia</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-justice-department-charges-two-russian-nationals-with-stealing-thousands-of-bitcoin-linked-mt-gox.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116459/312394/adobestock-71272800.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="635106"/></item><item><title>SEC Pursues 'Alternative Means' to Serve Legal Documents to Binance CEO</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-pursues-alternative-means-serve-legal-documents-binance-ceo.htm</link><description>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is looking for other ways to serve legal papers to Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), whose location is often hard to track down. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-pursues-alternative-means-serve-legal-documents-binance-ceo.htm"&gt;Read More: SEC Pursues 'Alternative Means' to Serve Legal Documents to Binance CEO&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-pursues-alternative-means-serve-legal-documents-binance-ceo.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116455/312387/adobestock-419123987-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="169782"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Google Cloud Offers Certain Customers Up To $1M for Cryptomining Attacks, Countdown Until MiCA Enters into Effect Officially Starts, Hong Kong to Lay Foundations to Implement Retail CBDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-google-cloud-offers-certain-customers-up-to-1m-for-cryptomining-attacks-countdown-until-mica-enters-into-effect-officially-starts-hong-kong-to-lay-foundations-to-implement-retail-cbdc.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-google-cloud-offers-certain-customers-up-to-1m-for-cryptomining-attacks-countdown-until-mica-enters-into-effect-officially-starts-hong-kong-to-lay-foundations-to-implement-retail-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Google Cloud Offers Certain Customers Up To $1M for Cryptomining Attacks, Countdown Until MiCA Enters into Effect Officially Starts, Hong Kong to Lay Foundations to Implement Retail CBDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Security</category><category>Google</category><category>Mining</category><category>Hack</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Regulation</category><category>EU</category><category>European Union</category><category>MiCA</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Hut 8</category><category>OKX</category><category>Sport</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-google-cloud-offers-certain-customers-up-to-1m-for-cryptomining-attacks-countdown-until-mica-enters-into-effect-officially-starts-hong-kong-to-lay-foundations-to-implement-retail-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116411/312341/adobestock-jhvephoto-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="254002"/></item><item><title>Robinhood Delists Cardano, Polygon and Solana Following SEC Labeling Them As Securities</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhood-delists-cardano-polygon-solana-following-sec-labeling-them-as-securities.htm</link><description>Brokerage firm Robinhood has decided to delist Cardano, Polygon and Solana after the US Securities and Exchange Commission said those three were securities in its charges against two large crypto exchanges this week. &lt;br /&gt;
Robinhood said it would end support for the three on June 27, and said that investors could still buy, sell and hold ADA, MATIC and SOL until the deadline. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhood-delists-cardano-polygon-solana-following-sec-labeling-them-as-securities.htm"&gt;Read More: Robinhood Delists Cardano, Polygon and Solana Following SEC Labeling Them As Securities&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Robinhood</category><category>SOL</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Cardano</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/robinhood-delists-cardano-polygon-solana-following-sec-labeling-them-as-securities.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116444/312375/adobestock-409328789-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="188738"/></item><item><title>Craig DeWitt, Co-Founder at Supermojo, on Creating New Payment Networks, Ripple, and NFT Payment Solutions | Ep. 237</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/craig-dewitt-co-founder-at-supermojo-on-creating-new-payment-networks-ripple-and-nft-payment-solutions-ep-237.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Craig DeWitt, Co-Founder of Supermojo, talks about the future of alternative payment methods using blockchain technology, creating new payment networks separate from ACH, and automatically creating wallets and self-custody options....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/craig-dewitt-co-founder-at-supermojo-on-creating-new-payment-networks-ripple-and-nft-payment-solutions-ep-237.htm"&gt;Read More: Craig DeWitt, Co-Founder at Supermojo, on Creating New Payment Networks, Ripple, and NFT Payment Solutions | Ep. 237&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/craig-dewitt-co-founder-at-supermojo-on-creating-new-payment-networks-ripple-and-nft-payment-solutions-ep-237.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116413/312327/craig-dewitt-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="134161"/></item><item><title>eToro Remains Committed to Crypto Amid SEC's High-Profile Lawsuits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-remains-committed-to-crypto-amid-secs-high-profile-lawsuits.htm</link><description>As the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to clamp down on Binance and Coinbase crypto exchanges, the entire crypto and financial markets remain attentive, with the likes of eToro weighing in. &lt;br /&gt;
eToro, one of the powerhouse platforms in financial trading, has reiterated its commitment to crypto and demonstrated a willingness to work in compliance with industry regulations....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-remains-committed-to-crypto-amid-secs-high-profile-lawsuits.htm"&gt;Read More: eToro Remains Committed to Crypto Amid SEC's High-Profile Lawsuits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>MANA</category><category>Cardano</category><category>eToro</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Algorand</category><category>Filecoin</category><category>Polygon</category><category>Sandbox</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/etoro-remains-committed-to-crypto-amid-secs-high-profile-lawsuits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116434/312395/adobestock-430692692-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="295318"/></item><item><title>Binance CEO Condemns Leaked Chat Logs, Acknowledges Significant 'Damage'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-condemns-leaked-chat-logs-acknowledges-significant-damage.htm</link><description>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao has condemned the move by the US Securities and Exchange Commission to leak employee chat records.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a letter to employees, CZ called the use of chat logs by the SEC "ridiculous," according to a translated copy of the memo shared by Odaily Planet Daily on Thursday. &lt;br /&gt;
"It's ridiculous for the SEC to use this as a poster, but we'll let the lawyers take care of it," the crypto boss wrote....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-condemns-leaked-chat-logs-acknowledges-significant-damage.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO Condemns Leaked Chat Logs, Acknowledges Significant 'Damage'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><category>Binance</category><category>SEC</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-condemns-leaked-chat-logs-acknowledges-significant-damage.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116429/312351/snapshot-min-media-librar.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="131061"/></item><item><title>As Traditional Banks Step Back, New Players Fill Gap in Crypto Banking</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-traditional-banks-step-back-new-players-fill-gap-crypto-banking.htm</link><description>With traditional banks becoming more cautious about servicing the cryptocurrency industry, smaller regional banks and alternative payment service providers are stepping up to fill the gap.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the US, Customers Bancorp, a Pennsylvania-based lender, has become a popular choice, having launched a real-time payment platform to support the settlement of US dollar transfers underlying cryptocurrency transactions, according to a new list of crypto-friendly banks compiled by Bloomberg News....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/as-traditional-banks-step-back-new-players-fill-gap-crypto-banking.htm"&gt;Read More: As Traditional Banks Step Back, New Players Fill Gap in Crypto Banking&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Banks</category><category>Silvergate</category><category>Silicon Valley Bank</category><category>Signature Bank</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/as-traditional-banks-step-back-new-players-fill-gap-crypto-banking.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/116420/312345/people-gd7e5df48f-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="198631"/></item></channel></rss>
