<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao Leads Praise for EU's New Crypto Regulation, MiCA</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-leads-praise-for-eus-new-crypto-regulation-mica.htm</link><description>The European Union Parliament has passed into law its MiCA act, and big-time industry player and CEO of Binance Changpeng Zhao is raising support following the new crypto regulations. &lt;br /&gt;
The European Union Parliament has passed a bill into law to combat its long-standing battle against the crypto market.  &lt;br /&gt;
For a long time, the crypto industry has gone without regulations and has been a concern for several regulatory bodies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-leads-praise-for-eus-new-crypto-regulation-mica.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao Leads Praise for EU's New Crypto Regulation, MiCA&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-changpeng-zhao-leads-praise-for-eus-new-crypto-regulation-mica.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111923/270639/cz.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="137088"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Gemini Ventures Outside the US With Plans for Derivatives Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-ventures-outside-us-with-plans-for-derivatives-platform.htm</link><description>Despite an ongoing legal tussle with US authorities, Winklevoss Twins-owned crypto exchange Gemini has announced the launch of a crypto derivatives platform.  &lt;br /&gt;
The new platform will only cater to crypto derivatives traders outside the North American nation. &lt;br /&gt;
In an April 21 blog post, the Gemini exchange announced the upcoming launch of a new crypto derivatives platform called Gemini Foundation. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-ventures-outside-us-with-plans-for-derivatives-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Gemini Ventures Outside the US With Plans for Derivatives Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-gemini-ventures-outside-us-with-plans-for-derivatives-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111911/270612/th-13.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="53451"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Long Liquidations Hit $150M in 3 Days as BTC Price Slumps Towards This Key Resistance Level</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-long-liquidations-hit-150m-3-days-as-btc-price-slumps-towards-key-resistance-level.htm</link><description>Leveraged long positions in the Bitcoin futures market have been getting “rekt” (i.e. stopped out in internet lingo) in the last few days. &lt;br /&gt;
According to data presented by crypto derivatives analytics website coinglass.com, long position liquidations have surpassed $150 million over the course of the last three days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-long-liquidations-hit-150m-3-days-as-btc-price-slumps-towards-key-resistance-level.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Long Liquidations Hit $150M in 3 Days as BTC Price Slumps Towards This Key Resistance Level&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Liquidations</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-long-liquidations-hit-150m-3-days-as-btc-price-slumps-towards-key-resistance-level.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111904/270581/btc-17.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="588341"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 21 April – RNDR, CFX, ZIL</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-21-april-rndr-cfx-zil.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has recently encountered a tumultuous period, having ascended past the $30,000 mark just last week only to experience a subsequent decline. &lt;br /&gt;
Reaching a nine-month peak, the achievement initially sparked market enthusiasm, but excitement waned as the cryptocurrency's value fell to $27,000. &lt;br /&gt;
How might this downturn in the cryptocurrency market affect the selection of the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-21-april-rndr-cfx-zil.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 21 April – RNDR, CFX, ZIL&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>LHINU</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Taro</category><category>Love Hate Inu</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Vote-To-Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>V2E</category><category>R2E</category><category>Freelance</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Render Token</category><category>RNDR</category><category>SWDTKN</category><category>Swords of Blood</category><category>Conflux</category><category>CFX</category><category>ZIL</category><category>Zilliqa</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-21-april-rndr-cfx-zil.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111900/270576/bc21a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="326218"/></item><item><title>U.S. Federal Government Greenlights Voyager's $1 Billion Binance.US Acquisition Deal</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-federal-government-greenlights-voyagers-1-billion-binanceus-acquisition-deal.htm</link><description>The U.S. federal government has approved the bid by Binance’s American branch to buy up the remaining assets of the bankrupt crypto lender Voyager Digital. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Twitter thread earlier this week, Voyager’s Official Committee of Unsecured Creditors said a resolution has been reached with the government that will “allow the Plan to move forward and go effective shortly.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-federal-government-greenlights-voyagers-1-billion-binanceus-acquisition-deal.htm"&gt;Read More: U.S. Federal Government Greenlights Voyager's $1 Billion Binance.US Acquisition Deal&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Voyager</category><category>Binance</category><category>Binance.us</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-federal-government-greenlights-voyagers-1-billion-binanceus-acquisition-deal.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111880/270527/green-light.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="203420"/></item><item><title>Interpol Red Notice Leads to Arrest of Crypto Exchange CEO – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/interpol-red-notice-leads-arrest-of-crypto-exchange-ceo-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The founder and former CEO of a now-defunct crypto exchange, Thodex, has been extradited to Turkey and was detained by police upon arrival in Istanbul. &lt;br /&gt;
Faruk Fatih Ozer, who founded Thodex in 2017, was arrested in Albania last year after an Interpol red notice against him, according to a Thursday report by state media AA.com....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/interpol-red-notice-leads-arrest-of-crypto-exchange-ceo-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Interpol Red Notice Leads to Arrest of Crypto Exchange CEO – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Thodex</category><category>Faruk Fatih Ozer</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Turkey</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/interpol-red-notice-leads-arrest-of-crypto-exchange-ceo-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111867/270498/ozer.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="42006"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Price Prediction as Binance Supports Terra Network Upgrade – What Happens Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-price-prediction-as-binance-supports-terra-network-upgrade-what-happens-now.htm</link><description>Things are not looking good for Terra Luna (LUNA) in 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency was last changing hands around $1.26 per token, 50% down from earlier annual highs to the north of $2.50. &lt;br /&gt;
That means LUNA has now erased the entirety of this year’s gains. &lt;br /&gt;
Compare that to Bitcoin and Ether, both of which are up in the 60-70% region....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-price-prediction-as-binance-supports-terra-network-upgrade-what-happens-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Price Prediction as Binance Supports Terra Network Upgrade – What Happens Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Terra Luna</category><category>Luna</category><category>Terra 2.0</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-price-prediction-as-binance-supports-terra-network-upgrade-what-happens-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111883/270535/luna-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="637521"/></item><item><title>Two Russian Crypto Laws Could Roll Out in June – Here’s What You Need to Know About Them</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/two-russian-crypto-laws-could-roll-out-june-heres-what-you-need-know-about-them.htm</link><description>Russian lawmakers could finally end the country’s long wait for crypto regulation – with two bills reportedly ready for adoption as early as June. &lt;br /&gt;
One will seek to permit the use of crypto in overseas payments. &lt;br /&gt;
The other will deal with the legalization of crypto mining. &lt;br /&gt;
Crypto regulation’s progress in the State Duma has stalled on multiple occasions in the past....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/two-russian-crypto-laws-could-roll-out-june-heres-what-you-need-know-about-them.htm"&gt;Read More: Two Russian Crypto Laws Could Roll Out in June – Here’s What You Need to Know About Them&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><category>Crypto Mining</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/two-russian-crypto-laws-could-roll-out-june-heres-what-you-need-know-about-them.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111852/270478/adobestock-75296848.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="850644"/></item><item><title>Julian Hosp, CEO of Cake DeFi, on DeFi for Bitcoin and the Current Crypto Market | Ep. 223</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/julian-hosp-ceo-of-cake-defi-defi-for-bitcoin-current-crypto-market-ep-223.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Dr. Julian Hosp, CEO and Co-Founder of Cake DeFi, talks about DeFi on BitCoin, the future of Binance, and the growing demand for DeFi for institutions. &lt;br /&gt;
Dr. Julian Hosp is the CEO and Co-Founder of Cake DeFi. Cake DeFi is a fully transparent, highly innovative fintech platform dedicated to providing easy access to decentralized financial services and applications by enabling users to generate returns from their crypto and digital assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/julian-hosp-ceo-of-cake-defi-defi-for-bitcoin-current-crypto-market-ep-223.htm"&gt;Read More: Julian Hosp, CEO of Cake DeFi, on DeFi for Bitcoin and the Current Crypto Market | Ep. 223&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/julian-hosp-ceo-of-cake-defi-defi-for-bitcoin-current-crypto-market-ep-223.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111864/270492/julian-hosp-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="119896"/></item><item><title>Berachain Secures $42 Million Series A at $420.69M Valuation, Boosting DeFi-focused Layer 1</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/berachain-secures-42-million-series-a-at-42069m-valuation-boosting-defi-focused-layer-1.htm</link><description>Decentralized finance (DeFi)-focused layer 1 blockchain Berachain has succeeded in raising a total of $42 million in its recently completed Series A funding round at a valuation of $420.69 million. &lt;br /&gt;
Led by Polychain Capital, the funding round enabled Berachain to source capital from a number of investors. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/berachain-secures-42-million-series-a-at-42069m-valuation-boosting-defi-focused-layer-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Berachain Secures $42 Million Series A at $420.69M Valuation, Boosting DeFi-focused Layer 1&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Berachain</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/berachain-secures-42-million-series-a-at-42069m-valuation-boosting-defi-focused-layer-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111866/270509/adobestock-578093349.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="390116"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as $20 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Is Now a Good Time to Buy BTC?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-20-billion-trading-volume-comes-now-good-time-buy-btc.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the world's largest cryptocurrency, has been quite fabulous since the start of 2023, soaring over 70% in the first quarter.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, the upward trend appears to be losing steam as BTC recently fell over 2% to $28,284.02.  &lt;br /&gt;
The current Bitcoin price is $28,238, and the 24-hour trading volume is $21 billion. Bitcoin has fallen by 2.61% in the previous 24 hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-20-billion-trading-volume-comes-now-good-time-buy-btc.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as $20 Billion Trading Volume Comes In – Is Now a Good Time to Buy BTC?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-20-billion-trading-volume-comes-now-good-time-buy-btc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111801/270451/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1408317"/></item><item><title>Terraform Labs Co-founder Do Kwon and CFO Charged with Forgery by Montenegro Prosecutors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-and-cfo-charged-with-forgery-by-montenegro-prosecutors.htm</link><description>Terra founder Do Kwon and Terraform Labs’ chief financial officer Han Chang-joon are both accused of forgery by prosecutors in Montenegro. &lt;br /&gt;
The two men are still in custody by Montenegro’s police after being arrested in the country in March, and prosecutors are now seeking to extend their detention. &lt;br /&gt;
The news was first reported by Bloomberg on Thursday, citing an official at the prosecutor’s office in Montenegro’s capital of Podgorica....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-and-cfo-charged-with-forgery-by-montenegro-prosecutors.htm"&gt;Read More: Terraform Labs Co-founder Do Kwon and CFO Charged with Forgery by Montenegro Prosecutors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Terra</category><category>Do Kwon</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terraform-labs-co-founder-do-kwon-and-cfo-charged-with-forgery-by-montenegro-prosecutors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111840/270464/do-kwon.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="92516"/></item><item><title>Youth Insolvency Spikes in South Korea – Is a Rise in Crypto Investment to Blame?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/youth-insolvency-spikes-south-korea-rise-crypto-investment-blame.htm</link><description>Crypto investment is being blamed for a spike in the number of South Korean people aged 20-39 declaring insolvency. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Maeil Shinmun, the Seoul Rehabilitation Court said: &lt;br /&gt;
“The rise in [insolvency] seems to have been influenced by a growth in economic activities such as cryptocurrency and stock market investment among young people.” &lt;br /&gt;
The court remarked that the problem was particularly pronounced in those “under the age of 30.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/youth-insolvency-spikes-south-korea-rise-crypto-investment-blame.htm"&gt;Read More: Youth Insolvency Spikes in South Korea – Is a Rise in Crypto Investment to Blame?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/youth-insolvency-spikes-south-korea-rise-crypto-investment-blame.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111834/270461/adobestock-525060536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="494200"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Unknown Whale Moves 30 Million XRP into New Wallet – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-unknown-whale-moves-30-million-xrp-into-new-wallet-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The XRP price has fallen by 4.5% in the past 24 hours, dropping to $0.471535 as the cryptocurrency market as a whole declines by 2%. &lt;br /&gt;
XRP's current price means that it has fallen by 8% in a week, although the altcoin has gained by 38% since the beginning of the year, suggesting that 2023 may end up being a year of recovery overall....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-unknown-whale-moves-30-million-xrp-into-new-wallet-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Unknown Whale Moves 30 Million XRP into New Wallet – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 10:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-unknown-whale-moves-30-million-xrp-into-new-wallet-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111824/270456/xrp-price-prediction-as-u.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1375415"/></item><item><title>Tornado Cash Dev Alex Pertsev to Be Released on Bail by Dutch Court</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tornado-cash-dev-alex-pertsev-released-bail-by-dutch-court.htm</link><description>Tornado Cash developer Alex Pertsev will be released under surveillance after spending nearly nine months in prison over allegations of facilitating money laundering. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Eléonore Blanc, founder of crypto education platform CryptoCanal, who was present at the court hearing, the crypto developer will be released on April 26 but under surveillance, meaning he will be awaiting trial from home....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tornado-cash-dev-alex-pertsev-released-bail-by-dutch-court.htm"&gt;Read More: Tornado Cash Dev Alex Pertsev to Be Released on Bail by Dutch Court&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Tornado Cash</category><category>Tornado</category><category>Alexsey Pertsev</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tornado-cash-dev-alex-pertsev-released-bail-by-dutch-court.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111829/270453/tornado-cash-media-librar.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="73822"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as European Financial Firm Launches Euro Stablecoin on Ethereum Blockchain – ETH to $10,000 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-european-financial-firm-launches-euro-stablecoin-ethereum-blockchain-eth-1-2023.htm</link><description>The Ethereum price has fallen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, as the cryptocurrency market suffers a similar 2% fall in the same period. &lt;br /&gt;
At $1,920, ETH is also down by 4.5% in the last week, yet remains up by 6% in the last 30 days and by 60.5% since the beginning of the year. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite today's fall, the bull case for ETH has been strengthened further by the news that major French bank Société Générale has launched a euro-denominated stablecoin on the Ethereum blockchain....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-european-financial-firm-launches-euro-stablecoin-ethereum-blockchain-eth-1-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as European Financial Firm Launches Euro Stablecoin on Ethereum Blockchain – ETH to $10,000 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-european-financial-firm-launches-euro-stablecoin-ethereum-blockchain-eth-1-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/111613/270436/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1446798"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 20 April – BTT, RNDR, TRX</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-20-april-btt-rndr-trx.htm</link><description>Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has voiced concerns over the lack of regulatory clarity in the United States, a development that has fed into increasing questions about the future of cryptocurrencies in the country. &lt;br /&gt;
But how might this regulatory ambiguity affect the selection of the best cryptos to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at a London-based fintech event, Armstrong suggested the company might consider relocating if the situation doesn't improve....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-20-april-btt-rndr-trx.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 20 April – BTT, RNDR, TRX&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>LHINU</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Taro</category><category>Love Hate Inu</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Vote-To-Earn</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>V2E</category><category>R2E</category><category>Freelance</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Render Token</category><category>Tron</category><category>Bittorrent</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-20-april-btt-rndr-trx.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/110932/268437/bc20a.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="386574"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Options Market Turns Negative on Short-term BTC Price Outlook, But Longer-term Bullish Bets Remain</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-options-market-turns-negative-on-short-term-btc-price-outlook-but-longer-term-bullish-bets-remain.htm</link><description>Investors have turned their most bearish on Bitcoin’s short-term price outlook in more than one month, according to options market data presented by crypto data analytics website The Block. &lt;br /&gt;
However, at the same time, investors seemingly remain confident in BTC’s longer-term outlook. &lt;br /&gt;
The 25% delta skew of Bitcoin options expiring in seven days fell to around -2 on Friday, its lowest level since the 14th of March....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-options-market-turns-negative-on-short-term-btc-price-outlook-but-longer-term-bullish-bets-remain.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Options Market Turns Negative on Short-term BTC Price Outlook, But Longer-term Bullish Bets Remain&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Options</category><category>Bull</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-options-market-turns-negative-on-short-term-btc-price-outlook-but-longer-term-bullish-bets-remain.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/110930/268432/btc-2.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="280028"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tumbles to $28,000 Support – Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-28000-support-time-buy-dip.htm</link><description>The BTC/USD has lost nearly 4.50% of its value in 24 hours, trading at $28,200. The leading cryptocurrency experienced a significant drop following a massive sell order on Binance. &lt;br /&gt;
Additionally, the BTC/USD decline is attributed to investors' concerns about ongoing inflation and rising interest rates....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-28000-support-time-buy-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Tumbles to $28,000 Support – Time to Buy the Dip?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-tumbles-28000-support-time-buy-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/110861/268320/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1130468"/></item><item><title>Tesla Earnings: No Changes to Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 2023 – Here's How Much BTC Tesla is Holding</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tesla-earnings-no-changes-bitcoin-holdings-q1-2023-heres-how-much-btc-tesla-holding.htm</link><description>Electric car maker Tesla revealed on Wednesday that its bitcoin (BTC) holdings remained untouched during the first quarter of 2023. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Tesla’s quarterly earnings report, the value of the “digital assets” held on the company’s balance sheet stood at $184 million, which is the same it was at for the prior quarter....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tesla-earnings-no-changes-bitcoin-holdings-q1-2023-heres-how-much-btc-tesla-holding.htm"&gt;Read More: Tesla Earnings: No Changes to Bitcoin Holdings in Q1 2023 – Here's How Much BTC Tesla is Holding&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Tesla</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tesla-earnings-no-changes-bitcoin-holdings-q1-2023-heres-how-much-btc-tesla-holding.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/110901/268370/tesla-bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="181855"/></item></channel></rss>
