<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>S Korean Police Bust ‘Crypto Scammer’ Who ‘Preyed on Housewives and Office Workers’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-crypto-scammer-who-preyed-housewives-office-workers.htm</link><description>South Korean police have arrest a suspected crypto scammer who allegedly preyed on “housewives and office workers.” &lt;br /&gt;
According to the broadcaster SBS, officers in Gimpo, Gyeonggi Province, arrested a 38-year-old man. &lt;br /&gt;
He was handed over to prosecutors on fraud-related charges. &lt;br /&gt;
Officers claimed the man duped his victims out of around $218,000. &lt;br /&gt;
He allegedly told them that they would be “guaranteed” “high profits” if they invested in his project....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-crypto-scammer-who-preyed-housewives-office-workers.htm"&gt;Read More: S Korean Police Bust ‘Crypto Scammer’ Who ‘Preyed on Housewives and Office Workers’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/s-korean-police-bust-crypto-scammer-who-preyed-housewives-office-workers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114961/277325/adobestock-423120616-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="530079"/></item><item><title>Seven Central Banks Contemplate the Future of Retail CBDCs in Latest Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/seven-central-banks-contemplate-future-of-retail-cbdcs-latest-report.htm</link><description>The Bank for International Settlements, which serves as a “bank for central banks,” released its latest paper examining retail central bank digital currencies, as its members “are approaching a point” as to whether or not they should move forward in their CBDC work. &lt;br /&gt;
Central banks representing Canada, Europe, Japan, Sweden, Switzerland, England and the US are working to explore CBDCs for retail use....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/seven-central-banks-contemplate-future-of-retail-cbdcs-latest-report.htm"&gt;Read More: Seven Central Banks Contemplate the Future of Retail CBDCs in Latest Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>BIS</category><category>Central Bank</category><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/seven-central-banks-contemplate-future-of-retail-cbdcs-latest-report.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114973/277355/earth-g19be5f7da-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="414707"/></item><item><title>DCG’s Subsidiary TradeBlock Is Shutting Its Doors: Bloomberg News</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcgs-subsidiary-tradeblock-shutting-its-doors-bloomberg-news.htm</link><description>TradeBlock, an institutional investor focused subsidiary of Barry Silbert’s crypto conglomerate Digital Currency Group, is closing down, according to Bloomberg News.  &lt;br /&gt;
“Due to the state of the broader economy and prolonged crypto winter, along with the challenging regulatory environment for digital assets in the US, we made the decision to sunset the institutional trading platform side of the business,” according to a statement from a DCG spokesperson Bloomberg recieved. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dcgs-subsidiary-tradeblock-shutting-its-doors-bloomberg-news.htm"&gt;Read More: DCG’s Subsidiary TradeBlock Is Shutting Its Doors: Bloomberg News&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>DCG</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><category>Genesis</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dcgs-subsidiary-tradeblock-shutting-its-doors-bloomberg-news.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114976/277364/bitcoin-g1239fefd8-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="168242"/></item><item><title>SingularityNET (AGIX) Price Prediction as AI Cryptos Gain Momentum</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/agix-price-prediction-as-ai-cryptos-gain-momentum.htm</link><description>AI cryptos are taking off amid ongoing breakthroughs and positive news in the AI space. SingularityNET (AGIX) is experiencing an impressive gain of almost 10% in the past 24 hours, for example, and is currently the second-largest AI cryptocurrency in terms of trading volume. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/agix-price-prediction-as-ai-cryptos-gain-momentum.htm"&gt;Read More: SingularityNET (AGIX) Price Prediction as AI Cryptos Gain Momentum&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Ai Crypto</category><category>SingularityNET</category><category>AGIX</category><category>AiDoge.com</category><category>yPredict</category><category>AI</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AGIX price prediction</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/agix-price-prediction-as-ai-cryptos-gain-momentum.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114971/277362/adobestock-265251856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="529965"/></item><item><title>Most Trending Crypto Coins on DEXTools Right Now - Pepe, RefundCoin, PSYOP, Ben, Apu</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today.htm</link><description>Crypto meme coin markets remain in a state of frenzy, with new coins popping up every day and many surging as investors hunt out the next major meme coin success story. &lt;br /&gt;
Here are the top five trending Ethereum-based ERC-20 coins on decentralized exchange (DEX) analysis website DEX Tools. &lt;br /&gt;
Pepe (PEPE) is back to the number one spot on the DEX Tools trending coins list....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Most Trending Crypto Coins on DEXTools Right Now - Pepe, RefundCoin, PSYOP, Ben, Apu&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>BEN</category><category>Pepe</category><category>RFD</category><category>PSYOP</category><category>APU</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/5-best-trending-coins-dextools-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114975/277361/crypto.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="9133175"/></item><item><title>Turbo, Capo Price Crash After Listed on OKX, Bybit - 4 New Coin Listings With 10x Potential</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/turbo-capo-price-crash-after-listed-on-okx-bybit-4-new-coin-listings-to-watch-with-10x-potential.htm</link><description>Since listing on OKX and ByBit, one of the world’s largest centralized cryptocurrency exchanges, four days ago, both Turbo Coin (TURBO) and Il Capo of Crypto (CAPO) token have fallen sharply. &lt;br /&gt;
TURBO, a meme coin created by generative artificial intelligence (AI) model GPT-4, which also powers viral AI chatbot ChatGPT, was last changing hands around $0.00036 per token....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/turbo-capo-price-crash-after-listed-on-okx-bybit-4-new-coin-listings-to-watch-with-10x-potential.htm"&gt;Read More: Turbo, Capo Price Crash After Listed on OKX, Bybit - 4 New Coin Listings With 10x Potential&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>OKX</category><category>ByBit</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>Love Hate Inu</category><category>LHINU</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/turbo-capo-price-crash-after-listed-on-okx-bybit-4-new-coin-listings-to-watch-with-10x-potential.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114972/277352/okx.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1680468"/></item><item><title>ARPA Price Prediction as Over 100% Rally This Week Puts Token in 10 Top Trending Crypto Coins on CoinMarketCap</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/arpa-price-prediction-as-over-100-rally-week-puts-token-10-top-trending-crypto-coins-coinmarketcap.htm</link><description>ARPA, the token that will power the ARPA Network protocol, has been on fire in recent days. &lt;br /&gt;
ARPA/USD was last changing hands across major cryptocurrency exchanges at around $0.11 per token, its highest level since February 2022, up around 100% this week and now up in the region of 320% for the year. &lt;br /&gt;
The recent surge helped ARPA reach the top 10 trending coins on CoinMarketCap, a big achievement for the coin which only has a market cap of $440 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/arpa-price-prediction-as-over-100-rally-week-puts-token-10-top-trending-crypto-coins-coinmarketcap.htm"&gt;Read More: ARPA Price Prediction as Over 100% Rally This Week Puts Token in 10 Top Trending Crypto Coins on CoinMarketCap&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>ARPA</category><category>ARPA Network</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 20:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/arpa-price-prediction-as-over-100-rally-week-puts-token-10-top-trending-crypto-coins-coinmarketcap.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114970/277349/arpa.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="612347"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 25 May – Leo, AiDoge, Ton, Neo, Sponge, Ecoterra, yPredict</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-25-may-leo-aidoge-ton-neo-sponge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm</link><description>The US stock market is attempting to recover after concerns over the debt ceiling and a general sense of uncertainty caused a decline on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
The Dow Jones Industrial Average is currently close to break even, while the S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq Composite, and Bitcoin are registering a recovery of 0.9%, 1.8%, and 1%, respectively. &lt;br /&gt;
In light of this ongoing macroeconomic development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-25-may-leo-aidoge-ton-neo-sponge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 25 May – Leo, AiDoge, Ton, Neo, Sponge, Ecoterra, yPredict&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Leo</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>TON</category><category>NEO</category><category>Sponge</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>yPredict</category><category>AI</category><category>Toncoin</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-25-may-leo-aidoge-ton-neo-sponge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114966/277332/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Fahrenheit Chosen As Winning Bid in Celsius Bankruptcy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fahrenheit-chose-as-winning-bid-celsius-bankruptcy.htm</link><description>Bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network LLC has chosen Fahrenheit as its winning bid, which will provide the capital and team to operate a new company. &lt;br /&gt;
Fahrenheit, which consists of a group of crypto firms, was selected as the winning bid on Thursday morning, according to a press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
The Blockchain Recovery Investment Consortium, or BRIC, was selected as the backup bid....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fahrenheit-chose-as-winning-bid-celsius-bankruptcy.htm"&gt;Read More: Fahrenheit Chosen As Winning Bid in Celsius Bankruptcy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fahrenheit-chose-as-winning-bid-celsius-bankruptcy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114967/277337/adobestock-517984220-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="252122"/></item><item><title>Binance CEO: China TV Broadcast 'Big Deal' for Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-china-tv-broadcast-big-deal-for-crypto.htm</link><description>A segment on Chinese state television about crypto has caught the attention of the cryptoverse, with Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) pointing out that similar reporting in the past has triggered bull runs. &lt;br /&gt;
“CCTV (China Central Television) just broadcasted crypto. It's a big deal. The Chinese speaking communities are buzzing. Historically, coverages like these led to bull runs,” CZ told his 8.4 million Twitter followers on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-china-tv-broadcast-big-deal-for-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance CEO: China TV Broadcast 'Big Deal' for Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>China</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Changpeng Zhao</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-china-tv-broadcast-big-deal-for-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114964/277331/cctv-building.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="828408"/></item><item><title>About 85,000 Bitcoin Options Contracts Set to Expire This Friday</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/about-85000-bitcoin-options-contracts-set-expire-friday.htm</link><description>About 85,000 bitcoin options contracts, worth around $2.3 billion, are set to expire on major cryptocurrency futures and options exchange Deribit this Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Deribit data, around 700,000 Ethereum options, valued at over $1.2 billion, are also set to expire on May 26.  &lt;br /&gt;
"This Friday a total value of USD 3.6 billion will expire, which equals approximately 26% of Deribit's open interest," the platform said in a recent tweet. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/about-85000-bitcoin-options-contracts-set-expire-friday.htm"&gt;Read More: About 85,000 Bitcoin Options Contracts Set to Expire This Friday&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Deribit</category><category>Options</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/about-85000-bitcoin-options-contracts-set-expire-friday.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114921/277227/bitcoin-g7bce6057a-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="427728"/></item><item><title>AiDoge.com's Presale Nears $14 Million Raised - 90% Sold Out</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/aidogecoms-presale-next-crypto-explode-with-nearly-14m-raised.htm</link><description>Sensational new artificial intelligence (AI)-powered meme generating and sharing platform AiDoge.com’s viral presale is nearly over, as FOMO for the next big meme coin to explode rages. &lt;br /&gt;
In barely one month, the Web3 AI/meme project has raised a stunning $13.7 million via the sale of the $AI token that will be used to power the AiDoge platform, with supporters raving about a novel new concept that AiDoge is introducing to the crypto world called “Meme-to-Earn” (M2E)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/aidogecoms-presale-next-crypto-explode-with-nearly-14m-raised.htm"&gt;Read More: AiDoge.com's Presale Nears $14 Million Raised - 90% Sold Out&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/aidogecoms-presale-next-crypto-explode-with-nearly-14m-raised.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114962/277345/aidoge.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="279959"/></item><item><title>Regulators Around the World Regulate Cryptocurrencies Despite Market's 'Steady-State'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-around-the-world-regulate-cryptocurrencies-despite-markets-steady-state.htm</link><description>The crypto market has seen a lot of pressure from regulators in diverse jurisdictions, even as the market trend has been more bearish recently. &lt;br /&gt;
A notable instance is the continuous regulatory actions by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission.  &lt;br /&gt;
The US SEC has been actively monitoring, warning, and suing some crypto firms, including Coinbase, Kraken, Paxos, Ripple, Bittrex, Etc. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-around-the-world-regulate-cryptocurrencies-despite-markets-steady-state.htm"&gt;Read More: Regulators Around the World Regulate Cryptocurrencies Despite Market's 'Steady-State'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-around-the-world-regulate-cryptocurrencies-despite-markets-steady-state.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114960/277326/hammer-ga7a9386d1-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="216167"/></item><item><title>Unveiling the Next Crypto to Explode: Simplifying Crypto Price Predictions with yPredict's Deep Data Analysis</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/unveiling-next-crypto-explode-simplifying-crypto-price-predictions-with-ypredicts-deep-data-analysis.htm</link><description>Crypto trading is fast-paced and highly unpredictable. Some traders rely on emotions and general sentiments to place their trades.  &lt;br /&gt;
However, many trading systems are highly unreliable and lead to loss of assets.  &lt;br /&gt;
yPredict is an Artificial Intelligence (AI) powered crypto ecosystem fully dedicated to providing the right tools for traders to succeed in a volatile market. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/unveiling-next-crypto-explode-simplifying-crypto-price-predictions-with-ypredicts-deep-data-analysis.htm"&gt;Read More: Unveiling the Next Crypto to Explode: Simplifying Crypto Price Predictions with yPredict's Deep Data Analysis&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/unveiling-next-crypto-explode-simplifying-crypto-price-predictions-with-ypredicts-deep-data-analysis.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114957/277322/ypredict.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="767714"/></item><item><title>Crypto-Assets Impact on Traditional Markets Is Small, But Can Pose Systemic Risk: EU Watchdog</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-impact-on-traditional-markets-is-small-but-can-pose-systemic-risk-eu-watchdog.htm</link><description>Europe’s financial overseer does not seem overly concerned about cryptocurrencies’ impact on the financial system, but still said regulators should monitor risks in case.  &lt;br /&gt;
The European Systemic Risk Board released a report on Thursday titled “Crypto-assets and decentralised finance- systemic implications and policy options.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-impact-on-traditional-markets-is-small-but-can-pose-systemic-risk-eu-watchdog.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto-Assets Impact on Traditional Markets Is Small, But Can Pose Systemic Risk: EU Watchdog&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>EU</category><category>Regulation</category><category>DeFi</category><category>stablecoins</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-impact-on-traditional-markets-is-small-but-can-pose-systemic-risk-eu-watchdog.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114959/277320/adobestock-104359443.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="177757"/></item><item><title>One of Ripple Labs' Top Defense Lawyers Calls it Quits in U.S. SEC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/one-of-ripple-labs-top-defense-lawyers-calls-it-quits-us-sec-lawsuit.htm</link><description>The crypto industry awaits the summary judgment in the ongoing case between the US SEC and Ripple.  &lt;br /&gt;
But while that stands, one of Ripple Labs Inc.’s key defense lawyers, Attorney Kylie Chiseul Kim, announced withdrawal from the case.  &lt;br /&gt;
Kim filed a motion in the Southern District of New York indicating she is no longer linked to the law firm Kellog, Hansen, Todd Figel &amp; Frederick, P.L.L.C, currently representing the crypto firm. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/one-of-ripple-labs-top-defense-lawyers-calls-it-quits-us-sec-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: One of Ripple Labs' Top Defense Lawyers Calls it Quits in U.S. SEC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/one-of-ripple-labs-top-defense-lawyers-calls-it-quits-us-sec-lawsuit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114954/277318/coin-g94c8432bc-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="280101"/></item><item><title>Is PepeDerp The Next Pepe Coin or a Scam? CoinMarketCap's Warning &amp; 3 Better Alternatives</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepederp-next-pepe-coin-or-scam-coinmarketcaps-warning-3-better-alternatives-aidoge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm</link><description>Due to the increasing frenzy surrounding the meme coin sector, several new meme tokens have emerged.  &lt;br /&gt;
Following the remarkable Pepe coin’s price explosion, a similar meme coin called PepeDerp emerged in the crypto space.  &lt;br /&gt;
Launched on May 21, 2023, PepeDerp’s design combines the Pepe the Frog character and Derp Face....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepederp-next-pepe-coin-or-scam-coinmarketcaps-warning-3-better-alternatives-aidoge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm"&gt;Read More: Is PepeDerp The Next Pepe Coin or a Scam? CoinMarketCap's Warning &amp; 3 Better Alternatives&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepederp-next-pepe-coin-or-scam-coinmarketcaps-warning-3-better-alternatives-aidoge-ecoterra-ypredict.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114945/277312/pepederp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="224921"/></item><item><title>Ripple Purchases Bitstamp Shares as it Ponders Further M&amp;A</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-purchases-bitstamp-shares-as-it-ponders-further-ma.htm</link><description>US fintech firm Ripple has bought shares in the European crypto exchange Bitstamp, taking another step on its journey to expand internationally. &lt;br /&gt;
Ripple has so far not disclosed anything about the transaction, which was revealed in Galaxy Digital’s latest quarterly report, where Galaxy said it had advised crypto hedge fund Pantera Capital on a sale of Bitstamp shares to Ripple during the first quarter of this year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-purchases-bitstamp-shares-as-it-ponders-further-ma.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple Purchases Bitstamp Shares as it Ponders Further M&amp;A&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Bitstamp</category><category>XRP</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-purchases-bitstamp-shares-as-it-ponders-further-ma.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114949/277283/ripple-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="122365"/></item><item><title>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis Runs for President, Promises To Protect Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-gov-ron-desantis-runs-for-president-promises-protect-bitcoin.htm</link><description>U.S. presidential candidate Ron DeSantis promised to protect bitcoin when announcing his bid for presidency this week.  &lt;br /&gt;
DeSantis announced his run for president during a Twitter space on Wednesday, hosted in part by billionaire Elon Musk.  &lt;br /&gt;
“As president, we will protect the ability to do things like bitcoin,” DeSantis said. “I think these are people that are sophisticated, they can make decisions. There are risks involved with it, but let them do that.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-gov-ron-desantis-runs-for-president-promises-protect-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis Runs for President, Promises To Protect Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Ron DeSantis</category><category>Florida</category><category>Presidential campaign</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/florida-gov-ron-desantis-runs-for-president-promises-protect-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114942/277261/screen-shot-2023-05-25-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="385058"/></item><item><title>Sam Altman Co-Founder of Worldcoin Raises $115 Million for Unique Cryptocurrency</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/altman-co-founder-of-worldcoin-raises-115-million-for-unique-cryptocurrency.htm</link><description>The Chief Executive Officer of OpenAI, Sam Altman, has raised $115 million in a Series C funding round for a cryptocurrency project.  &lt;br /&gt;
Blockchain Capital led the funding round and attracted the participation of other investors such as a16z, Bain Capital Crypto, and Distributed Global. &lt;br /&gt;
Worldcoin is a decentralized open-source protocol that was co-founded by the CEO of OpenAI. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/altman-co-founder-of-worldcoin-raises-115-million-for-unique-cryptocurrency.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Altman Co-Founder of Worldcoin Raises $115 Million for Unique Cryptocurrency&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 15:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/altman-co-founder-of-worldcoin-raises-115-million-for-unique-cryptocurrency.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114940/277255/alman-co-founder-of-world.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="929548"/></item></channel></rss>
