<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:14:09 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Liquidity Troubles for Shiba Inu; How Can Dogecoin and Caged Beasts Escape The Same Fate?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/liquidity-troubles-for-shiba-inu-how-can-dogecoin-and-caged-beasts-escape-the-same-fate</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 01:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/liquidity-troubles-for-shiba-inu-how-can-dogecoin-and-caged-beasts-escape-the-same-fate</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu, the intriguing token that gained attention during the 2021 bull market, is facing concerns about its liquidity. Despite once boasting a Total Value Locked (TVL) of $1.75 billion, ShibaSwap's TVL has plummeted to a mere $25.16 million. The token's developers made headlines by donating a significant portion to Ethereum's Vitalik Buterin and burning a large number of remaining tokens. However, the ongoing liquidity issue has raised worries among Shiba Inu enthusiasts.</p>
<p>Liquidity is crucial in the cryptocurrency market, as it signals stability and allows for precise pricing and trading. Unfortunately, the industry has been experiencing a prolonged liquidity crisis, impacting major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. The market has seen steep price declines and contentious issues. The duration of the current liquidity problem remains uncertain, leaving many individuals concerned about its resolution.</p>
<p>Despite Shiba Inu's impressive market capitalization of $5 billion, its popularity has decreased. The cryptocurrency industry's liquidity problem has affected the market's development, efficiency, and future. Analysts continue to debate the impact of this issue and its potential duration.</p>
<p>Overall, the decline in liquidity and its implications for Shiba Inu and the broader cryptocurrency market have captured the attention of crypto enthusiasts. The resolution of the ongoing liquidity issue remains uncertain, leaving stakeholders eagerly awaiting signs of improvement and stability.</p>
<p></p>
How Dogecoin (DOGE) Avoided the Same Fate
<p>Dogecoin is the first meme cryptocurrency that was created as a lighthearted and meme-inspired digital asset. Unlike Shiba Inu, which has faced liquidity troubles, Dogecoin has a more established market presence and higher liquidity. Dogecoin's liquidity can be attributed to its widespread acceptance and use, as well as its long-standing presence in the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, Dogecoin's active and supportive community plays a significant role in maintaining liquidity by actively trading and promoting the token. As a result, Dogecoin has managed to avoid the liquidity troubles that Shiba Inu has experienced, providing a more stable and liquid investment option for users.</p>
<p></p>
Can Caged Beasts (BEASTS) Avoid Shiba Inu's Liquidity Troubles?
<p>Caged Beasts ($BEASTS) distinguishes itself from other tokens by offering a secure fund-locking mechanism and implementing the concept of "Caged Liquidity." This innovative approach promotes transparency, security, and decentralization in the realm of finance. By securely locking 75% of raised funds until the specified release date, Caged Beasts ensures a solid foundation and mitigates liquidity problems.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This unique feature sets it apart from tokens like Shiba Inu, demonstrating a commitment to responsible tokenomics. By providing a visible demonstration of securely locked funds, Caged Beasts instills trust and confidence among investors, paving the way for a sustainable and liquid ecosystem.</p>
What Did We Learn?
<p>The liquidity troubles faced by Shiba Inu highlight the importance of liquidity in the cryptocurrency market. Liquidity refers to the ability to buy or sell an asset quickly and at a stable price without significantly impacting its value. It is a vital aspect of a healthy market as it ensures stability, efficient trading, and precise pricing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Dogecoin has avoided liquidity problems due to its widespread acceptance and active community, while Caged Beasts has taken a proactive approach by implementing a secure fund-locking mechanism to prevent liquidity issues. The ongoing liquidity crisis in the cryptocurrency industry emphasizes the need for responsible tokenomics and transparent strategies to maintain a sustainable and liquid market.</p>
<p>Learn more about Caged Beasts:Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shiba Inu, the intriguing token that gained attention during the 2021 bull market, is facing concerns about its liquidity. Despite once boasting a Total Value Locked (TVL) of $1.75 billion, ShibaSwap's TVL has plummeted to a mere $25.16 million. The token's developers made headlines by donating a significant portion to Ethereum's Vitalik Buterin and burning a large number of remaining tokens. However, the ongoing liquidity issue has raised worries among Shiba Inu enthusiasts.</p>
<p>Liquidity is crucial in the cryptocurrency market, as it signals stability and allows for precise pricing and trading. Unfortunately, the industry has been experiencing a prolonged liquidity crisis, impacting major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. The market has seen steep price declines and contentious issues. The duration of the current liquidity problem remains uncertain, leaving many individuals concerned about its resolution.</p>
<p>Despite Shiba Inu's impressive market capitalization of $5 billion, its popularity has decreased. The cryptocurrency industry's liquidity problem has affected the market's development, efficiency, and future. Analysts continue to debate the impact of this issue and its potential duration.</p>
<p>Overall, the decline in liquidity and its implications for Shiba Inu and the broader cryptocurrency market have captured the attention of crypto enthusiasts. The resolution of the ongoing liquidity issue remains uncertain, leaving stakeholders eagerly awaiting signs of improvement and stability.</p>
<p></p>
How Dogecoin (DOGE) Avoided the Same Fate
<p>Dogecoin is the first meme cryptocurrency that was created as a lighthearted and meme-inspired digital asset. Unlike Shiba Inu, which has faced liquidity troubles, Dogecoin has a more established market presence and higher liquidity. Dogecoin's liquidity can be attributed to its widespread acceptance and use, as well as its long-standing presence in the cryptocurrency market.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, Dogecoin's active and supportive community plays a significant role in maintaining liquidity by actively trading and promoting the token. As a result, Dogecoin has managed to avoid the liquidity troubles that Shiba Inu has experienced, providing a more stable and liquid investment option for users.</p>
<p></p>
Can Caged Beasts (BEASTS) Avoid Shiba Inu's Liquidity Troubles?
<p>Caged Beasts ($BEASTS) distinguishes itself from other tokens by offering a secure fund-locking mechanism and implementing the concept of "Caged Liquidity." This innovative approach promotes transparency, security, and decentralization in the realm of finance. By securely locking 75% of raised funds until the specified release date, Caged Beasts ensures a solid foundation and mitigates liquidity problems.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This unique feature sets it apart from tokens like Shiba Inu, demonstrating a commitment to responsible tokenomics. By providing a visible demonstration of securely locked funds, Caged Beasts instills trust and confidence among investors, paving the way for a sustainable and liquid ecosystem.</p>
What Did We Learn?
<p>The liquidity troubles faced by Shiba Inu highlight the importance of liquidity in the cryptocurrency market. Liquidity refers to the ability to buy or sell an asset quickly and at a stable price without significantly impacting its value. It is a vital aspect of a healthy market as it ensures stability, efficient trading, and precise pricing.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Dogecoin has avoided liquidity problems due to its widespread acceptance and active community, while Caged Beasts has taken a proactive approach by implementing a secure fund-locking mechanism to prevent liquidity issues. The ongoing liquidity crisis in the cryptocurrency industry emphasizes the need for responsible tokenomics and transparent strategies to maintain a sustainable and liquid market.</p>
<p>Learn more about Caged Beasts:Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ENO Token Lists on LATOKEN to Transform the Wine Industry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/eno-token-lists-on-latoken-to-transform-the-wine-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Latoken_-_1200x720_1687375225xJASO8qJtC.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Latoken_-_1200x720_1687375225xJASO8qJtC.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Latoken_-_1200x720_1687375225xJASO8qJtC.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:50:40 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/eno-token-lists-on-latoken-to-transform-the-wine-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Mexico City, Mexico, June 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>ENO, the native token of an emerging wine industry platform, has been listed on LATOKEN. The news marks a milestone in the history of wine while cementing LATOKEN&rsquo;s reputation as a testbed for innovative new tokens.</p><p>The ENO platform aims to provide access to a rapidly expanding wine ecosystem while distilling the greatest elements of the industry by combining centuries of tradition with web3 technology. Wine culture has fascinated people for centuries, and web3 offers exciting and disruptive opportunities.</p><p>ENO&rsquo;s listing on LATOKEN will allow users of the global exchange to tap into a new web3 vertical and to leverage a digital asset that enables users to enjoy exclusive experiences that combine art, music, web3 technology, and wine. Through the ENO platform, this club provides access to special auctions, unique wine-tasting experiences, and the opportunity to acquire limited-edition wine bottles in collaboration with renowned artists from around the world. Being part of this select group of wine enthusiasts and NFT collectors brings wine culture to a new audience.</p><p>The ENO platform also includes the Wine Academy, an educational portal that uses blockchain technology to issue digital certificates based on the courses aspiring vintners have completed. ENO brings together farmers, vineyards, exporters, importers, consumers, sommeliers, hotels, and wine enthusiasts in a decentralized community, expanding the horizon of wine culture.</p><p>The ENO token listed on LATOKEN on June 20, marking a new chapter in the fusion of tradition and technology.</p><p>About ENO</p><p>ENO is a platform that combines the tradition of wine with technological innovation. Its goal is to facilitate access to the wine ecosystem and promote the growth of wine culture worldwide through the implementation of advanced technologies such as tokenization.</p><p>About LATOKEN</p><p>LATOKEN is a globally recognized token exchange platform. It offers a stable trading environment backed by real assets and provides opportunities for participation in innovative and promising projects.</p><p>For more information about ENO and its inclusion in LATOKEN, please visit:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Telegram | Facebook | Instagram | YouTube Channel</p><p></p>ContactCo-FounderAlberto FernandezENOalberto@enotoken.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mexico City, Mexico, June 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>ENO, the native token of an emerging wine industry platform, has been listed on LATOKEN. The news marks a milestone in the history of wine while cementing LATOKEN&rsquo;s reputation as a testbed for innovative new tokens.</p><p>The ENO platform aims to provide access to a rapidly expanding wine ecosystem while distilling the greatest elements of the industry by combining centuries of tradition with web3 technology. Wine culture has fascinated people for centuries, and web3 offers exciting and disruptive opportunities.</p><p>ENO&rsquo;s listing on LATOKEN will allow users of the global exchange to tap into a new web3 vertical and to leverage a digital asset that enables users to enjoy exclusive experiences that combine art, music, web3 technology, and wine. Through the ENO platform, this club provides access to special auctions, unique wine-tasting experiences, and the opportunity to acquire limited-edition wine bottles in collaboration with renowned artists from around the world. Being part of this select group of wine enthusiasts and NFT collectors brings wine culture to a new audience.</p><p>The ENO platform also includes the Wine Academy, an educational portal that uses blockchain technology to issue digital certificates based on the courses aspiring vintners have completed. ENO brings together farmers, vineyards, exporters, importers, consumers, sommeliers, hotels, and wine enthusiasts in a decentralized community, expanding the horizon of wine culture.</p><p>The ENO token listed on LATOKEN on June 20, marking a new chapter in the fusion of tradition and technology.</p><p>About ENO</p><p>ENO is a platform that combines the tradition of wine with technological innovation. Its goal is to facilitate access to the wine ecosystem and promote the growth of wine culture worldwide through the implementation of advanced technologies such as tokenization.</p><p>About LATOKEN</p><p>LATOKEN is a globally recognized token exchange platform. It offers a stable trading environment backed by real assets and provides opportunities for participation in innovative and promising projects.</p><p>For more information about ENO and its inclusion in LATOKEN, please visit:</p><p>Official Website | Twitter | Telegram | Facebook | Instagram | YouTube Channel</p><p></p>ContactCo-FounderAlberto FernandezENOalberto@enotoken.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mega bitcoin pump defies SEC actions]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/mega-bitcoin-pump-defies-sec-actions</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-49.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-49.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-49.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 20:05:52 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/mega-bitcoin-pump-defies-sec-actions</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin breaches $30,000 in the face of the SEC&rsquo;s harsh treatment of the crypto sector. Could this be the start of a rally to $45,000?</p>
Bitcoin defies the odds
<p>Bitcoin is unstoppable. It&rsquo;s a rocket ship; a turbo-charged dynamo; an asset that can save anyone who has the nouse to climb onboard. The SEC and the US government can do what they may but bitcoin is sound money, something all fiat currencies completely lack.</p>
<p>The king of the cryptocurrencies is saying no to censorship, no to being taken down, and no to the madness of central banks and their attempt to gain full control over the citizenry with the eventual imposition of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Over the last couple of days bitcoin has proved the doubters wrong, and not only that, it has given the powers that be plenty to think about. SEC chairman Gary Gensler must have thought that he had put the stopper back into the bottle when he unleashed his attacks on the top crypto exchanges, but bitcoin has other ideas. Blackrock, Fidelity, and others' entry into the crypto space might also have something to do with it.</p>
What next?
<p>Of course, this particular pump may now be rejected from the $30,000 resistance. It will need some power behind it indeed if it is to somehow blast its way through. However, bitcoin has a history of doing the unexpected, and now the calvary, in the form of the big institutions, looks as though it is arriving and who knows now what might happen.</p>
<p>The next step for bitcoin, if it can maintain the momentum, is to make a new local high of around $31,000, which will surpass the one made in mid-April. From there it will be a case of also making a higher low than $24,800, although it might be hoped that $27,000 or even $30,000 can be the new support.</p>
So far infallible signal indicates upside
<p>One little known indicator in bitcoin&rsquo;s favour is the NVT &amp; HV Combo. This indicator flashed today as the signal line crossed the 40 level and maintained its green colour on the 5-day and the weekly time frames. Green means that price should continue to the upside, while red would signal the opposite. This particular indicator has flashed only 7 times previously since 2017 without any false signals. Today&rsquo;s signal is the eighth time, and many will hope that this signal is a particularly fruitful one. $45,000 beckons.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin breaches $30,000 in the face of the SEC&rsquo;s harsh treatment of the crypto sector. Could this be the start of a rally to $45,000?</p>
Bitcoin defies the odds
<p>Bitcoin is unstoppable. It&rsquo;s a rocket ship; a turbo-charged dynamo; an asset that can save anyone who has the nouse to climb onboard. The SEC and the US government can do what they may but bitcoin is sound money, something all fiat currencies completely lack.</p>
<p>The king of the cryptocurrencies is saying no to censorship, no to being taken down, and no to the madness of central banks and their attempt to gain full control over the citizenry with the eventual imposition of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Over the last couple of days bitcoin has proved the doubters wrong, and not only that, it has given the powers that be plenty to think about. SEC chairman Gary Gensler must have thought that he had put the stopper back into the bottle when he unleashed his attacks on the top crypto exchanges, but bitcoin has other ideas. Blackrock, Fidelity, and others' entry into the crypto space might also have something to do with it.</p>
What next?
<p>Of course, this particular pump may now be rejected from the $30,000 resistance. It will need some power behind it indeed if it is to somehow blast its way through. However, bitcoin has a history of doing the unexpected, and now the calvary, in the form of the big institutions, looks as though it is arriving and who knows now what might happen.</p>
<p>The next step for bitcoin, if it can maintain the momentum, is to make a new local high of around $31,000, which will surpass the one made in mid-April. From there it will be a case of also making a higher low than $24,800, although it might be hoped that $27,000 or even $30,000 can be the new support.</p>
So far infallible signal indicates upside
<p>One little known indicator in bitcoin&rsquo;s favour is the NVT &amp; HV Combo. This indicator flashed today as the signal line crossed the 40 level and maintained its green colour on the 5-day and the weekly time frames. Green means that price should continue to the upside, while red would signal the opposite. This particular indicator has flashed only 7 times previously since 2017 without any false signals. Today&rsquo;s signal is the eighth time, and many will hope that this signal is a particularly fruitful one. $45,000 beckons.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BIS Backs Tokenization, But Disses Crypto as “Flawed System”]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bis-backs-tokenization-but-disses-crypto-as-flawed-system</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bis-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bis-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bis-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:53:16 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bis-backs-tokenization-but-disses-crypto-as-flawed-system</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a new report, the BIS has expressed its approval for tokenizing assets, releasing a blueprint for a global &ldquo;unified ledger,&rdquo; but described crypto as a &ldquo;flawed system.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The Bank of International Settlements on Tuesday released a plan for a global &ldquo;unified ledger&rdquo; which would support central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and tokenized assets. The BIS, which is regarded as the central bank of central banks described in a report detailing the future of the monetary system, that tokenization, or converting money and other assets into digital tokens that can be traded on programmable platforms, says it offers a &ldquo;major leap&rdquo; in the financial system.</p>
<p>While advocating for a centralized option, the BIS described decentralized cryptocurrencies as a &ldquo;flawed system.&rdquo; Moreover, the report said:</p>

<p>Crypto and decentralized finance (DeFi) have offered a glimpse of tokenization&rsquo;s promise, but crypto is a flawed system that cannot take on the mantle of the future of money.</p>

<p>The BIS also further argued that &ldquo;crypto has collapsed&rdquo; and said the successful use of tokenization relies on the trust provided by central banks.</p>

<p>The collapse of crypto and the faltering progress of other tokenization projects underline a key lesson: tokenization&rsquo;s success rests on the foundation of trust provided by central bank money and its capacity to knit together key elements of the financial system.</p>

Tokenization is &ldquo;The Next Logical Step&rdquo;
<p>The bank further asserts that tokenization is &ldquo;the next logical step&rdquo; in asset transfer and digital record keeping. It said:</p>

<p>Tokenization could dramatically enhance the capabilities of the monetary and financial system by harnessing new ways for intermediaries to interact in serving end users, removing the traditional separation of messaging, reconciliation and settlement.</p>

BIS Identifies Smart Contracts as a Significant Use Case of a Unified Ledger &nbsp;
<p>In making its case for a unified ledger, the BIS identified its potential use case. The bank identifies smart contracts which could open the door to new types of &ldquo;arrangements and transactions that &ldquo;could expand the universe of possible contracting outcomes.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The report outlines that smart contracts can overcome coordination problems frequently occurring in joint ventures. It states blockchain technology could add to the stability of bank funding and eliminate free-riding.</p>

<p>A smart contract could specify that each participant contributes only a certain amount to a joint venture if all other participants also contribute, this way, free-riding is eliminated.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a new report, the BIS has expressed its approval for tokenizing assets, releasing a blueprint for a global &ldquo;unified ledger,&rdquo; but described crypto as a &ldquo;flawed system.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The Bank of International Settlements on Tuesday released a plan for a global &ldquo;unified ledger&rdquo; which would support central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and tokenized assets. The BIS, which is regarded as the central bank of central banks described in a report detailing the future of the monetary system, that tokenization, or converting money and other assets into digital tokens that can be traded on programmable platforms, says it offers a &ldquo;major leap&rdquo; in the financial system.</p>
<p>While advocating for a centralized option, the BIS described decentralized cryptocurrencies as a &ldquo;flawed system.&rdquo; Moreover, the report said:</p>

<p>Crypto and decentralized finance (DeFi) have offered a glimpse of tokenization&rsquo;s promise, but crypto is a flawed system that cannot take on the mantle of the future of money.</p>

<p>The BIS also further argued that &ldquo;crypto has collapsed&rdquo; and said the successful use of tokenization relies on the trust provided by central banks.</p>

<p>The collapse of crypto and the faltering progress of other tokenization projects underline a key lesson: tokenization&rsquo;s success rests on the foundation of trust provided by central bank money and its capacity to knit together key elements of the financial system.</p>

Tokenization is &ldquo;The Next Logical Step&rdquo;
<p>The bank further asserts that tokenization is &ldquo;the next logical step&rdquo; in asset transfer and digital record keeping. It said:</p>

<p>Tokenization could dramatically enhance the capabilities of the monetary and financial system by harnessing new ways for intermediaries to interact in serving end users, removing the traditional separation of messaging, reconciliation and settlement.</p>

BIS Identifies Smart Contracts as a Significant Use Case of a Unified Ledger &nbsp;
<p>In making its case for a unified ledger, the BIS identified its potential use case. The bank identifies smart contracts which could open the door to new types of &ldquo;arrangements and transactions that &ldquo;could expand the universe of possible contracting outcomes.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The report outlines that smart contracts can overcome coordination problems frequently occurring in joint ventures. It states blockchain technology could add to the stability of bank funding and eliminate free-riding.</p>

<p>A smart contract could specify that each participant contributes only a certain amount to a joint venture if all other participants also contribute, this way, free-riding is eliminated.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Wall Street Backed ‘EDX Markets’ Crypto Exchange Goes Live]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wall-street-backed-edx-markets-crypto-exchange-goes-live</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/edxm.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/edxm.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/edxm.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:54:23 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wall-street-backed-edx-markets-crypto-exchange-goes-live</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>EDX Markets, the crypto exchange endorsed by Wall Street heavyweights such as Fidelity and Citadel, launched its operations this week. The platform will offer trading in BTC, LTC, ETH and BCH. </p>
<p>EDX Markets launched its operations on Tuesday after it completed an investment round which saw it onboard new equity partners to join its founding investors Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, Sequoia Capital, and Charles Schwab.</p>
EDX Will Allow Trading In BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH
<p>In a press release, EDX explained that it offers a &ldquo;non-custodial&rdquo; model, meaning it does not hold clients&rsquo; digital assets. The platform instead works with a third-party custodian, said Chief Executive Officer Jamil Nazarali.</p>
<p>The exchange also said it successfully conducted an investment round to add investors such as Miami International Holdings, DV Crypto, GTS, GSR Markets LTD, and HRT Technology.</p>
<p>Nazarali said:</p>

<p>EDX&rsquo;s ability to attract new investors and partners in the face of sector headwinds demonstrates the strength of our platform and the demand for a safe and compliant cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>EDX further stated it aims to bring elements of traditional finance over to crypto, focusing on compliance and mitigating conflicts of interest.</p>

<p>We are committed to bringing the best of traditional finance to cryptocurrency markets, with an infrastructure built by market experts to embed key institutional best practices.</p>

<p>Unlike other crypto exchanges, EDX will only allow investors to trade four top cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC) and Bitcoin Cash (BCH). &nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s CEO said EDX would soon launch a clearing house.</p>

<p>With the endorsement of our new and growing list of investors and customers, we&rsquo;re proud to launch trading and look forward to further enhancements to our offering. Looking ahead, EDX Clearing will be a major differentiator for EDX -- and resolve an unmet need in the market &ndash; by enhancing competition and creating unparalleled operational efficiency through a single settlement process.</p>

Traditional Financial Institutions Bullish on Bitcoin
<p>In a time of intense regulatory scrutiny of the crypto industry, some traditional financial institutions are laying the groundwork to participate in the market. BlackRock, the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, announced last week that it applied for a Bitcoin spot ETF (exchange-traded fund). If approved, the ETF would become the first crypto spot ETF in the US.</p>
<p>Rumour also has it that Fidelity Investments applied with the SEC to develop a Bitcoin ETF similar to BlackRock&rsquo;s.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EDX Markets, the crypto exchange endorsed by Wall Street heavyweights such as Fidelity and Citadel, launched its operations this week. The platform will offer trading in BTC, LTC, ETH and BCH. </p>
<p>EDX Markets launched its operations on Tuesday after it completed an investment round which saw it onboard new equity partners to join its founding investors Citadel Securities, Fidelity Digital Assets, Sequoia Capital, and Charles Schwab.</p>
EDX Will Allow Trading In BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH
<p>In a press release, EDX explained that it offers a &ldquo;non-custodial&rdquo; model, meaning it does not hold clients&rsquo; digital assets. The platform instead works with a third-party custodian, said Chief Executive Officer Jamil Nazarali.</p>
<p>The exchange also said it successfully conducted an investment round to add investors such as Miami International Holdings, DV Crypto, GTS, GSR Markets LTD, and HRT Technology.</p>
<p>Nazarali said:</p>

<p>EDX&rsquo;s ability to attract new investors and partners in the face of sector headwinds demonstrates the strength of our platform and the demand for a safe and compliant cryptocurrency market.</p>

<p>EDX further stated it aims to bring elements of traditional finance over to crypto, focusing on compliance and mitigating conflicts of interest.</p>

<p>We are committed to bringing the best of traditional finance to cryptocurrency markets, with an infrastructure built by market experts to embed key institutional best practices.</p>

<p>Unlike other crypto exchanges, EDX will only allow investors to trade four top cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC), Ethereum (ETH), Litecoin (LTC) and Bitcoin Cash (BCH). &nbsp;</p>
<p>The platform&rsquo;s CEO said EDX would soon launch a clearing house.</p>

<p>With the endorsement of our new and growing list of investors and customers, we&rsquo;re proud to launch trading and look forward to further enhancements to our offering. Looking ahead, EDX Clearing will be a major differentiator for EDX -- and resolve an unmet need in the market &ndash; by enhancing competition and creating unparalleled operational efficiency through a single settlement process.</p>

Traditional Financial Institutions Bullish on Bitcoin
<p>In a time of intense regulatory scrutiny of the crypto industry, some traditional financial institutions are laying the groundwork to participate in the market. BlackRock, the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, announced last week that it applied for a Bitcoin spot ETF (exchange-traded fund). If approved, the ETF would become the first crypto spot ETF in the US.</p>
<p>Rumour also has it that Fidelity Investments applied with the SEC to develop a Bitcoin ETF similar to BlackRock&rsquo;s.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[PLAYA3ULL Games Enhance The Blockchain Ecosystem With A 10% Burn Mechanic And A New Dedicated Blockchain On An Avalanche Subnet]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/playa3ull-games-enhance-the-blockchain-ecosystem-with-a-10-burn-mechanic-and-a-new-dedicated-blockchain-on-an-avalanche-subnet</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-160340.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-160340.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-160340.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/playa3ull-games-enhance-the-blockchain-ecosystem-with-a-10-burn-mechanic-and-a-new-dedicated-blockchain-on-an-avalanche-subnet</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[Web3, Global Gaming Industry, June 21, 2023
<p class="s5">PLAYA3ULL GAMES, a front-runner in the blockchain gaming landscape, is revolutionizing the sector by launching its own blockchain on an Avalanche Subnet, strengthening security and improving integration capabilities.</p>
<p class="s5">In a significant development, the company has introduced a notable 10% burn mechanic designed to enhance the deflationary attribute of its native 3ULL coin strategically. This move guarantees to increase the coin's scarcity over time. All in-game assets in the PLAYA3ULL GAMES ecosystem are held in Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs). The burn mechanic will apply to all NFTs sold from the PLAYA3ULL GAMES Marketplace, encouraging a cycle where heightened community activity expedites the 3ULL coin burn, boosting its rarity and value.</p>
<p class="s5">Transitioning to the Avalanche Subnet allows PLAYA3ULL GAMES to maintain the robust security of the Avalanche Blockchain while implementing its new blockchain. This independent blockchain will host all nodes essential for the daily production of 3ULL coins and will serve as the bedrock of the PLAYA3ULL GAMES ecosystem. With 4,400 nodes already sold out of a total of 50,000, each node delivers a daily reward of 1,500 3ULL coins, a substantial incentive for potential node operators, strengthening the network.</p>
<p class="s5">This movement to an Avalanche Subnet, coupled with the introduction of a deflationary coin-burn mechanic, marks a new era of growth for PLAYA3ULL GAMES. These pioneering moves reinforce PLAYA3ULL GAMES' commitment to reshaping the gaming industry by offering exceptional opportunities to its expanding community.</p>
<p class="s5">To learn more about PLAYA3ULL GAMES, visit their website at&nbsp;www.playa3ull.games&nbsp;or follow their social media channels:</p>
<p class="s5">Discord:&nbsp;https://discord.gg/playa3ull</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter:&nbsp;https://twitter.com/playa3ull_games</p>
<p class="s5">YouTube:&nbsp;https://www.youtube.com/@PLAYA3ULL_GAMES</p>
<p class="s5">PLAYA3ULL GAMES, an international gaming company established in November 2021, pioneered the first NFT generator in June 2022 and launched its native 3ULL chain in June 2023. The flagship game, NEXUS, is scheduled for release on September 3, 2023, with two additional games expected before the end of the year. PLAYA3ULL GAMES' mission is to transform gaming into an asset class that rewards gamers for their time and investment, and it is generously supported by a community that serves as the heart of the project. </p>
<p class="s5">Press Contact: Jonathan Bouzanquet Founder &amp; CSO </p>
<p class="s5">Email: jb@playa3ull.games</p>
<p class="s5">Phone:&nbsp;+971523641388</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[Web3, Global Gaming Industry, June 21, 2023
<p class="s5">PLAYA3ULL GAMES, a front-runner in the blockchain gaming landscape, is revolutionizing the sector by launching its own blockchain on an Avalanche Subnet, strengthening security and improving integration capabilities.</p>
<p class="s5">In a significant development, the company has introduced a notable 10% burn mechanic designed to enhance the deflationary attribute of its native 3ULL coin strategically. This move guarantees to increase the coin's scarcity over time. All in-game assets in the PLAYA3ULL GAMES ecosystem are held in Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs). The burn mechanic will apply to all NFTs sold from the PLAYA3ULL GAMES Marketplace, encouraging a cycle where heightened community activity expedites the 3ULL coin burn, boosting its rarity and value.</p>
<p class="s5">Transitioning to the Avalanche Subnet allows PLAYA3ULL GAMES to maintain the robust security of the Avalanche Blockchain while implementing its new blockchain. This independent blockchain will host all nodes essential for the daily production of 3ULL coins and will serve as the bedrock of the PLAYA3ULL GAMES ecosystem. With 4,400 nodes already sold out of a total of 50,000, each node delivers a daily reward of 1,500 3ULL coins, a substantial incentive for potential node operators, strengthening the network.</p>
<p class="s5">This movement to an Avalanche Subnet, coupled with the introduction of a deflationary coin-burn mechanic, marks a new era of growth for PLAYA3ULL GAMES. These pioneering moves reinforce PLAYA3ULL GAMES' commitment to reshaping the gaming industry by offering exceptional opportunities to its expanding community.</p>
<p class="s5">To learn more about PLAYA3ULL GAMES, visit their website at&nbsp;www.playa3ull.games&nbsp;or follow their social media channels:</p>
<p class="s5">Discord:&nbsp;https://discord.gg/playa3ull</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter:&nbsp;https://twitter.com/playa3ull_games</p>
<p class="s5">YouTube:&nbsp;https://www.youtube.com/@PLAYA3ULL_GAMES</p>
<p class="s5">PLAYA3ULL GAMES, an international gaming company established in November 2021, pioneered the first NFT generator in June 2022 and launched its native 3ULL chain in June 2023. The flagship game, NEXUS, is scheduled for release on September 3, 2023, with two additional games expected before the end of the year. PLAYA3ULL GAMES' mission is to transform gaming into an asset class that rewards gamers for their time and investment, and it is generously supported by a community that serves as the heart of the project. </p>
<p class="s5">Press Contact: Jonathan Bouzanquet Founder &amp; CSO </p>
<p class="s5">Email: jb@playa3ull.games</p>
<p class="s5">Phone:&nbsp;+971523641388</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[10 Promising AI cryptocurrencies to watch in 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/10-promising-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-watch-in-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-154433.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-154433.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-154433.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/10-promising-ai-cryptocurrencies-to-watch-in-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies, like InQubeta (QUBE), that are linked to artificial intelligence (AI) have emerged as the top altcoins to buy as crypto investors look to capitalize on what many industry experts like Bill Gates have already predicted will be the next technological revolution. Gates has already warned that the world should expect to see many major changes within a few years.</p>
<p>The InQubeta presale is attracting lots of global investors as it&rsquo;s the first platform to create a simpler yet secure way for anyone, anywhere to buy equity in artificial intelligence startups. InQubeta isn&rsquo;t the only AI-linked altcoin that has been getting lots of attention lately. Others like Fetch.ai and Singlularity.NET are also seeing an influx of bullish investors. Even mainstream corporations that help to push innovations like Nvidia, which provides chips for AI software, have also seen a substantial increase in investment funds. Nvidia recently became a trillion-dollar corporation after announcing that the demand for chips that power AI software has increased by over 50%.</p>
InQubeta emerges as leader of AI cryptocurrencies
<p>Also known as machine learning, artificial intelligence is a type of software system that&rsquo;s based on neural networks. The technique was created decades ago, but couldn&rsquo;t be used to its full potential until new computing resources were developed.</p>
<p>Thanks to AI, vehicles with self-driving capabilities are already being mass-produced and many people have smartphones with effective image and voice recognition tools. Companies like Tesla&reg; are already working on humanoid robots that can perform manual labor and domestic tasks.</p>
<p>Even Wall Street has been firmly behind the AI revolution, with investments in the sector rising by over $100 billion from 2015 to 2022. Total investments in firms linked to AI are predicted to exceed $1.5 trillion by 2030. A large portion of these funds will go into AI-linked cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The top ten ones are:</p>
1. InQubeta (QUBE)
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) provides a platform that allows startups that focus on artificial intelligence to connect with potential investors. It bypasses the barriers associated with conventional investment channels like needing Silicon-Valley-type connections or being able to afford minimum account deposits that exceed the average person&rsquo;s annual income.</p>
<p>Firms raise money on the InQubeta platform by creating non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that denote equity and other bonuses in their companies. The NFTs are fractionalized, allowing investors to invest as little or as much as they want. They become equity-owning associates, while the company gets the capital it needs to innovate. Transactions are done with the platform&rsquo;s native currency, $QUBE tokens.</p>
<p>AI is expected to be, at the very least, as disruptive as the Internet revolution was. Those who invested in companies that quickly capitalized on the new opportunities created by the internet have made substantial returns on their investments since. For example, a $10,000 investment in Amazon during its initial public offering in 1997 would be worth more than $2.2 million today.</p>
<p>Thanks to InQubeta, everyone can now invest in companies that will push innovations in the sector.</p>
<p>InQubeta investors can earn extra bonuses by staking their $QUBE to help secure and run the blockchain. Rewards are sent periodically from a dedicated pool that is funded with a 5% sell levy on all $QUBE transactions. $QUBE tokens also give investors access to the platform&rsquo;s governance, allowing them to suggest and vote on issues that affect the project&rsquo;s development and future.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">&nbsp;</p>
2. Fetch.ai (FET)
<p>Fetch.ai is another interesting AI-driven cryptocurrency platform that has been getting lots of attention lately. It aims to automate web transactions on its decentralized platform. Each user gets a digital version of themselves called a &lsquo;digital twin&rsquo; that learns, interacts, and negotiates with the digital twins of goods or service providers.</p>
<p>Digital twins use set parameters given by users to negotiate on their behalf. For example, a user&rsquo;s digital twin might interact with the digital twins of concert ticket sellers to find the best deals for a specific event. These digital twins can also interact with other digital twins that have performed similar tasks in the past and learn from them. Fetch.ai digital twins can also be used for decentralized financial services. For example, a user&rsquo;s digital twin can notice price differences of a specific token on different cryptocurrency exchanges and take advantage of them autonomously. Bill Gates recently predicted that services like the ones provided by Fetch.ai would be the first to cause major disruptions as it has the potential to change how people shop online.</p>
3. Singlularity.NET (AGIX)
<p>Singularity.Net is a decentralized AI marketplace that uses blockchain technology to provide unrestricted access to applications and algorithms. One of the platform&rsquo;s main goals is to create Artificial General Intelligence from all the interactions between different AI algorithms.</p>
<p>Singularity.NET hosts its platform on the Cardano (ADA) and Ethereum (ETH) blockchains and anyone can use the learning models created on it. Its native currency the AGIX is used to pay transaction fees and purchase products. Over 70 AI services are already available on the platform and the user-friendly interface makes it easy for non-developers to navigate the space.</p>
4. The Graph (GRT)
<p>The Graph provides a system for querying and indexing data from blockchains, much like a search engine&rsquo;s index and query data from websites. The Graph&rsquo;s platform does this by organizing data into subgraphs. It&rsquo;s built on the Ethereum blockchain and it allows anyone to build and publish APIs that applications can query with GraphQL to secure blockchain data.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
5. Ocean Protocol (OCEAN)
<p>Ocean Protocol provides an Ethereum-based platform that allows individuals and businesses to monetize and exchange data and data-based services. For example, it can give researchers access to the data without the data holder having to relinquish it.</p>
<p>While many cryptocurrencies had a rough time in 2022, Ocean prices kept growing before finally coming down in early 2023.</p>
6. Cortex (CTXC)
<p>Cortex provides a peer-to-peer, open-source, decentralized blockchain-based platform that supports uploading and executing AI models on the distributed network. It aims for AI democratization where models can be integrated into smart contracts to create AI-powered decentralized applications.</p>
<p>Cortex hasn&rsquo;t enjoyed the price growth many other AI-driven cryptocurrencies have recently seen, but it has the potential to create a new class of decentralized applications and smart contracts in the future.</p>
7. iExec RLC (RLC)
<p>IExec offers a blockchain network that users can use to monetize their computing power or access on-demand computing resources. RLC is the network's native currency and it&rsquo;s used to pay transaction fees on the blockchain.</p>
<p>The iExec platform is currently the leading blockchain-based decentralized computing platform and it also allows users to monetize data sets and applications. iExec supports applications used in various fields like fintech, rendering, AI, and healthcare. iExec aims to reinvent the cloud computing space by creating a new blockchain-based cloud paradigm.</p>
<p>iExec&rsquo;s platform relies on XtremWeb-HEP, which is an open-source grid software that allows for features like security, data management, private infrastructure, and the development of virtual images.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
8. Numeraire (NMR)
<p>Numeraire runs an AI-powered blockchain network that acts like a hedge fund on behalf of users, using machine learning and artificial intelligence to invest in global stock markets. Its native currency the Numeraire is used to pay transaction fees on the network.</p>
<p>The Numeraire blockchain is Ethereum-based, allowing data scientists and developers to experiment and develop machine learning models. The platform aims to decentralize the data science field while allowing developers to make more effective machine-learning models.</p>
<p>Numeraire claims the title of being the first hedge fund to launch its cryptocurrency, but unlike conventional hedge funds, it uses predictions made by users to select stocks. It heavily relies on machine learning for its investment strategies.</p>
9. dKargo (DKA)
<p>dKargo is a blockchain network that uses artificial intelligence to address issues in the logistics industry by providing credible data to participants. The network also helps to establish efficient logistics networks based on improved communication provided by blockchain technology.</p>
<p>The dKargo platform helps to address trust issues created by split logistic nodes by using blockchain technology to enhance communication and create collaboration-based logistic networks that would be impossible without blockchain technology. The platform also provides Web3 logistic services. It gives users optimized routes and logistics that couldn&rsquo;t have been possible with the structure of silo logistics.</p>
10. Phala Network (PHA)
<p>Phala Network also provides AI-augmented blockchain-based cloud computing services, but its main focus is privacy. The platform is positioned as a decentralized alternative to traditional cloud computing providers like Google Cloud or Amazon AWS.</p>
<p>PHA is its native currency and used for various things like purchasing computing resources, paying data exchange fees, and security guarantees. Phala Network provides users with contract-based data exchange infrastructure for standardized trading protocols, analysis, and collection. PHA also serves as the platform&rsquo;s governance tokens giving users a say in the platform&rsquo;s development and operations.</p>
Summary
<p>2023 has been the year of AI-linked cryptos as they emerge as the top altcoins to buy. Investors remain bullish on these tokens that are driven by artificial intelligence while generally feeling bearish about most cryptocurrencies. AI-linked cryptos are taking over the crypto space and their futures look bright with a total of $1.5 trillion expected to be funneled into the AI sector.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrencies, like InQubeta (QUBE), that are linked to artificial intelligence (AI) have emerged as the top altcoins to buy as crypto investors look to capitalize on what many industry experts like Bill Gates have already predicted will be the next technological revolution. Gates has already warned that the world should expect to see many major changes within a few years.</p>
<p>The InQubeta presale is attracting lots of global investors as it&rsquo;s the first platform to create a simpler yet secure way for anyone, anywhere to buy equity in artificial intelligence startups. InQubeta isn&rsquo;t the only AI-linked altcoin that has been getting lots of attention lately. Others like Fetch.ai and Singlularity.NET are also seeing an influx of bullish investors. Even mainstream corporations that help to push innovations like Nvidia, which provides chips for AI software, have also seen a substantial increase in investment funds. Nvidia recently became a trillion-dollar corporation after announcing that the demand for chips that power AI software has increased by over 50%.</p>
InQubeta emerges as leader of AI cryptocurrencies
<p>Also known as machine learning, artificial intelligence is a type of software system that&rsquo;s based on neural networks. The technique was created decades ago, but couldn&rsquo;t be used to its full potential until new computing resources were developed.</p>
<p>Thanks to AI, vehicles with self-driving capabilities are already being mass-produced and many people have smartphones with effective image and voice recognition tools. Companies like Tesla&reg; are already working on humanoid robots that can perform manual labor and domestic tasks.</p>
<p>Even Wall Street has been firmly behind the AI revolution, with investments in the sector rising by over $100 billion from 2015 to 2022. Total investments in firms linked to AI are predicted to exceed $1.5 trillion by 2030. A large portion of these funds will go into AI-linked cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The top ten ones are:</p>
1. InQubeta (QUBE)
<p>InQubeta (QUBE) provides a platform that allows startups that focus on artificial intelligence to connect with potential investors. It bypasses the barriers associated with conventional investment channels like needing Silicon-Valley-type connections or being able to afford minimum account deposits that exceed the average person&rsquo;s annual income.</p>
<p>Firms raise money on the InQubeta platform by creating non-fungible tokens (NFTs) that denote equity and other bonuses in their companies. The NFTs are fractionalized, allowing investors to invest as little or as much as they want. They become equity-owning associates, while the company gets the capital it needs to innovate. Transactions are done with the platform&rsquo;s native currency, $QUBE tokens.</p>
<p>AI is expected to be, at the very least, as disruptive as the Internet revolution was. Those who invested in companies that quickly capitalized on the new opportunities created by the internet have made substantial returns on their investments since. For example, a $10,000 investment in Amazon during its initial public offering in 1997 would be worth more than $2.2 million today.</p>
<p>Thanks to InQubeta, everyone can now invest in companies that will push innovations in the sector.</p>
<p>InQubeta investors can earn extra bonuses by staking their $QUBE to help secure and run the blockchain. Rewards are sent periodically from a dedicated pool that is funded with a 5% sell levy on all $QUBE transactions. $QUBE tokens also give investors access to the platform&rsquo;s governance, allowing them to suggest and vote on issues that affect the project&rsquo;s development and future.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale &nbsp;</p>
<p class="s12">&nbsp;</p>
2. Fetch.ai (FET)
<p>Fetch.ai is another interesting AI-driven cryptocurrency platform that has been getting lots of attention lately. It aims to automate web transactions on its decentralized platform. Each user gets a digital version of themselves called a &lsquo;digital twin&rsquo; that learns, interacts, and negotiates with the digital twins of goods or service providers.</p>
<p>Digital twins use set parameters given by users to negotiate on their behalf. For example, a user&rsquo;s digital twin might interact with the digital twins of concert ticket sellers to find the best deals for a specific event. These digital twins can also interact with other digital twins that have performed similar tasks in the past and learn from them. Fetch.ai digital twins can also be used for decentralized financial services. For example, a user&rsquo;s digital twin can notice price differences of a specific token on different cryptocurrency exchanges and take advantage of them autonomously. Bill Gates recently predicted that services like the ones provided by Fetch.ai would be the first to cause major disruptions as it has the potential to change how people shop online.</p>
3. Singlularity.NET (AGIX)
<p>Singularity.Net is a decentralized AI marketplace that uses blockchain technology to provide unrestricted access to applications and algorithms. One of the platform&rsquo;s main goals is to create Artificial General Intelligence from all the interactions between different AI algorithms.</p>
<p>Singularity.NET hosts its platform on the Cardano (ADA) and Ethereum (ETH) blockchains and anyone can use the learning models created on it. Its native currency the AGIX is used to pay transaction fees and purchase products. Over 70 AI services are already available on the platform and the user-friendly interface makes it easy for non-developers to navigate the space.</p>
4. The Graph (GRT)
<p>The Graph provides a system for querying and indexing data from blockchains, much like a search engine&rsquo;s index and query data from websites. The Graph&rsquo;s platform does this by organizing data into subgraphs. It&rsquo;s built on the Ethereum blockchain and it allows anyone to build and publish APIs that applications can query with GraphQL to secure blockchain data.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
5. Ocean Protocol (OCEAN)
<p>Ocean Protocol provides an Ethereum-based platform that allows individuals and businesses to monetize and exchange data and data-based services. For example, it can give researchers access to the data without the data holder having to relinquish it.</p>
<p>While many cryptocurrencies had a rough time in 2022, Ocean prices kept growing before finally coming down in early 2023.</p>
6. Cortex (CTXC)
<p>Cortex provides a peer-to-peer, open-source, decentralized blockchain-based platform that supports uploading and executing AI models on the distributed network. It aims for AI democratization where models can be integrated into smart contracts to create AI-powered decentralized applications.</p>
<p>Cortex hasn&rsquo;t enjoyed the price growth many other AI-driven cryptocurrencies have recently seen, but it has the potential to create a new class of decentralized applications and smart contracts in the future.</p>
7. iExec RLC (RLC)
<p>IExec offers a blockchain network that users can use to monetize their computing power or access on-demand computing resources. RLC is the network's native currency and it&rsquo;s used to pay transaction fees on the blockchain.</p>
<p>The iExec platform is currently the leading blockchain-based decentralized computing platform and it also allows users to monetize data sets and applications. iExec supports applications used in various fields like fintech, rendering, AI, and healthcare. iExec aims to reinvent the cloud computing space by creating a new blockchain-based cloud paradigm.</p>
<p>iExec&rsquo;s platform relies on XtremWeb-HEP, which is an open-source grid software that allows for features like security, data management, private infrastructure, and the development of virtual images.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
8. Numeraire (NMR)
<p>Numeraire runs an AI-powered blockchain network that acts like a hedge fund on behalf of users, using machine learning and artificial intelligence to invest in global stock markets. Its native currency the Numeraire is used to pay transaction fees on the network.</p>
<p>The Numeraire blockchain is Ethereum-based, allowing data scientists and developers to experiment and develop machine learning models. The platform aims to decentralize the data science field while allowing developers to make more effective machine-learning models.</p>
<p>Numeraire claims the title of being the first hedge fund to launch its cryptocurrency, but unlike conventional hedge funds, it uses predictions made by users to select stocks. It heavily relies on machine learning for its investment strategies.</p>
9. dKargo (DKA)
<p>dKargo is a blockchain network that uses artificial intelligence to address issues in the logistics industry by providing credible data to participants. The network also helps to establish efficient logistics networks based on improved communication provided by blockchain technology.</p>
<p>The dKargo platform helps to address trust issues created by split logistic nodes by using blockchain technology to enhance communication and create collaboration-based logistic networks that would be impossible without blockchain technology. The platform also provides Web3 logistic services. It gives users optimized routes and logistics that couldn&rsquo;t have been possible with the structure of silo logistics.</p>
10. Phala Network (PHA)
<p>Phala Network also provides AI-augmented blockchain-based cloud computing services, but its main focus is privacy. The platform is positioned as a decentralized alternative to traditional cloud computing providers like Google Cloud or Amazon AWS.</p>
<p>PHA is its native currency and used for various things like purchasing computing resources, paying data exchange fees, and security guarantees. Phala Network provides users with contract-based data exchange infrastructure for standardized trading protocols, analysis, and collection. PHA also serves as the platform&rsquo;s governance tokens giving users a say in the platform&rsquo;s development and operations.</p>
Summary
<p>2023 has been the year of AI-linked cryptos as they emerge as the top altcoins to buy. Investors remain bullish on these tokens that are driven by artificial intelligence while generally feeling bearish about most cryptocurrencies. AI-linked cryptos are taking over the crypto space and their futures look bright with a total of $1.5 trillion expected to be funneled into the AI sector.</p>
<p class="s12">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p class="s12">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Data shows as PEPE  Accumulation Slows Down Investors are buying DigiToads in bulk.]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/ethereum-network-data-shows-as-pepe-accumulation-slows-down-investors-are-buying-digitoads-in-bulk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-153527.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-153527.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-153527.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/ethereum-network-data-shows-as-pepe-accumulation-slows-down-investors-are-buying-digitoads-in-bulk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">Pepe Coin Enthusiasts are taking advantage of the current market correlation to accumulate vast amounts of cryptocurrency. PEPE, the popular meme coin that uses a frog as its mascot gained widespread popularity in 2023 after a successful initial coin offering that sold out. However, PEPE iaccumilation has slowed down and that make space for other coins on the rise, investors have been quick to accumulate large amounts of DigiToads, one of PEPE's rivals that uses the toad as its mascot.</p>
DigiToads Presale Is Almost Sold Out
<p class="s7">DigiToads presale, which started a few weeks back, has been one of the hottest presales in 2023. Now in its Lilypad 8 stage, the presale has raised more than 4.85 million after selling more than 90% of the tokens allocated for the presale. As the launch of the $TOADS tokens approaches, investors have continued to show support for the project by purchasing TOADS tokens in chunks.</p>
<p class="s7">The fast presale growth of the DigiToads presale has led investors to predict a bright future for the token that includes massive growth of more than 1000%. Some market analysts even suggest that TOADs will quickly climb the ranks of cryptocurrencies and soon rank among the top fifty and then the top ten cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>
<p class="s13">&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
Why are investors so bullish about DigiToads?
<p class="s7">Well, DigiToads is a meme coin that stands out from the rest of the meme coins in the market, while most meme coins such as PEPE focus fully on the fun aspect and growing a community, DigiToads offers much more utility. This means that, unlike other meme coins that have to rely on community sentiment for value, the value of DigiToads is derived from the utility it offers investors.</p>
<p class="s7">Some of the features that differentiate DigiToads from other meme coin projects include a robust play-to-earn platform, deflationary nature, NFTS staking, a metaverse, and environmental consciousness.</p>
<p class="s7">The play-to-earn web3 gaming platform on DigiToads provides TOADs token holders with an immersive gaming experience that also rewards them with TOADs tokens for their efforts. In the game, players can collect, nurture and breed digital pet NFTS. Once a month, players battle their DigiToads against those of other players in a fierce competition where the top 25% of winners get rewards in the form of TOADs tokens. Players can use their rewards to enhance their rewards through staking, purchase more in-game items or buy more NFTs.</p>
<p class="s7">DigiToads is also getting recognition in the NFT space with the introduction of its NFT staking platform. Users have the opportunity to stake their TOADS NFTS and earn additional rewards. The longer they take their NFTS, the greater the rewards they earn. The staking pool receives funds from 2% of all TOADS transactions, ensuring a steady supply of rewards for participants in the staking process.</p>
<p class="s7">Another aspect of the DigiToads platform that has continued to attract investors is the monthly trading competitions. &nbsp;Once a month, DigiToads will hold a competition where traders will be required to show their trading skills and expertise. The winners will receive prestigious DigiToads, which give them access to funds in the treasury.</p>
<p class="s7">There will be 12 DigiToads available each year, and they will serve to ensure that only the top traders have control and access to the treasury, while also motivating other traders to sharpen their trading skills.</p>
<p class="s7">DigiToads will also play a role in conserving the environment by Donating 2.5% of its profits each month to a charity that is focused on conserving the Amazon rainforest and other natural habitats of wildlife like TOADs. This is a massive step in the right direction for DigiToads as it differentiates the project from other cryptocurrencies that have a rap for leaving a large carbon footprint.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
Final Word
<p class="s7">From an exciting metaverse to a rewarding play-to-earn game, staking and deflationary properties, DigiToads has all it needs to take off fast the most profitable crypto project of 2023, as an investor, this is your chance to hop on the DigiToads bandwagon and prepare yourself for insane growth.</p>
<p class="s7">If you haven&rsquo;t done so yet, head over to the DigiToads website and grab yourself some $TOADs tokens before it&rsquo;s too late.</p>
<p class="s7">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join thecommunity for regular updates.</p>
<p class="s7">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">Pepe Coin Enthusiasts are taking advantage of the current market correlation to accumulate vast amounts of cryptocurrency. PEPE, the popular meme coin that uses a frog as its mascot gained widespread popularity in 2023 after a successful initial coin offering that sold out. However, PEPE iaccumilation has slowed down and that make space for other coins on the rise, investors have been quick to accumulate large amounts of DigiToads, one of PEPE's rivals that uses the toad as its mascot.</p>
DigiToads Presale Is Almost Sold Out
<p class="s7">DigiToads presale, which started a few weeks back, has been one of the hottest presales in 2023. Now in its Lilypad 8 stage, the presale has raised more than 4.85 million after selling more than 90% of the tokens allocated for the presale. As the launch of the $TOADS tokens approaches, investors have continued to show support for the project by purchasing TOADS tokens in chunks.</p>
<p class="s7">The fast presale growth of the DigiToads presale has led investors to predict a bright future for the token that includes massive growth of more than 1000%. Some market analysts even suggest that TOADs will quickly climb the ranks of cryptocurrencies and soon rank among the top fifty and then the top ten cryptocurrencies by market cap.</p>
<p class="s13">&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
Why are investors so bullish about DigiToads?
<p class="s7">Well, DigiToads is a meme coin that stands out from the rest of the meme coins in the market, while most meme coins such as PEPE focus fully on the fun aspect and growing a community, DigiToads offers much more utility. This means that, unlike other meme coins that have to rely on community sentiment for value, the value of DigiToads is derived from the utility it offers investors.</p>
<p class="s7">Some of the features that differentiate DigiToads from other meme coin projects include a robust play-to-earn platform, deflationary nature, NFTS staking, a metaverse, and environmental consciousness.</p>
<p class="s7">The play-to-earn web3 gaming platform on DigiToads provides TOADs token holders with an immersive gaming experience that also rewards them with TOADs tokens for their efforts. In the game, players can collect, nurture and breed digital pet NFTS. Once a month, players battle their DigiToads against those of other players in a fierce competition where the top 25% of winners get rewards in the form of TOADs tokens. Players can use their rewards to enhance their rewards through staking, purchase more in-game items or buy more NFTs.</p>
<p class="s7">DigiToads is also getting recognition in the NFT space with the introduction of its NFT staking platform. Users have the opportunity to stake their TOADS NFTS and earn additional rewards. The longer they take their NFTS, the greater the rewards they earn. The staking pool receives funds from 2% of all TOADS transactions, ensuring a steady supply of rewards for participants in the staking process.</p>
<p class="s7">Another aspect of the DigiToads platform that has continued to attract investors is the monthly trading competitions. &nbsp;Once a month, DigiToads will hold a competition where traders will be required to show their trading skills and expertise. The winners will receive prestigious DigiToads, which give them access to funds in the treasury.</p>
<p class="s7">There will be 12 DigiToads available each year, and they will serve to ensure that only the top traders have control and access to the treasury, while also motivating other traders to sharpen their trading skills.</p>
<p class="s7">DigiToads will also play a role in conserving the environment by Donating 2.5% of its profits each month to a charity that is focused on conserving the Amazon rainforest and other natural habitats of wildlife like TOADs. This is a massive step in the right direction for DigiToads as it differentiates the project from other cryptocurrencies that have a rap for leaving a large carbon footprint.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
Final Word
<p class="s7">From an exciting metaverse to a rewarding play-to-earn game, staking and deflationary properties, DigiToads has all it needs to take off fast the most profitable crypto project of 2023, as an investor, this is your chance to hop on the DigiToads bandwagon and prepare yourself for insane growth.</p>
<p class="s7">If you haven&rsquo;t done so yet, head over to the DigiToads website and grab yourself some $TOADs tokens before it&rsquo;s too late.</p>
<p class="s7">For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join thecommunity for regular updates.</p>
<p class="s7">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Tradecurve technical indicators showing bullish signs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-and-tradecurve-technical-indicators-showing-bullish-signs</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152838.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152838.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152838.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-and-tradecurve-technical-indicators-showing-bullish-signs</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has gone through peaks and valleys, but recent developments indicate potential bullish trends for Bitcoin and Tradecurve. Bitcoin, the pioneer cryptocurrency, and Tradecurve, a promising hybrid trading platform currently in its presale phase, have garnered attention from traders and investors. </p>
<p>This article will explore the technical indicators that suggest a bullish outlook for these digital assets and what they could mean for the future.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) could see a surge in the making
<p>After a significant price fall, Bitcoin, sometimes seen as the leading indicator of the cryptocurrency market, has been in a period of consolidation. However, many technical indications suggest that there may be a positive reversal soon.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is on the verge of a bullish crossover, indicating a potential upward trend. Not only that, but the Bitcoin RSI is also in the buy zone, as it currently has a value of 65.802. With nearly all moving averages and technical indicators for Bitcoin showing buy signals, the future of this token looks bright. </p>
<p>Currently, Bitcoin has a value of $26,550.91 with a market cap of $515B, which is a rise of 4.06% in the last 24 hours. Moreover, Bitcoin has witnessed a notable increase in trading volume in recent weeks, indicating renewed market activity. Overnight, the trading volume of Bitcoin increased by 29.75% and now sits at $17,289,847,477. Experts have noticed these technical indicators as they forecast a rise to $27,000 once more for Bitcoin by the end of 2023. </p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) builds momentum for growth
<p>Tradecurve, a borderless, Ethereum-based trading platform aiming to disrupt the traditional financial landscape, is showing promising signs of growth. Let&rsquo;s go over some key indicators supporting its bullish outlook.</p>
<p>The number of registered users on Tradecurve has been steadily increasing, reflecting growing interest and adoption of the platform. Recently, the Tradecurve team announced that they had surpassed 10,000 registered users, and for a project that is currently in Stage 4 of its presale, that number is astonishing. As more users join the ecosystem, it creates a network effect that can attract additional traders.</p>
<p>Tradecurve boasts a robust hybrid infrastructure model that facilitates efficient trading and ensures a seamless user experience. With a focus on security, speed, and user-friendly features, Tradecurve is well-positioned to attract and retain traders. </p>
<p>The best aspects of DEX and CEX will be implemented on Tradecurve, meaning users will find low latency, access to multiple asset classes, decentralized asset and key control, fast order execution, and more on one platform. </p>
<p>One of Tradecurve&rsquo;s main selling points is the removal of sign-up KYC checks. Users must frequently produce personal identifying papers, like passports or driver&rsquo;s licenses, to undergo KYC checks and prove their identity on centralized exchanges. This procedure brings up privacy issues and the possible misuse of personal data. Users may keep their privacy and secure their sensitive data by forgoing the necessity for KYC checks.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Other notable features that benefit all traders, novice or experienced, will be the ability to trade all derivatives on one account, algorithmic trading, high leverage (beginning at 500:1), negative balance protection, and a Proof of Reserves (PoR) implementation. </p>
<p>Tradecurve&rsquo;s utility token, TCRV, will be a critical component of this ecosystem and bring holders various perks such as discounts on subscriptions for the AI-powered trading bots, governance voting rights letting you choose how the platform will develop, passive income via staking and more. </p>
<p>Currently, the TCRV token has a value of only $0.018, up 20% in the last week. If we look at the market cap of Tradecurve, which now sits at $32M as the token supply is 1.8B, we can deduce that it will see a much faster surge than Bitcoin as a lower amount of new funds will be needed. </p>
<p>Only 40% of the 1.8B token supply will be available during its presale, and with experts predicting a 50x increase by the time it ends, purchasing it now may put you in the proper position before it spikes. </p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has gone through peaks and valleys, but recent developments indicate potential bullish trends for Bitcoin and Tradecurve. Bitcoin, the pioneer cryptocurrency, and Tradecurve, a promising hybrid trading platform currently in its presale phase, have garnered attention from traders and investors. </p>
<p>This article will explore the technical indicators that suggest a bullish outlook for these digital assets and what they could mean for the future.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
Bitcoin (BTC) could see a surge in the making
<p>After a significant price fall, Bitcoin, sometimes seen as the leading indicator of the cryptocurrency market, has been in a period of consolidation. However, many technical indications suggest that there may be a positive reversal soon.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is on the verge of a bullish crossover, indicating a potential upward trend. Not only that, but the Bitcoin RSI is also in the buy zone, as it currently has a value of 65.802. With nearly all moving averages and technical indicators for Bitcoin showing buy signals, the future of this token looks bright. </p>
<p>Currently, Bitcoin has a value of $26,550.91 with a market cap of $515B, which is a rise of 4.06% in the last 24 hours. Moreover, Bitcoin has witnessed a notable increase in trading volume in recent weeks, indicating renewed market activity. Overnight, the trading volume of Bitcoin increased by 29.75% and now sits at $17,289,847,477. Experts have noticed these technical indicators as they forecast a rise to $27,000 once more for Bitcoin by the end of 2023. </p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve (TCRV) builds momentum for growth
<p>Tradecurve, a borderless, Ethereum-based trading platform aiming to disrupt the traditional financial landscape, is showing promising signs of growth. Let&rsquo;s go over some key indicators supporting its bullish outlook.</p>
<p>The number of registered users on Tradecurve has been steadily increasing, reflecting growing interest and adoption of the platform. Recently, the Tradecurve team announced that they had surpassed 10,000 registered users, and for a project that is currently in Stage 4 of its presale, that number is astonishing. As more users join the ecosystem, it creates a network effect that can attract additional traders.</p>
<p>Tradecurve boasts a robust hybrid infrastructure model that facilitates efficient trading and ensures a seamless user experience. With a focus on security, speed, and user-friendly features, Tradecurve is well-positioned to attract and retain traders. </p>
<p>The best aspects of DEX and CEX will be implemented on Tradecurve, meaning users will find low latency, access to multiple asset classes, decentralized asset and key control, fast order execution, and more on one platform. </p>
<p>One of Tradecurve&rsquo;s main selling points is the removal of sign-up KYC checks. Users must frequently produce personal identifying papers, like passports or driver&rsquo;s licenses, to undergo KYC checks and prove their identity on centralized exchanges. This procedure brings up privacy issues and the possible misuse of personal data. Users may keep their privacy and secure their sensitive data by forgoing the necessity for KYC checks.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Other notable features that benefit all traders, novice or experienced, will be the ability to trade all derivatives on one account, algorithmic trading, high leverage (beginning at 500:1), negative balance protection, and a Proof of Reserves (PoR) implementation. </p>
<p>Tradecurve&rsquo;s utility token, TCRV, will be a critical component of this ecosystem and bring holders various perks such as discounts on subscriptions for the AI-powered trading bots, governance voting rights letting you choose how the platform will develop, passive income via staking and more. </p>
<p>Currently, the TCRV token has a value of only $0.018, up 20% in the last week. If we look at the market cap of Tradecurve, which now sits at $32M as the token supply is 1.8B, we can deduce that it will see a much faster surge than Bitcoin as a lower amount of new funds will be needed. </p>
<p>Only 40% of the 1.8B token supply will be available during its presale, and with experts predicting a 50x increase by the time it ends, purchasing it now may put you in the proper position before it spikes. </p>
For more information about the Tradecurve presale:
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ride the Wave: 6 Best Cryptos to Buy With 100x Potential]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/ride-the-wave-6-best-cryptos-to-buy-with-100x-potential</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152724.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152724.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-06-21-at-152724.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/ride-the-wave-6-best-cryptos-to-buy-with-100x-potential</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Get ready to ride the crypto wave as we delve into the explosive growth of Uwerx, the groundbreaking Web 3 platform poised to revolutionize the freelance industry. </p>
<p class="s5">In this article, we will explore the potential for a massive increase in the crypto market, with a focus on Dash (DASH), Cosmos (ATOM), Algorand (ALGO), Solana (SOL), Voyager Token (VGX), and Uwerx. </p>
<p class="s5">Brace yourself for an exhilarating exploration of these six cryptocurrencies and their projected 100x surge in value in 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Top 6 Cryptos to Buy: Experts Forecast a 100x Surge in Price In 2023</p>
<p class="s5">1. Dash (DASH): Empowering Everyday Transactions in Developing Economies</p>
<p class="s5">2. Cosmos Hub (ATOM): Pioneering Interoperability for the Future of Blockchains</p>
<p class="s5">3. Algorand (ALGO): Building the Future of Decentralized Applications and Financial Services</p>
<p class="s5">4. Solana (SOL): Empowering Decentralized Applications with Lightning-Fast Speed and Scalability</p>
<p class="s5">5. Voyager Token (VGX): Unlocking Rewards and Safe Trading on the Regulated Crypto Broker Platform</p>
<p class="s5">6. Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionizing the Freelance Landscape with Unprecedented Security</p>
Dash (DASH): Empowering Everyday Transactions in Developing Economies
<p class="s5">Dash (DASH) is an open-source cryptocurrency dedicated to revolutionizing daily transactions. With the vision of becoming a widely accepted digital currency akin to cash, credit cards, or PayPal, Dash (DASH) aims to facilitate seamless and convenient purchases. </p>
<p class="s5">By venturing into economically distressed regions like Venezuela, Dash (DASH) has proven its commitment to providing accessible financial solutions in challenging environments. </p>
<p class="s5">Currently priced at $30.16, with a 24-hour trading volume of $30,669,214, Dash (DASH) has shown steady growth, experiencing a 2.52% increase in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p class="s5">Encouragingly, reputable market analysts predict a surge in Dash (DASH)'s value, projecting it to reach $54.31 by 2024. This forecast is attributed to the ongoing expansion of Dash (DASH)'s operations in developing countries, further bolstering its global presence.</p>
Cosmos Hub (ATOM): Pioneering Interoperability for the Future of Blockchains
<p class="s5">Cosmos Hub (ATOM) is a groundbreaking blockchain project revolutionizing the concept of interoperability among different blockchains. </p>
<p class="s5">With its mission to establish an "Internet of Blockchains," Cosmos Hub (ATOM) enhances connectivity and communication between disparate blockchain networks. </p>
<p class="s5">As of now, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) is valued at $8.76, with a 24-hour trading volume of $63,578,552. With a remarkable ranking of #20 on CoinMarketCap, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) boasts a market cap of $3,036,246,050.</p>
<p class="s5">Market experts project that the price of Cosmos Hub (ATOM) could soar to $17.70 by Q4 2024. This optimistic forecast stems from the project's relentless dedication to advancing interoperability, offering increased scalability, and fostering seamless interaction between blockchain ecosystems.</p>
Algorand (ALGO): Building the Future of Decentralized Applications and Financial Services
<p class="s5">Algorand (ALGO) is a revolutionary cryptocurrency and blockchain platform that aims to revolutionize the development of decentralized applications (dApps) and financial services.</p>
<p class="s5">Currently priced at $0.115308, with a 24-hour trading volume of $27,075,481, Algorand(ALGO) has emerged as a prominent player in the crypto market, securing the #42 ranking on CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p class="s5">Market experts predict a potential price increase of $0.21 by Q4 2024. This projection is based on Algorand (ALGO)'s solid technological foundations, its ability to address scalability concerns, and the growing demand for decentralized applications and financial services.</p>
Solana (SOL): Empowering Decentralized Applications with Lightning-Fast Speed and Scalability
<p class="s5">Solana (SOL) stands as a cutting-edge blockchain platform that delivers unparalleled speed, security, and scalability for decentralized applications (DApps) and crypto assets. </p>
<p class="s5">By incorporating a unique combination of advanced technologies and strategic design choices, Solana (SOL) tackles the scalability challenges that often plague other blockchain networks.</p>
<p class="s5">As of today, Solana (SOL) boasts a price of $15.21, accompanied by a robust 24-hour trading volume of $284,354,569. Solana's (SOL) impressive performance has earned it the #11 rank on CoinMarketCap, with a thriving live market cap of $6,068,806,983. </p>
<p class="s5">Analyzing market trends and conducting in-depth research, crypto analysts have expressed strong confidence in Solana (SOL)'s potential, predicting a potential price surge to $28.40 by the end of 2024.</p>
Voyager Token (VGX): Unlocking Rewards and Safe Trading on the Regulated Crypto Broker Platform
<p class="s5">Voyager Token (VGX) stands as the native cryptocurrency token utilized on the Voyager Token (VGX) platform, a regulated crypto broker that facilitates seamless and secure trading of crypto assets.</p>
<p class="s5">With a current price of $0.101582 and a 24-hour trading volume of $3,107,810, Voyager Token (VGX) has secured the #476 rank on CoinMarketCap, boasting a market cap of $28,288,865. </p>
<p class="s5">By conducting meticulous market analysis, experts in the field are confident in the potential growth of Voyager Token (VGX), projecting a price surge to $0.22 by the end of 2024.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionizing the Freelance Landscape with Unprecedented Security
<p class="s5">Uwerx, the revolutionary force in the freelance landscape, is set to make an extraordinary impact with its groundbreaking launch. One key aspect that sets Uwerx apart is its unwavering commitment to security and integrity.</p>
<p class="s5">Investors can find solace in the fact that team tokens are securely locked for nine months, ensuring stability and trust. Additionally, Uwerx plans to lock Token Liquidity for an impressive 25 years, providing long-term protection for investors and reinforcing the platform's credibility.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx has undergone rigorous audits by leading firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network to further solidify its commitment to security. Following its recent listing on CoinSniper and upcoming plans for Uniswap, Uwerx is actively broadening its horizons, increasing accessibility and market visibility.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Presale Opportunities and Thriving Community
<p class="s5">Uwerx's presale is making waves as it enters Stage 5, offering tokens at an enticing price of $0.041 each with a 15% bonus on every purchase. The response has been extraordinary, with Uwerx seamlessly completing presale stages 1 to 4 at an astonishing pace. </p>
<p class="s5">As the presale draws to a close on July 31st, Uwerx has captivating plans in store, including an exclusive Test Airdrop, providing users with a tantalizing taste of the immense possibilities that lie ahead.</p>
<p class="s5">The community's feedback is highly valued and has influenced token allocations, showcasing Uwerx's commitment to its users. Share your thoughts and suggestions at feedback@uwerx.network and be part of shaping the future of freelance platforms.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionary Platform Features and Exciting Milestones
<p class="s5">Uwerx has unveiled the Alpha version of its platform, providing users with a glimpse into its innovative capabilities. This initial release showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering an unparalleled user experience. Continuous updates and improvements are planned to further enhance the platform, setting the stage for an exciting journey of growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Recently, Uwerx released a comprehensive update on the Alpha platform, presenting users with a detailed and user-friendly PDF spanning ten pages. From the seamless signing-up process to the talent discovery journey, Uwerx ensures a seamless and intuitive user experience. </p>
<p class="s5">The transition from Alpha to Beta is on the horizon, marking a significant milestone in the project's trajectory and generating anticipation for the platform's future evolution.</p>
<p class="s5">Token holders of Uwerx can look forward to a meticulously designed 6-week vesting period following the conclusion of the presale. This carefully structured distribution schedule promotes stability and long-term commitment, with increasing percentages over time. By participating in Uwerx's success from day one, token holders become an integral part of the extraordinary journey that lies ahead.</p>
Join the Uwerx Revolution now by taking advantage of the 15% bonus in the presale:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Get ready to ride the crypto wave as we delve into the explosive growth of Uwerx, the groundbreaking Web 3 platform poised to revolutionize the freelance industry. </p>
<p class="s5">In this article, we will explore the potential for a massive increase in the crypto market, with a focus on Dash (DASH), Cosmos (ATOM), Algorand (ALGO), Solana (SOL), Voyager Token (VGX), and Uwerx. </p>
<p class="s5">Brace yourself for an exhilarating exploration of these six cryptocurrencies and their projected 100x surge in value in 2023.</p>
<p class="s5">Top 6 Cryptos to Buy: Experts Forecast a 100x Surge in Price In 2023</p>
<p class="s5">1. Dash (DASH): Empowering Everyday Transactions in Developing Economies</p>
<p class="s5">2. Cosmos Hub (ATOM): Pioneering Interoperability for the Future of Blockchains</p>
<p class="s5">3. Algorand (ALGO): Building the Future of Decentralized Applications and Financial Services</p>
<p class="s5">4. Solana (SOL): Empowering Decentralized Applications with Lightning-Fast Speed and Scalability</p>
<p class="s5">5. Voyager Token (VGX): Unlocking Rewards and Safe Trading on the Regulated Crypto Broker Platform</p>
<p class="s5">6. Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionizing the Freelance Landscape with Unprecedented Security</p>
Dash (DASH): Empowering Everyday Transactions in Developing Economies
<p class="s5">Dash (DASH) is an open-source cryptocurrency dedicated to revolutionizing daily transactions. With the vision of becoming a widely accepted digital currency akin to cash, credit cards, or PayPal, Dash (DASH) aims to facilitate seamless and convenient purchases. </p>
<p class="s5">By venturing into economically distressed regions like Venezuela, Dash (DASH) has proven its commitment to providing accessible financial solutions in challenging environments. </p>
<p class="s5">Currently priced at $30.16, with a 24-hour trading volume of $30,669,214, Dash (DASH) has shown steady growth, experiencing a 2.52% increase in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p class="s5">Encouragingly, reputable market analysts predict a surge in Dash (DASH)'s value, projecting it to reach $54.31 by 2024. This forecast is attributed to the ongoing expansion of Dash (DASH)'s operations in developing countries, further bolstering its global presence.</p>
Cosmos Hub (ATOM): Pioneering Interoperability for the Future of Blockchains
<p class="s5">Cosmos Hub (ATOM) is a groundbreaking blockchain project revolutionizing the concept of interoperability among different blockchains. </p>
<p class="s5">With its mission to establish an "Internet of Blockchains," Cosmos Hub (ATOM) enhances connectivity and communication between disparate blockchain networks. </p>
<p class="s5">As of now, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) is valued at $8.76, with a 24-hour trading volume of $63,578,552. With a remarkable ranking of #20 on CoinMarketCap, Cosmos Hub (ATOM) boasts a market cap of $3,036,246,050.</p>
<p class="s5">Market experts project that the price of Cosmos Hub (ATOM) could soar to $17.70 by Q4 2024. This optimistic forecast stems from the project's relentless dedication to advancing interoperability, offering increased scalability, and fostering seamless interaction between blockchain ecosystems.</p>
Algorand (ALGO): Building the Future of Decentralized Applications and Financial Services
<p class="s5">Algorand (ALGO) is a revolutionary cryptocurrency and blockchain platform that aims to revolutionize the development of decentralized applications (dApps) and financial services.</p>
<p class="s5">Currently priced at $0.115308, with a 24-hour trading volume of $27,075,481, Algorand(ALGO) has emerged as a prominent player in the crypto market, securing the #42 ranking on CoinMarketCap. </p>
<p class="s5">Market experts predict a potential price increase of $0.21 by Q4 2024. This projection is based on Algorand (ALGO)'s solid technological foundations, its ability to address scalability concerns, and the growing demand for decentralized applications and financial services.</p>
Solana (SOL): Empowering Decentralized Applications with Lightning-Fast Speed and Scalability
<p class="s5">Solana (SOL) stands as a cutting-edge blockchain platform that delivers unparalleled speed, security, and scalability for decentralized applications (DApps) and crypto assets. </p>
<p class="s5">By incorporating a unique combination of advanced technologies and strategic design choices, Solana (SOL) tackles the scalability challenges that often plague other blockchain networks.</p>
<p class="s5">As of today, Solana (SOL) boasts a price of $15.21, accompanied by a robust 24-hour trading volume of $284,354,569. Solana's (SOL) impressive performance has earned it the #11 rank on CoinMarketCap, with a thriving live market cap of $6,068,806,983. </p>
<p class="s5">Analyzing market trends and conducting in-depth research, crypto analysts have expressed strong confidence in Solana (SOL)'s potential, predicting a potential price surge to $28.40 by the end of 2024.</p>
Voyager Token (VGX): Unlocking Rewards and Safe Trading on the Regulated Crypto Broker Platform
<p class="s5">Voyager Token (VGX) stands as the native cryptocurrency token utilized on the Voyager Token (VGX) platform, a regulated crypto broker that facilitates seamless and secure trading of crypto assets.</p>
<p class="s5">With a current price of $0.101582 and a 24-hour trading volume of $3,107,810, Voyager Token (VGX) has secured the #476 rank on CoinMarketCap, boasting a market cap of $28,288,865. </p>
<p class="s5">By conducting meticulous market analysis, experts in the field are confident in the potential growth of Voyager Token (VGX), projecting a price surge to $0.22 by the end of 2024.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionizing the Freelance Landscape with Unprecedented Security
<p class="s5">Uwerx, the revolutionary force in the freelance landscape, is set to make an extraordinary impact with its groundbreaking launch. One key aspect that sets Uwerx apart is its unwavering commitment to security and integrity.</p>
<p class="s5">Investors can find solace in the fact that team tokens are securely locked for nine months, ensuring stability and trust. Additionally, Uwerx plans to lock Token Liquidity for an impressive 25 years, providing long-term protection for investors and reinforcing the platform's credibility.</p>
<p class="s5">Uwerx has undergone rigorous audits by leading firms such as SolidProof and InterFi Network to further solidify its commitment to security. Following its recent listing on CoinSniper and upcoming plans for Uniswap, Uwerx is actively broadening its horizons, increasing accessibility and market visibility.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Presale Opportunities and Thriving Community
<p class="s5">Uwerx's presale is making waves as it enters Stage 5, offering tokens at an enticing price of $0.041 each with a 15% bonus on every purchase. The response has been extraordinary, with Uwerx seamlessly completing presale stages 1 to 4 at an astonishing pace. </p>
<p class="s5">As the presale draws to a close on July 31st, Uwerx has captivating plans in store, including an exclusive Test Airdrop, providing users with a tantalizing taste of the immense possibilities that lie ahead.</p>
<p class="s5">The community's feedback is highly valued and has influenced token allocations, showcasing Uwerx's commitment to its users. Share your thoughts and suggestions at feedback@uwerx.network and be part of shaping the future of freelance platforms.</p>
Uwerx (WERX): Revolutionary Platform Features and Exciting Milestones
<p class="s5">Uwerx has unveiled the Alpha version of its platform, providing users with a glimpse into its innovative capabilities. This initial release showcases Uwerx's commitment to delivering an unparalleled user experience. Continuous updates and improvements are planned to further enhance the platform, setting the stage for an exciting journey of growth.</p>
<p class="s5">Recently, Uwerx released a comprehensive update on the Alpha platform, presenting users with a detailed and user-friendly PDF spanning ten pages. From the seamless signing-up process to the talent discovery journey, Uwerx ensures a seamless and intuitive user experience. </p>
<p class="s5">The transition from Alpha to Beta is on the horizon, marking a significant milestone in the project's trajectory and generating anticipation for the platform's future evolution.</p>
<p class="s5">Token holders of Uwerx can look forward to a meticulously designed 6-week vesting period following the conclusion of the presale. This carefully structured distribution schedule promotes stability and long-term commitment, with increasing percentages over time. By participating in Uwerx's success from day one, token holders become an integral part of the extraordinary journey that lies ahead.</p>
Join the Uwerx Revolution now by taking advantage of the 15% bonus in the presale:
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network/</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[CSA Warns Against Fake Crypto Regulatory Stamps]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/csa-warns-against-fake-crypto-regulatory-stamps</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/canada-crypto-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/canada-crypto-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/canada-crypto-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/csa-warns-against-fake-crypto-regulatory-stamps</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Canadian regulator has warned investors that some crypto websites use fake regulatory stamps and dispute resolution organizations to appear legitimate.&nbsp;</p>
Canadian Regulator Issues Investor Alert
<p>In a recent development, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) have issued an investor alert warning individuals about certain cryptocurrency websites that employ deceptive tactics to boost their credibility, deceive potential investors, and get them to deposit funds on fraudulent platforms.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>The investor alert released by the CSA stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In an effort to appear legitimate, the purported trading service providers claim they are certified by a fictitious authority or that they are members of a dispute resolution organization. One of them says its fictitious certification makes it &ldquo;a reliable and trustable online trading platform.&rdquo; Some of the purported trading services&rsquo; websites include links to these fake regulatory or dispute resolution organizations, which have their own websites.&rdquo;</p>

Canada Faces Fake Regulator Scam&nbsp;
<p>The investor alert revealed that the fake regulatory certificates utilized by these platforms are designed to resemble those issued by genuine regulatory authorities. They also create fictitious dispute resolution organizations, which purportedly serve as independent entities for conflict resolution between investors and the platforms, further complicating the identification of scams. These organizations, however, do not exist in reality, leaving investors without legitimate avenues for complaint and redress.</p>
CSA Warns Against Crypto &ldquo;Red Flags&rdquo;
<p>Therefore, although an initial glance at the fraudulent platforms might not pick up anything problematic, a deeper analysis unveils the more common &ldquo;red flags&rdquo; like awkward language, spelling and grammatical errors, unpolished syntax, promises of high returns with minimal risk, and so on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The CSA warned investors to verify the authenticity of regulatory certificates by cross-referencing them with official regulatory databases and conducting independent research. The organization also advised investors to consult with registered financial advisors or even follow the list of crypto platforms registered by the CSA before depositing their hard-earned money on any platform.</p>
Too Tough On Crypto?&nbsp;
<p>The organization has also listed some fictitious regulatory bodies and organizations being named by these fraudulent platforms to fake legitimacy. The country&rsquo;s strict regulatory environment has been challenging for many crypto firms, like Kraken, that had to jump through hoops to finally get the green signal from the country&rsquo;s regulatory watchdog. Other companies like Binance, ByBit, and dYdX have felt compelled to leave the company after being exposed to the highly unfavorable regulatory environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Canadian regulator has warned investors that some crypto websites use fake regulatory stamps and dispute resolution organizations to appear legitimate.&nbsp;</p>
Canadian Regulator Issues Investor Alert
<p>In a recent development, the Canadian Securities Administrators (CSA) have issued an investor alert warning individuals about certain cryptocurrency websites that employ deceptive tactics to boost their credibility, deceive potential investors, and get them to deposit funds on fraudulent platforms.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>The investor alert released by the CSA stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;In an effort to appear legitimate, the purported trading service providers claim they are certified by a fictitious authority or that they are members of a dispute resolution organization. One of them says its fictitious certification makes it &ldquo;a reliable and trustable online trading platform.&rdquo; Some of the purported trading services&rsquo; websites include links to these fake regulatory or dispute resolution organizations, which have their own websites.&rdquo;</p>

Canada Faces Fake Regulator Scam&nbsp;
<p>The investor alert revealed that the fake regulatory certificates utilized by these platforms are designed to resemble those issued by genuine regulatory authorities. They also create fictitious dispute resolution organizations, which purportedly serve as independent entities for conflict resolution between investors and the platforms, further complicating the identification of scams. These organizations, however, do not exist in reality, leaving investors without legitimate avenues for complaint and redress.</p>
CSA Warns Against Crypto &ldquo;Red Flags&rdquo;
<p>Therefore, although an initial glance at the fraudulent platforms might not pick up anything problematic, a deeper analysis unveils the more common &ldquo;red flags&rdquo; like awkward language, spelling and grammatical errors, unpolished syntax, promises of high returns with minimal risk, and so on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The CSA warned investors to verify the authenticity of regulatory certificates by cross-referencing them with official regulatory databases and conducting independent research. The organization also advised investors to consult with registered financial advisors or even follow the list of crypto platforms registered by the CSA before depositing their hard-earned money on any platform.</p>
Too Tough On Crypto?&nbsp;
<p>The organization has also listed some fictitious regulatory bodies and organizations being named by these fraudulent platforms to fake legitimacy. The country&rsquo;s strict regulatory environment has been challenging for many crypto firms, like Kraken, that had to jump through hoops to finally get the green signal from the country&rsquo;s regulatory watchdog. Other companies like Binance, ByBit, and dYdX have felt compelled to leave the company after being exposed to the highly unfavorable regulatory environment.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Bulls Eye 29458 Target - 22 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bulls-eye-29458-target-22-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-21-june-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-price-analysis-bulls-eye-29458-target-22-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bulls Eye 29458 Hurdle:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 22 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) advanced its recent appreciation early in the Asian session as the pair traded back above the 29000 figure for the first time since early May, reaching the 29226.26 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected above a series of upside price objectives related to buying pressure that first intensified around the 24750 area, including the 27419, 28119, 28243, 29068, and 29159 areas.&nbsp; Stops were also elected above price objectives associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 25143.24 area, including the 27718, 27810, 28325, 28634, and 29077 areas.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 29458, 30088, 30200, 30292, 30477, 31488, 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.Following recent upside price activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28169, 27516, 26988, 26459, 25806, and 25707 areas.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 31050 area include the 29563.20 and 29701.80 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26693.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27466.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Bulls Eye 29458 Hurdle:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 22 June 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) advanced its recent appreciation early in the Asian session as the pair traded back above the 29000 figure for the first time since early May, reaching the 29226.26 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected above a series of upside price objectives related to buying pressure that first intensified around the 24750 area, including the 27419, 28119, 28243, 29068, and 29159 areas.&nbsp; Stops were also elected above price objectives associated with buying pressure that emerged around the 25143.24 area, including the 27718, 27810, 28325, 28634, and 29077 areas.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 29458, 30088, 30200, 30292, 30477, 31488, 31737, 32125, and 33569 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 31674, 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.Following recent upside price activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 28169, 27516, 26988, 26459, 25806, and 25707 areas.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels linked to selling pressure that intensified around the 31050 area include the 29563.20 and 29701.80 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 26693.17 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27466.97.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Oracle Daemon Develops New Tools for Flare Network Data Providers]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/oracle-daemon-develops-new-tools-for-flare-network-data-providers</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image666.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image666.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cryptodaily-main-image666.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/oracle-daemon-develops-new-tools-for-flare-network-data-providers</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1">Flare Network announces strategic partnership with Oracle Daemon.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1">Oracle Daemon developers will build and develop several user tools.&nbsp;</li>
<li aria-level="1">The collaboration aims to enhance the user experience and data quality on the network.</li>
</ul>
<p>Flare Network, a highly scalable Layer 1 blockchain providing high-integrity data to developers, has announced a strategic collaboration with Oracle Daemon, a group of talented developers working on blockchain and Web 3 solutions. The Oracle Daemon developers have previously been original data providers for the Flare Time Series Oracle on both the Flare and Songbird networks.</p>
<p>Announced Monday, the collaboration aims at developing a new suite of user tools that enhance the user experience, provide better quality data, and introduce new features on Flare&rsquo;s network. Speaking on the latest collaboration with Oracle Daemon, David Pangerl, CEO &amp; Founder of Oracle Daemon, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have been building on Flare from the start, and with this collaboration, we will develop a number of important new tools to benefit the growing network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The developer group will build out three main user tools, namely the multi-wallet management tool, advanced data provider analytics tools and the auto-claiming executors. The multi-wallet management tool aims to streamline users' accounts and provide a detailed overview of all their balances in multiple wallets. The tool will allow users to manage funds in multiple wallets and accounts, offering simplified access to monitor and control their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The advanced data provider analytics tool is the crop of the three features set to be added to the Flare network. Oracle Daemon will develop a detailed analytics tool specifically tailored to data providers. By leveraging the tool, data providers can gain valuable insights into their performance metrics, including data quality, reliability, and usage. As a data oracle, Flare aims to provide the highest quality of trustless data, and this tool will help data providers achieve this.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m most excited about the advanced data provider analytics,&rdquo; Pangerl said on developing the advanced data providers analytics tool. &ldquo;Flare is the only blockchain focused on giving developers access to quality data at scale. So, whatever we can do to support and optimise the data provision process will benefit the whole network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Finally, the collaboration will see the addition of auto-claiming executors, which will automate all existing token-claiming processes. These executors help users collect rewards and later on disburse the rewards to the user. With multiple rewards up for grabs, manual token claiming can be some work for the user. The auto-claiming executor will encompass several rewards, including data provider rewards, validator rewards, FlareDrops, FTSO delegation rewards, and escrowed fund unlocks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1">Flare Network announces strategic partnership with Oracle Daemon.&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li aria-level="1">Oracle Daemon developers will build and develop several user tools.&nbsp;</li>
<li aria-level="1">The collaboration aims to enhance the user experience and data quality on the network.</li>
</ul>
<p>Flare Network, a highly scalable Layer 1 blockchain providing high-integrity data to developers, has announced a strategic collaboration with Oracle Daemon, a group of talented developers working on blockchain and Web 3 solutions. The Oracle Daemon developers have previously been original data providers for the Flare Time Series Oracle on both the Flare and Songbird networks.</p>
<p>Announced Monday, the collaboration aims at developing a new suite of user tools that enhance the user experience, provide better quality data, and introduce new features on Flare&rsquo;s network. Speaking on the latest collaboration with Oracle Daemon, David Pangerl, CEO &amp; Founder of Oracle Daemon, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have been building on Flare from the start, and with this collaboration, we will develop a number of important new tools to benefit the growing network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The developer group will build out three main user tools, namely the multi-wallet management tool, advanced data provider analytics tools and the auto-claiming executors. The multi-wallet management tool aims to streamline users' accounts and provide a detailed overview of all their balances in multiple wallets. The tool will allow users to manage funds in multiple wallets and accounts, offering simplified access to monitor and control their wallets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The advanced data provider analytics tool is the crop of the three features set to be added to the Flare network. Oracle Daemon will develop a detailed analytics tool specifically tailored to data providers. By leveraging the tool, data providers can gain valuable insights into their performance metrics, including data quality, reliability, and usage. As a data oracle, Flare aims to provide the highest quality of trustless data, and this tool will help data providers achieve this.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m most excited about the advanced data provider analytics,&rdquo; Pangerl said on developing the advanced data providers analytics tool. &ldquo;Flare is the only blockchain focused on giving developers access to quality data at scale. So, whatever we can do to support and optimise the data provision process will benefit the whole network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Finally, the collaboration will see the addition of auto-claiming executors, which will automate all existing token-claiming processes. These executors help users collect rewards and later on disburse the rewards to the user. With multiple rewards up for grabs, manual token claiming can be some work for the user. The auto-claiming executor will encompass several rewards, including data provider rewards, validator rewards, FlareDrops, FTSO delegation rewards, and escrowed fund unlocks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[WisdomTree and Invesco File Bitcoin ETF Applications]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wisdomtree-and-invesco-file-bitcoin-etf-applications</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/wisdomtree-and-invesco-file-bitcoin-etf-applications</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Global investment firm BlackRock's recent filing for a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) has reignited optimism in the industry and spurred a flurry of similar filings.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Less than a week after BlackRock's application, renowned investment firms WisdomTree and Invesco have followed suit, filing applications for their respective spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
WisdomTree's Persistence in Spot Bitcoin ETF Filing
<p class="md-end-block md-p">New York-based WisdomTree lodged its latest filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 21. If approved, the "WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust" would be listed on the Cboe BZX Exchange under the ticker "BTCW." Notably, this is WisdomTree's third attempt to secure approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF. Previous applications submitted in December 2021 and October 2022 were rejected due to the SEC's concerns about fraud and market manipulation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In their recent filing, WisdomTree, which oversees approximately $83 billion in assets, has expressed willingness to enter into a "surveillance sharing agreement" with a U.S.-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin. This step echoes BlackRock's approach in its recent filing, aiming to mitigate the SEC's concerns by establishing robust surveillance mechanisms to detect and prevent price distortions and manipulation.</p>
Invesco Reactivates Its Application for a Spot Bitcoin ETF
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Shortly after WisdomTree's application, Invesco, a global investment manager, reactivated its application for a similar spot Bitcoin ETF product. The proposed "Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF" aims to be listed on the Cboe BZX exchange, per the 19b-4 document informing the SEC of the proposed rule change.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Invesco's filing emphasizes the benefit of professional custodians and other service providers. This setup, they argue, reduces reliance on "loosely regulated offshore vehicles" and ensures better protection for investors' principal investments in Bitcoin.</p>
Impact of BlackRock's Strong ETF Approval Track Record
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bloomberg's senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas responded to the flurry of filings, attributing the renewed activity to BlackRock's entry into the race. Balchunas highlighted BlackRock's impressive track record, with a 575-1 success rate of ETF approvals by the SEC, adding weight to the firm's application.</p>
Speculations About Fidelity Investments' Entry
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Amid this resurgence of interest in Bitcoin ETFs, there are rumors that Fidelity Investments, a multi-trillion-dollar fund manager, might also join the fray. Speculation is rife that Fidelity, which manages roughly $4.9 trillion in assets, could file for its own spot Bitcoin ETF or possibly make an offer on Grayscale's GBTC ETF product.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the SEC has yet to approve a spot Bitcoin ETF, the recent wave of applications, driven by industry giant BlackRock's filing, has renewed hope and sparked a fresh round of interest in this segment of the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Global investment firm BlackRock's recent filing for a spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) has reignited optimism in the industry and spurred a flurry of similar filings.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Less than a week after BlackRock's application, renowned investment firms WisdomTree and Invesco have followed suit, filing applications for their respective spot Bitcoin ETFs.</p>
WisdomTree's Persistence in Spot Bitcoin ETF Filing
<p class="md-end-block md-p">New York-based WisdomTree lodged its latest filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 21. If approved, the "WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust" would be listed on the Cboe BZX Exchange under the ticker "BTCW." Notably, this is WisdomTree's third attempt to secure approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF. Previous applications submitted in December 2021 and October 2022 were rejected due to the SEC's concerns about fraud and market manipulation.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In their recent filing, WisdomTree, which oversees approximately $83 billion in assets, has expressed willingness to enter into a "surveillance sharing agreement" with a U.S.-based spot trading platform for Bitcoin. This step echoes BlackRock's approach in its recent filing, aiming to mitigate the SEC's concerns by establishing robust surveillance mechanisms to detect and prevent price distortions and manipulation.</p>
Invesco Reactivates Its Application for a Spot Bitcoin ETF
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Shortly after WisdomTree's application, Invesco, a global investment manager, reactivated its application for a similar spot Bitcoin ETF product. The proposed "Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF" aims to be listed on the Cboe BZX exchange, per the 19b-4 document informing the SEC of the proposed rule change.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Invesco's filing emphasizes the benefit of professional custodians and other service providers. This setup, they argue, reduces reliance on "loosely regulated offshore vehicles" and ensures better protection for investors' principal investments in Bitcoin.</p>
Impact of BlackRock's Strong ETF Approval Track Record
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bloomberg's senior ETF analyst Eric Balchunas responded to the flurry of filings, attributing the renewed activity to BlackRock's entry into the race. Balchunas highlighted BlackRock's impressive track record, with a 575-1 success rate of ETF approvals by the SEC, adding weight to the firm's application.</p>
Speculations About Fidelity Investments' Entry
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Amid this resurgence of interest in Bitcoin ETFs, there are rumors that Fidelity Investments, a multi-trillion-dollar fund manager, might also join the fray. Speculation is rife that Fidelity, which manages roughly $4.9 trillion in assets, could file for its own spot Bitcoin ETF or possibly make an offer on Grayscale's GBTC ETF product.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the SEC has yet to approve a spot Bitcoin ETF, the recent wave of applications, driven by industry giant BlackRock's filing, has renewed hope and sparked a fresh round of interest in this segment of the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano $ADA Updates System To Node 8.1.1]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cardano-ada-updates-system-to-node-8-1-1</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cardano-node-update-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cardano-node-update-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cardano-node-update-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/cardano-ada-updates-system-to-node-8-1-1</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cardano, a leading proof-of-stake blockchain platform, has launched an important update to its network, Node 8.1.1.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This update builds upon the foundational aspects of its predecessor, Node 8.0.0, and introduces several technical enhancements to the Cardano ecosystem, in particular for the ouroboros-network used for P2P topologies that don't yet contain DNS names.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">One of the major improvements brought by Node 8.1.1 is the enhancement of node performance at epoch boundaries. In Cardano's blockchain system, an epoch refers to a reward cycle lasting approximately 432,000 slots, or around five days. During these epochs, ADA tokens are staked, and new blocks are produced on the network. By optimizing the performance at these boundaries, the new update ensures a smoother transition between epochs and a more efficient rewards cycle.</p>
Technical Improvements and Innovations
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Node 8.1.1 update also addresses issues related to peer-to-peer network communications and the Cardano-based domain name system (DNS). These improvements help boost the network's overall performance and security, reducing potential bottlenecks and enhancing the pllatform's scalability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The new node no longer incorporates wallet or explorer functionalities. These are now managed by separate backend components that communicate with the node via local Inter-process communication (IPC), streamlining operations and making the system more efficient to avoid issues that have, in the past, damaged the Cardano blockchain.</p>
Regulatory Challenges and Cardano's Unwavering Commitment 
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Cardano remains dedicated to its growth and development goals. The successful launch of Node 8.1.1, amidst this regulatory pressure, speaks volumes about Cardano's commitment to continually enhance its network performance and stay at the forefront of blockchain technology.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cardano's decision to release updates and improvements, irrespective of external pressures, underlines its resilience and its firm focus on offering a robust, efficient, and secure blockchain platform to its users.</p>
Ecosystem Growth and Market Performance Analysis
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Node 8.1.1 brings tangible improvements to Cardano's network, which could potentially have a positive impact on Cardano's DeFi ecosystem. While ADA's market price did not immediately reflect these advancements, certain market indicators suggest a potential bullish trend in the future.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite a more than 8% decrease in ADA's price over the past week, indicators such as the Relative Strength Index (RSI), MVRV Ratio, and high whale activity hint at a possible bullish trend reversal. Notably, ADA's Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) displays a possibility of a bullish crossover, suggesting that a northward price movement might be on the horizon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the immediate lack of positive impact on ADA's price, the technical advancements brought by Node 8.1.1 and the steady ecosystem growth indicate Cardano's potential for strong performance in the future. This combination of continuous network improvements and strong market indicators underscores Cardano's resilience and growth potential in the ever-evolving world of blockchain and cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cardano, a leading proof-of-stake blockchain platform, has launched an important update to its network, Node 8.1.1.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This update builds upon the foundational aspects of its predecessor, Node 8.0.0, and introduces several technical enhancements to the Cardano ecosystem, in particular for the ouroboros-network used for P2P topologies that don't yet contain DNS names.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">One of the major improvements brought by Node 8.1.1 is the enhancement of node performance at epoch boundaries. In Cardano's blockchain system, an epoch refers to a reward cycle lasting approximately 432,000 slots, or around five days. During these epochs, ADA tokens are staked, and new blocks are produced on the network. By optimizing the performance at these boundaries, the new update ensures a smoother transition between epochs and a more efficient rewards cycle.</p>
Technical Improvements and Innovations
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Node 8.1.1 update also addresses issues related to peer-to-peer network communications and the Cardano-based domain name system (DNS). These improvements help boost the network's overall performance and security, reducing potential bottlenecks and enhancing the pllatform's scalability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The new node no longer incorporates wallet or explorer functionalities. These are now managed by separate backend components that communicate with the node via local Inter-process communication (IPC), streamlining operations and making the system more efficient to avoid issues that have, in the past, damaged the Cardano blockchain.</p>
Regulatory Challenges and Cardano's Unwavering Commitment 
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite ongoing regulatory scrutiny, especially from the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Cardano remains dedicated to its growth and development goals. The successful launch of Node 8.1.1, amidst this regulatory pressure, speaks volumes about Cardano's commitment to continually enhance its network performance and stay at the forefront of blockchain technology.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cardano's decision to release updates and improvements, irrespective of external pressures, underlines its resilience and its firm focus on offering a robust, efficient, and secure blockchain platform to its users.</p>
Ecosystem Growth and Market Performance Analysis
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Node 8.1.1 brings tangible improvements to Cardano's network, which could potentially have a positive impact on Cardano's DeFi ecosystem. While ADA's market price did not immediately reflect these advancements, certain market indicators suggest a potential bullish trend in the future.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite a more than 8% decrease in ADA's price over the past week, indicators such as the Relative Strength Index (RSI), MVRV Ratio, and high whale activity hint at a possible bullish trend reversal. Notably, ADA's Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD) displays a possibility of a bullish crossover, suggesting that a northward price movement might be on the horizon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the immediate lack of positive impact on ADA's price, the technical advancements brought by Node 8.1.1 and the steady ecosystem growth indicate Cardano's potential for strong performance in the future. This combination of continuous network improvements and strong market indicators underscores Cardano's resilience and growth potential in the ever-evolving world of blockchain and cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin breakout catches investors by surprise]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-breakout-catches-investors-by-surprise</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-48.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-48.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-48.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 12:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/bitcoin-breakout-catches-investors-by-surprise</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>After two months of slow sideways and downward price movement, bitcoin has suddenly broken the trend, giving control back to the bulls.</p>
Many investors had fled
<p>Following on from the mass of negativity caused by the Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s attack on the crypto industry culminating in suing the two biggest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, most investors had fled the scene, possibly thinking that crypto might die.</p>
<p>As mentioned in a Crypto Daily article published only two days previously, it is times like these that the intelligent and experienced traders are waiting for. In addition, the technicals were looking quite positive.</p>
Technicals looking good
<p>Bitcoin had been traversing in a downward sloping channel since mid-April (a bullish pattern in itself), which could even be taken as a bull flag that had gone on for rather a long time.</p>
<p>Had bitcoin fallen out of the bottom of the channel instead, then this would have been seen as extremely bearish. However, bitcoin did the most logical thing and broke out strongly to the upside.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is currently playing with $29,000, which it did hit earlier today. There is the possibility that the price could storm on to the major resistance at $30,300, but it could be expected to get rejected here, at least for the time being.</p>
Can the move be sustained?
<p>It might be wondered if bitcoin will be able to sustain a sizable rally on the scale of the 4 and a half month one it made from the beginning of the year. There is still much fear and negativity permeating the crypto space, and given the SEC actions, liquidity is very thin.</p>
<p>However, bitcoin has its halving cycle that will be drawing the king of the crypto assets higher. This is due to take place in April 2024, so still a lot of ups and downs before the bull run can start in earnest.</p>
Nothing comes close
<p>All does appear to be on track though. Bitcoin is still the scarcest and hardest form of money on the planet, and it is only a matter of time before traditional institutions take off the blinkers and do something about protecting their portfolios with bitcoin - Gensler and his SEC permitting of course.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After two months of slow sideways and downward price movement, bitcoin has suddenly broken the trend, giving control back to the bulls.</p>
Many investors had fled
<p>Following on from the mass of negativity caused by the Securities and Exchange Commission&rsquo;s attack on the crypto industry culminating in suing the two biggest crypto exchanges, Binance and Coinbase, most investors had fled the scene, possibly thinking that crypto might die.</p>
<p>As mentioned in a Crypto Daily article published only two days previously, it is times like these that the intelligent and experienced traders are waiting for. In addition, the technicals were looking quite positive.</p>
Technicals looking good
<p>Bitcoin had been traversing in a downward sloping channel since mid-April (a bullish pattern in itself), which could even be taken as a bull flag that had gone on for rather a long time.</p>
<p>Had bitcoin fallen out of the bottom of the channel instead, then this would have been seen as extremely bearish. However, bitcoin did the most logical thing and broke out strongly to the upside.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It is currently playing with $29,000, which it did hit earlier today. There is the possibility that the price could storm on to the major resistance at $30,300, but it could be expected to get rejected here, at least for the time being.</p>
Can the move be sustained?
<p>It might be wondered if bitcoin will be able to sustain a sizable rally on the scale of the 4 and a half month one it made from the beginning of the year. There is still much fear and negativity permeating the crypto space, and given the SEC actions, liquidity is very thin.</p>
<p>However, bitcoin has its halving cycle that will be drawing the king of the crypto assets higher. This is due to take place in April 2024, so still a lot of ups and downs before the bull run can start in earnest.</p>
Nothing comes close
<p>All does appear to be on track though. Bitcoin is still the scarcest and hardest form of money on the planet, and it is only a matter of time before traditional institutions take off the blinkers and do something about protecting their portfolios with bitcoin - Gensler and his SEC permitting of course.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Unleash the Beast Of Passive Income With Hot New Meme Coin Caged Beasts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/unleash-the-beast-of-passive-income-with-hot-new-meme-coin-caged-beasts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/unleash-the-beast-of-passive-income-with-hot-new-meme-coin-caged-beasts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[Should You Invest $100 Into The Presale?
<p>Are you tired of the same old cryptos that take themselves too seriously? Well, get ready to unleash your wild side with Caged Beasts (BEASTS), the hottest new meme coin in town! This revolutionary cryptocurrency is all about community, decentralization whilst having some fun along the way. Caged Beasts is moments before dropping it&rsquo;s presale on the crypto world&hellip; So, why should you invest $100 into the Caged Beasts presale? And how can you earn back even more with passive income? Let's dive into the world of Caged Beasts and find out!</p>
Caged Beasts: Where Fun Meets Finance 
<p>Caged Beasts (BEASTS) is not your average crypto - it aims to shake up the traditional finance system and bring transparency to the forefront. To ensure everyone's trust, the funds from the presale are securely locked until the release date. That means you can invest with confidence, knowing that your money is in safe hands.</p>
<p>But what truly sets Caged Beasts apart from the rest is its unique tokenomics, limited edition NFT release, and vibrant community engagement. During the presale, each stage will be celebrated with a limited edition NFT release of a unique creature. It's like collecting rare digital trading cards, but with a crypto twist! And here's the best part: there will only be 1000 NFTs available upon launch, and they will be tax-exempt. So, not only will you own a piece of crypto history, but you'll also do it in style!</p>
Meet the Playful Beasts
<p>Now, let's meet the stars of the show - the Caged Beasts themselves. Prepare to be amazed by the mischievous and whimsical personalities of these playful creatures. Take Champagne Charlie, for example. This mouthy and vicious parrot loves nothing more than indulging in self-medication with champagne. And then there's Drake, the color-obsessed chameleon who creates mind-blowing graffiti art. These colorful characters bring a whole new level of excitement to the world of cryptocurrency and make it incredibly entertaining for newcomers to jump in.</p>
<p>Outstanding Tokenomics and Community Engagement</p>
<p></p>
<p>But it's not all fun and games. Caged Beasts (BEASTS) has some seriously outstanding tokenomics that make it a worthwhile investment. With 100,000,000,000 tokens up for grabs and no sales or purchase taxes, you have the opportunity to dive into this vibrant market without any additional costs. Additionally, 75% of the assets will be frozen for liquidity until launch day, ensuring stability and security, and building a trusting relationship for $BEASTS holders. The remaining 25% of the generated funds will go towards the marketing wallet, fueling the growth and promotion of Caged Beasts.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts is all about community. Engaging with the locals is key to unlocking the full potential of this unique cryptocurrency. Get ready for a thrilling array of competitions, rewards, events, votes, and special releases exclusively for the community. You'll always be the first to learn about the latest news, especially when it comes to those coveted NFT releases. Caged Beasts aims to liberate the people and break away from the centralized finance system that has held us captive for far too long.</p>
Innovative Marketing and Growth Dynamics
<p>Caged Beasts employs a dynamic marketing approach that incorporates various methods such as social media competitions, giveaways, and events. These initiatives are designed to promote active participation within the community. Additionally, Caged Beasts has implemented an innovative referral system that benefits both those who refer others and those who are referred. This creative strategy, combined with an engaging narrative, has the potential to drive growth and establish a thriving Caged Beasts community.</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>So, if you're ready to embrace a wild and playful side while reclaiming your financial future, look no further than Caged Beasts. With its transparent and secure pre-sale, limited edition NFTs, engaging community, and innovative marketing strategies, this meme coin promises to bring joy and excitement to your crypto journey.Don't miss out on this opportunity to invest into Caged Beasts and discover the thrilling world of passive income. Let the beasts roam free, join the revolution, and watch your investments grow! Unleash the beasts and let the Caged Beasts community flourish!For All Things Caged Beasts (BEASTS): </p>
<p>Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[Should You Invest $100 Into The Presale?
<p>Are you tired of the same old cryptos that take themselves too seriously? Well, get ready to unleash your wild side with Caged Beasts (BEASTS), the hottest new meme coin in town! This revolutionary cryptocurrency is all about community, decentralization whilst having some fun along the way. Caged Beasts is moments before dropping it&rsquo;s presale on the crypto world&hellip; So, why should you invest $100 into the Caged Beasts presale? And how can you earn back even more with passive income? Let's dive into the world of Caged Beasts and find out!</p>
Caged Beasts: Where Fun Meets Finance 
<p>Caged Beasts (BEASTS) is not your average crypto - it aims to shake up the traditional finance system and bring transparency to the forefront. To ensure everyone's trust, the funds from the presale are securely locked until the release date. That means you can invest with confidence, knowing that your money is in safe hands.</p>
<p>But what truly sets Caged Beasts apart from the rest is its unique tokenomics, limited edition NFT release, and vibrant community engagement. During the presale, each stage will be celebrated with a limited edition NFT release of a unique creature. It's like collecting rare digital trading cards, but with a crypto twist! And here's the best part: there will only be 1000 NFTs available upon launch, and they will be tax-exempt. So, not only will you own a piece of crypto history, but you'll also do it in style!</p>
Meet the Playful Beasts
<p>Now, let's meet the stars of the show - the Caged Beasts themselves. Prepare to be amazed by the mischievous and whimsical personalities of these playful creatures. Take Champagne Charlie, for example. This mouthy and vicious parrot loves nothing more than indulging in self-medication with champagne. And then there's Drake, the color-obsessed chameleon who creates mind-blowing graffiti art. These colorful characters bring a whole new level of excitement to the world of cryptocurrency and make it incredibly entertaining for newcomers to jump in.</p>
<p>Outstanding Tokenomics and Community Engagement</p>
<p></p>
<p>But it's not all fun and games. Caged Beasts (BEASTS) has some seriously outstanding tokenomics that make it a worthwhile investment. With 100,000,000,000 tokens up for grabs and no sales or purchase taxes, you have the opportunity to dive into this vibrant market without any additional costs. Additionally, 75% of the assets will be frozen for liquidity until launch day, ensuring stability and security, and building a trusting relationship for $BEASTS holders. The remaining 25% of the generated funds will go towards the marketing wallet, fueling the growth and promotion of Caged Beasts.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts is all about community. Engaging with the locals is key to unlocking the full potential of this unique cryptocurrency. Get ready for a thrilling array of competitions, rewards, events, votes, and special releases exclusively for the community. You'll always be the first to learn about the latest news, especially when it comes to those coveted NFT releases. Caged Beasts aims to liberate the people and break away from the centralized finance system that has held us captive for far too long.</p>
Innovative Marketing and Growth Dynamics
<p>Caged Beasts employs a dynamic marketing approach that incorporates various methods such as social media competitions, giveaways, and events. These initiatives are designed to promote active participation within the community. Additionally, Caged Beasts has implemented an innovative referral system that benefits both those who refer others and those who are referred. This creative strategy, combined with an engaging narrative, has the potential to drive growth and establish a thriving Caged Beasts community.</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>So, if you're ready to embrace a wild and playful side while reclaiming your financial future, look no further than Caged Beasts. With its transparent and secure pre-sale, limited edition NFTs, engaging community, and innovative marketing strategies, this meme coin promises to bring joy and excitement to your crypto journey.Don't miss out on this opportunity to invest into Caged Beasts and discover the thrilling world of passive income. Let the beasts roam free, join the revolution, and watch your investments grow! Unleash the beasts and let the Caged Beasts community flourish!For All Things Caged Beasts (BEASTS): </p>
<p>Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Best Passive Income Ideas For Crypto: From Staking To Referral Schemes With Ethereum, TENET, and Caged Beasts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/best-passive-income-ideas-for-crypto-from-staking-to-referral-schemes-with-ethereum-tenet-and-caged-beasts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-641.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-641.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-641.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/best-passive-income-ideas-for-crypto-from-staking-to-referral-schemes-with-ethereum-tenet-and-caged-beasts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to an exciting exploration of crypto passive income ideas! Crypto passive income refers to the ability to earn money from your cryptocurrency investments without actively trading or constantly monitoring the market. It is highly regarded because it provides opportunities for diversification, potentially high returns on investment, and accessibility to individuals of all backgrounds. In this article, we will delve into the world of three high-potential coins: Ethereum (ETH), TENET (TENET), and the trailblazing Caged Beasts (BEASTS). Each of these cryptocurrencies offers unique opportunities for generating passive income and shaking up the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>Ethereum - Liquid Staking With The Alt King!Ethereum (ETH), the king of smart contract platforms, needs no introduction. It has revolutionized the crypto space, allowing developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) and launch their own tokens with ease. Compared to other crypto projects, Ethereum boasts unique strengths such as a robust ecosystem, widespread adoption, and the ability to execute complex smart contracts efficiently.</p>
<p>But what about liquid staking on Ethereum? Liquid staking combines the benefits of staking and liquidity, allowing users to stake their Ethereum while still having the flexibility to trade or use their staked assets. By utilizing platforms like Lido, users can seamlessly stake and unstake their ETH, earning lucrative yields while enjoying the freedom to access their assets at any time. This innovative approach to staking offers the best of both worlds and is a game-changer for passive income seekers.</p>
<p>TENET - The LSD-Driven Blockchain</p>
<p>Now, let's dive into the world of TENET (TENET), a more recent crypto gem that has emerged. Layer-1 blockchain Tenet has partnered with omnichain messaging protocol LayerZero to plug into a cross-chain decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem. This collaboration grants Tenet access to the wider DeFi landscape across multiple blockchains.</p>
<p>TENET's DeFi-focused ecosystem provides liquidity and yield products for liquid staking derivatives (LSDs). Similar to Ethereum's liquid staking pools, such as Lido, TENET's network enables users to stake and unstake assets seamlessly, unlocking the potential for lucrative yields. Moreover, TENET allows users to create projects and tokens, integrating them with LayerZero technology for enhanced interoperability across various smart contract blockchains. By leveraging this ecosystem, TENET empowers PoS native tokens to maximize their earnings potential, showcasing the power of LSDs in the DeFi space.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts - Defying Convention with Memetic Brilliance! </p>
<p>This article wouldn't be complete without a meme coin, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS) steals the spotlight. The proof-of-stake consensus algorithm is used to govern this decentralized Ethereum-based meme coin, assuring a robust and beneficial investment potential. With Ethereum as its foundation, Caged Beasts aims to revolutionize what a meme coin can truly accomplish.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts differentiates itself through its innovative concept called "Caged Liquidity." By championing decentralization, Caged Beasts enhances trust and stability within its ecosystem, offering investors a unique opportunity to be part of a thriving community. Additionally, Caged Beasts boasts a stellar referral program where users can create their own exclusive referral codes. With each successful referral, both the referrer and the investor bag a sweet bonus of 20% extra BEASTS tokens, creating a win-win situation for everyone involved.</p>
<p>If you&rsquo;d like to stay up to date with the latest news in the realm of Caged Beasts and be notified ahead of time for the presale drop, you can register your email here!</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>The crypto world is a rollercoaster of innovation and opportunity, and these three cryptos - Ethereum, TENET, and Caged Beasts - are leading the charge. Ethereum continues to dominate as the pioneer of smart contract platforms, while liquid staking on Ethereum and platforms like Lido unlock even greater passive income potential.TENET shakes things up by plugging into a cross-chain DeFi ecosystem, providing liquidity and yield products through its LSD-driven blockchain. And last but not least, Caged Beasts adds an element of fun and excitement with its decentralized meme token and captivating referral program.Whether you're seeking passive income, exploring alternative staking options, or simply looking for the next 10x altcoin, these three coins offer enticing opportunities for crypto enthusiasts. So, join the Crypto Carnival and buckle up for an exhilarating ride into the world of decentralized finance and the meme coin revolution!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For All Things Caged Beasts (BEASTS):</p>
<p>Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to an exciting exploration of crypto passive income ideas! Crypto passive income refers to the ability to earn money from your cryptocurrency investments without actively trading or constantly monitoring the market. It is highly regarded because it provides opportunities for diversification, potentially high returns on investment, and accessibility to individuals of all backgrounds. In this article, we will delve into the world of three high-potential coins: Ethereum (ETH), TENET (TENET), and the trailblazing Caged Beasts (BEASTS). Each of these cryptocurrencies offers unique opportunities for generating passive income and shaking up the crypto landscape.</p>
<p>Ethereum - Liquid Staking With The Alt King!Ethereum (ETH), the king of smart contract platforms, needs no introduction. It has revolutionized the crypto space, allowing developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) and launch their own tokens with ease. Compared to other crypto projects, Ethereum boasts unique strengths such as a robust ecosystem, widespread adoption, and the ability to execute complex smart contracts efficiently.</p>
<p>But what about liquid staking on Ethereum? Liquid staking combines the benefits of staking and liquidity, allowing users to stake their Ethereum while still having the flexibility to trade or use their staked assets. By utilizing platforms like Lido, users can seamlessly stake and unstake their ETH, earning lucrative yields while enjoying the freedom to access their assets at any time. This innovative approach to staking offers the best of both worlds and is a game-changer for passive income seekers.</p>
<p>TENET - The LSD-Driven Blockchain</p>
<p>Now, let's dive into the world of TENET (TENET), a more recent crypto gem that has emerged. Layer-1 blockchain Tenet has partnered with omnichain messaging protocol LayerZero to plug into a cross-chain decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem. This collaboration grants Tenet access to the wider DeFi landscape across multiple blockchains.</p>
<p>TENET's DeFi-focused ecosystem provides liquidity and yield products for liquid staking derivatives (LSDs). Similar to Ethereum's liquid staking pools, such as Lido, TENET's network enables users to stake and unstake assets seamlessly, unlocking the potential for lucrative yields. Moreover, TENET allows users to create projects and tokens, integrating them with LayerZero technology for enhanced interoperability across various smart contract blockchains. By leveraging this ecosystem, TENET empowers PoS native tokens to maximize their earnings potential, showcasing the power of LSDs in the DeFi space.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts - Defying Convention with Memetic Brilliance! </p>
<p>This article wouldn't be complete without a meme coin, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS) steals the spotlight. The proof-of-stake consensus algorithm is used to govern this decentralized Ethereum-based meme coin, assuring a robust and beneficial investment potential. With Ethereum as its foundation, Caged Beasts aims to revolutionize what a meme coin can truly accomplish.</p>
<p>Caged Beasts differentiates itself through its innovative concept called "Caged Liquidity." By championing decentralization, Caged Beasts enhances trust and stability within its ecosystem, offering investors a unique opportunity to be part of a thriving community. Additionally, Caged Beasts boasts a stellar referral program where users can create their own exclusive referral codes. With each successful referral, both the referrer and the investor bag a sweet bonus of 20% extra BEASTS tokens, creating a win-win situation for everyone involved.</p>
<p>If you&rsquo;d like to stay up to date with the latest news in the realm of Caged Beasts and be notified ahead of time for the presale drop, you can register your email here!</p>
<p>Final Thoughts</p>
<p>The crypto world is a rollercoaster of innovation and opportunity, and these three cryptos - Ethereum, TENET, and Caged Beasts - are leading the charge. Ethereum continues to dominate as the pioneer of smart contract platforms, while liquid staking on Ethereum and platforms like Lido unlock even greater passive income potential.TENET shakes things up by plugging into a cross-chain DeFi ecosystem, providing liquidity and yield products through its LSD-driven blockchain. And last but not least, Caged Beasts adds an element of fun and excitement with its decentralized meme token and captivating referral program.Whether you're seeking passive income, exploring alternative staking options, or simply looking for the next 10x altcoin, these three coins offer enticing opportunities for crypto enthusiasts. So, join the Crypto Carnival and buckle up for an exhilarating ride into the world of decentralized finance and the meme coin revolution!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>For All Things Caged Beasts (BEASTS):</p>
<p>Website: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Look Through The Top Passive Income Options In Crypto: Cosmos, Cardano & Caged Beasts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/look-through-the-top-passive-income-options-in-crypto-cosmos-cardano-caged-beasts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-640.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/look-through-the-top-passive-income-options-in-crypto-cosmos-cardano-caged-beasts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>If you are keen on making your money work for you, you may have tried looking for passive income options. Step into the exciting realm of cryptocurrencies and watch with bewilderment. Follow us as we skim through the top options that will tickle your financial senses: Cosmos, Cardano, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS). Read on to know about how these projects can potentially help you achieve your biggest financial goals.</p>
Encompass Cosmos With Cosmostation
<p>Cosmostation presents a user-friendly wallet and dashboard solution that brings convenience to the table. It provides a mobile wallet for seamless staking on your phone as well as a web wallet for secure hardware wallet transactions. Cosmostation has established itself as a reputable player in the Cosmos ecosystem, and is known for its exceptional user support and offerings like the Mintscan Explorer.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its extensive support for over 30 networks and a top-notch validator node, Cosmostation ensures a trustworthy staking experience. Interacting with the platform is straightforward, and it offers support for IBC-enabled tokens, as well as a range of helpful resources for any assistance you may need.</p>
Say Hello To Cardano&rsquo;s Staking Solution
<p></p>
<p>Cardano, the remarkable blockchain platform celebrated for its steadfast dedication to security and boundless scalability, offers more than just business opportunities. It invites you to embark on a captivating adventure of passive income.</p>
<p>By embracing Cardano's proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, you can become part of something truly extraordinary. By staking your ADA tokens, you become a cherished guardian of the network, strengthening its security while unlocking unprecedented rewards. It's like having your very own hidden treasure chest that replenishes itself over time!</p>
Caged Beasts Revolutionizing Passive Income
<p>Rabbit 4001 seeks revenge, and he needs your help. Welcome to the universe of Caged Beasts (BEASTS), a crypto project that seamlessly blends creativity, and community engagement, with the power of cryptocurrency. Get ready to be immersed in the enthralling storyline of Rabbit 4001, a troubled character on a mission to unveil a new generation of beasts as the token progresses, delivering an unparalleled and immersive crypto experience.</p>
<p>When it comes to generating passive income, BEASTS takes it to the next level with its exceptional referral program. By sharing your unique referral code with your friends, you unlock a win-win scenario for all participants.</p>
<p>Here's how it works: When a friend signs up using your code, you receive a generous 20% of their deposit in popular cryptocurrencies like ETH, BNB, or USDT, directly deposited into your crypto wallet. But that's not all&mdash;your friend who utilizes the referral code also receives an enticing 20% off of BEAST tokens. It's an incredible opportunity for both parties to reap the benefits of this thrilling venture.</p>
<p>With this mutually beneficial structure, not only do you enjoy the perks of being a referrer, but your friends also get to dive into the captivating world of BEASTS and earn their fair share. The aim is to build a vibrant community while unlocking the potential for a passive income stream. So buckle up for an extraordinary journey as you unleash the beasts and embark on this exhilarating crypto adventure together!</p>
<p></p>
The Takeaway
<p>While Cardano and Cosmos work as good passive income options, their popularity almost takes them to a fault. In contrast, Caged Beasts, while still in its early stages,&nbsp; presents an exciting opportunity to enhance your financial gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its exceptional versatility, this token has the potential for significant growth, ensuring substantial returns for its community. If you're aiming for a passive income of $100 per day, don't miss out on the chance to be part of the crypto revolution. Join the Caged Beasts community today and sign up to unlock your earning potential!</p>
<p>Join the Caged Beasts RevolutionWebsite: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you are keen on making your money work for you, you may have tried looking for passive income options. Step into the exciting realm of cryptocurrencies and watch with bewilderment. Follow us as we skim through the top options that will tickle your financial senses: Cosmos, Cardano, and Caged Beasts (BEASTS). Read on to know about how these projects can potentially help you achieve your biggest financial goals.</p>
Encompass Cosmos With Cosmostation
<p>Cosmostation presents a user-friendly wallet and dashboard solution that brings convenience to the table. It provides a mobile wallet for seamless staking on your phone as well as a web wallet for secure hardware wallet transactions. Cosmostation has established itself as a reputable player in the Cosmos ecosystem, and is known for its exceptional user support and offerings like the Mintscan Explorer.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its extensive support for over 30 networks and a top-notch validator node, Cosmostation ensures a trustworthy staking experience. Interacting with the platform is straightforward, and it offers support for IBC-enabled tokens, as well as a range of helpful resources for any assistance you may need.</p>
Say Hello To Cardano&rsquo;s Staking Solution
<p></p>
<p>Cardano, the remarkable blockchain platform celebrated for its steadfast dedication to security and boundless scalability, offers more than just business opportunities. It invites you to embark on a captivating adventure of passive income.</p>
<p>By embracing Cardano's proof-of-stake (PoS) consensus mechanism, you can become part of something truly extraordinary. By staking your ADA tokens, you become a cherished guardian of the network, strengthening its security while unlocking unprecedented rewards. It's like having your very own hidden treasure chest that replenishes itself over time!</p>
Caged Beasts Revolutionizing Passive Income
<p>Rabbit 4001 seeks revenge, and he needs your help. Welcome to the universe of Caged Beasts (BEASTS), a crypto project that seamlessly blends creativity, and community engagement, with the power of cryptocurrency. Get ready to be immersed in the enthralling storyline of Rabbit 4001, a troubled character on a mission to unveil a new generation of beasts as the token progresses, delivering an unparalleled and immersive crypto experience.</p>
<p>When it comes to generating passive income, BEASTS takes it to the next level with its exceptional referral program. By sharing your unique referral code with your friends, you unlock a win-win scenario for all participants.</p>
<p>Here's how it works: When a friend signs up using your code, you receive a generous 20% of their deposit in popular cryptocurrencies like ETH, BNB, or USDT, directly deposited into your crypto wallet. But that's not all&mdash;your friend who utilizes the referral code also receives an enticing 20% off of BEAST tokens. It's an incredible opportunity for both parties to reap the benefits of this thrilling venture.</p>
<p>With this mutually beneficial structure, not only do you enjoy the perks of being a referrer, but your friends also get to dive into the captivating world of BEASTS and earn their fair share. The aim is to build a vibrant community while unlocking the potential for a passive income stream. So buckle up for an extraordinary journey as you unleash the beasts and embark on this exhilarating crypto adventure together!</p>
<p></p>
The Takeaway
<p>While Cardano and Cosmos work as good passive income options, their popularity almost takes them to a fault. In contrast, Caged Beasts, while still in its early stages,&nbsp; presents an exciting opportunity to enhance your financial gains.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With its exceptional versatility, this token has the potential for significant growth, ensuring substantial returns for its community. If you're aiming for a passive income of $100 per day, don't miss out on the chance to be part of the crypto revolution. Join the Caged Beasts community today and sign up to unlock your earning potential!</p>
<p>Join the Caged Beasts RevolutionWebsite: https://cagedbeasts.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/CAGED_BEASTS&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/CAGEDBEASTS</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LBank Joins Forces with Seoul Meta Week 2023 as Co-Creation Partner]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-joins-forces-with-seoul-meta-week-2023-as-co-creation-partner</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230621_PR_article_cover_image-02_1687342396MrP2zD9Ej8.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230621_PR_article_cover_image-02_1687342396MrP2zD9Ej8.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/20230621_PR_article_cover_image-02_1687342396MrP2zD9Ej8.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:28:06 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/06/lbank-joins-forces-with-seoul-meta-week-2023-as-co-creation-partner</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Island, British Virgin Islands, June 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, a leading global crypto exchange, is proud to announce its partnership as a co-creation partner for Seoul Meta Week 2023. The conference will take place from June 26 to 30 at the elegant COEX Auditorium in the heart of Seoul.</p><p>LBank teams up with industry giants such as Tencent, Google Cloud, Roblox, Polygon, OKX, The Sandbox, and governmental organizations including Korea's Ministry of Science and ICT, the Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy, the Seoul Metropolitan Government, and the Seoul Tourism Organization, as co-creation partners for this week-long festival.</p><p>Seoul Meta Week 2023 brings together distinguished industry leaders, experts, and enthusiasts to explore the latest trends and advancements in blockchain technology. The conference features a diverse range of programs designed to inspire, educate, and connect participants. Attendees will have the opportunity to engage in enlightening conferences where renowned speakers exchange insights, explore captivating exhibitions by both local and international firms, participate in expert workshops, and enjoy networking opportunities with top industry players.</p><p>As a co-creation partner, LBank is excited to contribute its expertise and support to drive innovation and foster the growth of the Web3 and blockchain ecosystem. LBank's participation underscores its commitment to promoting technological advancements and facilitating the widespread adoption of digital assets. Through its presence at Seoul Meta Week 2023, LBank aims to foster collaboration, inspire industry players, and showcase the transformative potential of blockchain technology.</p>"We are delighted to support Seoul Meta Week 2023 as a co-creation partner," said Eric He, Chairman of LBank. "This partnership exemplifies our dedication to shaping the future of the Web3 industry and fostering a vibrant ecosystem. We look forward to engaging with industry leaders, sharing insights, and contributing to the success of this remarkable event."<p>Seoul Meta Week 2023 will take place within the COEX Convention &amp; Exhibition Center, located in the Samseong-dong ward of Seoul&rsquo;s Gangnam-gu district. The event is set to attract a diverse range of participants, including entrepreneurs, investors, Web3 developers, and crypto enthusiasts from around the globe. By providing a platform for networking, knowledge sharing, and collaboration, Seoul Meta Week 2023 aims to inspire innovative solutions to global challenges with this new breed of technology.</p><p>LBank Labs, LBank&rsquo;s venture capitalist arm and blockchain accelerator, is also set to partner up with the Seoul Metropolitan Government in late July to sponsor the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival to drive blockchain innovation in the country.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Island, British Virgin Islands, June 21st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>LBank, a leading global crypto exchange, is proud to announce its partnership as a co-creation partner for Seoul Meta Week 2023. The conference will take place from June 26 to 30 at the elegant COEX Auditorium in the heart of Seoul.</p><p>LBank teams up with industry giants such as Tencent, Google Cloud, Roblox, Polygon, OKX, The Sandbox, and governmental organizations including Korea's Ministry of Science and ICT, the Ministry of Trade, Industry and Energy, the Seoul Metropolitan Government, and the Seoul Tourism Organization, as co-creation partners for this week-long festival.</p><p>Seoul Meta Week 2023 brings together distinguished industry leaders, experts, and enthusiasts to explore the latest trends and advancements in blockchain technology. The conference features a diverse range of programs designed to inspire, educate, and connect participants. Attendees will have the opportunity to engage in enlightening conferences where renowned speakers exchange insights, explore captivating exhibitions by both local and international firms, participate in expert workshops, and enjoy networking opportunities with top industry players.</p><p>As a co-creation partner, LBank is excited to contribute its expertise and support to drive innovation and foster the growth of the Web3 and blockchain ecosystem. LBank's participation underscores its commitment to promoting technological advancements and facilitating the widespread adoption of digital assets. Through its presence at Seoul Meta Week 2023, LBank aims to foster collaboration, inspire industry players, and showcase the transformative potential of blockchain technology.</p>"We are delighted to support Seoul Meta Week 2023 as a co-creation partner," said Eric He, Chairman of LBank. "This partnership exemplifies our dedication to shaping the future of the Web3 industry and fostering a vibrant ecosystem. We look forward to engaging with industry leaders, sharing insights, and contributing to the success of this remarkable event."<p>Seoul Meta Week 2023 will take place within the COEX Convention &amp; Exhibition Center, located in the Samseong-dong ward of Seoul&rsquo;s Gangnam-gu district. The event is set to attract a diverse range of participants, including entrepreneurs, investors, Web3 developers, and crypto enthusiasts from around the globe. By providing a platform for networking, knowledge sharing, and collaboration, Seoul Meta Week 2023 aims to inspire innovative solutions to global challenges with this new breed of technology.</p><p>LBank Labs, LBank&rsquo;s venture capitalist arm and blockchain accelerator, is also set to partner up with the Seoul Metropolitan Government in late July to sponsor the Seoul Web 3.0 Festival to drive blockchain innovation in the country.</p><p>About LBank</p><p>LBank is one of the top crypto exchanges, established in 2015. It offers specialized financial derivatives, expert asset management services, and safe crypto trading to its users. The platform holds over 9 million users from more than 210 regions across the world. LBank is a cutting-edge growing platform that ensures the integrity of users&rsquo; funds and aims to contribute to the global adoption of cryptocurrencies.</p><p>Start Trading Now:&nbsp;lbank.com</p><p>Community &amp; Social Media:&nbsp;l&nbsp;Telegram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Twitter&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Facebook&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;LinkedIn&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;Instagram&nbsp;l&nbsp;&nbsp;YouTube</p>ContactGlobal PR DirectorJeremy Van der HaegenLBankpress@lbank.info]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
