<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 12:36:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>EOS Celebrates 5th Anniversary Owing to &#8216;Resilient&#8217; Community</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eos-celebrates-5th-anniversary-owing-to-resilient-community/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EOS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254727</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The EOS network has turned five.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EOS once charted in the top ten cryptocurrencies by market cap. Now it stands in the top 50. The setbacks in its journey have been one of the most talked about in the industry.</p>
<p>But EOS Network Foundation&#8217;s La Rose believes the formative years of EOS have taught them a lot and that the blockchain project is just getting started, all thanks to the community.</p>
<h2>EOS Network Bumpy Ride</h2>
<p>EOS &#8211; which launched with great fanfare, an active community, and strong tech &#8211; faced several hiccups along the way in the last five years. In what was touted to be the biggest ICO in history, EOS managed to raise over $4 billion in funds in 2018.</p>
<p>However, the project failed to live up to its hype. The subsequent congestion issues, as well as centralization concerns by researchers, triggered developer exodus from the EOS ecosystem. The development dried out, which led the community to feel left out and deceived.</p>
<p>As a result, the community-formed EOS Network Foundation (ENF) &#8211; a not-for-profit organization &#8211; took the baton to revive what was left of it by getting rid of its founding company, Block.one.</p>
<h2>Post ENF</h2>
<p>Since ENF took over, EOS <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eos-launches-evm-announces-60m-strategic-partnership-with-dwf-labs/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the beta launch of its Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) mainnet, designed to improve interoperability with the Ethereum Blockchain. The open-source blockchain platform also inked a strategic partnership with the market maker and investment firm DWF Labs via a $60 million investment deal to accelerate the ecosystem&#8217;s growth and development.</p>
<p>Later, the foundation pledged a sum of $20 million to developers looking to build DeFi as well as GameFi projects for users on EOS. For the revitalization of the network, ENF also partnered with industry heavyweights, including Binance and Messari.</p>
<p>In the latest press release shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, ENF Founder and CEO Yves La Rose commemorated the 5th anniversary of the launch and said he is inspired by the &#8220;resilience&#8221; of the EOS community.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We have endured much uncertainty standing against corporate greed in defense of our network. Today, we have emerged as champions for the ethos of free and open-source software, forging a path to boundless innovation, not just for ourselves, but for the entire Web3 space.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eos-celebrates-5th-anniversary-owing-to-resilient-community/" rel="nofollow">EOS Celebrates 5th Anniversary Owing to &#8216;Resilient&#8217; Community</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did You Know? Charles Hoskinson Has a Private Jet Business and Has Serviced Metallica</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/did-you-know-charles-hoskinson-has-a-private-jet-business-and-has-serviced-metallica/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 19:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charles Hoskinson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253840</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Metallica_Hoskinson.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Metallica_Hoskinson.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Cardano exec loans out his private jet regularly to other high-profile individuals. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst heat waves, a multi-year drought, and devastating floods, environmentalists have shifted their focus to celebrities using emissions-spewing private jets. The latest high-profile individual from the crypto industry who has made it to the list is Cardano founder Charles Hoskinson.</p>
<p>The exec&#8217;s private jet is reportedly among the top 15 biggest polluters in the US, according to Climate Jets, a website that tracks the estimated emissions from private jets owned by the ultra-rich. It claims that Hoskinson&#8217;s private aircraft emissions &#8220;exceeded the full carbon emissions of 186 average Americans.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Hoskinson&#8217;s Comments on Private Jets</h2>
<p>After weathering intense public criticism over the same, Hoskinson <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHy81Ci5WZ8" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a> that the website is &#8220;over-counting&#8221; the use of his private jet.  The exec said that when he is not using the aircraft for business, he employs a company that finds clients who use it regularly and has loaned out to some of the big names, including rock band Metallica and Hollywood heavyweight Dwayne &#8220;The Rock&#8221; Johnson.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I have a pretty broad range of clients that use it (aircraft) from Metallica to the Rock and others. It&#8217;s a great network tool as well because you can imagine these are the people you would like to do business with.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In 2022, the aircraft associated with the Cardano founder is <a href="https://climatejets.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">claimed</a> to have made 353 flights using 296,930 gallons (more than 1.12k liters) of jet fuel and emitted 2,895.06 metric tons of carbon dioxide, thereby surpassing the likes of Mark Zuckerberg, Mark Cuban, Jay-Z, Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk, Kim Kardashian, Steven Spielberg to name a few.</p>
<p>The jet&#8217;s frequent destinations prominently featured Denver, Los Angeles, and New York City, along with international routes such as Canada, UAE, Poland, Israel, and South Korea, among other countries.</p>
<h2>Bill Gates&#8217; Frequent Use of Private Jets</h2>
<p>Shots were also fired at Microsoft co-founder Bill Gates who is a staunch advocate for the fight against climate change and has founded a leading climate technology investment company called &#8216;Breakthrough Energy Ventures.&#8217; The billionaire also frequently uses private jets, which has prompted questions about authenticity when it comes to his activism.</p>
<p>Interestingly, Gates is <a href="https://climatejets.org/wrapped/bill-gates" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ranked</a> as the 13th biggest polluter in the United States. His three private jets logged over 657 hours in the air, spanning a distance of 528,787 kilometers, and emitted 3,058.71 metric tons of carbon dioxide. Citing the stats, Hoskinson said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There is a large movement, the ESG movement, that is pushing to reduce carbon. The great irony is that, when you look at the list that was aggregated, the vast majority of those are big boosters of the ESG movement for example Bill Gates and others of his ilk.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-you-know-charles-hoskinson-has-a-private-jet-business-and-has-serviced-metallica/" rel="nofollow">Did You Know? Charles Hoskinson Has a Private Jet Business and Has Serviced Metallica</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Polygon, Solana Join Cardano in Dismissing the SEC&#8217;s Allegations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-solana-join-cardano-in-dismissing-the-secs-allegations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 17:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254747</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SEC_MATIC_SOL.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/SEC_MATIC_SOL.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Solana Foundation wants to work on establishing clear regulations, but does not agree that SOL is a security. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission alleged that some of the largest altcoins, such as ADA, MATIC, and SOL, are unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Most assets slumped in value shortly after the allegations went out. Now, though, the organizations between the blockchains and the tokens have published official statements to refute the SEC&#8217;s claims.</p>
<h2>Polygon Responds</h2>
<p>MATIC traded at $0.9 last week, just a few days before the SEC went after Binance and Coinbase, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-outcome-instrumental-for-coinbase-binance-lawsuit-lawyer/" data-wpel-link="internal">alleging</a> in the lawsuits that the asset is an unregistered security. At first, MATIC declined alongside the rest of the market to $0.8. However, the situation worsened on Friday when it plummeted by almost 40% in a day to a multi-month low at $0.5.</p>
<p>Amid the harmful price drops, Polygon Labs decided to <a href="https://twitter.com/0xPolygonLabs/status/1667643925232852996" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">respond</a> to the allegations. The organization said the Polygon blockchain was &#8220;developed outside the US, deployed outside the US, and focused to this day on the global community that supports the network.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;MATIC was a necessary part of the Polygon technology from Day 1, ensuring that the network would be secure – and remains so to this day. Given our focus on network security, we made sure MATIC was available to a wide group of persons, but only with actions that did not target the US at any time.&#8221; &#8211; the statement reads.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Solana Disagrees, too</h2>
<p>SOL&#8217;s performance was quite similar to MATIC, given that it was also alleged to be an unregistered security. It stood at $22 last Sunday, retraced to just under $20 during the week, and then dumped by more than 30% on Friday and Saturday.</p>
<p>The Solana Foundation, similar to the team behind <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardanos-iog-dismisses-secs-claim-that-ada-is-a-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cardano</a>, has also refuted the SEC&#8217;s claims. The statement informed that the SF is looking forward to working with global regulators to establish clear legislative frameworks but &#8220;disagrees with the characterization of SOL as a security.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">The Solana Foundation disagrees with the characterization of SOL as a security. We welcome the continued engagement of policymakers as constructive partners on regulation to achieve legal clarity on these issues for the thousands of entrepreneurs across the U.S. building in the…</p>
<p>— Solana Foundation (@SolanaFndn) <a href="https://twitter.com/SolanaFndn/status/1667578529612017666?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-solana-join-cardano-in-dismissing-the-secs-allegations/" rel="nofollow">Polygon, Solana Join Cardano in Dismissing the SEC&#8217;s Allegations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arbitrum Remains Top Destination for Capital Flowing Away From Ethereum: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arbitrum-remains-top-destination-for-capital-flowing-away-from-ethereum-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 14:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitrum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optimism (OP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254585</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/arbitrum_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/arbitrum_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Amidst the regulatory upheaval, Arbitrum continues to dominate the layer-2 landscape. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arbitrum has managed to rake in a significant market share as demand for Ethereum rollups soars.</p>
<p>According to data shared by CoinShares, Arbitrum remains the top destination for capital flows away from Ethereum, among other protocols as well as layer 2s. As of May-end, the network attracted capital worth $4 billion.</p>
<ul>
<li>Closely following Arbitrum is Polygon raking in capital worth $3 billion, followed by Optimism with $983 million, and dYdX with $342 million, the stats <a href="https://twitter.com/CoinSharesCo/status/1666717049362448387" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a>.</li>
<li>In recent months, Arbitrum has managed to eclipse its rival protocols. One of the most significant developments was the much-anticipated <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-you-need-to-know-about-the-arbitrum-airdrop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of its native governance token, ARB, which was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arbitrum-airdrops-120m-worth-arb-tokens-to-125-daos/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">airdropped</a> to early platform users based on their activity on Arbitrum between specific duration.</li>
<li>In the days leading up to the event, the daily transaction on the Ethereum-layer 2 scaling system skyrocketed above 2.7 million.</li>
<li>As the hype faded, the transaction count <a href="https://arbiscan.io/chart/tx" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">dipped</a> near 724k but was still over 124% higher than the figures recorded at the beginning of the year.</li>
<li>Total addresses over time on Arbitrum <a href="https://dune.com/evulutionary/arbitrum-vs-optimism" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">crossed</a> seven million this week while that of its rival, Optimism, stood a little over three million.</li>
<li>Arbitrum recently stopped sending transactions to mainnet for roughly two hours due to a software bug affecting the optimistic rollup&#8217;s sequencer. The foundation&#8217;s community leaders <a href="https://discord.com/channels/585084330037084172/585085189823266875/1116054225135349932" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> the software bug &#8220;created network stress caused by the large backlog of transactions which hadn’t been posted on-chain.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arbitrum-remains-top-destination-for-capital-flowing-away-from-ethereum-data/" rel="nofollow">Arbitrum Remains Top Destination for Capital Flowing Away From Ethereum: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over 50% of BTC on Exchanges Have Moved Outside the US Due to Regulatory Uncertainty: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/over-50-of-btc-on-exchanges-have-moved-outside-the-us-due-to-regulatory-uncertainty-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 11:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254282</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/America_US-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The U.S. is losing its crypto market share as regulatory uncertainty drives firms and assets offshore.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Due to unclear regulations in the United States, more than half of the bitcoin (BTC) that crypto firms hold for their customers has moved to offshore and international exchanges.</p>
<p>According to a CryptoQuant research report shared with <em>CryptoPotato</em>, BTC reserves on U.S.-based crypto exchanges are down to 2017 levels, as they are being lost to non-U.S. platforms.</p>
<h2>Offshore Exchanges Dethrone US Crypto Platforms</h2>
<p>The significant decline in BTC reserves on American exchanges stems from the absence of a clear rule book for the crypto industry. Regulators have resorted to an enforcement-based <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" data-wpel-link="internal">approach</a>, driving crypto firms to offshore locations.</p>
<p>Regions like the EU and Hong Kong, which have developed comprehensive regulations for the nascent economy, are experiencing an inflow of capital, talent, and digital asset firms. Hong Kong, in particular, has opened up to crypto companies and stated that they would adopt the &#8220;same activity, same risks, same regulation&#8221; principle for entities akin to traditional financial firms.</p>
<p>Several exchanges have decided to exit the U.S., with others <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-plunge-4-following-sec-termination-of-kraken-staking/" data-wpel-link="internal">ceasing</a> certain products and services due to violation accusations. The country is gradually losing its market share of emerging and existing sectors as de-dollarization heightens.</p>
<h2>Over 50% of BTC and ETH Outside the U.S.</h2>
<p>Aside from decreasing BTC reserves in the U.S., ether (ETH) reserves have also been on a steady decline. About 56% of ETH on crypto exchanges are held outside the United States.</p>
<p>In addition, the trading volume of international crypto exchanges is four times greater than that of U.S.-based platforms. Bitcoin&#8217;s spot trading volume dominance in the U.S. has fallen below 2017 levels and is currently at 21%. American exchanges have little-to-no exposure to perpetual futures trading markets, which have a volume of 11x that of spot trading volume, as firms are not allowed to offer the service, the report added.</p>
<p>In contrast, Asia&#8217;s spot and futures trading volume growth is as high as 30% and 20%, respectively.</p>
<p>CryptoQuant&#8217;s research further found that the market cap of U.S.-based stablecoins has plummeted by 35%, losing $15 billion so far in 2023.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the U.S. remains the world&#8217;s dominant player in the Bitcoin mining industry. However, the country could lose that position due to bad regulation, as the government is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal">targeting</a> miners with the possibility of higher taxes. The U.S. is losing its crypto market share as regulatory uncertainty drives firms and assets offshore.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-50-of-btc-on-exchanges-have-moved-outside-the-us-due-to-regulatory-uncertainty-data/" rel="nofollow">Over 50% of BTC on Exchanges Have Moved Outside the US Due to Regulatory Uncertainty: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADA, SOL, SHIB Recover 8% Following Saturday&#8217;s Crash, XRP Reclaims $0.5 (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ada-sol-shib-recover-8-following-saturdays-crash-xrp-reclaims-0-5-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 08:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254728</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BTC_XRP_ADA_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BTC_XRP_ADA_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Several of yesterday's worst performers have bounced of rather impressively. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Albeit in a more modest fashion than the alts, bitcoin slumped hard yesterday by almost a grand before experiencing more volatility throughout the day.</p>
<p>Most alternative coins, though, plummeted hard by double digits. The past 24 hours have been more positive as ADA, SOL, SHIB, and many others have managed to bounce off.</p>
<h2>Alts&#8217; Rollercoaster</h2>
<p>It&#8217;s safe to say that the recent allegations made by the US Securities and Exchange Commission that many cryptocurrencies could actually be unregistered securities have started to take their toll on the market. The events from yesterday <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloodbath-the-reasons-behind-sol-matic-ada-sand-crash-today/" data-wpel-link="internal">validate</a> this.</p>
<p>Many of the mentioned by the SEC in its lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/altcoins-crash-double-digits-bitcoin-dominance-soars-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">plummeted</a> by double digits yesterday. These include <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cardano-ada-crashes-23-in-a-day-as-total-liquidations-near-400-million/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cardano</a> (ADA), Solana (SOL), Shiba Inu (SHIB), Avalanche (AVAX), Filecoin (FIL), and many others.</p>
<p>Today, however, the landscape for some of them is quite different. ADA has jumped by 9% since yesterday&#8217;s low and has pumped to over $0.26. SHIB is up by a similar percentage, SOL has added 7%, which was also mimicked by FIL, CRO, GRT, and others.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap lost over $60 billion in a day yesterday but has recovered $20 billion today and is up to $1.050 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254729" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254729" style="width: 1882px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254729" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1882" height="850" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5.jpg 1882w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5-1024x462.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5-768x347.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5-1536x694.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-5-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1882px) 100vw, 1882px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254729" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<h2>BTC Reacted Better</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency experienced enhanced volatility almost a week ago when it dumped from $27,000 to under $25,400 once the SEC announced its two back-to-back lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase. Interestingly, it reacted well and skyrocketed by $2,000 after the second one.</p>
<p>It retraced slightly in the next few days and had calmed at around $26,500. However, the overall market decline that started late on Friday affected BTC as well, which dropped by a grand in minutes.</p>
<p>Its rollercoaster continued as it pumped back up to $26,200 before it slipped just as quickly back down to under $25,500. It has recovered a few hundred dollars since then but still struggles below $26,000.</p>
<p>Its market cap is down to $500 billion, but its dominance over the alts shot up yesterday to 48% before retracing to 47.6% as of now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_254730" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254730" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-254730" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-8-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254730" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ada-sol-shib-recover-8-following-saturdays-crash-xrp-reclaims-0-5-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">ADA, SOL, SHIB Recover 8% Following Saturday&#8217;s Crash, XRP Reclaims $0.5 (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FancyCrypto: Making Crypto Mining More Accessible</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fancycrypto-making-crypto-mining-more-accessible/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254522</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Mining &#8211; the process of verifying transactions and packing them in blocks to send to the blockchain &#8211; is a critical component of many networks, including the largest one &#8211; Bitcoin. It’s the foundation around the entire cryptocurrency ecosystem (for a large part) is built on, and it is absolutely paramount to the concepts of [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mining &#8211; the process of verifying transactions and packing them in blocks to send to the blockchain &#8211; is a critical component of many networks, including the largest one &#8211; Bitcoin.</p>
<p>It’s the foundation around the entire cryptocurrency ecosystem (for a large part) is built on, and it is absolutely paramount to the concepts of crypto. However, it’s also very technical.</p>
<p>It’s a process that requires complex technical setups in terms of both hardware and software, sufficient electrical supply, and, if it’s made efficient &#8211; a dedicated storage space that’s being kept at the right temperature.</p>
<p>The above in itself put forward plenty of barriers to entry for many retail investors who don’t have access to significant capital. In essence, it bars retail investors from meaningfully participating in a way they can also earn a considerable profit.</p>
<p>Cloud mining comes as an attempted solution. The following explains what Cloud Mining is and looks at one of the more popular providers.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-254524" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg" alt="fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/fancycrypto_mining_sponsored_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>What is Crypto Cloud Mining?</h2>
<p>The crux of the concept comes from the word cloud. It’s a virtual space. Cloud mining allows retail investors to put as much money as they are comfortable with and, in return, rent cloud mining space from a company that normally operates (or rents itself) data centers.</p>
<p>In essence, cloud mining is the way to mine crypto using a remote data center with shared processing power.</p>
<p>This particular type of mining allows users to mine BTC or other cryptocurrencies without having to manage hardware on their own.</p>
<p>The mining rigs themselves are housed and maintained in a facility that’s owned by a mining company. The customer simply needs to register and purchase mining contracts or shares &#8211; depending on how the agreement is framed.</p>
<p>An important consideration here is that users are strongly advised to make proper research into the cloud mining provider that they choose. Just as with a lot of other initiatives in the industry, there have been instances of fraud, so it’s important to maintain vigilance.</p>
<h2>What is FancyCrypto?</h2>
<p><a href="https://fancycrypto.pro/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">FancyCrypto</a> is a cloud mining provider, and according to its website, it has earned the trust of hundreds of thousands of users.</p>
<p>The company’s mission is to make mining more accessible to everyone, enabling access to large-scale technology and industrial data centers from virtually any device or location. The website claims that FancyCrypto operates between 2% and 10% of the world’s cloud mining hash rate.</p>
<p>FancyCrypto was founded in London in 2016. As a pioneering cloud mining company, Fancy Crypto has already carved out a reputation as being a trustworthy hash rate provider for over 360,000 users all over the world. It wants to provide access to large-scale industrial data centers aided by cutting-edge technologies to make cloud mining available to everyone.</p>
<p>The platform allows the mining of multiple cryptocurrencies, which include: Bitcoin, Litecoin, DOGE, Ethereum Classic, and others. It also offers a range of different packages that users can purchase, starting from cheaper ones for $10 and getting to as high as $5,000. The daily profits also range, depending on the contract of choice. <a href="https://fancycrypto.com/plans" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Their packages</a> include:</p>
<p><strong>Free cloud mining</strong>: Such a contract stays valid for one day and costs $10. It has a fixed return of $10.15.</p>
<p><strong>Experienced project cloud mining</strong>: It is priced at $100 and is valid within your days. Its fixed return is $105</p>
<p><strong>Ethereum project cloud mining</strong>: It is priced at 300, valid for five days, and has a fixed return of $324.</p>
<p>The platform has a range of other packages of up to $5,000, all of which you can check on the official website.</p>
<p>Some of the features of cloud mining through FancyCrypto include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed Fees</li>
</ul>
<p>There are no hidden fees or commissions &#8211; users are able to monitor every transaction in a transparent dashboard.</p>
<ul>
<li>Ease of use</li>
</ul>
<p>There’s no hassle involved, as users don’t have to set up their own mining hardware and install relevant software. The platform’s dashboard is made to be easy and comprehensible, even for people without experience.</p>
<ul>
<li>Multiple choices</li>
</ul>
<p>Many platforms only offer Bitcoin cloud mining. FancyCrypto has a more versatile range of products that users can choose between.</p>
<p><strong>Summary </strong></p>
<p>FancyCrypto has been highly impactful to the cryptocurrency cloud mining scene. It has emerged as a preferred choice for many users who seek a feature-packed, economical, and hassle-free mining experience.</p>
<p>If you want to explore further details, take a look at the official website: <a href="https://fancycrypto.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://fancycrypto.com/</a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fancycrypto-making-crypto-mining-more-accessible/" rel="nofollow">FancyCrypto: Making Crypto Mining More Accessible</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Years in Prison for Arizona Entrepreneur for Offering Shadow Banking Services to Crypto Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/6-years-in-prison-for-arizona-entrepreneur-for-offering-shadow-banking-services-to-crypto-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254041</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Jail.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Former Co-Owner of Minnesota Vikings' acquisition of a stake in the AAF, in part, led to its collapse and subsequent bankruptcy declaration, the prosecutors said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A joint investigation by the FBI’s Money Laundering Squad and Internal Revenue Service-Criminal Investigations led to a 75-month prison sentence for 64-year-old Arizona entrepreneur Reginald Fowler. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A former co-owner of the professional American football team Minnesota Vikings, Fowler has also been asked by the court to pay a forfeiture of $74.02 million and restitution of $5.31 million to the Association of American Football (AAF), a short-lived American football minor league. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The prosecution was led by the United States Attorney’s Office’s Money Laundering and Transnational Criminal Enterprises Unit. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Offering Shadow Banking Services</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Damian Williams, US Attorney’s Office, Southern District of New York (SDNY)) in a PR on June 5, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/former-co-owner-minnesota-vikings-sentenced-75-months-prison-providing-shadow-banking" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Fowler processed nearly $750 million of transactions for cryptocurrency exchanges acting as a payment processor while his company Global Trading Solution did not have a license for money transmitting business as required by the US federal laws. While doing so, he also lied to US banks.  </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“FOWLER also directed other individuals to include false information on wire transfer instructions to further deceive banks about the nature of GTS’s business. In less than ten months, FOWLER processed approximately $750 million in cryptocurrency transactions in various currencies,” the PR from Attorney’s office said.  </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Defrauding American Football League </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He was also found guilty of defrauding the Association of American Football, in which he acquired a significant stake by investing customers’ funds claiming them to be his personal wealth.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“As he did when opening bank accounts, FOWLER lied to AAF executives, telling them that the funds in the GTS bank accounts derived from real estate investments as well as government contracts and that the tens of millions of dollars in the GTS accounts were liquid assets he could use to invest in the AAF,” Williams said. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In part, due to Fowler’s lies, the AAF declared bankruptcy in April 2019. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Catching Up with Crypto Crimes</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Given the rising number of cryptocurrency-related crime and fraud cases, the US Department of Justice (DoJ) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-doj-established-a-unit-of-prosecutors-to-limit-crypto-crime/" data-wpel-link="internal">formed</a> the “National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team” in September 2022. Cybersecurity prosecutor Eun Young Choi heads the team of 150 prosecutors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In May, a Russian man was </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russian-man-charged-for-200-million-in-ransomware-crimes-involving-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">charged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the DoJ with being part of three ransomware gangs that netted nearly $200 million through various ransomware attacks targeting police departments, hospitals, and schools.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/6-years-in-prison-for-arizona-entrepreneur-for-offering-shadow-banking-services-to-crypto-exchanges/" rel="nofollow">6 Years in Prison for Arizona Entrepreneur for Offering Shadow Banking Services to Crypto Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is The Market Crashing? Binance&#8217;s CZ Chips in on a Few Narratives</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-the-market-crashing-binances-cz-chips-in-on-a-few-narratives/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254697</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CZ chips in on the matter why the market is crashing, as well as touching on a few ongoing narratives. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The market took a beating over the past 24 hours, and certain altcoins performed a lot worse than others.</p>
<p>A lot of the worst-performing cryptocurrencies were also named in the lawsuit that the US Securities and Exchange Commission filed against Coinbase. The agency alleges that they are securities. These include Cardano&#8217;s ADA, Solana&#8217;s SOL, NEAR, Polygon&#8217;s MATIC, and so forth.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is down 3.4%, while Ethereum &#8211; 5.7%. Even though both of them decreased, it&#8217;s nowhere near the 20% decline that the above altcoins are charting.</p>
<p>Now, CZ &#8211; Binance&#8217;s CEO &#8211; chips in on some of the ongoing narratives.</p>
<ul>
<li>Changpeng Zhao, the CEO of Binance, chipped in on why the market is crashing. He outlined that &#8220;no one really knows&#8221; while also explaining that &#8220;there are many sellers and buyers in a market, everyone may have their own reasons.&#8221;</li>
<li>However, he also touched on a few ongoing narratives, sharing his thoughts on the matter.</li>
<li>CZ said that there&#8217;s a false narrative of Binance converting its holdings to fiat.</li>
<li>Instead, he claimed that the fiat and stablecoin reserves of Binance decreased &#8211; they are the ones used to pay for short-term salaries or expenses.</li>
<li>He also said that the crypto reserves of the exchange increased throughout the past months, weeks, and days.</li>
<li>A second narrative that he admitted to having no idea about is the matter of Robinhood and what happened to $1.3 billion worth of alts on the platform.</li>
<li>In any case, CZ explained that there are two emotions that anyone needs to manage in any market &#8211; greed and fear.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Why is the market is going up or down? No one really knows. A lot of people claim to know, and can often pin it on a single (often wrong) reason. In reality, there are many sellers and buyers in a market, everyone may have their own reasons. A few examples.</p>
<p>False narrative:… <a href="https://t.co/LQDkEOK2as" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/LQDkEOK2as</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1667439122137358336?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-is-the-market-crashing-binances-cz-chips-in-on-a-few-narratives/" rel="nofollow">Why Is The Market Crashing? Binance&#8217;s CZ Chips in on a Few Narratives</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Third Canadian HODLer Lost Money in Crypto Scams (Study)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-canadian-hodler-lost-money-in-crypto-scams-study/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 15:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[HODL]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254544</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Canada-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the survey, 35% of Canadian crypto owners have been conned by crypto scammers. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Research carried out by contributors of the Toronto Metropolitan University (TMU) estimated that 35% of Canadians owning digital assets had fallen victim to crypto fraud.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study further determined that approximately 9% of the locals have purchased cryptocurrencies or NFTs, with the share being higher among individuals who graduated from universities.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Less Educated People Seem More Likely to Get Scammed</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report, conducted via a representative survey of 2,000 Canadian residents, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://dais.ca/reports/risky-business-the-cyber-and-sociotechnical-security-threats-of-crypto-asset-trading/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that fraudulent schemes related to cryptocurrencies are a serious problem in the country. Per the results, over a third of those who have invested in digital assets have been lured into some sort of scam.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">14% (the largest share) said they had been contacted by a person who presented themselves as a crypto investment manager and who later stole a fee for his &#8220;services.&#8221; 10% admitted sharing their wallet information following a request for additional information, while 7% have purchased digital currencies from a mysterious individual who then disappeared.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;When users fall prey to these cryptocurrency scams, significant financial loss can result, sometimes compromising large amounts of money from lines of credit, credit cards, and life savings. Not only are there financial losses, but also the risk of personal and financial information being stolen. The scale of these types of fraud and scams seems substantial in Canada,&#8221; the research&#8217;s authors warned.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">People from the lower income brackets and those with less education are more likely to get conned. Individuals earning over $50,000 per year and having university degrees seem more aware of the risks in the industry and are more cautious when approached by scammers. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The survey also estimated that most Canadians are wary of cryptocurrency exchanges. Nearly 50% have &#8220;low trust&#8221; in such companies, 25% are &#8220;neutral,&#8221; whereas only 9% have &#8220;high trust.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In comparison, the confidence in local banks is much higher. Just 12% do not believe in domestic banking institutions, while 46% have &#8220;high trust.&#8221;</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_254566" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-254566" style="width: 784px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a style="font-weight: bold; background-color: transparent;" href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-254566" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png" alt="Canadians' Trust in Crypto Exchanges" width="784" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada.png 1157w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-300x153.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-1024x522.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-768x392.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Canada-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 784px) 100vw, 784px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-254566" class="wp-caption-text">Canadians&#8217; Trust in Crypto Exchanges, Source: DAIS</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The study suggested that roughly one in 10 Canadians have hopped on the crypto bandwagon by purchasing bitcoin, ether, or another digital asset. The majority of investors are men aged between 25 and 35. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Painful Lesson Learned by a Canadian Couple</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While some scams are not that devastating and result mainly in frustration among victims, others could be crucial. One example is an elderly man and his wife from Toronto who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-a-canadian-couple-lost-nearly-300000-in-a-crypto-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">parted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with $300,000 in such a scheme. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The couple wanted to invest their life savings and were approached by an unknown individual online. After presenting themself as &#8220;professional and knowledgeable&#8221; in the investment field, they advised the family to distribute funds on a dubious cryptocurrency platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">At first, everything seemed legit, and the duo saw their investment growing &#8220;significantly&#8221; in time. However, the problems started when they asked to withdraw some assets. The wrongdoer said they have to pay considerable fees to complete such transactions. Later, the couple saw that their entire investment had vanished, proving their fears that they had fallen victim to a crypto fraud. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Fortunately for them, the Toronto Police Service recovered a &#8220;significant portion of lost funds.&#8221; The identity of the criminal who drained the money, though, remained unclear, meaning they could be located in another country.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/every-third-canadian-hodler-lost-money-in-crypto-scams-study/" rel="nofollow">Every Third Canadian HODLer Lost Money in Crypto Scams (Study)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
