<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao Plan to Submit Motion to Dismiss CFTC Lawsuit</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-plan-submit-motion-dismiss-cftc-lawsuit.htm</link><description>Binance, the world's biggest crypto exchange, billionaire founder Changpeng Zhao – CZ – and the exchange’s former compliance chief Samuel Lim have intended to file two motions to dismiss a complaint from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). &lt;br /&gt;
Per a court filing on Monday, Binance and its parties' response to the CFTC lawsuit is due on July 27....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-plan-submit-motion-dismiss-cftc-lawsuit.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance and CEO Changpeng Zhao Plan to Submit Motion to Dismiss CFTC Lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-ceo-cz-plan-submit-motion-dismiss-cftc-lawsuit.htm</guid></item><item><title>Spanish Bank A&amp;G Launches Crypto Investment Fund Offering</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-bank-ag-launches-crypto-investment-fund-offering.htm</link><description>The leading Spanish private bank A&amp;G has launched a crypto investment fund offering, in a sign adoption is continuing to rise in the European nation. &lt;br /&gt;
Europa Press reported that A&amp;G will launch an investment fund product after registering the fund’s brochure with the regulatory National Securities Market Commission (CNMV). &lt;br /&gt;
The fund will be the first of its kind in Spain. &lt;br /&gt;
The bank said investors had expressed “great interest” in crypto investment....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-bank-ag-launches-crypto-investment-fund-offering.htm"&gt;Read More: Spanish Bank A&amp;G Launches Crypto Investment Fund Offering&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Spain</category><category>Bank</category><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/spanish-bank-ag-launches-crypto-investment-fund-offering.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120492/319780/adobestock-460500509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="481524"/></item><item><title>Top Lawmaker Suggests China and Russia’s CBDCs Are ‘Compatible’</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-lawmaker-suggests-china-russias-cbdcs-are-compatible.htm</link><description>A leading Russian lawmaker says China and Russia’s CBDCs may be “compatible” and could be used to make international payments between the nations. &lt;br /&gt;
Per RBC, the comments were made by Anatoly Aksakov, a member of the State Duma from Chuvashia’s Kanash constituency and the Chairman of the State Duma Committee on the Financial Markets. &lt;br /&gt;
Aksakov told attendees at a CBDC-related forum:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-lawmaker-suggests-china-russias-cbdcs-are-compatible.htm"&gt;Read More: Top Lawmaker Suggests China and Russia’s CBDCs Are ‘Compatible’&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-lawmaker-suggests-china-russias-cbdcs-are-compatible.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120407/319588/adobestock-90805572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="309241"/></item><item><title>Eco-Friendly Crypto Chimpzee Approaches $1 Million Raise for Saving Animals Using Blockchain – Next Big Thing?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-chimpzee-approaches-1-million-raise-for-saving-animals-using-blockchain-next-big-thing-1.htm</link><description>As the eco-friendly cryptocurrency project Chimpzee races towards raising $1 million in its presale, the blockchain-based platform is making progress on its charitable roadmap commitments to help save endangered animals and fight climate change....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-chimpzee-approaches-1-million-raise-for-saving-animals-using-blockchain-next-big-thing-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Eco-Friendly Crypto Chimpzee Approaches $1 Million Raise for Saving Animals Using Blockchain – Next Big Thing?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Chimpzee Presale</category><category>Eco Friendly Crypto Presale</category><category>Green Crypto</category><category>Eco Friendly Crypto</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Crypto Startup</category><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/eco-friendly-crypto-chimpzee-approaches-1-million-raise-for-saving-animals-using-blockchain-next-big-thing-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120525/319841/f1zojdbx0aamtx0.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="192481"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 24 July – Flex Coin, ApeCoin, The Graph</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-july-flex-coin-apecoin-graph.htm</link><description>Bitcoin is currently trading at $29,038 and has dipped by 3.47% so far today, likely due to market anticipation of the Federal Reserve's interest rate announcement on July 26. &lt;br /&gt;
The broader cryptocurrency market is also experiencing declines. Ether, the second-largest crypto, is down 2.39% and trading at $1,844. &lt;br /&gt;
Other major cryptos, such as Ripple and Binance Coin, have also fallen, dropping 4.89% and 1.98%, respectively....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-july-flex-coin-apecoin-graph.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 24 July – Flex Coin, ApeCoin, The Graph&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><category>Flex Coin</category><category>Evil Pepe Coin</category><category>ApeCoin</category><category>Burn kenny</category><category>The Graph</category><category>Flex Price</category><category>Ape price</category><category>GRT price</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Meme Coins 2023</category><category>Best Meme Coins</category><category>$KENNY</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-24-july-flex-coin-apecoin-graph.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120516/319821/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Keep BTC Below $30,000 – Where is BTC Heading Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-keep-btc-below-30000-where-btc-heading-next.htm</link><description>In the midst of ongoing market fluctuations, the outlook for Bitcoin (BTC) remains a topic of intense speculation.  &lt;br /&gt;
As bears exert pressure and keep the price below the critical $30,000 level, traders and investors are closely monitoring the next potential moves.  &lt;br /&gt;
With the market dynamics at play, the future trajectory of BTC remains uncertain. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-keep-btc-below-30000-where-btc-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Keep BTC Below $30,000 – Where is BTC Heading Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-keep-btc-below-30000-where-btc-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120515/319820/24.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="483751"/></item><item><title>$45 Million in Bitcoin Longs Wiped Out as Price Briefly Dips Below $29K – Here’s Where BTC Is Headed Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/45-million-bitcoin-longs-wiped-out-as-price-briefly-dips-below-29k-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm</link><description>Leveraged long positions in the bitcoin (BTC) futures market worth $41.5 million were liquidated on Monday, the second largest daily for long liquidations so far this month, as per CoinGlass.com. &lt;br /&gt;
The spike in long liquidations came as bitcoin fell nearly 3.5% to fresh one-month lows under $29,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/45-million-bitcoin-longs-wiped-out-as-price-briefly-dips-below-29k-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: $45 Million in Bitcoin Longs Wiped Out as Price Briefly Dips Below $29K – Here’s Where BTC Is Headed Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Liquidations</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 19:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/45-million-bitcoin-longs-wiped-out-as-price-briefly-dips-below-29k-heres-where-btc-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120513/319810/btc-18.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="84730"/></item><item><title>Hot Meme Coin Burn Kenny Price Pumps 1.5x at Launch, 3-Day 30% Supply Burn Starts and Alpha Calls Kick In</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hot-meme-coin-burn-kenny-price-pumps-15x-at-launch-3-day-30-supply-burn-starts-and-alpha-calls-kick-in.htm</link><description>South Park-inspired meme coin Burn Kenny saw its token price soar 1.5x on launch day before finding a near-term bottom, and is now consolidating as it gears up for more advances. &lt;br /&gt;
Presale buyers of the coin were sitting on initial gains of 60%, having bought the coin for $0.0001875 to see it touch $0.0002987 for its intraday high....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hot-meme-coin-burn-kenny-price-pumps-15x-at-launch-3-day-30-supply-burn-starts-and-alpha-calls-kick-in.htm"&gt;Read More: Hot Meme Coin Burn Kenny Price Pumps 1.5x at Launch, 3-Day 30% Supply Burn Starts and Alpha Calls Kick In&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hot-meme-coin-burn-kenny-price-pumps-15x-at-launch-3-day-30-supply-burn-starts-and-alpha-calls-kick-in.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120507/319806/kennyweth-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="329882"/></item><item><title>Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Slumps 12% to One-month Lows – Here’s Where Its Headed Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-slumps-12-to-one-month-lows-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm</link><description>Pepe Coin (PEPE), the third most valuable meme coin in the crypto space which exploded onto the scene earlier this year, has come under heavy selling pressure on Monday. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE was last trading at one-month lows in the $0.0000013s, having slumped over 12% in the last 24 hours, as per CoinGecko. &lt;br /&gt;
The meme coin is coming under pressure amid a broader downturn in the crypto market that has seen the likes of bitcoin (BTC) dip back to $29,000 and ether (ETH) dip under $1,850....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-slumps-12-to-one-month-lows-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Price Prediction as PEPE Slumps 12% to One-month Lows – Here’s Where Its Headed Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-price-prediction-as-pepe-slumps-12-to-one-month-lows-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120512/319808/pepe.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="304592"/></item><item><title>Nevada Woman Sentenced to 5 Years for Trying to Hire Hitman with Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-woman-sentenced-5-years-for-trying-hire-hitman-with-bitcoin.htm</link><description>A Nevada woman has been sentenced to five years in prison for attempting to hire a hitman using Bitcoin (BTC) to kill her ex-husband.  &lt;br /&gt;
Kristy Lynn Felkins, the 38-year-old resident of Fallon, Nevada, pleaded guilty in March to a murder-for-hire charge as part of a deal with federal prosecutors, according to a press release by the US Department of Justice (DOJ). &lt;br /&gt;
As per the court filings, Felkins struck the plea deal to avoid going to trial....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-woman-sentenced-5-years-for-trying-hire-hitman-with-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Nevada Woman Sentenced to 5 Years for Trying to Hire Hitman with Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Legal</category><category>Nevada</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nevada-woman-sentenced-5-years-for-trying-hire-hitman-with-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120504/319796/prison-gf0c52ad45-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="106030"/></item><item><title>FTX Lawsuit Reveals Alleged Plan to Use Island as Doomsday Bunker</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-lawsuit-reveals-alleged-plan-use-island-as-doomsday-bunker.htm</link><description>A newly filed lawsuit has alleged that the FTX Foundation planned to use the island nation of Nauru as a safe refuge for effective altruists for “some event where 50% - 99.99% of people die.” &lt;br /&gt;
According to the lawsuit, filed by FTX’s current management, the plan to use the island as a giant doomsday bunker was discussed between the exchange’s former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, his brother Gabriel Bankman-Fried, and another unnamed officer of the FTX Foundation....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-lawsuit-reveals-alleged-plan-use-island-as-doomsday-bunker.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Lawsuit Reveals Alleged Plan to Use Island as Doomsday Bunker&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-lawsuit-reveals-alleged-plan-use-island-as-doomsday-bunker.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120500/319790/doomsday.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="224707"/></item><item><title>Sam Altman's Eyeball-Scanning Crypto Project Worldcoin Launches Global Digital Identity Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-launches-global-digital-identity-platform.htm</link><description>On Monday, June 24, Worldcoin, a cryptocurrency and digital ID project led by OpenAI chief Sam Altman, launched to create a "privacy-preserving" global identity system after years of development.  &lt;br /&gt;
The goal is to build a reliable solution for distinguishing humans from AI online, facilitating global identity processes, and significantly increasing economic opportunities....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-launches-global-digital-identity-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Sam Altman's Eyeball-Scanning Crypto Project Worldcoin Launches Global Digital Identity Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Worldcoin</category><category>WLD</category><category>Sam Altman</category><category>chatGPT</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sam-altmans-eyeball-scanning-crypto-project-worldcoin-launches-global-digital-identity-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120506/319799/crypto-worldcoin-orb-2303.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="81477"/></item><item><title>TRM Labs: ISIS Allies Utilized Crypto to Raise Millions for Terrorism</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trm-labs-isis-allies-utilized-crypto-raise-millions-for-terrorism.htm</link><description>Middle Eastern terrorist groups associated with ISIS are increasingly turning to cryptocurrency to conduct their operations, according to a new report from TRM Labs. &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, the blockchain analytics and compliance firm wrote that it has found “mounting on-chain evidence” of the organization’s networks in Tajikistan, Indonesia, Pakistan, and Afghanistan digital assets – especially Tether stablecoins (USDT) on the Tron (TRX) network. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trm-labs-isis-allies-utilized-crypto-raise-millions-for-terrorism.htm"&gt;Read More: TRM Labs: ISIS Allies Utilized Crypto to Raise Millions for Terrorism&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/trm-labs-isis-allies-utilized-crypto-raise-millions-for-terrorism.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120503/319795/adobestock-97193316-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="47753"/></item><item><title>Elon Musk X Twitter Rebrand Superapp - Which Coins Will it Use For Payments?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-x-twitter-rebrand-superapp-which-coins-will-it-use-for-payments.htm</link><description>Twitter owner Elon Musk is in the process of implementing a long-awaited rebrand of the social media platform to a new super-app called “X”. &lt;br /&gt;
“X is the future state of unlimited interactivity – centered in audio, video, messaging, payments/banking – creating a global marketplace for ideas, goods, services, and opportunities,” Twitter CE Linda Yaccarino said on Sunday. &lt;br /&gt;
“Powered by AI, X will connect us all in ways we’re just beginning to imagine....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-x-twitter-rebrand-superapp-which-coins-will-it-use-for-payments.htm"&gt;Read More: Elon Musk X Twitter Rebrand Superapp - Which Coins Will it Use For Payments?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>X</category><category>Twitter</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>DOGE</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>BTC20</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>WSM</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/elon-musk-x-twitter-rebrand-superapp-which-coins-will-it-use-for-payments.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120502/319794/x.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="369568"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: WeChat &amp; Alipay Enable Foreigners to Pay at Chinese Retailers, ETH 699,816 Paid as Royalties to NFT Projects on Ethereum, Hana Bank &amp; Woori Bank 'Interested in Certificate of Deposit' Tokens</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-wechat-alipay-enable-foreigners-to-pay-at-chinese-retailers-eth-699816-paid-as-royalties-to-nft-projects-on-ethereum-hana-bank-woori-bank-interested-in-certificate-of-deposit-tokens.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-wechat-alipay-enable-foreigners-to-pay-at-chinese-retailers-eth-699816-paid-as-royalties-to-nft-projects-on-ethereum-hana-bank-woori-bank-interested-in-certificate-of-deposit-tokens.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: WeChat &amp; Alipay Enable Foreigners to Pay at Chinese Retailers, ETH 699,816 Paid as Royalties to NFT Projects on Ethereum, Hana Bank &amp; Woori Bank 'Interested in Certificate of Deposit' Tokens&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>China</category><category>WeChat</category><category>Alipay</category><category>Credit Card</category><category>Payments</category><category>NFT</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Nansen</category><category>Yuga Labs</category><category>Banking</category><category>Hana Bank</category><category>Woori Bank</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Web3</category><category>Polygon</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Dapp</category><category>Chainalysis</category><category>Bitfinex</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Legal</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-wechat-alipay-enable-foreigners-to-pay-at-chinese-retailers-eth-699816-paid-as-royalties-to-nft-projects-on-ethereum-hana-bank-woori-bank-interested-in-certificate-of-deposit-tokens.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120466/319751/adobestock-ralf-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="270829"/></item><item><title>Hackers Steal $3.2 Million Worth of Ethereum From Conic Finance DeFi Protocol</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/hackers-steal-32-million-worth-of-ethereum-from-conic-finance-defi-protocol.htm</link><description>The decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Conic Finance has lost more than $3.2 million worth of Ether (ETH) in two separate hacking incidents in recent days. &lt;br /&gt;
The first attack, which happened on Friday last week, was described by the Conic Finance team as a "re-entrancy attack” that exploited a vulnerability in Curve V2 pools, earning the attacker 1,700 ETH tokens. &lt;br /&gt;
“A fix to the affected contract is being deployed,” the team wrote....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/hackers-steal-32-million-worth-of-ethereum-from-conic-finance-defi-protocol.htm"&gt;Read More: Hackers Steal $3.2 Million Worth of Ethereum From Conic Finance DeFi Protocol&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>DeFi</category><category>hacking</category><category>Conic Finance</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/hackers-steal-32-million-worth-of-ethereum-from-conic-finance-defi-protocol.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120488/319776/hacker.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="79181"/></item><item><title>Fresh Speculation Arises as US Federal Reserve Debuts FedNow Instant Payments Service</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fresh-speculation-arises-as-us-federal-reserve-debuts-fednow-instant-payments-service.htm</link><description>The US Federal Reserve recently unveiled the FedNow Service system to facilitate instant payments; however, experts warn that the system might become a precursor to the infrastructure for a central bank digital currency (CBDC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fresh-speculation-arises-as-us-federal-reserve-debuts-fednow-instant-payments-service.htm"&gt;Read More: Fresh Speculation Arises as US Federal Reserve Debuts FedNow Instant Payments Service&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>Jerome Powell</category><category>U.S. Federal Reserve</category><category>FedNow</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fresh-speculation-arises-as-us-federal-reserve-debuts-fednow-instant-payments-service.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120481/319768/fednow-logo-rgb-gradiant-jpg-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="88010"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Chainlink? LINK Price Shoots Up 20% in 7 Days and BTC20 is the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-chainlink-link-price-shoots-up-20-7-days-btc20-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</link><description>In a strong bounce back since the pits of early June, Chainlink (LINK) has been on the climb pushing up +75% over the last month, but as price action rejects from the upper trendline, is it too late to buy Chainlink? &lt;br /&gt;
LINK has been caught in a predictable range characterized by +/- 80% chop for more than a year, as Chainlink holders continue to weather a gentle downside slide following the 2021 crypto bull run....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-chainlink-link-price-shoots-up-20-7-days-btc20-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Chainlink? LINK Price Shoots Up 20% in 7 Days and BTC20 is the Next Crypto to Explode – Here's Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-chainlink-link-price-shoots-up-20-7-days-btc20-next-crypto-explode-heres-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120470/319743/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="341647"/></item><item><title>The Effects Of The SEC v Ripple Ruling Remains Ambiguous: Bank of America Insists on Clarity</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/effects-of-sec-v-ripple-ruling-remains-ambiguous-bank-of-america-insists-clarity.htm</link><description>The aftermath of the court ruling in the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) case against Ripple continues to be debated along many lines as industry analysts mirror the judgment to seek regulatory directions. &lt;br /&gt;
In a new research report released on Friday, Bank of America (BAC) opined that a holistic look at the ruling shows that it did little or nothing to clarify the current situation. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/effects-of-sec-v-ripple-ruling-remains-ambiguous-bank-of-america-insists-clarity.htm"&gt;Read More: The Effects Of The SEC v Ripple Ruling Remains Ambiguous: Bank of America Insists on Clarity&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>SEC</category><category>XRP</category><category>Bank of America</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/effects-of-sec-v-ripple-ruling-remains-ambiguous-bank-of-america-insists-clarity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120482/319752/ripple-logo-media-library.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="124462"/></item><item><title>Futureverse Raises $54 Million to Fuel Expansion of Diversified Metaverse Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/futureverse-raises-54-million-fuel-expansion-of-diversified-metaverse-platform.htm</link><description>Futureverse, a crypto tech and gaming startup, has secured $54 million in Series A funding to support its expansion in the metaverse space.  &lt;br /&gt;
The funding round was led by venture capital firm 10T Holdings, with participation from Ripple Labs, the creator of XRP Ledger, the company said in a recent press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
Futureverse said it plans to use the funds for research and development purposes, as well as to advance its gaming-focused blockchain, called The Root Network. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/futureverse-raises-54-million-fuel-expansion-of-diversified-metaverse-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Futureverse Raises $54 Million to Fuel Expansion of Diversified Metaverse Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Futureverse</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>Metaverse Gaming</category><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/futureverse-raises-54-million-fuel-expansion-of-diversified-metaverse-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/120463/319712/woman-ga78d03725-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="337441"/></item></channel></rss>
