<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:56:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Soars to $30K as Crypto Markets add $25 Billion in Hours: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-to-30k-as-crypto-markets-add-25-billion-in-hours-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265293</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_trx_mw_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/btc_trx_mw_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin topped $30K but was unable to sustain. Shiba Inu (SHIB) soared almost 10% daily. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Well, there it is. After weeks of stagnation and prolonged inactivity, Bitcoin&#8217;s price has taken off and, fortunately for the bulls, in an upward direction.</p>
<p>The entire market has taken a positive swing as it&#8217;s all painted green today, so let&#8217;s have a look.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Challenges $30K Again</h2>
<p>Following weeks of considerable inactivity and a complete absence of any kind of volatility, the market has finally awakened from its slumber.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price took for the skies and is once again challenging the critical support &#8211; both psychological and technical &#8211; at $30K.</p>
<p>In fact, the cryptocurrency was able to briefly surpass this level, but, unfortunately, the buyers were unable to maintain the pressure, and bears managed to push the price back below it, as seen in the following chart:</p>
<figure id="attachment_265294" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265294" style="width: 1697px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265294" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0908231" width="1697" height="1244" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231.jpg 1697w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231-300x220.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231-1024x751.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231-768x563.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231-1536x1126.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/btc_price_chart_0908231-50x37.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1697px) 100vw, 1697px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265294" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that this also caused a spike in liquidations throughout the market, as short sellers got punished. The total number amounts to around $82 million for the past 24 hours, $65 million of which were short positions.</p>
<h2>Altcoin Market Also Green</h2>
<p>The majority of the altcoins are also painted green, charting somewhat considerable gains throughout the past 24 hours. This is true for all of the major altcoins by means of total market capitalization, as seen in this heatmap:</p>
<figure id="attachment_265295" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265295" style="width: 1662px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265295" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231" width="1662" height="1158" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231.jpg 1662w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231-300x209.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231-1024x713.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231-768x535.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231-1536x1070.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/cryptocurrency_market_heatmap_0908231-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1662px) 100vw, 1662px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265295" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>That said, one of the best performers altogether is Shiba Inu (SHIB). The meme coin exploded by a massive 9% throughout the day and is now extending its rally that started last week. It&#8217;s interesting to see if this will continue in the following days.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth noting that the market sentiment has improved, as somewhat expected. The interesting thing to watch now is if this is just a quick bounce to major resistance areas or if it will shape up into a more resilient and sustained bullish rally. Time will tell.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-soars-to-30k-as-crypto-markets-add-25-billion-in-hours-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Soars to $30K as Crypto Markets add $25 Billion in Hours: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>TRON and USDD Resilience Unveiled: Insights from Messari, Reflexivity, and JPMorgan&#8217;s Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tron-and-usdd-resilience-unveiled-insights-from-messari-reflexivity-and-jpmorgans-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265194</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1213_1691522972aCGCbBGxNN.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/1213_1691522972aCGCbBGxNN.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire] In-depth reports on the performance of TRON and USDD in 2023, published by renowned blockchain analytics firms Messari and Reflexivity have recently been published. Messari&#8217;s Analysis: TRON&#8217;s Q2 2023 Performance Messari&#8217;s report highlights TRON&#8217;s substantial growth across various performance metrics. Growth in Network Activity: The report [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Geneva, Switzerland, August 8th, 2023, Chainwire]</strong></p>
<p>In-depth reports on the performance of TRON and USDD in 2023, published by renowned blockchain analytics firms Messari and Reflexivity have recently been published.</p>
<h2>Messari&#8217;s Analysis: TRON&#8217;s Q2 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>Messari&#8217;s <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-tron-q2-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> highlights TRON&#8217;s substantial growth across various performance metrics.</p>
<p>Growth in Network Activity: The report observes TRON&#8217;s daily average active accounts, new accounts, and transactions surging by 14%, 13.4%, and 28.9% respectively, paralleling the rollout of BitTorrent Bridge and Stake 2.0 integrations.</p>
<p>Outshining Other L1’s: The report additionally underscores TRON&#8217;s exceptional performance in Q2, highlighting a 14.7% QoQ market cap increase, in stark contrast to a 23% average decline for other major Layer 1 blockchains.</p>
<p>Expanding the DeFi Sphere: The report applauds TRON&#8217;s efforts to continue to expand DeFi, with several applications and infrastructure providers integrating TRX liquid staking and the decentralized resource marketplace.</p>
<p>Enhancing Network Functionality: Finally, Messari notes TRON&#8217;s dedication to improving network functionality through the introduction of Stake 2.0 (TIP-467), GreatVoyage-V4.7.1.1 (Pittacus), and initiation of Great Voyage &#8211; V4.7.2 (Periander).</p>
<p>TRON employs a Delegated-Proof-of-Stake (DPoS) mechanism, with block validation being performed by a group of validators known as Super Representatives (SRs). Interestingly, the pool of SR candidates has grown from ~390 in Q1 to over 400 in Q2, illustrating the democratic nature of TRON’s ecosystem.</p>
<p>At the end of Q2, TRON nodes were dispersed across more than 75 global locations. This diverse geographical distribution of nodes is a promising step towards a more decentralized network, reducing vulnerabilities to localized disruptions and geopolitical risks.</p>
<h2>Messari&#8217;s Analysis: USDD&#8217;s Q2 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>Messari&#8217;s <a href="https://messari.io/report/state-of-usdd-q2-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> also paints a positive picture for USDD during Q2.</p>
<p>Peg Stability and Increased Backing: Messari notes that USDD traded close to its peg throughout Q2, allowing an accumulation of $13 million in backing within the PSM and a return to balance in the Curve pool.</p>
<p>Adoption Metrics: The report states that USDD&#8217;s adoption metrics remained stable with volumes and holders experiencing minimal fluctuations quarter over quarter.</p>
<p>Improved Backing: The backing for USDD strengthened in Q2, with BTC and TRX prices rising 7% and 15% respectively. Notably, with the inclusion of TRX assets, the stablecoin is now 171% collateralized, showcasing a robust backing that provides stability to its value.</p>
<p>Q2 saw the initiation of governance for USDD. The Messari report details how TRON DAO Reserve activated the first governance proposal, allowing TRX holders to vote, signifying the increasing democratization of USDD’s operations.</p>
<h2>Reflexivity&#8217;s Analysis: TRON&#8217;s H1 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>Reflexivity’s <a href="https://docsend.com/view/yhd38bv2c5usmyyf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> starts with an overview of TRON&#8217;s network design, highlighting the network&#8217;s high transaction speed, low cost, and hosting of the largest circulating supply of Tether (USDT). Utilizing a Delegated-Proof-of-Stake (DPoS) consensus mechanism, TRON maintains 27 Super Representatives elected by the community every six hours, from a pool of ~400 Super Representative Candidates, resulting in seamless network operations.</p>
<p>Network Performance: In the first half of 2023, TRON&#8217;s block height exceeded an impressive 52.5 million with 7,385 nodes across the network, marking a substantial 33.5% increase. Reflexivity underscores the significance of Stake 2.0, which was approved and deployed on TRON’s mainnet in early April, bringing about major enhancements in resource utilization and system stability.</p>
<p>Influence in the Stablecoin Ecosystem: TRON&#8217;s growing influence in the stablecoin ecosystem has been evident, absorbing over $5 billion in stablecoin inflows following the USDC depeg in March. Overall, the market capitalization of stablecoins on TRON saw a substantial 30.3% surge in the first half of the year, signifying its rising dominance.</p>
<h2>Reflexivity&#8217;s Analysis: USDD&#8217;s H1 2023 Performance</h2>
<p>Reflexivity’s <a href="https://docsend.com/view/vcje8ekhvgq5uuee" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> on USDD demonstrates the stablecoin&#8217;s resilience and adaptability during a tumultuous first half of the year.</p>
<p>Stability and PSM: By the end of H1, USDD’s collateral ratio stood at a robust 177.8%, marking a vital element of its stability. The Peg Stability Module (PSM), allowing 1:1 conversions from USDC to USDD, facilitated over $640 million in volume for Q2, playing a crucial role in maintaining the peg&#8217;s stability.</p>
<p>Partnerships and Integrations: The report emphasizes USDD’s continued expansion in its partnerships and integrations with other key players in the crypto industry. From major chains and protocols to wallets and external service providers, USDD has successfully extended its reach and functionality. Partnerships include Venus, BSC’s leading borrow-and-lend protocol, and Huobi.</p>
<h2>JPMorgan Acknowledges TRON&#8217;s Performance in Difficult DeFi Conditions</h2>
<p>A recent <a href="https://www.theblock.co/post/243063/jpmorgan-curve-finance-attack-comments" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">article</a> on The Block reflects on JPMorgan&#8217;s comments concerning the resilience of certain segments in the DeFi ecosystem following the Curve Finance attack. The analysts highlighted the positive performance of the TRON ecosystem. Despite the broader market turbulence, TRON has seen its total value locked (TVL) increase over the recent months.</p>
<p>&#8220;The rise in their TVL could be attributed to them offering faster and cheaper transactions to users, who otherwise were facing network congestion and higher transaction costs in Ethereum,&#8221; the analysts said. This statement further underscores the insights from the Messari and Reflexivity reports, reinforcing TRON&#8217;s performance amidst challenging market conditions.</p>
<p><strong>About TRON DAO</strong></p>
<p>TRON DAO is a community-governed DAO dedicated to accelerating the decentralization of the internet via blockchain technology and dApps.</p>
<p>Founded in September 2017 by H.E. Justin Sun, the TRON network has continued to deliver impressive achievements since MainNet launch in May 2018. July 2018 also marked the ecosystem integration of BitTorrent, a pioneer in decentralized Web3 services boasting over 100 million monthly active users. The TRON network has gained incredible traction in recent years. As of August 2023, it has over 177.44 million total user accounts on the blockchain, more than 6.22 billion total transactions, and over $13.27 billion in total value locked (TVL), as reported on TRONSCAN.</p>
<p>In addition, TRON hosts the largest circulating supply of USD Tether (USDT) stablecoin across the globe, overtaking USDT on Ethereum since April 2021. The TRON network completed full decentralization in December 2021 and is now a community-governed DAO. Most recently in October 2022, TRON was designated as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, which marks the first time a major public blockchain partnered with a sovereign nation to develop its national blockchain infrastructure. On top of the government’s endorsement to issue Dominica Coin (“DMC”), a blockchain-based fan token to help promote Dominica’s global fanfare, seven existing TRON-based tokens &#8211; TRX, BTT, NFT, JST, USDD, USDT, TUSD, have been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country.</p>
<p><a href="https://tron.network/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">TRONNetwork</a> |<a href="https://trondao.org/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> TRONDAO</a> |<a href="https://twitter.com/TRONDAO" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> Twitter</a> |<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5OPOGRq02iK-0T9sKse_kA" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"> YouTube</a></p>
<p><strong>About USDD</strong></p>
<p>USDD is an over-collateralized decentralized stablecoin launched collaboratively by the TRON DAO Reserve and top-tier mainstream blockchain institutions. The USDD protocol runs on the TRON network, is connected to Ethereum and BNB Chain through the <a href="https://bttc.bittorrent.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">BTTC</a> cross-chain protocol, and will be accessible across more blockchains in the future. USDD is pegged to the US Dollar through TRX under a Linked Exchange Rate System (LERS) and maintains its price stability under the guidance of the TRON DAO Reserve. It enables access to a stable and decentralized digital dollar system that, in turn, assures financial liberty for everyone. With the designation of TRON as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, USDD has been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country, effective on October 7th 2022.</p>
<p><a href="https://usdd.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/usddio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/usddio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-and-usdd-resilience-unveiled-insights-from-messari-reflexivity-and-jpmorgans-analysis/" rel="nofollow">TRON and USDD Resilience Unveiled: Insights from Messari, Reflexivity, and JPMorgan&#8217;s Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Federal Court Case Uses Blockchain Tech to Fight Russian and North Korean Hackers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/federal-court-case-uses-blockchain-tech-to-fight-russian-and-north-korean-hackers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265201</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/clip3_1691522086rcqbgTDMEM.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/clip3_1691522086rcqbgTDMEM.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Chicago, Illinois, August 8th, 2023] For years, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) have been the favored methods of payment for cybercriminals. Ransomware crime rings rely almost exclusively on Bitcoin payments to extract vast sums from major institutions, including hospitals and providers of critical infrastructure. But, in a groundbreaking move, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Chicago, Illinois, August 8th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>For years, cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) have been the favored methods of payment for cybercriminals. Ransomware crime rings rely almost exclusively on Bitcoin payments to extract vast sums from major institutions, including hospitals and providers of critical infrastructure. But, in a groundbreaking move, a <a href="https://loevy-content-uploads.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/2023/08/28.Final-Judgment-Order.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">federal court case</a> in Chicago has turned the tables on cybercriminals by using inventive technology to digitally lock the criminals out of their blockchain accounts.</p>
<p>The case was brought against Russian and North Korean hackers who are under sanctions by the United States Treasury Department.</p>
<blockquote><p>Mike Kanovitz, CEO of <a href="https://jurat.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Jurat Blockchains</a>, the firm behind the technology deployed in the case, remarked, “It is encouraging to witness this invention in action, fighting criminals who misuse blockchains and give cryptocurrency a bad name.” Kanovitz explained that “Jurat technology provides the base layer for legal enforcement on blockchains by working in conjunction with official courts. It can help government officials prevent crime and lets cryptocurrency users access courts if they have had their cryptocurrency stolen, been defrauded, or lost their private keys.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The court’s order applies to 16 individuals and international criminal organizations sanctioned under Executive Orders of the President of the United States. Among those targeted was Hydra Market, the focus of “a collaborative initiative joined by the U.S. Department of Justice, Federal Bureau of Investigations, Drug Enforcement Administration, Internal Revenue Service Criminal Investigation, and Homeland Security Investigations,” according to a <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0701" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">U.S. Treasury Department press release</a>.  Another major target named in the lawsuit is the <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0768" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Lazarus Group</a>, which engaged in “malicious cyber activities and money-laundering of stolen virtual currency” on behalf of the Democratic People’s Republic of Korea. The state-sponsored hackers committed “the largest virtual currency heist to date, worth almost $620 million, from a blockchain project linked to the online game Axie Infinity.”</p>
<p>Using the first-of-its-kind judicial injunction, the federal court has locked all accounts belonging to the 16 criminals that contain the cryptocurrency $JTC. The coin emerged following an update to Bitcoin’s software, resulting in a “fork” that left two blockchains, BTC and JTC, hosting the same accounts. Victims who previously lost $BTC can claim their $JTC using the Jurat Wallet app or by filing an action to enforce their legal rights in court. Industry estimates of cryptocurrency crimes range above $20 billion annually.</p>
<p>The case was handled by Jon Loevy, of Loevy &amp; Loevy Attorneys at Law in Chicago.</p>
<p><strong>About Jurat Blockchains</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://jurat.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Jurat Blockchains</a> provides Web3 legal tech and reg tech for blockchains, smart contracts, and DAOs. It launched its first public blockchain, JTC, in 2022 and has additional layer 1 projects and dispute resolution system dApps in the pipeline. For further information about Jurat, find us at <a href="https://jurat.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">www.jurat.io</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-court-case-uses-blockchain-tech-to-fight-russian-and-north-korean-hackers/" rel="nofollow">Federal Court Case Uses Blockchain Tech to Fight Russian and North Korean Hackers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Explodes but How High it Can Go? 3 Critical Things to Watch Today (PEPE Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-explodes-but-how-high-it-can-go-3-critical-things-to-watch-today-pepe-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265230</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE has turned bullish these past two days and may signal the start of a significant rally. Key Support levels: $0.00000105 Key Resistance levels: $0.00000123 1. Breakout from the Wedge PEPE managed to end its correction and broke above the falling wedge. This is a bullish signal. If the resistance at $0.0000012 turns into support, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">PEPE has turned bullish these past two days and may signal the start of a significant rally.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.00000105</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.00000123</strong></p>
<h2>1. Breakout from the Wedge</h2>
<p>PEPE managed to end its correction and broke above the falling wedge. This is a bullish signal. If the resistance at $0.0000012 turns into support, then this rally will likely become significant.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265240" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265240" style="width: 1818px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265240" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44.png" alt="PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44" width="1818" height="836" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44.png 1818w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44-300x138.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44-1024x471.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44-768x353.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44-1536x706.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-19-44-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1818px) 100vw, 1818px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265240" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. Buyers Return</h2>
<p>With the breakout confirmed, the volume has been in green these past two days as buyers rushed to get exposure. With each subsequent resistance that is broken, the buying pressure could accelerate.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265239" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265239" style="width: 1819px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265239" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43.png" alt="PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43" width="1819" height="835" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43.png 1819w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43-300x138.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43-1024x470.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43-768x353.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43-1536x705.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-20-43-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1819px) 100vw, 1819px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265239" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>3. Imminent Bullish Cross on MACD</h2>
<p>The daily MACD is also about to give a bullish signal as its moving averages are about to cross to the positive side if bulls maintain the pressure. If that happens, then PEPE could enter a sustained rally.</p>
<figure id="attachment_265238" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265238" style="width: 1819px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265238" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1.png" alt="PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50" width="1819" height="836" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1.png 1819w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1-300x138.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1-1024x471.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1-768x353.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1-1536x706.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/PEPEUSDT_2023-08-09_14-21-50-1-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1819px) 100vw, 1819px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265238" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for PEPE is bullish.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for PEPE Price</h2>
<p>It seems that PEPE is likely to test the key resistance levels and potentially even move higher in the coming days. If buyers don&#8217;t lose strength, then this memecoin could easily reach $0.00000136 next.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-explodes-but-how-high-it-can-go-3-critical-things-to-watch-today-pepe-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Explodes but How High it Can Go? 3 Critical Things to Watch Today (PEPE Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BiFinance: Paving the Way for Global Cryptocurrency Adoption</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bifinance-paving-the-way-for-global-cryptocurrency-adoption/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265255</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency industry has changed by leaps and bounds throughout the past couple of years. This is partly due to the fact that the market went through a parabolic rally that sent crypto into the mainstream and put it in front of the eyes of anyone who hadn’t heard about it before. This includes institutions. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry has changed by leaps and bounds throughout the past couple of years.</p>
<p>This is partly due to the fact that the market went through a parabolic rally that sent crypto into the mainstream and put it in front of the eyes of anyone who hadn’t heard about it before.</p>
<p>This includes institutions. Many are already involved, but the fact of the matter is that most of them are merely dipping their toes in the industry.</p>
<p>The reasons for that are multifold, but undoubtedly a contributing factor is the lack of precise infrastructure that’s both convenient and safe.</p>
<p>It’s also true that many retail traders are experiencing issues with finding a solution that is a one-stop shop and covers all of their crypto requirements.</p>
<p>This is where <a href="https://www.bifinance.com/home" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">BiFinance</a> steps into the picture.</p>
<h2>What is BiFinance?</h2>
<p>BiFinance puts forward an institutional-grade digital asset trading platform that unravels a multitude of high-quality digital asset targets and innovative investments while also focusing on research audit standards.</p>
<p>The company is operated by a team of very experienced professionals who’ve tried and tested the waters in both traditional finance and crypto for many years. This has put them in a leading position in terms of technology, abundant product lines, appropriate security risk control integrations, and maintenance systems.</p>
<p>In general, the team is laser-focused on its mission, which is to solve the problem of solving difficulties for small as well as medium-sized enterprises.</p>
<p>The platform offers a myriad of products but perhaps etched into the spotlight are its spot and derivatives trading offerings.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265262" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover.jpg" alt="bifinance_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bifinance_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h3>Spot Crypto Trading</h3>
<p>The exchange offers spot cryptocurrency transactions for its users globally. They can buy various coins with a simple click and sell them just as easily.</p>
<p>Mainstream cryptocurrencies such as BTC and ETH are supported, as well as a range of others. The team at BiFinance puts a lot of effort into discovering new opportunities while also retaining its high level of integrity.</p>
<h3>Derivatives Crypto Trading</h3>
<p>Traders are able to develop and expand the depth of their derivatives trading with BiFinance’s products. The choices are multiple and versatile.</p>
<p>It’s worth noting that the exchange is also conducting compliance development when it comes to its derivatives trading. This includes perpetual contracts and futures. Moreover, the platform also plans to launch stable income products, which include deposits, interest-bearing instruments, and others.</p>
<p>That’s far from the only thing that the platform is offering, though. Users can also expect:</p>
<ul>
<li>Launchpad</li>
<li>DeFi Asset management</li>
<li>BiFinance earn</li>
</ul>
<h2>The Exciting Road Ahead</h2>
<p>Despite having developed a robust set of products already, the team at BiFinance is nowhere near being done.</p>
<p>Just recently, in April, BiFinance obtained permission for the US MSB license and is now officially holding this license. The registration serial number is 31000241154611. The company is also registered as a monetary service business entity in the US Bank of Constitution (BSA) 31CFR1022.380 (A)-(F).</p>
<p>In addition, the team participated in the Wikiexpo event held in Singapore and conducted multiple roadshows in the city-state.</p>
<p>In June, BiFinance officially submitted its application for a VASP license in Hong Kong.</p>
<p>It’s also worth noting that the company will start its Series B financing in August. Keep in mind that BiFinance was successful in holding a Series A, raising a total of $7.5 million.</p>
<p>Last but not least, the exchange will also be launching its very own native token called BFT. The launch is planned for the third quarter of this year, so stay tuned.</p>
<p>To find out more about BiFinance and start trading, please take a look at the <a href="https://www.bifinance.com/home" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">official website</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bifinance-paving-the-way-for-global-cryptocurrency-adoption/" rel="nofollow">BiFinance: Paving the Way for Global Cryptocurrency Adoption</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitstamp Delists SOL, MATIC and More: Here&#8217;s When</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitstamp-delisting-major-tokens-like-sol-matic-important-deadline/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitstamp]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265241</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bitstamp_stop_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/bitstamp_stop_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitstamp has made the decision to halt trading for a number of cryptocurrencies, including SOL, SAND, and MATIC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US-based users of the Bitstamp crypto exchange will no longer be able to make trades on several high-profile tokens, including Solana (SOL), Polygon (MATIC), and NEAR.</p>
<ul>
<li>In an unexpected <a href="https://blog.bitstamp.net/post/important-update-halt-of-axs-chz-ex-ny-mana-matic-near-sand-and-sol/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announcement</a> on its official blog, Bitstamp said it would suspend trading for seven cryptocurrencies for its US customers starting August 29, 2023.</li>
<li>In addition to major tokens like SOL, MATIC, and NEAR, the suspension will also affect a cluster of metaverse gaming and entertainment tokens, including Axie Infinity (AXS), Decentraland (MANA), Sandbox (SAND), and Chiliz (CHZ).</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Update for our US users <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f4e2.png" alt="📢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Starting August 29: AXS, CHZ, MANA, MATIC, NEAR, SAND, and SOL trading will be halted after evaluating recent market developments.</p>
<p>Execute any open trades. Holding and withdrawing tokens afterwards will be unaffected.</p>
<p>More info:…</p>
<p>— Bitstamp (@Bitstamp) <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitstamp/status/1688846041129328641?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 8, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>Bitstamp explained its decision was influenced by “recent developments” in the US regulatory environment, although it did not go into specifics.</li>
<li>The suspension means that from August 29, the exchange will disable any new orders involving the seven tokens and their trading pairs and cancel all existing ones. However, Bitstamp clarified that users can still hold and withdraw the tokens.</li>
<li>The company also asked its US users to carry out any pending trades involving the affected cryptocurrencies before the August 29 deadline, following which it will not permit any more transactions on them.</li>
<li>The clamping down on SOL and the other tokens comes in the wake of reports that Bitstamp is actively looking for strategic investors to help in its expansion plans. In a recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-08-07/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-fundraising-talks-seeks-expansion" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with Bloomberg, Bitstamp CEO Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux stated the company had initiated fundraising plans in June aided by Galaxy Digital.</li>
<li>Graftieaux explained that Bitstamp, which sold a minority stake to XRP earlier in the year, intended to use funds it would raise to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitstamp-secures-an-operational-license-in-france/" data-wpel-link="internal">grow</a> its operations, including launching derivatives trading in Europe.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitstamp-delisting-major-tokens-like-sol-matic-important-deadline/" rel="nofollow">Bitstamp Delists SOL, MATIC and More: Here&#8217;s When</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Price Skyrockets 8%: This Whale Bought Almost 1 Trillion PEPE Coin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-price-skyrockets-8-this-whale-bought-almost-1-trillion-pepe-coin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265228</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/pepe_rocket_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/pepe_rocket_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE Coin skyrockets by over 8% in the past 24 hours. Could this whale be the reason?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The PEPE meme coin witnessed significant activity on August 9, with a major crypto investor spending 1 million USDC to purchase 807 billion tokens.</p>
<ul>
<li>The PEPE coin price has had a rough seven days, see-sawing between a high of $0.00000128 and a low of $0.00000108.</li>
<li>But after <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-plunges-5-daily-bitcoin-might-be-preparing-for-a-huge-move-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">shedding</a> off 5% from its price on August 8, Pepe took a turn, rising rapidly from $0.00000113 to $0.00000122. During this rise, the unnamed whale took a punt and splashed 1 million USDC ($1,000,300) on 807 billion PEPE coins, each priced at around $0.000001239.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_265229" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-265229" style="width: 624px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-265229" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-2.png" alt="Picture1" width="624" height="317" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-2.png 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-2-300x152.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-2-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-265229" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Lookonchain via Debank</figcaption></figure>
<p>Source: Lookonchain via Debank.com</p>
<ul>
<li>With PEPE currently trading at $0.00000120, an 8.4% jump from the previous 24 hours, the whale’s meme coin stash is valued at approximately $968,000.</li>
<li>Ever since PEPE hit its all-time high of $0.0000044 on May 5, the coin has rarely gone <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-price-down-over-10-but-new-cowabunga-meme-coin-is-pumping/" data-wpel-link="internal">above</a> the $0.000002 level, but data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">CoinGecko</a> shows that its trading volume has increased significantly in the last three days, rising from $53 million on August 7 to $132.1 million on August 9.</li>
<li>It reflects the growing interest in the meme coin as bulls troop back into the market.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-price-skyrockets-8-this-whale-bought-almost-1-trillion-pepe-coin/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Price Skyrockets 8%: This Whale Bought Almost 1 Trillion PEPE Coin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blockchain.com Obtains Regulatory Approval in Singapore</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264962</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new license enables Blockchain.com to provide digital token payment services to institutional and accredited investors.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading cryptocurrency exchange Blockchain.com received a payment institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This marks the company&#8217;s second license in the city-state after the in-principle approval secured in September 2022.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-265097" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg" alt="blockchain_com_singapore_license" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/blockchain_com_singapore_license-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Blockchain.com </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/blockchaincom-receives-major-payment-institution-license-from-monetary-authority-of-singapore-301895088.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that its recently-obtained authorization in Singapore follows the entity&#8217;s strategy to comply with regulators in every region where it conducts business.</span></li>
<li>The team behind the exchange said the Asian city-state has emerged as a &#8220;profitable trading hub&#8221; focused on global institutional and accredited investor clients.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Over 90 percent of the group&#8217;s institutional and accredited investors business is in Singapore,&#8221; Rakesh Madamanchi &#8211; Blockchain.com&#8217;s head of institutional compliance and Singapore operations revealed. </span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another reason why the marketplace views Singapore as a key area is because it serves as its Southeast Asia headquarters. Commenting on the regulatory approval was also CEO Peter Smith:</span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are thrilled to receive this license that will allow Blockchain.com to bring our industry-leading products and services to Singapore, we commend the Monetary Authority of Singapore on its transparent regulatory process that prioritizes crypto industry oversight while allowing innovation to thrive.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Multiple cryptocurrency exchanges and firms have recently focused on Singapore due to the city-state&#8217;s comprehensive regulations. </span></li>
<li><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-eyes-uae-expansion-amid-us-uncertainty-crypto-com-gets-mpi-license-in-singapore/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto.com</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Circle, Paxos, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-receives-in-principle-singapore-payments-license-us-crypto-exodus-continues/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ripple</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> are some organizations that have secured authorization there over the past several months. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockchain-com-obtains-regulatory-approval-in-singapore/" rel="nofollow">Blockchain.com Obtains Regulatory Approval in Singapore</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody&#8217;s Mulls Downgrades For Top U.S. Banks Citing Funding Risks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/moodys-mulls-downgrades-for-top-u-s-banks-citing-funding-risks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=265195</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/09/Banks-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The agency says top banks are facing weaker profits and reduced availability of CRE credit.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Big Three credit rating agency Moody’s has downgraded numerous regional banks in the United States due to weak earnings last quarter and sizable unrealized losses, according to the firm’s Monday note.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, banking giants including Bank of New York Mellon (BK.N), US Bancorp (USB.N), State Street (STT.N) and Truist Financial (TFC.N) have been placed on review for potential downgrades.</p>
<h2>Stress in the Banking Sector</h2>
<p>As reported by <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/moodys-downgrades-10-us-banks-warns-possible-cuts-others-2023-08-08/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Reuters</a></em> on Tuesday, Moody’s note highlighted “profitability pressures” at many banks that are expected to hinder their ability to generate further capital. Banks downgraded by the firm include M&amp;T Bank (MTB.N), Pinnacle Financial Partners (PNFP.O), Prosperity Bank, and BOK Financial Corp (BOKF.O).</p>
<p>Meanwhile, high exposure to commercial real estate (CRE) poses a significant risk due to the nation’s high-interest rate environment. Last month, the Federal Reserve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-loses-30k-as-us-federal-reserve-hikes-interest-rates-by-another-25bps-this-weeks-crypto-recap/" data-wpel-link="internal">rose</a> its benchmark rate to between 5.25% and 5.5% – its highest level since January 2001.</p>
<p>&#8220;This comes as a mild U.S. recession is on the horizon for early 2024 and asset quality looks set to decline, with particular risks in some banks’ commercial real estate portfolios,” the note added.</p>
<p>According to Federal Reserve survey data from last week, U.S. banks reported both weaker loan demand and tighter credit standards in Q2.</p>
<p>The U.S. banking sector has already been plagued by a crisis of confidence this year, with Silvergate Bank, Signature Bank, and Silicon Valley Bank collectively collapsing in March. The latter fell as customers rushed for the exits when the bank reported that it had realized a $1.8 billion loss on its long-term bond portfolio.</p>
<p>Indeed, Moody’s warned that U.S. banks sitting on high unrealized losses face similar risks related to a crisis of confidence, especially given today’s high-interest rate environment.</p>
<h2>Government Gets Downgraded</h2>
<p>High rates are part of what has prompted Fitch Ratings – another top-rated agency – to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fitch-us-ratings-downgrade-is-fine-for-bitcoin-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">downgrade</a> the U.S. government&#8217;s credit to AA+ as of last month, away from the upper echelon shared with international competitors.</p>
<p>Given the country’s high debt-to-GDP ratio, the agency noted that the country would start struggling to manage growing interest payments as it rolled over existing debt at a higher borrowing rate.</p>
<p>The government’s annual interest payments have skyrocketed since last year and now approach $1 trillion. Mike Novogratz, CEO of Galaxy Digital, has told followers to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/novogratz-advises-investors-to-buy-bitcoin-as-federal-interest-payments-skyrocket/" data-wpel-link="internal">buy Bitcoin</a> in response.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/moodys-mulls-downgrades-for-top-u-s-banks-citing-funding-risks/" rel="nofollow">Moody&#8217;s Mulls Downgrades For Top U.S. Banks Citing Funding Risks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circle&#8217;s Jeremy Allaire Estimates Majority of USDC Adoption Originates Beyond US Borders</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/circles-jeremy-allaire-estimates-majority-of-usdc-adoption-originates-beyond-us-borders/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=264980</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Circle_Banks.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Circle is directing its attention to international markets where there is a rising trend in adoption.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stablecoin issuer Circle is a US-based company, and 70% of its USDC adoption originates from non-US regions.</p>
<p>According to the estimations of Circle CEO Jeremy Allaire, some of the fastest growing areas are emerging and developing markets, which are not in the country that has been facing severe regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<h2>Not Fixated on US</h2>
<p>Allaire took to X (formerly Twitter) to <a href="https://twitter.com/jerallaire/status/1688672056898928640" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reveal</a> observing &#8220;strong progress&#8221; across Asia, LATAM, and Africa, highlighting the demand for &#8220;safe, transparent digital dollars.&#8221;</p>
<p>Circle isn&#8217;t the only company that has demonstrated not being particularly fixated on the US ecosystem. In fact, Tether&#8217;s chief technology officer, Paolo Ardoino, also echoed a similar sentiment when he earlier revealed the stablecoin company&#8217;s aim to position USDT as &#8220;a safe tool for emerging markets and developing countries, a life-life for many communities that are suffering from a heavy devaluation of their national currencies.&#8221;</p>
<p>Allaire&#8217;s remarks coincide with a reduction in the supply of the USDC stablecoin since the start of 2023 as a result of diminishing demand and a rise in redemptions. With redemptions surpassing issuance, concerns over USDC&#8217;s liquidity surfaced again. The Circle CEO also <a href="https://twitter.com/jerallaire/status/1688667728737959937" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">addressed</a> the situation and confirmed issuing $5 billion worth of USDC and redeeming $6.6 billion worth of USDC.</p>
<p>Doubling down on Circle&#8217;s expansion, Allaire revealed that the stablecoin issuer company was actively collaborating with several reputable financial institutions across key global regions.</p>
<h2>Shift in Stablecoin Landscape</h2>
<p>USDC has had a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-usdc-outflows-surpassed-10b-since-svb-collapse-tether-dominance-rises/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">rocky start</a> shedding over 43% since the beginning of the year. The stablecoin, however, held up its market cap above $26 billion over the past few weeks following a brief slump below the level. This is despite Binance selling a significant chunk of the token, as recently revealed by Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong.</p>
<p>The unexpected <a href="https://protos.com/brian-armstrong-revealed-binance-sold-all-its-usdc-in-coinbase-earnings-call/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">comment</a> by the exec came during Coinbase&#8217;s second-quarter earnings, during which he said,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Binance actually moved some of their funds from USDC into another stablecoin. I think the data we have in the last six or seven weeks, I believe, that the USDC market cap is up net of that. And so that’s an important data point.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>A lookout for a different stablecoin follows the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-regulator-reportedly-stops-paxos-from-issuing-busd-but-is-it-just-fud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">order</a> to stop issuing the dollar-pegged BUSD stablecoin. Binance shifted its focus to TrueUSD (TUSD) as a solution for its stablecoin requirements. But TUSD lost its peg, and its issuance ceased by June 10th.</p>
<p>The rise of FDUSD, on the other hand, caught the attention of Tether&#8217;s Ardoino, who observed that USDT faced downward pressure, and its primary competitor, USDC, which is experienced significant redemptions instead of gaining from such a situation.</p>
<p>The change in the stablecoin landscape is further validated by this week&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-launches-usd-stablecoin-for-payments-and-transfers/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launch</a> of PYUSD by global payments giant PayPal.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circles-jeremy-allaire-estimates-majority-of-usdc-adoption-originates-beyond-us-borders/" rel="nofollow">Circle&#8217;s Jeremy Allaire Estimates Majority of USDC Adoption Originates Beyond US Borders</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
