<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 20:08:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>GameStop Terminates its Crypto Wallet Program Citing &#8216;Regulatory Uncertainty&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/gamestop-terminates-its-crypto-wallet-program-citing-regulatory-uncertainty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263845</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/gamestop_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/gamestop_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The company advised customers to gain access to their secret passphrase by October 1, 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American gaming merchandise retailer &#8211; GameStop &#8211; announced it will remove its cryptocurrency wallets from the market as of November 1, 2023. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity launched those features in the spring of last year, enabling users to manage digital assets and non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The End of the Offering</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">GameStop </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://wallet.gamestop.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">disclosed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> on its official website that it will remove its iOS and Chrome Extension wallets as of the beginning of November due to &#8220;the regulatory uncertainty of the crypto space.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It warned that all clients must have access to their secret passphrase by October 1 to be able to &#8220;recover their account in any compatible wallet.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">GameStop </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gamestop-rolls-out-self-custodial-wallet-for-cryptocurrencies-and-nfts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">rolled out</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its self-custodial wallet in May last year, giving customers a chance to send, receive, store, and use crypto assets and NFTs across decentralized applications without leaving their web browsers. The firm doubled down on the field a few months later when it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gamestop-launches-long-awaited-nft-marketplace/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">introduced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an NFT marketplace built on the Ethereum layer 2 network Loopring L2.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that the interest in digital collectibles has shrunk over the past few years. Despite the emergence of new marketplaces, like Blur, which quickly made their way to the top, the current NFT trading volume is far from the peaks registered in 2021 and 2022. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">GameStop&#8217;s Connection With FTX</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides offering digital asset wallets and launching an NFT trading platform, the gaming giant teamed up with the American subsidiary of the now-bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX in September 2022. As part of the deal, GameStop </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gamestop-shakes-hands-with-ftx-us-after-announcing-q2-results/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to introduce its clients to the community of FTX.US and offer gift cards from the marketplace in select stores across the States.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, the company terminated the partnership shortly after the exchange filed for bankruptcy protection, assuring that users will receive full refunds.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;GameStop is winding down its relationship and pilot gift card marketing partnership with FTX US and will be providing full refunds to impacted customers. Please reach out to customer service if you purchased a gift card,&#8221; it </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/GameStop/status/1591177707123081232" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tweeted </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">in November 2022.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Esports giant &#8211; TSM &#8211; and the video game developer &#8211; Riot Games &#8211; also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/league-of-legends-developer-wants-to-cut-all-ties-with-ftx-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">cut ties</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the collapsed platform in the following months. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/gamestop-terminates-its-crypto-wallet-program-citing-regulatory-uncertainty/" rel="nofollow">GameStop Terminates its Crypto Wallet Program Citing &#8216;Regulatory Uncertainty&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals Team Launches Non-Profit to Support Bitcoin NFT Developers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-non-profit-to-support-bitcoin-nft-developers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 21:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ordinals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263829</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/NFT_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ordinals creator Casey Rodarmor will be one of the four board members of the new initiative. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Ordinals protocol team announced the launch of a non-profit organization, dubbed &#8216;Open Ordinals Institute,&#8217; to fund its open-source development.</p>
<p>The Open Ordinals Institute is a registered 501(c)(3) California-based public charity that will collect donations in Bitcoin to back the protocol’s development by funding its core group of developers.</p>
<p>The focus will also be on the creation of user-friendly tools to enable less technically proficient users to create Bitcoin Digital Artifacts with ease.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the official <a href="https://ordinals.org/about/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog</a> post, the initiative also seeks to fund designers, reviewers, researchers, educators, and other contributors who play a vital role in improving and promoting the technology.</li>
<li>Previously, Casey Rodarmor, who is responsible for introducing inscriptions on Bitcoin’s mainnet for the first time, used to fund the project.</li>
<li>In addition to Rodarmor, Open Ordinals will consist of four team members serving the board, including the project’s pseudonymous lead maintainer Raph, Bitcoin-focused podcast host Erin Redwing, an anonymous Ordinals developer known as Ordinally.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Open Ordinals Institute is committed to supporting developers involved in this protocol, as well as those creating user-friendly tools that facilitate less technically proficient users to create Bitcoin Digital Artifacts.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The recently launched Ordinals.org site will be used to accept donations to the institute via two Bitcoin wallet addresses.</li>
<li>This year, the Ordinals protocol gained significant traction leaving the Bitcoin community divided over its viability.</li>
<li>The initial hype may have faded, but Bitcoin <a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">boasts</a> more than 21 million Ordinals inscriptions at writing time, representing a 40% <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vitalik-buterin-lauds-bitcoin-ordinals-believes-brc-20-standard-could-revive-stagnancy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">increase</a> in less than a month.</li>
<li>The trading volume of Bitcoin Ordinals surged by 2,834% from Q1 to Q2 of 2023, hitting $210.7 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-team-launches-non-profit-to-support-bitcoin-nft-developers/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Ordinals Team Launches Non-Profit to Support Bitcoin NFT Developers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bloomberg Boosts Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval Odds To 65%: Here&#8217;s Why</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bloomberg-boosts-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval-odds-to-65-heres-why/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263987</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/bitcoinetf_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/bitcoinetf_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Grayscale’s lawsuit against the SEC remains the most likely route to approval, analysts say.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bloomberg ETF analysts have boosted their approval odds for a U.S. Bitcoin (BTC) spot ETF from 50% to 65%, in light of “recent events and new information.”</p>
<p>The analysts believe it is most likely that the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) will simultaneously approve all recent applications for the product after Grayscale defeats the agency in federal court.</p>
<h2>The ETF Approval Thesis</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff/status/1686707919696568320" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">published</a> by analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balcunas to Bloomberg Terminal, a flurry of new developments make the approval seem close.</p>
<p>These include SEC chairman Gary Gensler’s “downplaying” of his role at the agency, and the regulator’s “<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wanted-coinbase-to-delist-all-crypto-assets-except-bitcoin-before-lawsuit-ft/" data-wpel-link="internal">tacit approval</a>” of Coinbase as a Bitcoin exchange. Coinbase has been selected by an array of new applicants – including BlackRock and Fidelity – to form a surveillance-sharing agreement with relevant exchanges to help meet the SEC’s requirements for detecting BTC market manipulation.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Pressure from BlackRock and possibly Democrats could make denying the ETF politically untenable for Gensler,” they added.</p></blockquote>
<p>However, Bloomberg highlighted Grayscale – the owner of the world’s largest Bitcoin fund – as its main source of optimism.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The lynchpin for this current thesis is a Grayscale victory over the SEC in Federal court,” wrote Seyffart to Twitter on Wednesday. “Which COULD set things up for a wave of SEC approvals sometime in the 4th quarter? All depends on how much Gensler wants to fight here.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Grayscale is fighting to convert its Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) into a Bitcoin spot ETF in court, by challenging the SEC’s prior denials of their attempts as “arbitrary and capricious.” The firm maintains that its proposed surveillance-sharing partner – CME Bitcoin Futures – should be able to satisfy the agency’s requirements.</p>
<p>In fact, the company sent a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-claims-coinbase-wont-work-as-a-bitcoin-etf-surveillance-partner/" data-wpel-link="internal">letter</a> to the SEC last week arguing that none of the recent applicants partnering with Coinbase should be approved, based on the commission’s denial of applications with similar arrangements in the past.</p>
<p>If they do, Grayscale argued that the SEC must approve all ETF products at the same time – including their own, for the sake of fairness.</p>
<h2>ETF Approval Deadlines</h2>
<p>The SEC’s first <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-an-approximate-list-of-all-bitcoin-etf-approval-deadlines-bbg/" data-wpel-link="internal">deadline</a> to approve one of the recent ETF filings is on August 13 for the Ark 21Shares Bitcoin ETF (ARKB). This deadline can be postponed until January 10, however, which Seyffart has previously acknowledged as a likely outcome.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Grayscale <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale/status/1686029477791305729" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">expects</a> to receive a decision in its lawsuit against the SEC before Fall 2023.</p>
<p>However, even if they win the case, some experts believe this may not lead to immediate approval for its conversion. &#8220;A “win” may just mean the court of appeals directs the SEC to revisit their decision,” said Joe Carlasare, a commercial litigator, to CryptoPotato last month.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloomberg-boosts-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval-odds-to-65-heres-why/" rel="nofollow">Bloomberg Boosts Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval Odds To 65%: Here&#8217;s Why</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fitch Ratings Downgrades US Government Debt To AA+</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fitch-ratings-downgrades-us-government-debt-to-aa/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263980</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/united-states-2361405_640-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/united-states-2361405_640-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Fitch claims there’s been an “erosion of governance” on how to manage U.S. government debt, but the Treasury Department disagrees. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fitch Ratings – one of the world’s “Big Three” credit rating agencies – has removed the United States from its position among the very highest tier of long-term lending counterparties.</p>
<p>The nation’s Long-Term Foreign-Currency Issuer Default Rating (IDR) slid from AAA to AA+ on Tuesday, prompting criticisms against Fitch from both the U.S. Treasury Department and the White House.</p>
<h2>Why The Downgrade?</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.fitchratings.com/research/sovereigns/fitch-downgrades-united-states-long-term-ratings-to-aa-from-aaa-outlook-stable-01-08-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Fitch</a>, the downgrade reflects expectations of “fiscal deterioration,” the country’s “growing general government debt burden,” and an “erosion of governance” regarding how to manage that debt relative to its AA and AAA-rated peers.</p>
<p>Firstly, the government deficit has been rising over time and is expected to reach 6.3% by the end of 2023, versus 3.7% at the end of 2022. Fitch attributes the expected rise to “weaker government revenues, new spending initiatives, and a higher interest burden.”</p>
<blockquote><p>“Fitch forecasts a GG deficit of 6.6% of GDP in 2024 and a further widening to 6.9% of GDP in 2025,” the agency added.</p></blockquote>
<p>The sheer size of the nation’s debt also dwarfs nations within comparable credit rating categories. The United States’ debt-to-GDP ratio is expected to reach 118% by 2025, which is nearly three times the AAA median of 39.3%.</p>
<p>As debt rises, so will the country’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/novogratz-advises-investors-to-buy-bitcoin-as-federal-interest-payments-skyrocket/" data-wpel-link="internal">interest burden</a>, which Fitch expects interest payments alone to comprise 3.6% of GDP by 2033.</p>
<p>So far, negotiations to address that debt have proven consistently chaotic in the United States over the past two decades. Fitch cited the bipartisan agreement in June, where Congress agreed to suspend the nation’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-would-happen-to-bitcoin-if-the-us-debt-ceiling-cracks-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">debt limit</a> entirely until January 2025 – after the next federal election.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The repeated debt-limit political standoffs and last-minute resolutions have eroded confidence in fiscal management,” wrote Fitch. “In addition, the government lacks a medium-term fiscal framework, unlike most peers, and has a complex budgeting process.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Government Responds</h2>
<p>U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen was not pleased with Fitch’s downgrade, calling their decision “arbitrary and based on outdated data.” She said she has seen progress in many economic indicators used by Fitch, “including those related to governance.”</p>
<p>Meanwhile, White House Press Secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said the downgrade “defies reality” in a Tuesday <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/08/01/statement-from-press-secretary-karine-jean-pierre-on-the-recent-decision-by-fitch-ratings/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a>, claiming that the President has “led the strongest recovery of any major economy in the world,” and blamed Republicans for previously “cheerleading” a debt default.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fitch-ratings-downgrades-us-government-debt-to-aa/" rel="nofollow">Fitch Ratings Downgrades US Government Debt To AA+</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Satoshi Coin Hosts Presale and Prepares to Launch Environmentally Friendly Cryptocurrency</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/satoshi-coin-hosts-presale-and-prepares-to-launch-environmentally-friendly-cryptocurrency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263969</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Youtube_Cover_A_1690979535W4LKJIvOK4.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Youtube_Cover_A_1690979535W4LKJIvOK4.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; London, United Kingdom, August 2nd, 2023] The cryptocurrency landscape is about to be shaken up by the release of Satoshi Coin, a new cryptocurrency that has a number of unique features. Satoshi Coin offers a novel approach to mining and staking through its Proof of Computing Power (PoCP) algorithm. The presale for [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; London, United Kingdom, August 2nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>The cryptocurrency landscape is about to be shaken up by the release of Satoshi Coin, a new cryptocurrency that has a number of unique features. Satoshi Coin offers a novel approach to mining and staking through its Proof of Computing Power (PoCP) algorithm. The presale for Satoshi Coin is currently underway. It will run from August 2 until all available coins have been purchased.</p>
<p>An Ethereum-based token, Satoshi Coin introduces a next-generation crypto mining and staking solution. This system combines efficiency, accessibility, and sustainability. Unlike traditional energy-intensive methods, Satoshi Coin&#8217;s PoCP algorithm harnesses the latent power of a miner’s CPU, GPU, and RAM, without burdening their system or consuming excessive energy.</p>
<p>Key features of Satoshi Coin include an innovative Proof of Computing Power (PoCP) algorithm. This ensures seamless, energy-efficient mining and staking, enhancing the crypto landscape by minimising environmental impact.</p>
<p>The project’s user-friendly app is available on Windows, MacOS, Linux, iOS, and Android. This makes it easy for consumers to effortlessly mine or stake SAT tokens. The Satoshi Coin app analyses the system’s computing power, distributing rewards based on the miner’s CPU, GPU, and RAM performance. Mining and staking have never been this user-friendly and accessible. Satoshi Coin&#8217;s PoCP algorithm ensures that mining and staking are environmentally responsible activities.</p>
<p>Satoshi Coin’s presale offers a unique opportunity for crypto enthusiasts to become a part of this journey. By participating in the presale, crypto fans will not only contribute to the advancement of the underlying technology but claim a stake in the greener crypto future that Satoshi Coin is building.</p>
<p>Presale Details:</p>
<p>&#8211; Start Date: 2 August 2023 &#8211; 17:22 UTC</p>
<p>&#8211; End Date: Until Sold Out</p>
<p>&#8211; Token: Satoshi Coin (SAT)</p>
<p>&#8211; Token Type: Ethereum-based ERC-20</p>
<p>&#8211; Presale Price: Phase 1 &#8211; $0.23 / Phase 2 &#8211; $0.5 / Phase 3 &#8211; $1</p>
<p>&#8211; Accepted Currencies: ETH, BNB, USDT, USDC, BUSD (USDT in both ETH and BSC networks)</p>
<p>For more information and to participate in the Satoshi Coin presale, please visit Satoshi&#8217;s <a href="https://SatoshiCoin.pro" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">official website</a> or join Satoshi&#8217;s <a href="https://t.me/SatoshiCoinETH" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a>.</p>
<p><strong>About Satoshi Coin</strong></p>
<p>Satoshi Coin is an Ethereum-based token that introduces the Proof of Computing Power (PoCP) algorithm, redefining the way cryptocurrency enthusiasts mine and stake. With a commitment to efficiency, accessibility, and sustainability, Satoshi Coin is leading the charge toward a greener and more inclusive crypto landscape.</p>
<p>Contact:</p>
<p>Satoshi Nakamoto &#8211; Founder of Satoshi Coin and Inventor of Proof of Computing Power Algorithm (PoCP)</p>
<p><a href="https://satoshicoin.pro/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a> | <a href="https://t.me/SatoshiCoinETH" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a> | <a href="https://satoshicoin.pro/Satoshi-Coin.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Whitepaper</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/satoshi-coin-hosts-presale-and-prepares-to-launch-environmentally-friendly-cryptocurrency/" rel="nofollow">Satoshi Coin Hosts Presale and Prepares to Launch Environmentally Friendly Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Shouldn&#8217;t be Detained for Leaking Details From Ellison&#8217;s Diary, Lawyers Claim</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-shouldnt-be-detained-for-leaking-details-from-ellisons-diary-lawyers-claim/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263812</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sam_Bankman-Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sam_Bankman-Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA["Detaining Mr. Bankman-Fried based on his communications with a reporter raises serious First Amendment concerns," the attorneys stated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cohen &amp; Gresser &#8211; an international law firm representing the former CEO of FTX Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) &#8211; maintained that he did not attempt to intimidate Caroline Ellison (ex-leader of Alameda Research) or taint the jury&#8217;s sentiment when talking to a New York Times reporter.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 31-year-old, who faces several fraud charges and is accused of being the main culprit behind the collapse of the once-leading crypto exchange, shared quoted excerpts of Ellison&#8217;s private diary, revealing that her psychological condition was shaken prior to the catastrophe. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Department of Justice (DOJ) insisted on SBF&#8217;s detention and a bond revocation, maintaining that his actions could have tampered with the woman, who may be summoned as a witness at his trial set for the beginning of October.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Lawyers&#8217; Response </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Mark Cohen and Christian Everdell &#8211; attorneys at Cohen &amp; Gresser &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/66631291/185/united-states-v-bankman-fried/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sent</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a letter to Judge Lewis Kaplan, requesting that their client Bankman-Fried should not be imprisoned for leaking information from Caroline Ellison&#8217;s diary.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawyers argued that SBF&#8217;s contact with the journalist was &#8220;a proper exercise of his rights to make fair comment on an article already in progress, for which the reporter already had alternate sources.&#8221; They also insisted that the defendant has a right to talk to the press about his case to protect his reputation &#8220;as long as the communications are not calculated to pervert the course of justice.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The Government&#8217;s proffered factual basis to revoke Mr. Bankman-Fried&#8217;s bail is extremely thin and relies heavily on assumptions, unsupported inferences, and innuendo. The Government recognizes that, even under its view of the facts, Mr. Bankman-Fried&#8217;s contact with the New York Times reporter by itself is not sufficient to justify detaining him,&#8221; the letter reads.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, Cohen &amp; Gresser claimed that detaining SBF (as requested by the US DOJ) &#8220;would make it impossible for him to fully participate in his defense.&#8221; The firm reminded that federal prison inmates are not allowed Internet access, which &#8220;will cut off Mr. Bankman-Fried from key parts of the discovery entirely and render the rest effectively unreviewable.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sharing data from Ellison&#8217;s private dairy (SBF&#8217;s ex-girlfriend) is just one of the many charges the former crypto tycoon faces. He was accused of orchestrating a massive scam that led to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the fall of FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in November last year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ellison, who was in charge of the sister company Alameda Research, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-alameda-crisis-caroline-ellison-gary-wang-plead-guilty-to-fraud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pleaded</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> guilty to playing a role in the frauds that contributed to the exchange&#8217;s meltdown and the consecutive multi-billion investor losses. She agreed to cooperate with the relevant authorities and is expected to participate as a witness during SBF&#8217;s mega trial starting on October 2. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Leaked Data</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The New York Times coverage (published last month) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/07/20/technology/ftx-caroline-ellison-bankman-fried.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that Ellison was &#8220;unhappy and overwhelmed&#8221; with her job months before the crash of FTX. She also told SBF that she had &#8220;significantly decreased&#8221; her excitement about Alameda Research due to the couple&#8217;s breakup. Ellison also questioned her capabilities as the leader of the entity.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The 28-year-old </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://nypost.com/2022/12/23/caroline-ellison-faced-110-years-behind-bars-before-plea/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">faced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a jail sentence of 101 years before agreeing to &#8220;cooperate fully&#8221; with the US authorities. It remains unclear what her eventual punishment will be, with some experts suggesting she could receive just probation for pleading guilty and testifying in SBF&#8217;s trial.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-shouldnt-be-detained-for-leaking-details-from-ellisons-diary-lawyers-claim/" rel="nofollow">SBF Shouldn&#8217;t be Detained for Leaking Details From Ellison&#8217;s Diary, Lawyers Claim</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Signal Not Seen Since Feb 2018 Flashes: Is BTC in Danger? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/signal-not-seen-since-feb-2018-flashes-is-btc-in-danger-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263906</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In mid-July, Bitcoin attempted multiple times to break the significant resistance at $30K but ultimately failed and declined toward the 100-day moving average. Nevertheless, the price is currently trading within a critical range, and a breakout could trigger a substantial price movement. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart On the daily chart, the 100-day [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In mid-July, Bitcoin attempted multiple times to break the significant resistance at $30K but ultimately failed and declined toward the 100-day moving average.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the price is currently trading within a critical range, and a breakout could trigger a substantial price movement.</p>
<h1>Technical Analysis</h1>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h2>The Daily Chart</h2>
<p>On the daily chart, the 100-day moving average is acting as a support level, preventing further declines. However, it has been unable to push the price back above the $30K mark in the last few months.</p>
<p>Also, the prolonged divergence between the price and the RSI indicator suggests a possibility of a downside break, potentially pushing the price toward the 200-day moving average of around $27K.</p>
<p>The 200-day MA is a significant indicator that could act as support and propel the price higher, as it did back in February. Alternatively, if the price manages to climb back above the key $30K level, it may trigger a rally toward the $38K resistance zone in the upcoming weeks.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263909" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263909" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263909 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0208231" width="1835" height="913" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily.jpg 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-300x149.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-1024x509.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-768x382.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-1536x764.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-Daily-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263909" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>The 4-Hour Chart</h2>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, the situation for BTC looks intriguing. Following the correction that began in early July, the price has reached the 0.5 and 0.618 Fibonacci retracement levels, which serve as crucial support and could potentially halt the recent downward spiral.</p>
<p>If the price finds support around this level, it is likely to enter a new bullish phase and surge higher. However, there is still a chance for a break below the price range between the 0.5 and 0.618 Fibonacci levels, which would be concerning.</p>
<p>In such a scenario, a breakdown might lead to a rapid decline toward the $25K support level in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263911" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263911" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263911 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0208232" width="1835" height="913" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H.jpg 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-300x149.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-1024x509.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-768x382.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-1536x764.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/BTC-4H-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263911" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<p>The &#8220;Exchange Whale Ratio&#8221; measures the proportion of the top 10 large inflows to the total inflows on a cryptocurrency exchange. High values of this ratio suggest that significant amounts of funds from large players, commonly referred to as &#8220;whales,&#8221; are being deposited into the exchange.</p>
<p>Currently, the Exchange Whale Ratio is at its lowest level, with the last instance of such low levels observed back in February 2018. When this ratio is low, it may not have an immediate impact, but historically, when it experiences a rebound, it tends to affect the price of Bitcoin (BTC) adversely.</p>
<p>For instance, in February 2018 and again in May 2021, when the ratio rebounded from an all-time low, the price of BTC reached its peak and subsequently started declining. This indicates that when the ratio increases, suggesting a surge in whale activity on exchanges, it could signal a potential downward trend in BTC&#8217;s price.</p>
<p>Since the fourth quarter of 2022, the Exchange Whale Ratio has been steadily declining, and during this period, there hasn&#8217;t been a significant drop in BTC&#8217;s price. However, it is essential to monitor this ratio closely as it could bounce back at any time, following historical patterns, potentially leading to changes in BTC&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263910" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263910" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263910 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_exchange_whale_ratio_chart_0208231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Bitcoin-Exchange-Whale-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263910" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/signal-not-seen-since-feb-2018-flashes-is-btc-in-danger-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Signal Not Seen Since Feb 2018 Flashes: Is BTC in Danger? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Spikes on MicroStrategy News While Traders Are Also Backing New XRP20 Token</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-spikes-on-microstrategy-news-while-traders-are-also-backing-new-xrp20-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 14:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263929</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_btc_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_btc_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies saw a strong resurgence over the past day as the global crypto market cap expanded by 1.5%. Bitcoin surged past the $30,000 price level before correcting slightly to currently trade at $29.4K. The largest cryptocurrency received a strong boost as MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor revealed that his company purchased another 467 BTC tokens [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Major cryptocurrencies saw a strong resurgence over the past day as the global crypto market cap expanded by 1.5%. Bitcoin surged past the $30,000 price level before correcting slightly to currently trade at $29.4K.</p>
<p>The largest cryptocurrency received a strong boost as <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1686468084574412800?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor</a> revealed that his company purchased another 467 BTC tokens in July for $14.4 Million.</p>
<p>Crypto traders have been frustrated with the lack of upside displayed by Bitcoin in recent weeks. Despite its latest surge, it continues to trade between the $29K &#8211; $30K price range.</p>
<p>Investors are now looking for newly launched tokens that can outperform the sluggish crypto market, with XRP20 emerging as a top contender. The token is already nearing the $100k mark in the presale in less than a day.</p>
<h2><strong>Michael Saylor Remains Bullish On BTC Despite Recent Lack Of Volatility</strong></h2>
<p>Michael Saylor’s MicroStrategy is one of the biggest holders of Bitcoin in the world. Its purchase of additional 467 tokens in July puts its total BTC holdings at 152,800 tokens worth $4.5 Billion.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263932" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="320" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-300x159.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture5-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Furthermore, according to the latest SEC filing, the company sold $750 million worth of its Class A common stock and intends to use the proceeds to <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1050446/000119312523200621/d533407d424b5.htm#toca533407_7" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">purchase additional BTC tokens</a>.</p>
<p>MicroStrategy&#8217;s accumulation strategy has been traditionally bullish for Bitcoin. At the current price level, $750 million would amount to a purchase of additional 25,380 BTC tokens, which can provide a major boost and raise hopes of Bitcoin finally breaking above the $31k resistance.</p>
<p>Saylor is one of the biggest supporters of Bitcoin, calling it the best asset in the world on multiple occasions. He remains firm in his bullish stance on Bitcoin despite the recent lack of upside, which is not a surprise considering his BTC accumulation last year despite the ensuing bear market.</p>
<p>However, Saylor is now being joined by big money TradFi institutions in his support for the largest crypto asset. Bitcoin saw a major bullish growth in June when asset management firm <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/blackrock-files-for-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-7547609" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BlackRock filed for a spot BTC ETF</a>. Other mega institutions such as Citadel, Charles Schwab, Fidelity and Valkyrie have also entered the market to offer BTC trading.</p>
<p>Larry Fink, the CEO of BlackRock, recently stated in a CNBC interview that <a href="https://twitter.com/saylor/status/1679857360011943938?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Bitcoin will outperform every international currency</a> due to its global demand. A recent research paper published by BlackRock also recommended an <a href="https://twitter.com/IIICapital/status/1683902622594367497?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">optimal BTC allocation of 80-100%</a> to its clients.</p>
<p>On-chain data firm Glassnode revealed that Bitcoin’s long-term holder supply reached a new all-time high by the end of July, highlighting that mature and <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1683401299956465665?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">smart money investors continue to hold</a> the token.</p>
<p>However, retail investors are getting impatient over BTC’s lack of growth as the token is down 4% over the past month.</p>
<p>Expert crypto analysts <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1686474382212829184?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Michael van de Poppe</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoCon_/status/1686373259019976705?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">CryptoCon</a> believe that Bitcoin is already in a new bull cycle and can display explosive growth any time now. Similarly, long-term crypto analyst <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoJelleNL/status/1684134027928694784?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">@CryptoJelleNL</a> believes that the BTC price is primed for a strong upward move and will peak in the 4th quarter of 2025.</p>
<p>Another trader, <a href="https://twitter.com/i_am_jackis/status/1682731178846044160?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">@i_am_jackis</a>, reveals that the upcoming decade will be a decade of commodities. Despite its hawkish stance on crypto, the SEC has stated that Bitcoin is one crypto asset that is definitely a commodity. Therefore, BTC can see sustained growth over the next decade, especially if the institutional money continues to back the token.</p>
<h2><strong>Which Other Token Can Show A Bull Rally?</strong></h2>
<p>Similar to Bitcoin, XRP has remained sluggish in recent weeks as Ripple’s post-win enthusiasm has faded and the threat of an SEC appeal looms large.</p>
<p>However, the new stake-to-earn XRP20 token is seeing an investor frenzy in its newly launched presale, capitalizing on the recent surge of interest in XRP.</p>
<h2><strong>New XRP20 Token Sees Surging Demand &amp; $100K In Presale in Just 3 Days</strong></h2>
<p>The new <a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=bitcoin-price-spikes-on-microstrategy-news-while-traders-are-also-backing-new-xrp20-token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20 token</a> is generating hype and FOMO as it claims a second opportunity for investors who missed out on XRP’s 22,700% bull rally.</p>
<p>The token is priced at just $0.000092 in the presale and claims to be offering the same growth potential as purchasing XRP at its all-time low of $0.0028.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263931" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="351" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-300x175.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture6-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Investors are lining up for the presale as the token has already raised over $90k in less than a day.</p>
<p>XRP20 is designed as an ERC-20 asset, offering compatibility with existing Ethereum platforms and wallets and making it easier for investors to trade, track and store the token. Its on-chain staking mechanism is also a major point of attraction for retail investors, providing an excellent opportunity to generate passive income.</p>
<p>10% of the entire token supply has also been reserved for providing decentralized exchange liquidity, ensuring a smooth trading experience for traders. Another 20% of the tokens have been allocated to be burned, resulting in deflationary supply and surging token value.</p>
<p>The recent hype around XRP and the pent-up demand for superior returns has set the stage for a stellar performance by XRP20.</p>
<p>However, the presale has a hard cap of $3,680,000, which is expected to sell out quickly.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=bitcoin-price-spikes-on-microstrategy-news-while-traders-are-also-backing-new-xrp20-token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit XRP20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-spikes-on-microstrategy-news-while-traders-are-also-backing-new-xrp20-token/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Spikes on MicroStrategy News While Traders Are Also Backing New XRP20 Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Much XRP Does Ripple Labs Have? Company Talks About SEC Ruling in Q2 Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-xrp-does-ripple-labs-have-company-talks-about-sec-ruling-in-q2-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263901</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ripple_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/ripple_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple's quarterly reports could take a new turn, while the company claims that it would continue to maintain transparency. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said the contents of the company&#8217;s quarterly financial reports could take a different turn from the usual after the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) used the firm&#8217;s disclosures against it in the lawsuit.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, XRP holders lawyer John Deaton believes Ripple&#8217;s transparency saved the firm from facing fraud and manipulation allegations.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Ripple Increases XRP Holdings in Q2 2023</h2>
<p dir="ltr">Garlinghouse stated that the company voluntarily started releasing the quarterly reports on its XRP holdings as a sign of transparency but said the reports were used against it in the lawsuit while hinting that there could be changes in their format in the future.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We began these reports to voluntarily provide updates given our XRP holdings. Sadly, they were used against us in the SEC lawsuit &#8211; however, we remain steadfast in our commitment to transparency but I suspect they’re going to look a bit different moving forward <a href="https://t.co/oANR6WCG09" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/oANR6WCG09</a></p>
<p>— Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1686618130674774016?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Ripple <a href="https://ripple.com/insights/q2-2023-xrp-markets-report/?utm_campaign=&amp;utm_medium=organic_social&amp;utm_source=twitter" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">released</a> its quarterly XRP markets report for Q2 2023 on July 31, which was different and focused on the landmark court ruling and misconceptions and also included the company&#8217;s XRP holdings.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the court ruled in favor of Ripple, with Judge Analise Torres declaring that XRP is not a security, in a case involving the SEC and Ripple Labs that dragged on for nearly three years.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The report also moved to debunk some of the misconceptions following the court&#8217;s decision. Ripple clarified that the ruling was not only a victory for the firm but for the broader crypto industry. The company also debunked a misconception stating that XRP is partially a security token, asserting that based on the judge&#8217;s ruling, the asset &#8220;is not in and of itself&#8221; a security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Furthermore, the firm addressed the misconception that believed the ruling protected institutional buyers and not retail traders. According to Ripple, the decision focused on the reach of the SEC, while adding that the regulator&#8217;s claims to protect investors did the opposite.</p>
<p dir="ltr">As stated in the report, the SEC lawsuit in 2020 caused panic selling among investors, which led to a loss of $15 billion in market capitalization at the expense of US holders.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Ripple&#8217;s XRP holdings at the end of Q2 2023, which ended on June 30, stand at 5,551,119,094, an increase from 5,506,585918 recorded on March 31. Also, the total XRP on ledger escrow was reduced from 42,800,000,013 at the end of Q1 2023 to 41,900,000,005 in Q2 2023.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Deaton on Ripple&#8217;s Transparency</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While Ripple could change the format of its reports moving forward, XRP holders&#8217; lawyer John Deaton believes the company&#8217;s transparency saved it from facing fraud and manipulation charges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">It is absolutely true that the SEC used the transparency of these reports against Ripple and its two executives. As a private company, Ripple was under no obligation to share this info. Other companies not only didn’t share token sales, but intentionally disguised those… <a href="https://t.co/mbAO6feEfW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/mbAO6feEfW</a></p>
<p>— John E Deaton (@JohnEDeaton1) <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnEDeaton1/status/1686627185774166016?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p dir="ltr">Deaton stated that Ripple published its quarterly reports even when it was not obliged to as a private company, while other firms hid token sales and deliberately disguised the transactions.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to the lawyer, the SEC would have included fraud, misrepresentation, or manipulation charges in its lawsuit if the agency saw the possibility, adding, &#8220;When you&#8217;re transparent, they can’t claim fraud &#8211; even when they want to.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-much-xrp-does-ripple-labs-have-company-talks-about-sec-ruling-in-q2-report/" rel="nofollow">How Much XRP Does Ripple Labs Have? Company Talks About SEC Ruling in Q2 Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can SHIB Explode Higher? Here&#8217;s What You Need to Know (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/can-shib-explode-higher-heres-what-you-need-to-know-shiba-inu-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SHIBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263842</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Shiba Inu is in a clear uptrend, and momentum still favors bulls. Key Support levels: $0.0000080 Key Resistance levels: $0.0000094   1. Clear Higher Highs The price has been making higher highs since late June, and SHIB has not stopped since. This puts the price in a clear uptrend which could take SHIB to the key [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: left;">Shiba Inu is in a clear uptrend, and momentum still favors bulls.</p>
<p><strong>Key Support levels: $0.0000080</strong></p>
<p><strong>Key Resistance levels: $0.0000094  </strong></p>
<h2>1. Clear Higher Highs</h2>
<p>The price has been making higher highs since late June, and SHIB has not stopped since. This puts the price in a clear uptrend which could take SHIB to the key resistance at $0.0000094.</p>
<p>However, in the process, this meme coin also appears to have formed a bearish wedge which could see the price break under it once the key resistance is hit.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263850" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263850" style="width: 1826px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263850" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00" width="1826" height="895" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00.png 1826w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-00-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1826px) 100vw, 1826px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263850" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>2. Sustained Buy Volume</h2>
<p>Despite regular pullbacks, buyers continue to dominate the chart. This is also represented in the price that has slowly moved higher every week. Buyers appear to rush in whenever SHIB breaches a key resistance pushing the price higher in a short amount of time which sustains the bullish bias.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263849" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263849" style="width: 1826px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263849" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31" width="1826" height="896" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31.png 1826w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31-768x377.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31-1536x754.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-49-31-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1826px) 100vw, 1826px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263849" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>3. Bullish Momentum</h2>
<p>The momentum is clearly positive on the MACD and RSI indicators, as they both show higher highs. With good support at $0.0000080, SHIB seems to be on a clear path to hit the key resistance.</p>
<figure id="attachment_263848" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263848" style="width: 1826px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-263848" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16.png" alt="SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16" width="1826" height="895" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16.png 1826w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16-300x147.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16-1024x502.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16-768x376.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16-1536x753.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/SHIBUSDT_2023-08-02_13-52-16-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1826px) 100vw, 1826px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263848" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Bias</h2>
<p>The bias for SHIB is bullish.</p>
<h2>Short-Term Prediction for SHIB Price</h2>
<p>A test of the key resistance at $0.0000094 appears imminent. Nevertheless, it&#8217;s important to watch closely how the wedge will resolve as a break below it could lead to a correction. On the other hand, a break above it could likely be extremely bullish for Shiba Inu&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/can-shib-explode-higher-heres-what-you-need-to-know-shiba-inu-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Can SHIB Explode Higher? Here&#8217;s What You Need to Know (Shiba Inu Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
