<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:05:26 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[AAG Marks A New Era Of Web3 With Its Event In Manila]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/aag-marks-a-new-era-of-web3-with-its-event-in-manila</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/xxxxx_1689603806oQBjg8TEH8.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/xxxxx_1689603806oQBjg8TEH8.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/xxxxx_1689603806oQBjg8TEH8.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:28:36 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/aag-marks-a-new-era-of-web3-with-its-event-in-manila</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>MANILA, PHILIPPINES, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>AAG, a Web3 infrastructure company, successfully held its maiden live event on June 21, further bolstering the Philippines' immersion into the Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>The event, a confluence of Web2 and Web3 aficionados, saw the participation of industry leaders like Lazada, GCash, and DITO CME, along with renowned key opinion leaders (KOLs) and strategic partners.</p><p>CEO and co-founder of AAG, Jack Vinijtrongjit, emphasized, "AAG's commitment to integrating the worlds of Web2 and Web3 is instrumental in shaping the future. We are thrilled to lead this transformation and collaborate with enterprises on this exciting journey."</p><p>Key Highlights of the Event:</p><ol><li>The launch of AAG's MetaOne Affiliate Program was a significant milestone. This path-breaking program offers users of AAG&rsquo;s seedless self-custody wallet an opportunity to earn lifetime fee shares up to 80%. Furthermore, the program boasts enticing rewards, including monthly iPhone giveaways and a chance to win a BMW car!</li><li>The event was graced by around 50 prominent KOLs, with a cumulative follower base of over 6 million.</li><li>Leading Web3 companies such as Lazada, GCash, and DITO CME were present, contributing their insights on the latest evolutions in the Web3 arena.</li></ol>Donald Lim, COO of DITO CME, joined Jack Vinijtrongjit in a panel discussion about the transformative potential of Web3 technology on established businesses. Vinijtrongjit said, "Businesses can leverage the innovative power of Web3 and blockchain technology to revolutionize customer relationship management. AAG, through its advanced tech stack, is enabling businesses to exploit Web3 capabilities and discover new avenues in their existing business models."<p>The successful conclusion of AAG's event in Manila underlined the burgeoning potential of the Web3 world, not only in the Philippines but on a global scale.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>About AAG</p><p>AAG is a web3 infrastructure company focused on providing software that helps simplify interactions with blockchain applications and the Metaverse for both mainstream users and traditional companies. AAG provides a secure and easy-to-use MetaOne&reg; wallet, as well as infrastructure software, such as a cross-chain search engine and Saakuru blockchain for enterprise companies. With the belief that education is the key to unlock the potential of web3, AAG is also exploring the concept of Learn-and-Earn with the mission of enabling economic opportunities worldwide via the Metaverse economy. AAG aims to bring 1 billion people into the Metaverse economy by 2030.</p><p>For more information about AAG, visit: AAG Linktree</p><p></p>ContactCEOJack Vinijtrongjitpartnership@aag.ventures]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MANILA, PHILIPPINES, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>AAG, a Web3 infrastructure company, successfully held its maiden live event on June 21, further bolstering the Philippines' immersion into the Web3 ecosystem.</p><p>The event, a confluence of Web2 and Web3 aficionados, saw the participation of industry leaders like Lazada, GCash, and DITO CME, along with renowned key opinion leaders (KOLs) and strategic partners.</p><p>CEO and co-founder of AAG, Jack Vinijtrongjit, emphasized, "AAG's commitment to integrating the worlds of Web2 and Web3 is instrumental in shaping the future. We are thrilled to lead this transformation and collaborate with enterprises on this exciting journey."</p><p>Key Highlights of the Event:</p><ol><li>The launch of AAG's MetaOne Affiliate Program was a significant milestone. This path-breaking program offers users of AAG&rsquo;s seedless self-custody wallet an opportunity to earn lifetime fee shares up to 80%. Furthermore, the program boasts enticing rewards, including monthly iPhone giveaways and a chance to win a BMW car!</li><li>The event was graced by around 50 prominent KOLs, with a cumulative follower base of over 6 million.</li><li>Leading Web3 companies such as Lazada, GCash, and DITO CME were present, contributing their insights on the latest evolutions in the Web3 arena.</li></ol>Donald Lim, COO of DITO CME, joined Jack Vinijtrongjit in a panel discussion about the transformative potential of Web3 technology on established businesses. Vinijtrongjit said, "Businesses can leverage the innovative power of Web3 and blockchain technology to revolutionize customer relationship management. AAG, through its advanced tech stack, is enabling businesses to exploit Web3 capabilities and discover new avenues in their existing business models."<p>The successful conclusion of AAG's event in Manila underlined the burgeoning potential of the Web3 world, not only in the Philippines but on a global scale.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>About AAG</p><p>AAG is a web3 infrastructure company focused on providing software that helps simplify interactions with blockchain applications and the Metaverse for both mainstream users and traditional companies. AAG provides a secure and easy-to-use MetaOne&reg; wallet, as well as infrastructure software, such as a cross-chain search engine and Saakuru blockchain for enterprise companies. With the belief that education is the key to unlock the potential of web3, AAG is also exploring the concept of Learn-and-Earn with the mission of enabling economic opportunities worldwide via the Metaverse economy. AAG aims to bring 1 billion people into the Metaverse economy by 2030.</p><p>For more information about AAG, visit: AAG Linktree</p><p></p>ContactCEOJack Vinijtrongjitpartnership@aag.ventures]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BRISE Outshines ETH, BNB, SOL, with Usual Price Gains, as Listing on 10 Major Exchanges Nears]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/brise-outshines-eth-bnb-sol-with-usual-price-gains-as-listing-on-10-major-exchanges-nears</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brise-outshines-eth-bnb-sol-with-usual-price-gains-as-listing.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brise-outshines-eth-bnb-sol-with-usual-price-gains-as-listing.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brise-outshines-eth-bnb-sol-with-usual-price-gains-as-listing.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/brise-outshines-eth-bnb-sol-with-usual-price-gains-as-listing-on-10-major-exchanges-nears</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<table style="width: 675px;">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="s8" style="width: 665px;">

● Bitgert celebrates its second anniversary by listing its BRISE on ten exchanges.
● The platform also introduces a meme character for BRISE to bring a new level of fun and engagement to the community.
● While BRISE maintained over 16% over the week, ETH and BNB barely had single-digit gains.

</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p class="s5">BRISE, the native token of the Bitgert crypto platform, has recently led the crypto market with phenomenal price gains. In a report that captured the eventful week performance of BRISE, it was reported that the coin gained over 30%, pushing its crypto market cap to over $103 million.</p>
<p class="s5">Contrasting the positive growth of BRISE, other major cryptocurrencies like Ethereum (ETH), Binance Coin (BNB), Solana (SOL), and Cardano (ADA) experienced losses in the last 24 hours. According to data from CoinMarketCap, while BRISE maintained over 16% upward trajectory over the past seven days, ETH and BNB barely had single-digit gains.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, BRISE has climbed three steps up the ranking of the most significant coins within two weeks, gaining more than $3 million in market cap. The interest in the coin can be attributed to exciting development, celebrations, and collaborations around Bitgert.</p>
<p class="s5">In a recent tweet, the project announced the listing of its token, BRISE, on ten major crypto exchanges, inviting the community to join in this significant milestone.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">🎉 Celebrating our 2nd anniversary which happened on 7th July 2023! 🎂 As part of the festivities, we're thrilled to announce the listing of our token on 10 major crypto exchanges. Join us in this milestone moment! 🚀#BRISE #bitgert pic.twitter.com/YA8viNIzCE</p>
&mdash; Bitgert - $BRISE (@bitgertbrise) July 11, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="s5">The image shared in the tweet provided a timeline of the exchange listings scheduled throughout August. The first listing will come on August 1, with subsequent ones coming within about four days intervals until August 30.</p>
<p class="s5">Adding more fun and engagement to its ecosystem, Bitgert introduced a meme character for its native token, BRISE. It expressed enthusiasm for the new level of entertainment that the character would bring, promising comical posts and community engagements.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">🚨Big news alert🚨 We've created our very own meme character for #BRISE! Get ready for a whole new level of fun as we spice things up with hilarious announcements and community interactions.Guess the meme character and let us know in comments. pic.twitter.com/vOnJPiQVWp</p>
&mdash; Bitgert - $BRISE (@bitgertbrise) July 14, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="s5">The community was invited to participate in the guessing game and share their guesses in the comments.</p>
<p class="s5">Furthermore, the platform has partnered with ChangeNow to allow users to purchase BRISE using fiat currency, enhancing accessibility for investors. Additionally, the NFT platform NFTFeed is integrated into the Bitgert ecosystem to provide liquidity to the NFT market. Similarly, &nbsp;the partnership with the gaming platform Lifty.io expanded Bitgert's reach into the gaming sector.</p>
<p class="s5">While BRISE currently has a market share of around $103 million, the team asked the crypto community to prepare for a multi-billion market capitalization shortly.</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<table style="width: 675px;">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="s8" style="width: 665px;">

● Bitgert celebrates its second anniversary by listing its BRISE on ten exchanges.
● The platform also introduces a meme character for BRISE to bring a new level of fun and engagement to the community.
● While BRISE maintained over 16% over the week, ETH and BNB barely had single-digit gains.

</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p class="s5">BRISE, the native token of the Bitgert crypto platform, has recently led the crypto market with phenomenal price gains. In a report that captured the eventful week performance of BRISE, it was reported that the coin gained over 30%, pushing its crypto market cap to over $103 million.</p>
<p class="s5">Contrasting the positive growth of BRISE, other major cryptocurrencies like Ethereum (ETH), Binance Coin (BNB), Solana (SOL), and Cardano (ADA) experienced losses in the last 24 hours. According to data from CoinMarketCap, while BRISE maintained over 16% upward trajectory over the past seven days, ETH and BNB barely had single-digit gains.</p>
<p class="s5">Additionally, BRISE has climbed three steps up the ranking of the most significant coins within two weeks, gaining more than $3 million in market cap. The interest in the coin can be attributed to exciting development, celebrations, and collaborations around Bitgert.</p>
<p class="s5">In a recent tweet, the project announced the listing of its token, BRISE, on ten major crypto exchanges, inviting the community to join in this significant milestone.</p>
<p class="s5">&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">🎉 Celebrating our 2nd anniversary which happened on 7th July 2023! 🎂 As part of the festivities, we're thrilled to announce the listing of our token on 10 major crypto exchanges. Join us in this milestone moment! 🚀#BRISE #bitgert pic.twitter.com/YA8viNIzCE</p>
&mdash; Bitgert - $BRISE (@bitgertbrise) July 11, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="s5">The image shared in the tweet provided a timeline of the exchange listings scheduled throughout August. The first listing will come on August 1, with subsequent ones coming within about four days intervals until August 30.</p>
<p class="s5">Adding more fun and engagement to its ecosystem, Bitgert introduced a meme character for its native token, BRISE. It expressed enthusiasm for the new level of entertainment that the character would bring, promising comical posts and community engagements.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">🚨Big news alert🚨 We've created our very own meme character for #BRISE! Get ready for a whole new level of fun as we spice things up with hilarious announcements and community interactions.Guess the meme character and let us know in comments. pic.twitter.com/vOnJPiQVWp</p>
&mdash; Bitgert - $BRISE (@bitgertbrise) July 14, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p class="s5">The community was invited to participate in the guessing game and share their guesses in the comments.</p>
<p class="s5">Furthermore, the platform has partnered with ChangeNow to allow users to purchase BRISE using fiat currency, enhancing accessibility for investors. Additionally, the NFT platform NFTFeed is integrated into the Bitgert ecosystem to provide liquidity to the NFT market. Similarly, &nbsp;the partnership with the gaming platform Lifty.io expanded Bitgert's reach into the gaming sector.</p>
<p class="s5">While BRISE currently has a market share of around $103 million, the team asked the crypto community to prepare for a multi-billion market capitalization shortly.</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Xangle and Republic Crypto Form Strategic Partnership to Power Korean Enterprises’ Adoption of Web3]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xangle-and-republic-crypto-form-strategic-partnership-to-power-korean-enterprises-adoption-of-web3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d072bb1c-5d08-464b-a88d-959a60c347d0_1689601462XwewoV1vqp.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d072bb1c-5d08-464b-a88d-959a60c347d0_1689601462XwewoV1vqp.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/d072bb1c-5d08-464b-a88d-959a60c347d0_1689601462XwewoV1vqp.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:49:29 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/xangle-and-republic-crypto-form-strategic-partnership-to-power-korean-enterprises-adoption-of-web3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Seoul, South Korea, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Xangle, a leading web3 data and intelligence platform based in South Korea, has formed a strategic partnership with Republic Crypto, a leading US-based advisory firm that helps global enterprises seamlessly enter the web3 space.</p><p>To date, Xangle has primarily focused on providing web3 data, intelligence and advisory services to Korean enterprises, arming them with the essential tools and knowledge to make informed decisions regarding web3 strategy and its application to their business models. With this strategic partnership, Xangle clients now can gain access to Republic Crypto's renowned experience in web3 execution, offering clients a comprehensive toolkit that includes blockchain infrastructure setup, digital asset management, tokenomics design, and more.</p><p>"The partnership with Republic Crypto marks a significant milestone for the web3 industry in Asia," stated James Kim, Co-Founder and CEO of Xangle. "Enterprises in Korea now have access to comprehensive strategic and seamless implementation support for their blockchain initiatives. We are thrilled to be at the forefront of onboarding the next wave of mainstream web3 adoption, leveraging the exciting technologies that have matured in recent years."</p><p>"We are excited to work alongside Xangle in expanding our advisory presence in Asia and driving web3 adoption," said Bryan Myint, Co-Founder and Head of Republic Crypto&rsquo;s web3 advisory division. "Asia is positioning itself as a hub for the future wave of web3 innovation and adoption, and our aim is to support any company looking to dive into this exciting new phase of the economy."</p><p>This strategic partnership positions Xangle and Republic Crypto to empower enterprises on their path to embracing web3 technologies and seizing the opportunities in the evolving digital and financial landscape. Together, they enable businesses in Korea and other Asian technology hubs to expand into the decentralized frontier, leveraging the combined expertise and dedicated support of both companies. With this alliance, enterprises can confidently navigate the web3 space and unlock the full potential of an increasingly decentralized future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Xangle</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Xangle is one of the leading web3 data &amp; intelligence platforms based in South Korea, providing essential on-chain data infrastructure, solutions &amp; research for various web2&amp;3 stakeholders. Our mission is to foster sustainable growth and mass adoption of blockchain technology via educating the mass by offering comprehensive and granular insights on the blockchain industry by sector, therefore enabling more informed decision making. We also aim to facilitate Web3 adoption from traditional Web2 giants in their respective industries by providing advisory services and bridging with notable Web3 projects.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Republic Crypto</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Republic Crypto offers web3 advisory services, blockchain infrastructure, and digital asset management to the world&rsquo;s most ambitious builders and investors. Republic Crypto is part of Republic, a global technology firm pioneering the digital transformation of finance. Republic&rsquo;s ecosystem has made it possible for 2.5M+ community members to deploy $2.5B+ into 2000+ private ventures.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactItai ElizurMarketAcrossitai@marketacross.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seoul, South Korea, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Xangle, a leading web3 data and intelligence platform based in South Korea, has formed a strategic partnership with Republic Crypto, a leading US-based advisory firm that helps global enterprises seamlessly enter the web3 space.</p><p>To date, Xangle has primarily focused on providing web3 data, intelligence and advisory services to Korean enterprises, arming them with the essential tools and knowledge to make informed decisions regarding web3 strategy and its application to their business models. With this strategic partnership, Xangle clients now can gain access to Republic Crypto's renowned experience in web3 execution, offering clients a comprehensive toolkit that includes blockchain infrastructure setup, digital asset management, tokenomics design, and more.</p><p>"The partnership with Republic Crypto marks a significant milestone for the web3 industry in Asia," stated James Kim, Co-Founder and CEO of Xangle. "Enterprises in Korea now have access to comprehensive strategic and seamless implementation support for their blockchain initiatives. We are thrilled to be at the forefront of onboarding the next wave of mainstream web3 adoption, leveraging the exciting technologies that have matured in recent years."</p><p>"We are excited to work alongside Xangle in expanding our advisory presence in Asia and driving web3 adoption," said Bryan Myint, Co-Founder and Head of Republic Crypto&rsquo;s web3 advisory division. "Asia is positioning itself as a hub for the future wave of web3 innovation and adoption, and our aim is to support any company looking to dive into this exciting new phase of the economy."</p><p>This strategic partnership positions Xangle and Republic Crypto to empower enterprises on their path to embracing web3 technologies and seizing the opportunities in the evolving digital and financial landscape. Together, they enable businesses in Korea and other Asian technology hubs to expand into the decentralized frontier, leveraging the combined expertise and dedicated support of both companies. With this alliance, enterprises can confidently navigate the web3 space and unlock the full potential of an increasingly decentralized future.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Xangle</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Xangle is one of the leading web3 data &amp; intelligence platforms based in South Korea, providing essential on-chain data infrastructure, solutions &amp; research for various web2&amp;3 stakeholders. Our mission is to foster sustainable growth and mass adoption of blockchain technology via educating the mass by offering comprehensive and granular insights on the blockchain industry by sector, therefore enabling more informed decision making. We also aim to facilitate Web3 adoption from traditional Web2 giants in their respective industries by providing advisory services and bridging with notable Web3 projects.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Republic Crypto</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Republic Crypto offers web3 advisory services, blockchain infrastructure, and digital asset management to the world&rsquo;s most ambitious builders and investors. Republic Crypto is part of Republic, a global technology firm pioneering the digital transformation of finance. Republic&rsquo;s ecosystem has made it possible for 2.5M+ community members to deploy $2.5B+ into 2000+ private ventures.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactItai ElizurMarketAcrossitai@marketacross.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Whales and Institutional Investors Acquire over $4.7 Billion of Bitcoin (BTC), InQubeta (QUBE) Poised for 1000% Growth in 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/whales-and-institutional-investors-acquire-over-47-billion-of-bitcoin-btc-inqubeta-qube-poised-for-1000-growth-in-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-17-at-142756.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-17-at-142756.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-07-17-at-142756.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/whales-and-institutional-investors-acquire-over-47-billion-of-bitcoin-btc-inqubeta-qube-poised-for-1000-growth-in-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, two significant developments have taken center stage, capturing the attention of investors and crypto enthusiasts alike. InQubeta (QUBE) stands out as a revolutionary cryptocurrency, seamlessly integrating the realms of crypto, AI technology, and profitability. Simultaneously, Bitcoin (BTC) has witnessed a remarkable surge in market performance, fueled by the accumulation of over $4.7 billion worth of Bitcoin by whales and institutional investors.</p>
<p class="s5">The success of InQubeta's ongoing live presale, coupled with its diverse ecosystem encompassing high-profit potential and popular NFTs, makes InQubeta poised for 1000% growth in 2023. This projected growth is also thanks to InQubeta's focus on facilitating the crowdfunding of AI startups and providing a secure, transparent, and rewarding platform for every investor.</p>
<p class="s5">Let's explore how InQubeta is poised for 1000% growth in 2023 while whales and institutional investors acquire over $4.7 billion of Bitcoin.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE) Effectively Leverages Crypto, Profitability, and AI Synergy
<p class="s5">InQubeta is an outstanding crypto platform that highlights blockchain technology and AI innovation. It facilitates the connection between AI startups and investors to actualize its fundraising mission for beginner AI companies. The second stage of the ongoing InQubetapresale is witnessing remarkable momentum, attracting many investors eager to acquire QUBE tokens at a market-friendly rate of $0.0098 per token. InQubeta has sold over 174 million QUBE tokens and raised over $1.3 million.</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta's high-profit guarantee convinces investors of its capability to experience 1000% growth before the end of 2023. InQubeta aims to maximize returns and provide enticing rewards for investors in the DeFi market. InQubeta's native QUBE coin operates on a deflationary model, strategically reducing its supply to instill a sense of exclusivity and scarcity among QUBE token holders, encouraging them to hold their tokens for future gains. Holding QUBE tokens presents an opportunity to accrue 300% profits on investments due to the appreciating value of the QUBE coin throughout the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta's engaging NFT marketplace contributes to its potential to grow by 1000% in 2023. This virtual marketplace serves as a space for AI startups to exhibit their curated collections of popular NFTs. The unique NFTs attract QUBE investors to actively support their preferred AI startups by purchasing NFT assets. As an incentive, AI startups can offer discounts on products and services or rewards as equity-based NFTs, further solidifying InQubeta's reputation as one of the best DeFi investment prospects.</p>
<p class="s8"></p>
Bitcoin (BTC) Rises in Value Following a Surge in Accumulation
<p class="s5">Bitcoin utilizes its native BTC token to enable secure peer-to-peer transactions. Since its inception in 2009, Bitcoin has gained immense popularity as a pioneering crypto project many cryptocurrencies imitate. Between late June and July 4, 2023, whales and institutional investors in the BTC cryptocurrency actively amassed billions of dollars of Bitcoin at an accelerated pace. Their holdings ranged from 10 to 10,000 BTC, totaling over 154,600 BTC and yielding over $4.7 billion.</p>
<p class="s5">This surge in accumulation occurred after BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, filed for a spot in the Bitcoin project's exchange-traded fund (ETF). Afterward, the BTC token recorded heightened trading activity, propelling the price of each Bitcoin to rise above $31,000, reaching a new yearly high. Renowned crypto analyst Willy Woo has speculated that this progressive price trend may lead to the value of the BTC token possibly surpassing $300,000 in the future.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Investors and enthusiasts in the DeFi market are intrigued by the rapid accumulation of Bitcoin by whales and institutional investors and the promising growth of InQubeta's QUBE coin. The influx of billions of dollars into Bitcoin's funding showcases the continued interest and confidence in the leading cryptocurrency, with price predictions reaching new highs. Conversely, InQubeta's unique combination of crypto, profitability, and AI technology positions it as one of the best DeFi cryptocurrencies, with a projected growth of 1000% in 2023.</p>
<p class="s16">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p>Join The InQubeta Communities</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrencies, two significant developments have taken center stage, capturing the attention of investors and crypto enthusiasts alike. InQubeta (QUBE) stands out as a revolutionary cryptocurrency, seamlessly integrating the realms of crypto, AI technology, and profitability. Simultaneously, Bitcoin (BTC) has witnessed a remarkable surge in market performance, fueled by the accumulation of over $4.7 billion worth of Bitcoin by whales and institutional investors.</p>
<p class="s5">The success of InQubeta's ongoing live presale, coupled with its diverse ecosystem encompassing high-profit potential and popular NFTs, makes InQubeta poised for 1000% growth in 2023. This projected growth is also thanks to InQubeta's focus on facilitating the crowdfunding of AI startups and providing a secure, transparent, and rewarding platform for every investor.</p>
<p class="s5">Let's explore how InQubeta is poised for 1000% growth in 2023 while whales and institutional investors acquire over $4.7 billion of Bitcoin.</p>
InQubeta (QUBE) Effectively Leverages Crypto, Profitability, and AI Synergy
<p class="s5">InQubeta is an outstanding crypto platform that highlights blockchain technology and AI innovation. It facilitates the connection between AI startups and investors to actualize its fundraising mission for beginner AI companies. The second stage of the ongoing InQubetapresale is witnessing remarkable momentum, attracting many investors eager to acquire QUBE tokens at a market-friendly rate of $0.0098 per token. InQubeta has sold over 174 million QUBE tokens and raised over $1.3 million.</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta's high-profit guarantee convinces investors of its capability to experience 1000% growth before the end of 2023. InQubeta aims to maximize returns and provide enticing rewards for investors in the DeFi market. InQubeta's native QUBE coin operates on a deflationary model, strategically reducing its supply to instill a sense of exclusivity and scarcity among QUBE token holders, encouraging them to hold their tokens for future gains. Holding QUBE tokens presents an opportunity to accrue 300% profits on investments due to the appreciating value of the QUBE coin throughout the presale.</p>
<p class="s5">InQubeta's engaging NFT marketplace contributes to its potential to grow by 1000% in 2023. This virtual marketplace serves as a space for AI startups to exhibit their curated collections of popular NFTs. The unique NFTs attract QUBE investors to actively support their preferred AI startups by purchasing NFT assets. As an incentive, AI startups can offer discounts on products and services or rewards as equity-based NFTs, further solidifying InQubeta's reputation as one of the best DeFi investment prospects.</p>
<p class="s8"></p>
Bitcoin (BTC) Rises in Value Following a Surge in Accumulation
<p class="s5">Bitcoin utilizes its native BTC token to enable secure peer-to-peer transactions. Since its inception in 2009, Bitcoin has gained immense popularity as a pioneering crypto project many cryptocurrencies imitate. Between late June and July 4, 2023, whales and institutional investors in the BTC cryptocurrency actively amassed billions of dollars of Bitcoin at an accelerated pace. Their holdings ranged from 10 to 10,000 BTC, totaling over 154,600 BTC and yielding over $4.7 billion.</p>
<p class="s5">This surge in accumulation occurred after BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, filed for a spot in the Bitcoin project's exchange-traded fund (ETF). Afterward, the BTC token recorded heightened trading activity, propelling the price of each Bitcoin to rise above $31,000, reaching a new yearly high. Renowned crypto analyst Willy Woo has speculated that this progressive price trend may lead to the value of the BTC token possibly surpassing $300,000 in the future.</p>
Conclusion
<p class="s5">Investors and enthusiasts in the DeFi market are intrigued by the rapid accumulation of Bitcoin by whales and institutional investors and the promising growth of InQubeta's QUBE coin. The influx of billions of dollars into Bitcoin's funding showcases the continued interest and confidence in the leading cryptocurrency, with price predictions reaching new highs. Conversely, InQubeta's unique combination of crypto, profitability, and AI technology positions it as one of the best DeFi cryptocurrencies, with a projected growth of 1000% in 2023.</p>
<p class="s16">Visit InQubeta Presale</p>
<p>Join The InQubeta Communities</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Network’s Report Card - Solana (SOL) Seeks NFT Support As Tradecurve Makes Market Bullish]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-networks-report-card-solana-sol-seeks-nft-support-as-tradecurve-makes-market-bullish</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-93.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-93.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-93.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/cardano-ada-networks-report-card-solana-sol-seeks-nft-support-as-tradecurve-makes-market-bullish</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In recent weeks, the crypto market has traveled through a bumpy road, with its fair share of ups and downs. For one, Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) have introduced new updates to improve their shaky position.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the same time, Tradecurve (TCRV) launch has captured a lot of attention. This new project has become an instant hit due to its uniqueness, and enormous growth potential. Its ongoing presale has broken records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Cardano&rsquo;s (ADA) Network Activity Falls
<p>The Cardano (ADA) community is hopeful that the recent developments in its ecosystem, including the release of a novel Dynamic P2P networking scheme, will increase the traction on the network. Dynamic P2P has been launched to bring scalability and modularity to the Cardano network. However, experts have raised concerns over the latest on-chain data related to Cardano.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per Santiment&rsquo;s data, the number of daily active addresses on the Cardano network has plummeted by 71% in the past month. The social dominance of Cardano has also taken a hit. Subsequently, the exchange rate of Cardano has suffered a drop of 23% in the last 30 days. At press time, Cardano is available to change hands at $0.29.</p>
<p></p>
Solana (SOL) Aims To Benefit From Firedancer
<p>To get out of the clutches of bears, and prevent its price from falling further, Solana (SOL) has shifted its focus to the NFT space. This shift in focus has come as Solana has taken a dip of 11% in the past 30 days.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result, the current exchange rate of Solana is $19.19, which is 93% below its peak of $260.06. However, the new validator client for Solana, Firedancer, is expected to provide market support to SOL.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per the data from Messari, Firedancer can lower latency times on the Solana network, enhancing DeFi maturity. This, in turn, will enable faster transaction processing on Solana, attracting more users to the network. Meanwhile, analysts have pointed out the declining TVL of Solana.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Presale Becomes More Appealing With 50x Growth
<p>According to data, about 5 new cryptocurrencies enter the market every day, and there are more than 26,000 digital currencies in circulation. Subsequently, crypto trading has also boomed. However, existing crypto exchanges have been criticized for their high fees, limited investment options, and data insecurity. To address these issues, and meet dynamic market demands, Tradecurve (TCRV) has launched a disruptive crypto exchange.</p>
<p>This new Web3 trading platform enables users to invest in different markets, such as forex, equity, cryptocurrency, CFDs, and more, with a single account. What is more exciting for traders is the platform&rsquo;s privacy feature. It does not require users to fulfill any KYC requirements. Contrary to this, exchanges like Coinbase and Robinhood mandate users to share their private details.</p>
<p>Additionally, the platform boasts high-leverage trading that starts from 500:1, and a VIP account service. It will also provide traders with distributed liquidity, and non-custodial storage to enhance their trading experience. The Metaverse Trading Academy is another remarkable feature of this platform. Through the academy, users can learn better and more profitable trading strategies.</p>
<p>The presale round of the platform is live, and a TCRV token is available to purchase for $0.018, an 80% increase from the launch price. Experts forecast that the tokens will record 50x gains during the presale round, and 100 times growth after their launch on tier-1 exchanges.</p>
<p>To find more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token, visit the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent weeks, the crypto market has traveled through a bumpy road, with its fair share of ups and downs. For one, Cardano (ADA) and Solana (SOL) have introduced new updates to improve their shaky position.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the same time, Tradecurve (TCRV) launch has captured a lot of attention. This new project has become an instant hit due to its uniqueness, and enormous growth potential. Its ongoing presale has broken records.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
Cardano&rsquo;s (ADA) Network Activity Falls
<p>The Cardano (ADA) community is hopeful that the recent developments in its ecosystem, including the release of a novel Dynamic P2P networking scheme, will increase the traction on the network. Dynamic P2P has been launched to bring scalability and modularity to the Cardano network. However, experts have raised concerns over the latest on-chain data related to Cardano.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per Santiment&rsquo;s data, the number of daily active addresses on the Cardano network has plummeted by 71% in the past month. The social dominance of Cardano has also taken a hit. Subsequently, the exchange rate of Cardano has suffered a drop of 23% in the last 30 days. At press time, Cardano is available to change hands at $0.29.</p>
<p></p>
Solana (SOL) Aims To Benefit From Firedancer
<p>To get out of the clutches of bears, and prevent its price from falling further, Solana (SOL) has shifted its focus to the NFT space. This shift in focus has come as Solana has taken a dip of 11% in the past 30 days.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As a result, the current exchange rate of Solana is $19.19, which is 93% below its peak of $260.06. However, the new validator client for Solana, Firedancer, is expected to provide market support to SOL.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As per the data from Messari, Firedancer can lower latency times on the Solana network, enhancing DeFi maturity. This, in turn, will enable faster transaction processing on Solana, attracting more users to the network. Meanwhile, analysts have pointed out the declining TVL of Solana.</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve Presale Becomes More Appealing With 50x Growth
<p>According to data, about 5 new cryptocurrencies enter the market every day, and there are more than 26,000 digital currencies in circulation. Subsequently, crypto trading has also boomed. However, existing crypto exchanges have been criticized for their high fees, limited investment options, and data insecurity. To address these issues, and meet dynamic market demands, Tradecurve (TCRV) has launched a disruptive crypto exchange.</p>
<p>This new Web3 trading platform enables users to invest in different markets, such as forex, equity, cryptocurrency, CFDs, and more, with a single account. What is more exciting for traders is the platform&rsquo;s privacy feature. It does not require users to fulfill any KYC requirements. Contrary to this, exchanges like Coinbase and Robinhood mandate users to share their private details.</p>
<p>Additionally, the platform boasts high-leverage trading that starts from 500:1, and a VIP account service. It will also provide traders with distributed liquidity, and non-custodial storage to enhance their trading experience. The Metaverse Trading Academy is another remarkable feature of this platform. Through the academy, users can learn better and more profitable trading strategies.</p>
<p>The presale round of the platform is live, and a TCRV token is available to purchase for $0.018, an 80% increase from the launch price. Experts forecast that the tokens will record 50x gains during the presale round, and 100 times growth after their launch on tier-1 exchanges.</p>
<p>To find more information about Tradecurve and the TCRV token, visit the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[FSB Publishes Recommendations for Global Regulatory Framework]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-regulatory-framework</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fsb-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fsb-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/fsb-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 14:26:45 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/fsb-publishes-recommendations-for-global-regulatory-framework</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Financial Stability Board (FSB) published its finalized global regulatory framework for crypto assets. </p>
<p>On Monday, the Financial Stability Board (FSB) published its recommendations for a global regulatory framework for crypto-assets to &ldquo;promote the comprehensiveness and international consistency of regulatory and supervisory approaches.&rdquo;</p>
FSB Bases Framework on Principle of &ldquo;Same Activity, Same Risk, Same Regulation&rdquo; &nbsp;
<p>The FSB is an international organization that monitors the global financial system. The organization published guidelines for a global approach to crypto-related activities.</p>
<p>The board was tasked by the Group of 20 Nations (G20) to coordinate the delivery of an effective regulatory, supervisory and oversight framework for crypto-assets in light of recent events that took place in the digital asset industry.</p>
<p>The G20 previously said in a document summarizing the outcomes of meetings held with finance ministers and central bank governors that the FSB, IMF (International Monetary Fund), and BIS (Bank for International Settlements) are to deliver papers and recommendations establishing standards for a global crypto regulatory framework.</p>
<p>The FSB&rsquo;s document consists of two sets of recommendations: high-level recommendations for crypto regulation in general and &ldquo;revised high-level recommendations&rdquo; for a &ldquo;global stablecoin.&rdquo;</p>
FSB Maintains Respect for Privacy
<p>According to the FSB&rsquo;s recommendations, crypto platforms must segregate clients&rsquo; digital assets from their own funds and must clearly separate their functions to avoid conflicts of interest. Regulators are responsible for ensuring tight cross-border cooperation and oversight.</p>
<p>Despite stricter oversight measures, the FSB respects the principle of privacy. The international organization demands local regulators to ensure that there is no activity that &ldquo;may frustrate the identification of the responsible entity or affiliated entities.&rdquo; the regulator points to DeFi protocols in its recommendation of privacy and states:</p>

<p>Authorities should have access to the data as necessary and appropriate to fulfil their regulatory, supervisory and oversight mandates.</p>

FSB Requires Stablecoin Issuers to Have At least One &ldquo;Governance Body&rdquo;
<p>In its guidelines, the FSB addressed global stablecoin arrangements (GSCs) across jurisdictions to address their potential risks at a domestic and international level while supporting responsible innovation and providing adequate flexibility for jurisdictions to implement domestic approaches.</p>
<p>The board mandates any stablecoin issuer to have one or more identifiable and responsible individuals or legal entities it calls a &ldquo;governance body.&rdquo; It further requires issuers to maintain minimum reserve assets at a 1:1 ratio unless the issuer &ldquo;is subject to adequate prudential requirements&rdquo; equivalent to commercial bank standards.</p>
<p>The FSB also introduced a potential obligation for &ldquo;global stablecoin&rdquo; issuers to obtain a permit to operate in each jurisdiction. Guidelines state:</p>

<p>Authorities should not permit the operation of a GSC arrangement in their jurisdiction unless the GSC arrangement meets all of their jurisdiction&rsquo;s regulatory, supervisory, and oversight requirements, including affirmative approval.</p>

Implementation of Recommendations To Be Reviewed by End 2025
<p>The guidelines published by the FSB make up the first part of a global crypto framework, with further guidance from the IMF and BIS to come.</p>
<p>The FSB and the IMF will jointly submit &ldquo;a synthesis paper integrating the macroeconomic and regulatory perspectives of crypto assets&rdquo; in September 2023.</p>
<p>The IMF will also independently report on the &ldquo;potential macro-financial implications of the widespread adoption&rdquo; of CBDCs. At the same time, the BIS will provide a report on analytical and conceptual issues and possible risk mitigation strategies related to crypto assets.</p>
<p>The FSB said it will review the state of implementing its recommendations worldwide by the end of 2025.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Financial Stability Board (FSB) published its finalized global regulatory framework for crypto assets. </p>
<p>On Monday, the Financial Stability Board (FSB) published its recommendations for a global regulatory framework for crypto-assets to &ldquo;promote the comprehensiveness and international consistency of regulatory and supervisory approaches.&rdquo;</p>
FSB Bases Framework on Principle of &ldquo;Same Activity, Same Risk, Same Regulation&rdquo; &nbsp;
<p>The FSB is an international organization that monitors the global financial system. The organization published guidelines for a global approach to crypto-related activities.</p>
<p>The board was tasked by the Group of 20 Nations (G20) to coordinate the delivery of an effective regulatory, supervisory and oversight framework for crypto-assets in light of recent events that took place in the digital asset industry.</p>
<p>The G20 previously said in a document summarizing the outcomes of meetings held with finance ministers and central bank governors that the FSB, IMF (International Monetary Fund), and BIS (Bank for International Settlements) are to deliver papers and recommendations establishing standards for a global crypto regulatory framework.</p>
<p>The FSB&rsquo;s document consists of two sets of recommendations: high-level recommendations for crypto regulation in general and &ldquo;revised high-level recommendations&rdquo; for a &ldquo;global stablecoin.&rdquo;</p>
FSB Maintains Respect for Privacy
<p>According to the FSB&rsquo;s recommendations, crypto platforms must segregate clients&rsquo; digital assets from their own funds and must clearly separate their functions to avoid conflicts of interest. Regulators are responsible for ensuring tight cross-border cooperation and oversight.</p>
<p>Despite stricter oversight measures, the FSB respects the principle of privacy. The international organization demands local regulators to ensure that there is no activity that &ldquo;may frustrate the identification of the responsible entity or affiliated entities.&rdquo; the regulator points to DeFi protocols in its recommendation of privacy and states:</p>

<p>Authorities should have access to the data as necessary and appropriate to fulfil their regulatory, supervisory and oversight mandates.</p>

FSB Requires Stablecoin Issuers to Have At least One &ldquo;Governance Body&rdquo;
<p>In its guidelines, the FSB addressed global stablecoin arrangements (GSCs) across jurisdictions to address their potential risks at a domestic and international level while supporting responsible innovation and providing adequate flexibility for jurisdictions to implement domestic approaches.</p>
<p>The board mandates any stablecoin issuer to have one or more identifiable and responsible individuals or legal entities it calls a &ldquo;governance body.&rdquo; It further requires issuers to maintain minimum reserve assets at a 1:1 ratio unless the issuer &ldquo;is subject to adequate prudential requirements&rdquo; equivalent to commercial bank standards.</p>
<p>The FSB also introduced a potential obligation for &ldquo;global stablecoin&rdquo; issuers to obtain a permit to operate in each jurisdiction. Guidelines state:</p>

<p>Authorities should not permit the operation of a GSC arrangement in their jurisdiction unless the GSC arrangement meets all of their jurisdiction&rsquo;s regulatory, supervisory, and oversight requirements, including affirmative approval.</p>

Implementation of Recommendations To Be Reviewed by End 2025
<p>The guidelines published by the FSB make up the first part of a global crypto framework, with further guidance from the IMF and BIS to come.</p>
<p>The FSB and the IMF will jointly submit &ldquo;a synthesis paper integrating the macroeconomic and regulatory perspectives of crypto assets&rdquo; in September 2023.</p>
<p>The IMF will also independently report on the &ldquo;potential macro-financial implications of the widespread adoption&rdquo; of CBDCs. At the same time, the BIS will provide a report on analytical and conceptual issues and possible risk mitigation strategies related to crypto assets.</p>
<p>The FSB said it will review the state of implementing its recommendations worldwide by the end of 2025.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[NEAR APAC Showcases “Unlimited Future” at Vietnam's Premier Blockchain Conference]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/near-apac-showcases-unlimited-future-at-vietnams-premier-blockchain-conference</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/387e8be5-f808-4f19-80d5-29283cadbd64_1689597757tAO6BYosSi.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/387e8be5-f808-4f19-80d5-29283cadbd64_1689597757tAO6BYosSi.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/387e8be5-f808-4f19-80d5-29283cadbd64_1689597757tAO6BYosSi.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 13:49:40 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/near-apac-showcases-unlimited-future-at-vietnams-premier-blockchain-conference</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>NEAR APAC, Vietnam's largest blockchain conference, is set to take place on September 9th-10th, 2023, at Thiskyhall Sala Convention Center in Ho Chi Minh City. The event promises to be a global gathering, bringing together leading blockchain experts, developers, students, enterprises, and startups from the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region and beyond.</p><p>Themed "Unlimited Future," NEAR APAC will serve as a platform for exploring the latest advancements in blockchain technology and multi-chain decentralized applications within the APAC region. The conference will offer a diverse range of activities designed to engage and inspire participants beyond traditional panel discussions and keynote presentations.</p><p>Participants can immerse themselves in a virtual reality playground, explore the Web3 Dating zone tailored for startups and venture capitalists, witness cutting-edge technology demonstrations, and partake in thrilling NFT and gaming activities. NEAR APAC aims to provide a dynamic and interactive environment that fosters networking, collaboration, and the exploration of emerging technologies.</p><p>With over 8,000 expected attendees, NEAR APAC is set to attract a wide array of participants, including 100+ global blockchain leaders as speakers, 1,000+ developers, students from 10+ universities, 300+ projects and startups, and representatives from 100+ enterprises. Register now at and secure your place at the forefront of the blockchain revolution.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The world&rsquo;s leading web3 PR and marketing agency, MarketAcross&mdash;known for their work in the region with companies like Polygon and Hashed Emergent&mdash;will be joining the event as a media partner. This follows multiple web3 events where MarketAcross serves as the official media partner like Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, Paris Blockchain Week and IVS Kyoto.</p><p>The conference offers unique opportunities for each target audience:</p><p>Builders: NEAR APAC will host a Web3 Hackfest, Web3 Code Challenge, and Builder stage, providing developers with a platform to showcase their skills and engage in collaborative coding sessions. The conference will also feature a dedicated hacking area for participants to further explore their ideas. Learn more at https://web3hackfest.org/.</p><p>VCs and Start-ups: The Greenhouse Program at NEAR APAC brings venture capitalists on board as speakers, partners, and judges for the Hackathon. Start-ups can benefit from the guidance and support of experienced investors. Visit https://nearapac.org/the-greenhouse/ for more information.</p><p>Blockchain Community, IT Students, and Start-ups: NEAR APAC hosts the Web2 &amp; Web3 Career Fair in collaboration with TOP CV, Vietnam's largest recruitment platform. This unique opportunity allows start-ups and projects to connect with talented individuals and find suitable candidates for their companies.</p><p>NEAR APAC is further elevating the event experience with additional attractions designed to captivate and engage attendees. A Web2 technology show will feature fascinating displays such as robot beer servers, holograms, and flying motorcycles. A travel game with a substantial prize pool will incentivize participants to explore every booth, maximizing the benefits for booth sponsors. By completing tasks and collecting NFTs, participants will have a chance to share in the $15,000 prize pool. These activities aim to drive user engagement and provide booth sponsors with maximum marketing exposure during the event.</p><p>Register now and secure your place at the forefront of the blockchain revolution.</p><p>About NEAR APAC:</p><p>NEAR APAC is Vietnam's largest blockchain/crypto conference entity, focused on showcasing the latest advancements in blockchain technology and multi-chain decentralized applications within the APAC region. With its "Unlimited Future" theme, NEAR APAC aims to foster networking, collaboration, and the exploration of emerging technologies in an interactive environment. For more information, visit https://nearapac.org/.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactNear APACnearapac@near.foundation]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>NEAR APAC, Vietnam's largest blockchain conference, is set to take place on September 9th-10th, 2023, at Thiskyhall Sala Convention Center in Ho Chi Minh City. The event promises to be a global gathering, bringing together leading blockchain experts, developers, students, enterprises, and startups from the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region and beyond.</p><p>Themed "Unlimited Future," NEAR APAC will serve as a platform for exploring the latest advancements in blockchain technology and multi-chain decentralized applications within the APAC region. The conference will offer a diverse range of activities designed to engage and inspire participants beyond traditional panel discussions and keynote presentations.</p><p>Participants can immerse themselves in a virtual reality playground, explore the Web3 Dating zone tailored for startups and venture capitalists, witness cutting-edge technology demonstrations, and partake in thrilling NFT and gaming activities. NEAR APAC aims to provide a dynamic and interactive environment that fosters networking, collaboration, and the exploration of emerging technologies.</p><p>With over 8,000 expected attendees, NEAR APAC is set to attract a wide array of participants, including 100+ global blockchain leaders as speakers, 1,000+ developers, students from 10+ universities, 300+ projects and startups, and representatives from 100+ enterprises. Register now at and secure your place at the forefront of the blockchain revolution.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The world&rsquo;s leading web3 PR and marketing agency, MarketAcross&mdash;known for their work in the region with companies like Polygon and Hashed Emergent&mdash;will be joining the event as a media partner. This follows multiple web3 events where MarketAcross serves as the official media partner like Korea Blockchain Week, WebX, Paris Blockchain Week and IVS Kyoto.</p><p>The conference offers unique opportunities for each target audience:</p><p>Builders: NEAR APAC will host a Web3 Hackfest, Web3 Code Challenge, and Builder stage, providing developers with a platform to showcase their skills and engage in collaborative coding sessions. The conference will also feature a dedicated hacking area for participants to further explore their ideas. Learn more at https://web3hackfest.org/.</p><p>VCs and Start-ups: The Greenhouse Program at NEAR APAC brings venture capitalists on board as speakers, partners, and judges for the Hackathon. Start-ups can benefit from the guidance and support of experienced investors. Visit https://nearapac.org/the-greenhouse/ for more information.</p><p>Blockchain Community, IT Students, and Start-ups: NEAR APAC hosts the Web2 &amp; Web3 Career Fair in collaboration with TOP CV, Vietnam's largest recruitment platform. This unique opportunity allows start-ups and projects to connect with talented individuals and find suitable candidates for their companies.</p><p>NEAR APAC is further elevating the event experience with additional attractions designed to captivate and engage attendees. A Web2 technology show will feature fascinating displays such as robot beer servers, holograms, and flying motorcycles. A travel game with a substantial prize pool will incentivize participants to explore every booth, maximizing the benefits for booth sponsors. By completing tasks and collecting NFTs, participants will have a chance to share in the $15,000 prize pool. These activities aim to drive user engagement and provide booth sponsors with maximum marketing exposure during the event.</p><p>Register now and secure your place at the forefront of the blockchain revolution.</p><p>About NEAR APAC:</p><p>NEAR APAC is Vietnam's largest blockchain/crypto conference entity, focused on showcasing the latest advancements in blockchain technology and multi-chain decentralized applications within the APAC region. With its "Unlimited Future" theme, NEAR APAC aims to foster networking, collaboration, and the exploration of emerging technologies in an interactive environment. For more information, visit https://nearapac.org/.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactNear APACnearapac@near.foundation]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Network Now Live On Binance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-lightning-network-now-live-on-binance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-new-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-lightning-network-now-live-on-binance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Binance has successfully integrated Bitcoin Lightning Network on its platform for faster BTC withdrawals and deposits.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Integrates Bitcoin Lightning Network
<p>Binance, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has achieved a significant milestone by successfully integrating the Bitcoin Lightning Network on its platform. Around the end of June, the company had announced its decision to integrate the Bitcoin Lightning Network to scale up its BTC transaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Earlier today, the Binance team put out a statement on its website, announcing the successful integration and providing all the details users would need to access these transactions. Binance users will now be able to now conduct BTC deposits and withdrawals on the Lightning Network, opening up new possibilities for faster and more cost-effective transactions.</p>
How Does Lightning Network Work?
<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network serves as a layer-two scaling solution that operates on top of the Bitcoin blockchain. Its primary objective is to enhance transaction speed, reduce fees, and address scalability concerns. By creating off-chain transaction channels, the Lightning Network facilitates near-instantaneous and economically viable transactions for users.</p>
<p>With the completion of the integration, Binance users can locate their designated Bitcoin deposit addresses specifically tailored for the Lightning Network. These unique deposit addresses can be found on the platform's Deposit Crypto page.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Lightning Network Advantages
<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network offers several advantages over traditional on-chain transactions, primarily by alleviating congestion on the Bitcoin blockchain and enabling a higher number of transactions per second. By moving most transactions off-chain, the Lightning Network significantly enhances the scalability of the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>Because Lightning Network transactions do not require confirmation by miners, it is conducive to near-instantaneous payment settlements. Users can enjoy the convenience of transactions being processed within seconds or even milliseconds, further enhancing the user experience.</p>
<p>Furthermore, transactions on the Bitcoin Lightning Network typically incur lower fees than those executed directly on the Bitcoin network. This cost reduction makes microtransactions economically viable and encourages broader adoption across various use cases.</p>
<p>In addition to its speed and cost advantages, the Lightning Network provides enhanced privacy protection. By not revealing individual transaction details on the blockchain, the Lightning Network safeguards users' privacy, ensuring a secure and confidential transaction environment.</p>
<p>This move from Binance underscores its commitment to embracing innovative solutions that enhance cryptocurrency functionality and usability. By leveraging the Lightning Network's advantages, Binance aims to improve the efficiency and speed of Bitcoin transactions, thereby offering users a more streamlined trading experience.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance has successfully integrated Bitcoin Lightning Network on its platform for faster BTC withdrawals and deposits.&nbsp;</p>
Binance Integrates Bitcoin Lightning Network
<p>Binance, one of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges, has achieved a significant milestone by successfully integrating the Bitcoin Lightning Network on its platform. Around the end of June, the company had announced its decision to integrate the Bitcoin Lightning Network to scale up its BTC transaction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Earlier today, the Binance team put out a statement on its website, announcing the successful integration and providing all the details users would need to access these transactions. Binance users will now be able to now conduct BTC deposits and withdrawals on the Lightning Network, opening up new possibilities for faster and more cost-effective transactions.</p>
How Does Lightning Network Work?
<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network serves as a layer-two scaling solution that operates on top of the Bitcoin blockchain. Its primary objective is to enhance transaction speed, reduce fees, and address scalability concerns. By creating off-chain transaction channels, the Lightning Network facilitates near-instantaneous and economically viable transactions for users.</p>
<p>With the completion of the integration, Binance users can locate their designated Bitcoin deposit addresses specifically tailored for the Lightning Network. These unique deposit addresses can be found on the platform's Deposit Crypto page.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
Lightning Network Advantages
<p>The Bitcoin Lightning Network offers several advantages over traditional on-chain transactions, primarily by alleviating congestion on the Bitcoin blockchain and enabling a higher number of transactions per second. By moving most transactions off-chain, the Lightning Network significantly enhances the scalability of the Bitcoin network.</p>
<p>Because Lightning Network transactions do not require confirmation by miners, it is conducive to near-instantaneous payment settlements. Users can enjoy the convenience of transactions being processed within seconds or even milliseconds, further enhancing the user experience.</p>
<p>Furthermore, transactions on the Bitcoin Lightning Network typically incur lower fees than those executed directly on the Bitcoin network. This cost reduction makes microtransactions economically viable and encourages broader adoption across various use cases.</p>
<p>In addition to its speed and cost advantages, the Lightning Network provides enhanced privacy protection. By not revealing individual transaction details on the blockchain, the Lightning Network safeguards users' privacy, ensuring a secure and confidential transaction environment.</p>
<p>This move from Binance underscores its commitment to embracing innovative solutions that enhance cryptocurrency functionality and usability. By leveraging the Lightning Network's advantages, Binance aims to improve the efficiency and speed of Bitcoin transactions, thereby offering users a more streamlined trading experience.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Kalima Secures $10 Million Investment Commitment and Announces Private Sale and DEX Listing]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Kalima2_1689336268PZjRljAPG7.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Kalima2_1689336268PZjRljAPG7.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Kalima2_1689336268PZjRljAPG7.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:04:24 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/kalima-secures-10-million-investment-commitment-and-announces-private-sale-and-dex-listing</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Delegated proof-of-stake blockchain Kalima has entered into an agreement with ABO Digital, a private alternative funding group based in the Bahamas and Dubai. This significant partnership involves a commitment of US$10 million into the French-based blockchain company. Kalima has also released details of its KLX token sale.</p><p>Kalima is a rapidly growing ecosystem that allows businesses, developers, and startups to build web3 enterprise and data governance applications, with a focus on IoT (Internet of Things) data in order to solve real-world problems.</p>Kalima CEO Andr&eacute; Legendre said: &ldquo;The funding commitment from ABO Digital marks a significant milestone for Kalima, which plans to utilize the funds to further innovate and refine IoT solutions to revolutionize industries and drive digital transformation. The arrangement with ABO Digital will enable Kalima to enhance its IoT blockchain solutions for industrial companies and bolster strategic partnerships within the IoT and blockchain ecosystem.&rdquo;&ldquo;We are excited to work with the Kalima team going forward,&rdquo; said Amine Nedjai, CEO of ABO Digital. &ldquo;Kalima&rsquo;s innovative approach and expertise in web3 enterprise applications align perfectly with our commitment to driving technological advancements in enterprise blockchain solutions.&rdquo;<p>The Kalima team has also announced a 24-hour private sale of its KLX token on Pinksale. The event will provisionally take place on July 19. A general purpose utility token, KLX can be used to pay for transactions and access blockchain services on the Kalima protocol.</p><p>To support the growth of the KLX token, on July 10 Kalima Blockchain Governance created several proposals. These include bridging the KLX token from Polygon to the Ethereum network and proposing the 24-hour token sale on Pinksale. Following completion of the private sale event, KLX will be made available for trading on Uniswap, where a KLX-ETH pair will be established.</p><p>The primary objective of the private sale, which will have a hard cap of 300 ETH, is to create a sufficiently deep liquidity pool on Uniswap. The Uniswap listing of the KLX token is planned for July 21.</p><p>About Kalima</p><p>Kalima is a low-consumption layer one blockchain for enterprises and IoT. It provides an interconnected blockchain for achieving decentralization and increasing scalability, adopting a framework popularized by blockchains such as Cosmos and Polkadot. Kalima can be embedded into very small IoT devices and allows AI inferences to be executed at the network&rsquo;s edge using its native smart contracts.</p><p>About ABO Digital</p><p>ABO Digital is an investment firm providing alternative financing solutions to cryptocurrency projects around the world. As part of the Alpha Blue Ocean group, which has executed more than $2B in financing commitments for publicly listed companies since its inception in 2017, ABO Digital brings institutional-grade expertise and flexible financing solutions for blockchain developers worldwide.</p><p class="ql-align-center"></p>ContactHead of PRYousef BatterWhite Label Strategyyousef.batter@whitelabelstrategy.io+971559356531]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Delegated proof-of-stake blockchain Kalima has entered into an agreement with ABO Digital, a private alternative funding group based in the Bahamas and Dubai. This significant partnership involves a commitment of US$10 million into the French-based blockchain company. Kalima has also released details of its KLX token sale.</p><p>Kalima is a rapidly growing ecosystem that allows businesses, developers, and startups to build web3 enterprise and data governance applications, with a focus on IoT (Internet of Things) data in order to solve real-world problems.</p>Kalima CEO Andr&eacute; Legendre said: &ldquo;The funding commitment from ABO Digital marks a significant milestone for Kalima, which plans to utilize the funds to further innovate and refine IoT solutions to revolutionize industries and drive digital transformation. The arrangement with ABO Digital will enable Kalima to enhance its IoT blockchain solutions for industrial companies and bolster strategic partnerships within the IoT and blockchain ecosystem.&rdquo;&ldquo;We are excited to work with the Kalima team going forward,&rdquo; said Amine Nedjai, CEO of ABO Digital. &ldquo;Kalima&rsquo;s innovative approach and expertise in web3 enterprise applications align perfectly with our commitment to driving technological advancements in enterprise blockchain solutions.&rdquo;<p>The Kalima team has also announced a 24-hour private sale of its KLX token on Pinksale. The event will provisionally take place on July 19. A general purpose utility token, KLX can be used to pay for transactions and access blockchain services on the Kalima protocol.</p><p>To support the growth of the KLX token, on July 10 Kalima Blockchain Governance created several proposals. These include bridging the KLX token from Polygon to the Ethereum network and proposing the 24-hour token sale on Pinksale. Following completion of the private sale event, KLX will be made available for trading on Uniswap, where a KLX-ETH pair will be established.</p><p>The primary objective of the private sale, which will have a hard cap of 300 ETH, is to create a sufficiently deep liquidity pool on Uniswap. The Uniswap listing of the KLX token is planned for July 21.</p><p>About Kalima</p><p>Kalima is a low-consumption layer one blockchain for enterprises and IoT. It provides an interconnected blockchain for achieving decentralization and increasing scalability, adopting a framework popularized by blockchains such as Cosmos and Polkadot. Kalima can be embedded into very small IoT devices and allows AI inferences to be executed at the network&rsquo;s edge using its native smart contracts.</p><p>About ABO Digital</p><p>ABO Digital is an investment firm providing alternative financing solutions to cryptocurrency projects around the world. As part of the Alpha Blue Ocean group, which has executed more than $2B in financing commitments for publicly listed companies since its inception in 2017, ABO Digital brings institutional-grade expertise and flexible financing solutions for blockchain developers worldwide.</p><p class="ql-align-center"></p>ContactHead of PRYousef BatterWhite Label Strategyyousef.batter@whitelabelstrategy.io+971559356531]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Australian Banks Block Payments to “High-Risk” Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/australian-banks-block-payments-to-high-risk-crypto-exchanges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/australia-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/australia-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/australia-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:54:56 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/australian-banks-block-payments-to-high-risk-crypto-exchanges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>National Australia Bank joins other large Australian banks to block payments to &ldquo;high-risk&rdquo; crypto exchanges to protect customers. </p>
<p>National Australia Bank (NAB) announced Monday that it had blocked some payments to &ldquo;high-risk&rdquo; crypto exchanges over the past few months to protect its customers.</p>
<p>The lender said Australians lost around $151 million last year due to crypto-related scams. The NAB did not disclose which platforms it involved.</p>
NAB Halts Millions in Payments Between March and July
<p>In a statement, the NAB said it &ldquo;intervened&rdquo; in more than AU$270 million worth of payments which raised concerns over scams in the past four months between March and July.</p>
<p>The bank said it introduced several measures to protect its customers from scams. Chris Sheehan, the NAB&rsquo;s Executive for Group Investigations and Fraud, said:</p>

<p>Introducing payment prompts, taking action on spoofing and stopping the use of links in unexpected text messages are among key measures we&rsquo;ve introduced recently.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re now also taking action to block some payments to high-risk cryptocurrency exchanges in a further effort to stop scammers.</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;While many customers ultimately complete their payment after receiving a prompt, we&rsquo;re seeing around $290,000 worth of payments abandoned daily. This tells us that customers are taking the time to stop and think before they make a payment.</p>
<p>While we&rsquo;re focused on making banking simple and digital, we&rsquo;ve added this extra friction to help alert customers to warning signs. We need to do everything we can to stop the crime before it happens.&rdquo;</p>

Australian Banks Become Stricter to Prevent Customers Falling Victim to Scams
<p>The NAB joins the Commonwealth Bank of Australia to restrict customer payments to &ldquo;certain&rdquo; exchanges due to crypto-related scams.</p>
<p>The NAB further said in its statement that almost 50% of scam funds reported to the Australian Financial Crimes Exchange were linked to crypto in a recent 30-day period.</p>
<p>Mr Sheehan noted:</p>

<p>These scammers are part of organized, transnational crime groups. Increasingly, we&rsquo;re seeing them use cryptocurrency platforms to send stolen funds quickly and often overseas.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Australia Bank joins other large Australian banks to block payments to &ldquo;high-risk&rdquo; crypto exchanges to protect customers. </p>
<p>National Australia Bank (NAB) announced Monday that it had blocked some payments to &ldquo;high-risk&rdquo; crypto exchanges over the past few months to protect its customers.</p>
<p>The lender said Australians lost around $151 million last year due to crypto-related scams. The NAB did not disclose which platforms it involved.</p>
NAB Halts Millions in Payments Between March and July
<p>In a statement, the NAB said it &ldquo;intervened&rdquo; in more than AU$270 million worth of payments which raised concerns over scams in the past four months between March and July.</p>
<p>The bank said it introduced several measures to protect its customers from scams. Chris Sheehan, the NAB&rsquo;s Executive for Group Investigations and Fraud, said:</p>

<p>Introducing payment prompts, taking action on spoofing and stopping the use of links in unexpected text messages are among key measures we&rsquo;ve introduced recently.</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re now also taking action to block some payments to high-risk cryptocurrency exchanges in a further effort to stop scammers.</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;While many customers ultimately complete their payment after receiving a prompt, we&rsquo;re seeing around $290,000 worth of payments abandoned daily. This tells us that customers are taking the time to stop and think before they make a payment.</p>
<p>While we&rsquo;re focused on making banking simple and digital, we&rsquo;ve added this extra friction to help alert customers to warning signs. We need to do everything we can to stop the crime before it happens.&rdquo;</p>

Australian Banks Become Stricter to Prevent Customers Falling Victim to Scams
<p>The NAB joins the Commonwealth Bank of Australia to restrict customer payments to &ldquo;certain&rdquo; exchanges due to crypto-related scams.</p>
<p>The NAB further said in its statement that almost 50% of scam funds reported to the Australian Financial Crimes Exchange were linked to crypto in a recent 30-day period.</p>
<p>Mr Sheehan noted:</p>

<p>These scammers are part of organized, transnational crime groups. Increasingly, we&rsquo;re seeing them use cryptocurrency platforms to send stolen funds quickly and often overseas.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[5 Thrilling Augmented Reality Games Available To Play Right Now]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/5-thrilling-augmented-reality-games-available-to-play-right-now</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/5-thrilling-augmented-reality-games-available-to-play-right-now</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The interactive monster-collecting app Pokemon Go was a global phenomenon that increased awareness of the potential of augmented reality games, inspiring millions of people around the world to grab their mobile device and set off into the great outdoors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since then, the AR gaming genre has grown to encompass quite a few fresh ideas. AR games work by using the device&rsquo;s camera to superimpose 3D graphical elements onto the real world, as viewed on its display. The idea is to incorporate the user&rsquo;s physical surroundings into the gameplay, creating a surreal mixed reality experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AR games involve mapping the user&rsquo;s surroundings in order to overlay 3D virtual objects onto it. In the case of Pokemon Go, it meant users could get out and about, exploring their town or city in order to hunt for collectible Pokemon creatures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One key advantage of AR games is that they can be played on even the cheapest mobile phone, so there&rsquo;s no need to invest in an expensive and bulky VR headset. Simply grab your phone, switch the game on and explore your surroundings to try and complete the objectives.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world. Here&rsquo;s some of the hottest new AR games you can try today!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Angry Birds AR: Isle of Pigs
<p>This is pretty much as you would imagine an augmented reality version of the popular Angry Birds game to be. Launch the game and it sets up a structure on a nearby table that can be viewed through your phone&rsquo;s camera. Then, you use a slingshot to shoot those colorful, loveable Angry Birds at the structure in an attempt to destroy it and kill those nasty green pigs hiding inside. There are 70 different levels on the game, and many of the original characters from the popular franchise appear in it. The game is a couple of years old, but it works well and provides a very different and entertaining take on the classic Angry Birds experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Ingress Prime
<p>Created by Niantic, the developer of the original AR hit Pokemon Go, Ingress Prime is widely considered to be one of the best AR games ever made. In the game, the discovery of an unknown, transdimensional force known as Exotic Matter by a team of scientists at CERN resulted in the creation of two factions, the Enlightened and the Resistance. The Enlightened faction seeks to harness and embrace the power of XM to transcend humanity to a higher dimension. Meanwhile the Resistance sees XM as humanity&rsquo;s biggest threat, and is sworn to defend mankind by resisting the efforts of the Enlightened faction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ingress Prime uses your device&rsquo;s GPS to locate and interact with &ldquo;portals&rdquo; in real-world locations, found at points of interest where human creativity is expressed, such as statues, monuments, unique architecture and historic buildings. Players choose a faction then use the map to find nearby portals, and are tasked with &ldquo;hacking&rdquo; them and building them up so the other team can&rsquo;t get them. The game uses the portals as elements of a science fiction backstory along with a continuous open narrative provided through various forms of media.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;
Peer
<p>Launching this summer, Peer is the creator of a unique social network that&rsquo;s overlaid onto the real world, where users can explore physical locations and find information and digital objects amid their surroundings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s an extremely ambitious project that aims to bring AR to the masses by overlaying 3D graphics atop of the entire world. In some ways, it can be considered an enhanced version of Google Maps, enabling users to search for nearby restaurants for example. When they arrive at their chosen restaurant to grab a bite to eat, they may be able to pick up a coupon placed outside by the restaurant owner, entitling them to a free coffee. Peer can also be used by creators, such as NFT artists, tasking people to visit different locations to mint digital collectibles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Alternatively, a dinosaur museum can create huge, 3D dinosaurs that roam around the physical world outside their premises, enticing people to come and visit its exhibits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Jurassic World Alive
<p>Staying with the dinosaur theme, Jurassic World Alive enables players to get outside in the real world searching for various dinosaurs they need to collect. In some ways it&rsquo;s similar to Pokemon Go, with users having to search different locations to discover the most difficult to find dinosaurs. Once they collect a dinosaur, they can train it and breed it to create hybrid dinosaurs, and then use them to fight battles with other players nearby.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the game initially had a few bugs, the developer has seemingly ironed most of them out and it has built up a loyal player base. Players can even subscribe to the game to earn rewards, instead of spending money on in-app purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Zombies, Run!&nbsp;
<p>The extremely original Zombies, Run! is not so much a game as a gamified fitness app that uses AR to simulate zombies and scare people into running away from them. To play the game, you&rsquo;ll need some earbuds or headphones to listen to the audio as it narrates the story and tasks you with completing various missions while you're out and about on your daily jog. As the story progresses, there will be occasional interruptions by flesh-eating zombies that jump out of the shadows and chase after you, forcing you to start sprinting to outrun them. The game also works just as well on a treadmill.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Zombies, Run! cleverly merges AR elements with an enthralling audio story to motivate people to keep moving and it has proven incredibly effective and popular. The first four missions are available to play for free, and new ones can be unlocked either by paying for them, or by completing various challenges each week.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The interactive monster-collecting app Pokemon Go was a global phenomenon that increased awareness of the potential of augmented reality games, inspiring millions of people around the world to grab their mobile device and set off into the great outdoors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since then, the AR gaming genre has grown to encompass quite a few fresh ideas. AR games work by using the device&rsquo;s camera to superimpose 3D graphical elements onto the real world, as viewed on its display. The idea is to incorporate the user&rsquo;s physical surroundings into the gameplay, creating a surreal mixed reality experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AR games involve mapping the user&rsquo;s surroundings in order to overlay 3D virtual objects onto it. In the case of Pokemon Go, it meant users could get out and about, exploring their town or city in order to hunt for collectible Pokemon creatures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One key advantage of AR games is that they can be played on even the cheapest mobile phone, so there&rsquo;s no need to invest in an expensive and bulky VR headset. Simply grab your phone, switch the game on and explore your surroundings to try and complete the objectives.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world. Here&rsquo;s some of the hottest new AR games you can try today!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Angry Birds AR: Isle of Pigs
<p>This is pretty much as you would imagine an augmented reality version of the popular Angry Birds game to be. Launch the game and it sets up a structure on a nearby table that can be viewed through your phone&rsquo;s camera. Then, you use a slingshot to shoot those colorful, loveable Angry Birds at the structure in an attempt to destroy it and kill those nasty green pigs hiding inside. There are 70 different levels on the game, and many of the original characters from the popular franchise appear in it. The game is a couple of years old, but it works well and provides a very different and entertaining take on the classic Angry Birds experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Ingress Prime
<p>Created by Niantic, the developer of the original AR hit Pokemon Go, Ingress Prime is widely considered to be one of the best AR games ever made. In the game, the discovery of an unknown, transdimensional force known as Exotic Matter by a team of scientists at CERN resulted in the creation of two factions, the Enlightened and the Resistance. The Enlightened faction seeks to harness and embrace the power of XM to transcend humanity to a higher dimension. Meanwhile the Resistance sees XM as humanity&rsquo;s biggest threat, and is sworn to defend mankind by resisting the efforts of the Enlightened faction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ingress Prime uses your device&rsquo;s GPS to locate and interact with &ldquo;portals&rdquo; in real-world locations, found at points of interest where human creativity is expressed, such as statues, monuments, unique architecture and historic buildings. Players choose a faction then use the map to find nearby portals, and are tasked with &ldquo;hacking&rdquo; them and building them up so the other team can&rsquo;t get them. The game uses the portals as elements of a science fiction backstory along with a continuous open narrative provided through various forms of media.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;
Peer
<p>Launching this summer, Peer is the creator of a unique social network that&rsquo;s overlaid onto the real world, where users can explore physical locations and find information and digital objects amid their surroundings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s an extremely ambitious project that aims to bring AR to the masses by overlaying 3D graphics atop of the entire world. In some ways, it can be considered an enhanced version of Google Maps, enabling users to search for nearby restaurants for example. When they arrive at their chosen restaurant to grab a bite to eat, they may be able to pick up a coupon placed outside by the restaurant owner, entitling them to a free coffee. Peer can also be used by creators, such as NFT artists, tasking people to visit different locations to mint digital collectibles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Alternatively, a dinosaur museum can create huge, 3D dinosaurs that roam around the physical world outside their premises, enticing people to come and visit its exhibits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Jurassic World Alive
<p>Staying with the dinosaur theme, Jurassic World Alive enables players to get outside in the real world searching for various dinosaurs they need to collect. In some ways it&rsquo;s similar to Pokemon Go, with users having to search different locations to discover the most difficult to find dinosaurs. Once they collect a dinosaur, they can train it and breed it to create hybrid dinosaurs, and then use them to fight battles with other players nearby.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the game initially had a few bugs, the developer has seemingly ironed most of them out and it has built up a loyal player base. Players can even subscribe to the game to earn rewards, instead of spending money on in-app purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Zombies, Run!&nbsp;
<p>The extremely original Zombies, Run! is not so much a game as a gamified fitness app that uses AR to simulate zombies and scare people into running away from them. To play the game, you&rsquo;ll need some earbuds or headphones to listen to the audio as it narrates the story and tasks you with completing various missions while you're out and about on your daily jog. As the story progresses, there will be occasional interruptions by flesh-eating zombies that jump out of the shadows and chase after you, forcing you to start sprinting to outrun them. The game also works just as well on a treadmill.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Zombies, Run! cleverly merges AR elements with an enthralling audio story to motivate people to keep moving and it has proven incredibly effective and popular. The first four missions are available to play for free, and new ones can be unlocked either by paying for them, or by completing various challenges each week.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mainstream media blackout on introduction of new BRICS currency]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/mainstream-media-blackout-on-introduction-of-new-brics-currency</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:08:34 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/mainstream-media-blackout-on-introduction-of-new-brics-currency</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the earth shattering development of a new BRICS currency to rival the dollar, Western mainstream news media is generally silent on the matter.</p>
A rival reserve currency
<p>The hegemony of the US dollar as the world&rsquo;s reserve currency has remained intact since the Bretton Woods agreement in 1944. However, the average citizen in the West is probably not aware that a group of countries termed the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) is about to announce a new rival reserve currency, with the likelihood that it will be backed by gold.</p>
<p>The announcement is expected to take place at the BRICS summit, in late August, only a matter of weeks away, and none of the mainstream media outlets in the West have reported on what has the potential to be the biggest monetary change since Bretton Woods.</p>
Backlash against the dollar
<p>The weaponisation of the dollar in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine was seen by many countries as a move that could potentially be used against them in the future, and so a move away from the dollar has begun.</p>
<p>This rebellion against US hegemony has undoubtedly been led by Putin, but has the backing of the other BRICS nations and countries that are in the process of joining them, including Saudi Arabia, and the Gulf Cooperation Council among others.</p>
Gold backing
<p>Originally, the BRICS currency was to be backed by a basket of commodities, which included gold, but according to Alistair Mcleod, Head of Research at GoldMoney.com, this would probably not work, and therefore gold on its own is likely to be that backing.</p>
<p>Therefore, the flow of gold from West to East over recent decades can certainly be accounted for, along with the increase of gold mining production in China and Russia.</p>
<p>With as many as 41 countries either joining or expressing interest in joining the BRICS trading bloc, the combined populations and GDP would be equal to more than half of the world and would be far bigger than that of the Western alliance.</p>
The West needs to wake up
<p>This introduction of a new rival reserve currency is not likely to usurp the dollar&rsquo;s position any time soon. However, the attraction of a currency that is actually backed by a real asset, instead of the dollar, which is printed out of thin air and has no backing at all, might be anticipated to grow steadily over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Such a development should greatly alarm the West. Media blackouts on the situation should not be the alternative to free and open dialogues on such a critical evolution in the global monetary system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the earth shattering development of a new BRICS currency to rival the dollar, Western mainstream news media is generally silent on the matter.</p>
A rival reserve currency
<p>The hegemony of the US dollar as the world&rsquo;s reserve currency has remained intact since the Bretton Woods agreement in 1944. However, the average citizen in the West is probably not aware that a group of countries termed the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) is about to announce a new rival reserve currency, with the likelihood that it will be backed by gold.</p>
<p>The announcement is expected to take place at the BRICS summit, in late August, only a matter of weeks away, and none of the mainstream media outlets in the West have reported on what has the potential to be the biggest monetary change since Bretton Woods.</p>
Backlash against the dollar
<p>The weaponisation of the dollar in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine was seen by many countries as a move that could potentially be used against them in the future, and so a move away from the dollar has begun.</p>
<p>This rebellion against US hegemony has undoubtedly been led by Putin, but has the backing of the other BRICS nations and countries that are in the process of joining them, including Saudi Arabia, and the Gulf Cooperation Council among others.</p>
Gold backing
<p>Originally, the BRICS currency was to be backed by a basket of commodities, which included gold, but according to Alistair Mcleod, Head of Research at GoldMoney.com, this would probably not work, and therefore gold on its own is likely to be that backing.</p>
<p>Therefore, the flow of gold from West to East over recent decades can certainly be accounted for, along with the increase of gold mining production in China and Russia.</p>
<p>With as many as 41 countries either joining or expressing interest in joining the BRICS trading bloc, the combined populations and GDP would be equal to more than half of the world and would be far bigger than that of the Western alliance.</p>
The West needs to wake up
<p>This introduction of a new rival reserve currency is not likely to usurp the dollar&rsquo;s position any time soon. However, the attraction of a currency that is actually backed by a real asset, instead of the dollar, which is printed out of thin air and has no backing at all, might be anticipated to grow steadily over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Such a development should greatly alarm the West. Media blackouts on the situation should not be the alternative to free and open dialogues on such a critical evolution in the global monetary system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Pressure Congress To Pass Crypto Law]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-lawmakers-pressure-congress-to-pass-crypto-law</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:02:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-lawmakers-pressure-congress-to-pass-crypto-law</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Following SEC's victory over Ripple, several US lawmakers have called on Congress for regulatory clarity regarding the crypto industry.</p>
<p>As one of the lawmakers stated, &ldquo;Gary Gensler&rsquo;s SEC cannot continue to pursue its regulation by enforcement approach, which only harms investors and creates uncertainty.&rdquo;</p>
The Ripple vs SEC Case
<p>Following a lengthy 3-year court battle, the SEC-Ripple case has finally ended with a "partial victory" for the latter. As per the Southern District of New York Court's ruling, all XRP sales fall under three buckets &ndash;&nbsp; institutional sales, programmatic sales, and other distributions. While the SEC prevailed in the case of institutional sales, Ripple secured a favorable outcome regarding programmatic sales and other distributions. It should be noted that t the SEC still has the option to appeal the court's decisions in the future.</p>
The Lawmakers Respond
<p>Following the ruling, the Chairman of the House Financial Services Committee, Patrick McHenry (NC-10), and the Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee, Glenn &ldquo;GT&rdquo; Thompson (PA-15), issued a joint statement.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This decision underscores the need for Congress to provide clear rules of the road for the digital asset ecosystem&mdash;it&rsquo;s misguided to think otherwise. The ruling gives large institutional investors greater protections than everyday Americans. Outcomes like this happen when regulators force courts to make policy instead of Congress. Our comprehensive market structure legislation will give all investors, customers, and market participants the same longstanding protections found in traditional financial markets."</p>

<p>The lawmakers also noted the flaws in the Gensler-led SEC's regulatory approach since digital assets may not &ldquo;be inherently securities, but can be offered as part of an investment contract in certain circumstances, which our legislation acknowledges." The SEC's one-size-fits-all approach creates uncertainty and harms investors.</p>
The Lummis-Gillibrand Crypto Bill
<p>Echoing her colleagues' sentiments, Senator Cynthia Lummis urged to pass the Lummis-Gillibrand Responsible Financial Innovation Act, emphasizing the need for regulatory clarity. The bill primarily aims to pass authority over crypto regulation from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the Commodities Future Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following SEC's victory over Ripple, several US lawmakers have called on Congress for regulatory clarity regarding the crypto industry.</p>
<p>As one of the lawmakers stated, &ldquo;Gary Gensler&rsquo;s SEC cannot continue to pursue its regulation by enforcement approach, which only harms investors and creates uncertainty.&rdquo;</p>
The Ripple vs SEC Case
<p>Following a lengthy 3-year court battle, the SEC-Ripple case has finally ended with a "partial victory" for the latter. As per the Southern District of New York Court's ruling, all XRP sales fall under three buckets &ndash;&nbsp; institutional sales, programmatic sales, and other distributions. While the SEC prevailed in the case of institutional sales, Ripple secured a favorable outcome regarding programmatic sales and other distributions. It should be noted that t the SEC still has the option to appeal the court's decisions in the future.</p>
The Lawmakers Respond
<p>Following the ruling, the Chairman of the House Financial Services Committee, Patrick McHenry (NC-10), and the Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee, Glenn &ldquo;GT&rdquo; Thompson (PA-15), issued a joint statement.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This decision underscores the need for Congress to provide clear rules of the road for the digital asset ecosystem&mdash;it&rsquo;s misguided to think otherwise. The ruling gives large institutional investors greater protections than everyday Americans. Outcomes like this happen when regulators force courts to make policy instead of Congress. Our comprehensive market structure legislation will give all investors, customers, and market participants the same longstanding protections found in traditional financial markets."</p>

<p>The lawmakers also noted the flaws in the Gensler-led SEC's regulatory approach since digital assets may not &ldquo;be inherently securities, but can be offered as part of an investment contract in certain circumstances, which our legislation acknowledges." The SEC's one-size-fits-all approach creates uncertainty and harms investors.</p>
The Lummis-Gillibrand Crypto Bill
<p>Echoing her colleagues' sentiments, Senator Cynthia Lummis urged to pass the Lummis-Gillibrand Responsible Financial Innovation Act, emphasizing the need for regulatory clarity. The bill primarily aims to pass authority over crypto regulation from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the Commodities Future Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[QED: A zk-Native blockchain capable of serving millions of concurrent users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/qed-a-zk-native-blockchain-capable-of-serving-millions-of-concurrent-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:00:50 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/qed-a-zk-native-blockchain-capable-of-serving-millions-of-concurrent-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Startup Open Asset Standards has recently announced QED, the world's first ZK 2.0 blockchain protocol. Unlike existing zero-knowledge blockchain protocols, QED has a novel state model which is horizontally scalable, meaning it is no longer limited by TPS restrictions that have previously prevented adoption of blockchain technologies in Web2 use cases such as social networks, traditional finance, and gaming.</p><p>Enabled by advances in fast recursive zero-knowledge proofs, QED is able to achieve this scale without compromising security or decentralization and proves all transactions end-to-end using proof recursion (verifying a zero-knowledge proof in a zero-knowledge proof ). This process of decentralized recursive proving culminates in a single block proof that can be verified by an Ethereum smart contract, making the protocol only reliant on the Proof of Math itself, rather than an incentive based consensus system vulnerable to collusion, hacking and misaligned incentives.</p><p>As the first blockchain capable of serving billions of users in a single block, QED does away with the need for a zk-VM by compiling smart contract functions directly to zero knowledge circuits, making it the first zk-Native blockchain. QED&rsquo;s novel approach to ZKP allows users to prove their own transactions on their own device in milliseconds, enabling a new privacy-centric internet where transactions are private by default and sensitive data never has to leave a user&rsquo;s device.</p><p>With its announcement of the QED Protocol, Open Asset Standards unveiled QED's official Dapen Smart Contract IDE. With Dapen, Web2 developers can write zk Smart Contracts in the world's 2 most popular programming languages, JavaScript and Python, which have a developer market share 357 times larger than the Solidity community which only makes up a miniscule 0.1% of the world&rsquo;s developers.</p><p>In addition to making blockchain accessible to more developers than ever before, Dapen has integrated support for Markdown smart contracts which allow even non-technical users to write smart contracts in English using their integration with several large language AI models (LLMs) including ChatGPT.</p><p>Backed by Animoca Brands' fund Sparkle Ventures whose General Partners include Sebastien Borget, Co-founder of Sandbox, and Yat Siu, Co-founder of Animoca Brands, QED is set to see major adoption within the gaming space which regularly support millions of concurrent gamers playing at once. Due to its horizontal scaling model, QED is able to add transaction processing capacity by simply adding more proving nodes to its network, allowing large-scale gaming to integrate with blockchain technologies such as dynamic NFTs for the first time.</p><p>Headed up by Founder and CEO Carter Feldman, a former childhood hacking prodigy and reverse engineer, the QED core team is made up of a diverse team from both Web2 tech giants and Web3 titans including Binance, reflecting the protocol's mission to unite Web2 and Web3.</p><p>About QED</p><p>QED is the world's first zk-Native blockchain protocol, built to scale trustless computation and privacy for the next generation of the internet.</p><p>Twitter: Official | Founder&nbsp;</p>ContactQED Protocolnews@qedprotocol.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Startup Open Asset Standards has recently announced QED, the world's first ZK 2.0 blockchain protocol. Unlike existing zero-knowledge blockchain protocols, QED has a novel state model which is horizontally scalable, meaning it is no longer limited by TPS restrictions that have previously prevented adoption of blockchain technologies in Web2 use cases such as social networks, traditional finance, and gaming.</p><p>Enabled by advances in fast recursive zero-knowledge proofs, QED is able to achieve this scale without compromising security or decentralization and proves all transactions end-to-end using proof recursion (verifying a zero-knowledge proof in a zero-knowledge proof ). This process of decentralized recursive proving culminates in a single block proof that can be verified by an Ethereum smart contract, making the protocol only reliant on the Proof of Math itself, rather than an incentive based consensus system vulnerable to collusion, hacking and misaligned incentives.</p><p>As the first blockchain capable of serving billions of users in a single block, QED does away with the need for a zk-VM by compiling smart contract functions directly to zero knowledge circuits, making it the first zk-Native blockchain. QED&rsquo;s novel approach to ZKP allows users to prove their own transactions on their own device in milliseconds, enabling a new privacy-centric internet where transactions are private by default and sensitive data never has to leave a user&rsquo;s device.</p><p>With its announcement of the QED Protocol, Open Asset Standards unveiled QED's official Dapen Smart Contract IDE. With Dapen, Web2 developers can write zk Smart Contracts in the world's 2 most popular programming languages, JavaScript and Python, which have a developer market share 357 times larger than the Solidity community which only makes up a miniscule 0.1% of the world&rsquo;s developers.</p><p>In addition to making blockchain accessible to more developers than ever before, Dapen has integrated support for Markdown smart contracts which allow even non-technical users to write smart contracts in English using their integration with several large language AI models (LLMs) including ChatGPT.</p><p>Backed by Animoca Brands' fund Sparkle Ventures whose General Partners include Sebastien Borget, Co-founder of Sandbox, and Yat Siu, Co-founder of Animoca Brands, QED is set to see major adoption within the gaming space which regularly support millions of concurrent gamers playing at once. Due to its horizontal scaling model, QED is able to add transaction processing capacity by simply adding more proving nodes to its network, allowing large-scale gaming to integrate with blockchain technologies such as dynamic NFTs for the first time.</p><p>Headed up by Founder and CEO Carter Feldman, a former childhood hacking prodigy and reverse engineer, the QED core team is made up of a diverse team from both Web2 tech giants and Web3 titans including Binance, reflecting the protocol's mission to unite Web2 and Web3.</p><p>About QED</p><p>QED is the world's first zk-Native blockchain protocol, built to scale trustless computation and privacy for the next generation of the internet.</p><p>Twitter: Official | Founder&nbsp;</p>ContactQED Protocolnews@qedprotocol.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flipster to give away huge 1,500,000 USDT worth of Bonus]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/flipster-to-give-away-huge-1500000-usdt-worth-of-bonus</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:43:22 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/flipster-to-give-away-huge-1500000-usdt-worth-of-bonus</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>seychelles, seychelles, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As part of Flipster's (formerly AQX) name launch, the business today announced an additional 1,500,000 USD worth of bonus rewards to encourage new users to join and trade on their exchange. Until the rewards are fully distributed, the futures exchange will run at least one campaign per week to encourage new users to signup and trade derivatives on the Flipster platform. Under the old name the exchange has already made available more than 400,000USDT worth bonus in past campaigns.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The first promotion in the series kicked off on the 17th of July, 2023 (running for seven days). A massive 110,000 USDT in bonuses has been allocated. 10,000 USDT to reward new users when completing identity verification with a 10 USDT Bonus. The remaining 100,000 USDT bonus is to incentivise and reward high volume traders that give the platform a chance. The top performer by trading volume will be rewarded with 10,000 USDT in Bonus at the end of the weekly campaign.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Flipster has reimagined futures trading with a mobile-first approach to appeal to casual crypto traders with limited experience in derivatives trading (or, as they say, Flipping).&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The method is to specialize in derivatives trading, stripping back the app experience to make it faster to learn and easier to use. Novice traders can open, close and monitor positions from any location. Potentially meaning some users may make more money on the bus to work, than from their days Labor. Beyond ease of use, the portable experience makes trading fun and feels less like a technical task.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The flip to a mobile-first approach came after initially having a web experience similar to other futures exchanges. The traditional UI for futures trading has a steep learning curve and is considerably more technical, which strongly contrasts with the UI that most contemporary apps users have become familiar with. The data concluded that users new to derivatives were not attracted to this experience as it had been built for experienced traders. The Flipster team discovered a few alternative UIs for future trading and none that have successfully been created to onboard new users to crypto futures trading at scale.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">While the focus is on simplicity, Flipster has features that will spark the interest of experienced traders as well. The exchange regularly adds new perpetual swap contracts, and as of today, over 120 assets can be traded with leverage, making Flipster a competitive exchange for traders to consider. Amongst their assets are tokens not found for futures on other exchanges and some even with low visibility in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>CEO Yongjin Kim said, "The team has been working very hard on bringing this new vision for futures trading to life, and now is the right time to incentivise users to trade with us. Once users start trading on our platform, they will be coming back again and again. Rather than just copying what every other exchange has done, we are doing something fresh, and I believe the market is ready for some injection of new ideas. To our existing users, I want to thank you for being with us, and to the new guys coming in now, Welcome".&nbsp;<p class="ql-align-justify">Get started by creating a Flipster account flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Flipster</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Flipster (ex AQX) is the industry's easy-to-use crypto derivatives trading platform. It offers users an all-in-one platform trading more than 120 tokens with leverage up to 50x. Get started at flipster.xyz to join online or download the app and play store. For media enquiries including interviews with the team reach out at pr@flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information follow Flipater on Twitter.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactHead of MarketingBen RogersPrex Ltdbenrogers@prestlabs.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>seychelles, seychelles, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As part of Flipster's (formerly AQX) name launch, the business today announced an additional 1,500,000 USD worth of bonus rewards to encourage new users to join and trade on their exchange. Until the rewards are fully distributed, the futures exchange will run at least one campaign per week to encourage new users to signup and trade derivatives on the Flipster platform. Under the old name the exchange has already made available more than 400,000USDT worth bonus in past campaigns.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The first promotion in the series kicked off on the 17th of July, 2023 (running for seven days). A massive 110,000 USDT in bonuses has been allocated. 10,000 USDT to reward new users when completing identity verification with a 10 USDT Bonus. The remaining 100,000 USDT bonus is to incentivise and reward high volume traders that give the platform a chance. The top performer by trading volume will be rewarded with 10,000 USDT in Bonus at the end of the weekly campaign.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Flipster has reimagined futures trading with a mobile-first approach to appeal to casual crypto traders with limited experience in derivatives trading (or, as they say, Flipping).&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The method is to specialize in derivatives trading, stripping back the app experience to make it faster to learn and easier to use. Novice traders can open, close and monitor positions from any location. Potentially meaning some users may make more money on the bus to work, than from their days Labor. Beyond ease of use, the portable experience makes trading fun and feels less like a technical task.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The flip to a mobile-first approach came after initially having a web experience similar to other futures exchanges. The traditional UI for futures trading has a steep learning curve and is considerably more technical, which strongly contrasts with the UI that most contemporary apps users have become familiar with. The data concluded that users new to derivatives were not attracted to this experience as it had been built for experienced traders. The Flipster team discovered a few alternative UIs for future trading and none that have successfully been created to onboard new users to crypto futures trading at scale.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">While the focus is on simplicity, Flipster has features that will spark the interest of experienced traders as well. The exchange regularly adds new perpetual swap contracts, and as of today, over 120 assets can be traded with leverage, making Flipster a competitive exchange for traders to consider. Amongst their assets are tokens not found for futures on other exchanges and some even with low visibility in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>CEO Yongjin Kim said, "The team has been working very hard on bringing this new vision for futures trading to life, and now is the right time to incentivise users to trade with us. Once users start trading on our platform, they will be coming back again and again. Rather than just copying what every other exchange has done, we are doing something fresh, and I believe the market is ready for some injection of new ideas. To our existing users, I want to thank you for being with us, and to the new guys coming in now, Welcome".&nbsp;<p class="ql-align-justify">Get started by creating a Flipster account flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Flipster</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Flipster (ex AQX) is the industry's easy-to-use crypto derivatives trading platform. It offers users an all-in-one platform trading more than 120 tokens with leverage up to 50x. Get started at flipster.xyz to join online or download the app and play store. For media enquiries including interviews with the team reach out at pr@flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information follow Flipater on Twitter.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactHead of MarketingBen RogersPrex Ltdbenrogers@prestlabs.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Another Test of 30281 - 17 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-another-test-of-30281-17-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-another-test-of-30281-17-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Again Tests 30281:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lacked clear technical direction early in the Asian session as the pair again bounced higher from the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area. &nbsp;&nbsp;Buying pressure emerged around the 30145.47 area during a pullback, a move lower that represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp;&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30499.23 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30481.11.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Again Tests 30281:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lacked clear technical direction early in the Asian session as the pair again bounced higher from the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area. &nbsp;&nbsp;Buying pressure emerged around the 30145.47 area during a pullback, a move lower that represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp;&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30499.23 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30481.11.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Elected Below 30147 - 16 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-30147-16-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-30147-16-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 30147:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained confined to an extremely tight range early in the Asian session as the pair encountered minor technical buying pressure around the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30482.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30473.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 30147:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained confined to an extremely tight range early in the Asian session as the pair encountered minor technical buying pressure around the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30482.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30473.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: $XRP Soars After SEC Victory And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-xrp-soars-after-sec-victory-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-xrp-soars-after-sec-victory-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The most exciting news in the industry this week has been Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in the SEC case. Experts are opining that it could shake the market out of its rut. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Judge Analise Torres of the Southern District of New York handed a partial win over to Ripple Labs after its three-year-long battle with the SEC.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p>Europe&rsquo;s highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin ETF is finally set to debut later this year amidst huge anticipation surrounding its imminent arrival.</p>
<p>The US Department of Justice is finally moving the BTC reserves it seized from the Silk Road, the notorious online marketplace predominantly used for illicit activities.</p>
<p>Vanguard Group, which manages $7.2 trillion in assets, has significantly ramped up its investments in the bitcoin mining sector, with its total stake now exceeding $560 million.</p>
<p>The UK&rsquo;s FCA has shut down 26 cryptocurrency ATMs this year following a coordinated investigation with other law enforcement agencies.</p>
<p>Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021.</p>
<p>Satoshis are now being given out as rewards on Satlantis, a unique Bitcoin-themed Minecraft server.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated that he has not invested in Bitcoin, even though financial records prove otherwise.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>The transactions per second on the Etheruem blockchain will receive a significant boost now that Starknet&rsquo;s Quantum Leap upgrade has been deployed on the Ethereum mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Aave community members will be voting on whether to finally deploy gho ($GHO) on the Ethereum chain.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol, Rodeo Finance, lost $1.53 million in Ethereum due to a code vulnerability exploitation in its Oracle.</p>
<p>ConsenSys has announced the launch of its layer-2 network Linea, as the Ethereum ecosystem welcomed yet another scaling solution.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>20-year-old Argentinian Federico Jaime has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p>Kain Warwick, the founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p>Uniswap users can now start swapping their Avalanche tokens on the Uniswap website, as the decentralized exchange has now launched on the Avalanche network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000.</p>
Altcoins
<p>The pronouncement by the SDNY judge that XRP can only be partially classed as a security led to a massive market surge.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Polygon, the prominent Ethereum layer 2 scaling solution, is making strides towards a significant upgrade, changing its token from $MATIC to $POL.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p>Coinbase has launched an encrypted messaging service on its self-custodial wallet app, using the open-source Web3 messaging network of Texas-based startup XMTP.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month.</p>
<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After a significant downturn in the crypto market, it appears that in the first half of 2023, the venture investment market, much like the price of Bitcoin, has found its bottom.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin has surpassed 2 million sign-ups for its World ID program in half the time it took to reach the first million sign-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX recently launched its claims portal, allowing users from around the world to file a claim.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto data firm Arkham Intelligence is under fire after privacy-conscious users discovered that the firm has been irresponsible about user data.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP skyrocketed by around 70% in the 24 hours after its landmark partial win over the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Australian crypto investment firm, Monochrome Asset Management is working to introduce spot Bitcoin ETF on the Australian Securities Exchange.</p>
<p>Coinbase has paused its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the SEC can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
NFT
<p>Starbucks&rsquo; Web3 loyalty program Odyssey has announced a collaboration with the Aku NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>Blockchain security and analytics firm Chainalysis has suggested that the multimillion-dollar exploit of the Multichain Protocol could be indicative of a rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam after users reported receiving "fake approval" requests that led to exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The most exciting news in the industry this week has been Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in the SEC case. Experts are opining that it could shake the market out of its rut. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Judge Analise Torres of the Southern District of New York handed a partial win over to Ripple Labs after its three-year-long battle with the SEC.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p>Europe&rsquo;s highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin ETF is finally set to debut later this year amidst huge anticipation surrounding its imminent arrival.</p>
<p>The US Department of Justice is finally moving the BTC reserves it seized from the Silk Road, the notorious online marketplace predominantly used for illicit activities.</p>
<p>Vanguard Group, which manages $7.2 trillion in assets, has significantly ramped up its investments in the bitcoin mining sector, with its total stake now exceeding $560 million.</p>
<p>The UK&rsquo;s FCA has shut down 26 cryptocurrency ATMs this year following a coordinated investigation with other law enforcement agencies.</p>
<p>Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021.</p>
<p>Satoshis are now being given out as rewards on Satlantis, a unique Bitcoin-themed Minecraft server.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated that he has not invested in Bitcoin, even though financial records prove otherwise.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>The transactions per second on the Etheruem blockchain will receive a significant boost now that Starknet&rsquo;s Quantum Leap upgrade has been deployed on the Ethereum mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Aave community members will be voting on whether to finally deploy gho ($GHO) on the Ethereum chain.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol, Rodeo Finance, lost $1.53 million in Ethereum due to a code vulnerability exploitation in its Oracle.</p>
<p>ConsenSys has announced the launch of its layer-2 network Linea, as the Ethereum ecosystem welcomed yet another scaling solution.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>20-year-old Argentinian Federico Jaime has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p>Kain Warwick, the founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p>Uniswap users can now start swapping their Avalanche tokens on the Uniswap website, as the decentralized exchange has now launched on the Avalanche network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000.</p>
Altcoins
<p>The pronouncement by the SDNY judge that XRP can only be partially classed as a security led to a massive market surge.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Polygon, the prominent Ethereum layer 2 scaling solution, is making strides towards a significant upgrade, changing its token from $MATIC to $POL.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p>Coinbase has launched an encrypted messaging service on its self-custodial wallet app, using the open-source Web3 messaging network of Texas-based startup XMTP.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month.</p>
<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After a significant downturn in the crypto market, it appears that in the first half of 2023, the venture investment market, much like the price of Bitcoin, has found its bottom.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin has surpassed 2 million sign-ups for its World ID program in half the time it took to reach the first million sign-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX recently launched its claims portal, allowing users from around the world to file a claim.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto data firm Arkham Intelligence is under fire after privacy-conscious users discovered that the firm has been irresponsible about user data.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP skyrocketed by around 70% in the 24 hours after its landmark partial win over the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Australian crypto investment firm, Monochrome Asset Management is working to introduce spot Bitcoin ETF on the Australian Securities Exchange.</p>
<p>Coinbase has paused its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the SEC can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
NFT
<p>Starbucks&rsquo; Web3 loyalty program Odyssey has announced a collaboration with the Aku NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>Blockchain security and analytics firm Chainalysis has suggested that the multimillion-dollar exploit of the Multichain Protocol could be indicative of a rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam after users reported receiving "fake approval" requests that led to exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Face Difficulty Ahead of Halving, JP Morgan Warns]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-miners-face-difficulty-ahead-of-halving-jp-morgan-warns</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-miners-face-difficulty-ahead-of-halving-jp-morgan-warns</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report suggests that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees need to rise substantially to balance the reduced block reward.</p>
Unsettling Times Ahead for Miners
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The analysis predicts potential difficulties for Bitcoin miners as the hash rate, representing the computational power used to mine cryptocurrency, hits new highs. Factors such as fluctuating electricity costs and intensified competition among miners are expected to increase the cost of production. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The halving event, which takes place approximately every four years, will cut miners' rewards by half. "The upcoming bitcoin halving event in April/May 2024 could be a stress test for Bitcoin miners," states the report, co-authored by JP Morgan analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This event will lower the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, effectively reducing miners&rsquo; revenue while concurrently increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost. The report explains that while Bitcoin halving typically has a positive impact on the Bitcoin price given that the production cost has historically acted as a floor, it presents a considerable challenge for miners.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[The halving] would reduce the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, implying a reduction in miners&rsquo; revenue, effectively increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost at the same time [...] As a result, while Bitcoin halving is seen as having a positive effect on the bitcoin price given the production cost acted historically as a floor, it poses a challenge for bitcoin miners," the report indicated.</p>

Hash Rate Volatility and Energy Costs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Based on a global average electricity cost of $0.05/kWh, it presently costs around $20,000 to mine a Bitcoin, currently valued at around $30,000 according to public blockchain explorer data. JP Morgan highlighted the hash rate's volatility, suggesting a range of energy sources and potential advantages for miners who have access to lower-priced power.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm revealed that a one-cent increase in the cost per kilowatt-hour translates into a $4,300 increase in Bitcoin production costs. After the halving event, this sensitivity is expected to double, thereby escalating the risk and susceptibility for higher-cost producers (in simpler terms, they will effectively be "priced out" of the competitive sphere for Bitcoin mining).</p>
Institutional Support and the Importance of Rising Bitcoin Prices
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report also points to growing institutional interest in Bitcoin mining as a source of support for struggling miners, citing investments in mining rigs from companies like Galaxy Digital and Grayscale Investments. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"It seems unlikely that the Bitcoin hash rate will continue to rise at the same pace post the April/May 2024 halving event without any sustained rise in the Bitcoin price above its production cost or a large increase in transaction fees that could offset the reduction in issuance rewards."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite this, however, to offset the lower block reward, JP Morgan stresses that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees must see substantial growth. The analysts furtherl noted that declining enthusiasm around cryptocurrencies could pose an additional challenge for miners' revenues, if indeed the trend in terms of declining interest in crypto proves to be a long-term trend.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report suggests that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees need to rise substantially to balance the reduced block reward.</p>
Unsettling Times Ahead for Miners
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The analysis predicts potential difficulties for Bitcoin miners as the hash rate, representing the computational power used to mine cryptocurrency, hits new highs. Factors such as fluctuating electricity costs and intensified competition among miners are expected to increase the cost of production. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The halving event, which takes place approximately every four years, will cut miners' rewards by half. "The upcoming bitcoin halving event in April/May 2024 could be a stress test for Bitcoin miners," states the report, co-authored by JP Morgan analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This event will lower the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, effectively reducing miners&rsquo; revenue while concurrently increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost. The report explains that while Bitcoin halving typically has a positive impact on the Bitcoin price given that the production cost has historically acted as a floor, it presents a considerable challenge for miners.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[The halving] would reduce the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, implying a reduction in miners&rsquo; revenue, effectively increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost at the same time [...] As a result, while Bitcoin halving is seen as having a positive effect on the bitcoin price given the production cost acted historically as a floor, it poses a challenge for bitcoin miners," the report indicated.</p>

Hash Rate Volatility and Energy Costs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Based on a global average electricity cost of $0.05/kWh, it presently costs around $20,000 to mine a Bitcoin, currently valued at around $30,000 according to public blockchain explorer data. JP Morgan highlighted the hash rate's volatility, suggesting a range of energy sources and potential advantages for miners who have access to lower-priced power.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm revealed that a one-cent increase in the cost per kilowatt-hour translates into a $4,300 increase in Bitcoin production costs. After the halving event, this sensitivity is expected to double, thereby escalating the risk and susceptibility for higher-cost producers (in simpler terms, they will effectively be "priced out" of the competitive sphere for Bitcoin mining).</p>
Institutional Support and the Importance of Rising Bitcoin Prices
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report also points to growing institutional interest in Bitcoin mining as a source of support for struggling miners, citing investments in mining rigs from companies like Galaxy Digital and Grayscale Investments. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"It seems unlikely that the Bitcoin hash rate will continue to rise at the same pace post the April/May 2024 halving event without any sustained rise in the Bitcoin price above its production cost or a large increase in transaction fees that could offset the reduction in issuance rewards."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite this, however, to offset the lower block reward, JP Morgan stresses that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees must see substantial growth. The analysts furtherl noted that declining enthusiasm around cryptocurrencies could pose an additional challenge for miners' revenues, if indeed the trend in terms of declining interest in crypto proves to be a long-term trend.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Claims SEC Case May Take Years To Appeal $XRP]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-claims-sec-case-may-take-years-to-appeal-xrp</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-claims-sec-case-may-take-years-to-appeal-xrp</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to an interview from Garlinghouse with Bloomberg on July 15, the executive estimates that the SEC's opportunity for appeal could take "years." No other precise detail in terms of this claim was disclosed, however.</p>
Judge's Ruling on XRP
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On July 13, Judge Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit initiated by the SEC in 2020. The judgement states that the XRP token, with respect to retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not a security. However, Judge Torres ruled that XRP qualifies as a security when sold to institutional investors, in accordance with the criteria of the Howey Test.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse emphasized that the ruling about institutional sales represents "the smallest piece" of the lawsuit. He believes that if the SEC decides to appeal the ruling regarding retail sales, it would only "further solidify" Judge Torres' decision.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"As a matter of law, the law of the land right now is that XRP is not a security. Until there is an opportunity for the SEC to file an appeal, which would take years, frankly, we are very optimistic.&rdquo;</p>

SEC Accused of Bullying Tactics
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse also took the opportunity to criticize the SEC, alleging it acted as a "bully" by targeting "weak players" in the crypto industry incapable of mounting a strong defense. He indicated that the Ripple lawsuit marked the first defeat for the SEC in a "crypto case."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple CEO noted the SEC's lawsuit initially led to uncertainty among U.S. crypto exchanges, causing a wait-and-see attitude due to market confusion. According to Garlinghouse, the SEC deliberately fostered this confusion to increase its power, thereby stifling innovation in the U.S.</p>
Impact on the Crypto Market
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse argued that the SEC's power play and political manoeuvring have overshadowed sound policy and clear regulatory guidelines. This stance, he says, has hampered U.S. entrepreneurs and investors from fully participating in the crypto market and embracing blockchain technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the recent performance of XRP may be impacted by these developments, the broader implications revolve around regulatory clarity in the crypto industry, and this is something that requires closer attention in terms of how it evolves and becomes more complex with each new case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to an interview from Garlinghouse with Bloomberg on July 15, the executive estimates that the SEC's opportunity for appeal could take "years." No other precise detail in terms of this claim was disclosed, however.</p>
Judge's Ruling on XRP
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On July 13, Judge Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit initiated by the SEC in 2020. The judgement states that the XRP token, with respect to retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not a security. However, Judge Torres ruled that XRP qualifies as a security when sold to institutional investors, in accordance with the criteria of the Howey Test.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse emphasized that the ruling about institutional sales represents "the smallest piece" of the lawsuit. He believes that if the SEC decides to appeal the ruling regarding retail sales, it would only "further solidify" Judge Torres' decision.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"As a matter of law, the law of the land right now is that XRP is not a security. Until there is an opportunity for the SEC to file an appeal, which would take years, frankly, we are very optimistic.&rdquo;</p>

SEC Accused of Bullying Tactics
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse also took the opportunity to criticize the SEC, alleging it acted as a "bully" by targeting "weak players" in the crypto industry incapable of mounting a strong defense. He indicated that the Ripple lawsuit marked the first defeat for the SEC in a "crypto case."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple CEO noted the SEC's lawsuit initially led to uncertainty among U.S. crypto exchanges, causing a wait-and-see attitude due to market confusion. According to Garlinghouse, the SEC deliberately fostered this confusion to increase its power, thereby stifling innovation in the U.S.</p>
Impact on the Crypto Market
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse argued that the SEC's power play and political manoeuvring have overshadowed sound policy and clear regulatory guidelines. This stance, he says, has hampered U.S. entrepreneurs and investors from fully participating in the crypto market and embracing blockchain technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the recent performance of XRP may be impacted by these developments, the broader implications revolve around regulatory clarity in the crypto industry, and this is something that requires closer attention in terms of how it evolves and becomes more complex with each new case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
