<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:16:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ferrari BTC Purchase Gone Wrong and A Scam Story From Morocco (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ferrari-btc-purchase-gone-wrong-and-a-scam-story-from-morocco-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 04:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249394</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Clausi has already served most of his prison sentence.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Casablanca Court of Appeals ruled that the 21-year-old Frenchman &#8211; Thomas Clausi &#8211; will serve an 18-month prison sentence for orchestrating a crypto scheme. The defendant must compensate the victims of his scam and pay a fine of 3.4 million euros ($3.7 million) to customs authorities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto fraudsters have been quite inventive recently, draining significant sums from investors. Fortunately, law enforcement agencies have arrested and sent to jail some of them. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For example, Gilbert Armenta &#8211; the ex-lover of Ruja Ignatove (better known as the &#8220;Cryptoqueen&#8221;) &#8211; will go behind bars for five years after participating in the infamous OneCoin scam. Cooper Morgenthau &#8211; the former CFO of African Gold &#8211; was sentenced to three years after stealing $5 million from different SPACs to trade meme stocks.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jail Time for the Frenchman, but There Is a Catch</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <a href="https://www.moroccoworldnews.com/2023/05/355308/frenchman-sentenced-to-18-months-in-prison-in-casablanca-for-crypto-scam" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by Morocco World News, the Casablanca magistrates confirmed the 18-month sentence of the youngster. Trial proceedings against the defendant started a few years back when a Frenchwoman residing in Morocco sold him a Ferrari car for $440,000 worth of bitcoin. Local law considers the use of digital assets to be an illicit payment method.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another individual claimed Clausi bought three luxury watches in exchange for a counterfeit check. The Casablanca Court ordered the man to refund the owner of the items for $4,000. It also ruled that the defendant must pay a penalty of $3.7 million to customs authorities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Clausi&#8217;s lawyer &#8211; Mohamed Aghanaj &#8211; said his client has almost served his jail sentence since he&#8217;s been in a correctional facility since December 2021:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;He has one month and a few days left in prison.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the hostile stance from the Moroccan lawmakers, cryptocurrencies have become increasingly popular in the region. The country&#8217;s central bank &#8211; Al-Maghrib &#8211; has previously displayed intentions to design a pertinent regulatory framework for the asset class to ensure maximum security for users.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some of the Previous Sentences</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Southern District of New York (SDNY) Courthouse </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptoqueens-ex-boyfriend-sent-to-prison-for-5-years-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sentenced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Gilbert Armenta &#8211; the former boyfriend of Ruja Ignatova &#8211; to serve five years in federal prison for laundering $300 million embezzled from OneCoin investors. Prosecutors claimed that Armenta used a portion of the funds to purchase a jet plane while gambling the remaining part.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato</em> recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ex-cfo-sentenced-3-years-in-prison-for-stealing-from-spacs-to-trade-meme-stocks-crypto/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Cooper Morgenthau &#8211; ex-boss of African Gold &#8211; will also see the prison cell from the inside. He supposedly drained more than $5 million from three SPACs and used the money to trade equities and options of &#8220;meme stocks&#8221; and cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Speaking of crypto scammers and eventual jail sentences, one should mention the notorious Do Kwon (co-founder of Terraform Labs) and Sam Bankman-Fried (the former CEO of FTX).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to numerous failed investors and agencies, both men have orchestrated multi-billion cryptocurrency frauds and deserve to go to prison. The authorities of Montenegro </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-reportedly-arrested-in-montenegro/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">arrested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Kwon in March after he was allegedly on the run for several months. He could be extradited to either the USA or South Korea in the near future, where a trial will determine whether he is guilty and his possible punishment.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bankman-Fried currently resides at his parent&#8217;s house in California after serving a brief time in a Bahamian jail. His </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">trial</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> at the beginning of October will rule whether he had a hand in the gigantic FTX meltdown. Should he be proclaimed guilty, he could spend his life in prison.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ferrari-btc-purchase-gone-wrong-and-a-scam-story-from-morocco-report/" rel="nofollow">Ferrari BTC Purchase Gone Wrong and A Scam Story From Morocco (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kenya Mulls 3% Tax on Crypto (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-mulls-3-tax-on-crypto-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 23:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249372</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Kenya.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Kenya.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Kenyan lawmakers could implement a 3% tax on crypto transfers and 15% levy on the monetization of digital content.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The government of Kenya plans to impose a 3% tax on cryptocurrency transfers to narrow the fiscal deficit of the country and boost its domestic revenues.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kenya is among the leaders on the African continent in terms of crypto adoption. Patrick Njoroge &#8211; Governor of the Central Bank &#8211; has previously suggested that bitcoin could solve the nation&#8217;s problems with its depreciating official currency.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Included in the New Bill</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/kenya-s-government-plans-to-introduce-3-crypto-influencer-tax-as-cash-sources-dry-1.1916205" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Bloomberg, Kenya&#8217;s lawmakers might implement a 3% tax on the transfer or exchange of cryptocurrencies, whereas a 15% levy could affect creators of monetized online content. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The proposal is part of a newly-designed bill that could stabilize the financial condition of the African nation. President William Ruto aims to double tax collections to 5 trillion shillings (around $37 billion) in five years and use the funds to promote monetary growth.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legislation will become official from the beginning of July should the Kenyan lawmakers give their nod. The country estimates revenue of approximately $21 billion during the first 365 days (14% more than the anticipated collections for the ongoing fiscal year). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kenya ranks as a lower-middle-income economy, with over 16% of its population living below the international poverty line. Economic inequality, health issues, and government corruption are the main factors for the negative trend. Despite its problems, it remains one of the most developed counties in eastern and central Africa. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kenya: the African Crypto Leader</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the financial difficulties in the country, a substantial number of Kenyans have turned their focus toward the cryptocurrency industry in the past few years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Research carried out by the United Nations (UN) in the summer of 2022 </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-is-the-african-leader-in-crypto-adoption-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">estimated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that 8.5% of the population (more than 4 million individuals) were HODLers: the highest adoption rate in Africa. South Africans (7.1%) and Nigerians (6.3%) rounded up the top 3 list. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">However, the UN could not determine the approximate value of digital assets held by Kenyans due to the lack of comprehensive regulations in the industry:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The returns from cryptocurrency trading and holding are, as with other speculative trades, highly individual. On balance, they are overshadowed by the risks and costs they pose in developing countries. The sector is not regulated in the country and remains largely unregulated even in the developed world.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that Kenya&#8217;s central bank has a somewhat positive stance on bitcoin (unlike many other centralized financial institutions across the globe). Governor Njoroge </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-central-bank-explores-using-bitcoin-to-fight-the-depreciating-shilling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggested</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in 2021 that adopting the primary cryptocurrency could ease the financial turmoil that hit the region shortly after the COVID-19 pandemic. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our decision to shift to Bitcoin is both tactical and logical. Our currency has always been the punching bag for the IMF, which always claims that the Kenya Shilling is overvalued. This has led to too much pressure on the Kenyan Shilling, and this has a negative effect on the economy,&#8221; he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kenya-mulls-3-tax-on-crypto-report/" rel="nofollow">Kenya Mulls 3% Tax on Crypto (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stripe Launches Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp With New Hosted Option</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stripe-launches-fiat-to-crypto-onramp-with-new-hosted-option/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249326</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Bitcoin_Stripe.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Bitcoin_Stripe.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Stripe's new offering would allow customers to buy crypto at the "precise moment" they need it. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Payment giant Stripe announced the launch of a fiat-to-crypto onramp to streamline process the for Web3 companies to enable US-based customers to purchase crypto.</p>
<p>The company will also be opening the onramp to all Web3 users, in addition to the ones who joined the waitlist over the last few months.</p>
<ul>
<li>The onramp, whether embedded on a company&#8217;s site or hosted by Stripe, focuses on optimizing conversion and authorization rates. Such a mechanism in place makes it more likely that legitimate purchases go through.</li>
<li>The new offering includes built-in fraud tools and identity verification to support companies in meeting KYC and compliance checks necessary to prevent manipulation and fraud.</li>
<li>Commenting on the latest development, James Mudgett, vice president of Web3 products at Brave, <a href="https://stripe.com/zh-cn-hk/newsroom/news/fiat-to-crypto-onramp" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stated</a>,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We&#8217;re thrilled to partner with Stripe as they expand their offerings in the crypto space. We&#8217;re excited to offer a fiat payment solution that will allow us to reach new Web3 users.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The latest offering follows December&#8217;s release of a fiat-to-crypto widget that can be embedded in any crypto product allowing users to enter their card information and acquire crypto that can be used in another web3 product.</li>
<li>Earlier this year, Stripe <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/payment-giant-stripe-clinches-6-5b-funding-at-50b-valuation/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> signing agreements to raise more than $6.5 billion at a valuation of $50 billion with existing shareholders Andreessen Horowitz, Baillie Gifford, Founders Fund, General Catalyst, MSD Partners, and Thrive Capital, as well as new investors GIC, Goldman Sachs Asset and Wealth Management and Temasek.</li>
<li>The company had previously stated that the proceeds would be deployed to employee liquidity and does not need the capital to run its business.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stripe-launches-fiat-to-crypto-onramp-with-new-hosted-option/" rel="nofollow">Stripe Launches Fiat-to-Crypto Onramp With New Hosted Option</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Ordered 10 Days to File Response to Coinbase&#8217;s Petition</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249238</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/CoinbaseSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SEC failed to respond to Coinbase's petition over rulemaking for over nine months. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A US court has ordered the Securities and Exchange Commission to respond to Coinbase&#8217;s complaint about clarity on whether the securities regulator would allow the industry to be regulated using existing frameworks.</p>
<p>The latest development emerges amidst escalating tensions between the SEC and Coinbase, with the former ramping up enforcement actions and warnings against crypto firms, including the US crypto giant.</p>
<h2>SEC&#8217;s 10-Day Deadline</h2>
<p>Coinbase chief legal officer Paul Grewal took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/iampaulgrewal/status/1653898889311948800" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">announce</a> that the Third Circuit Court of Appeals issued a text-only order directing the SEC to file a response to the crypto exchange&#8217;s mandamus petition within ten days. The court also granted Coinbase the right to file a reply within seven days of the SEC&#8217;s response.</p>
<p>The original petition dates back to July 2022, when Coinbase asked if the SEC would propose and adopt rules to govern the regulation of securities that are offered and traded via digitally native methods. The agency, however, refrained from offering specific public responses.</p>
<p>In the meantime, the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-and-legal-officer-respond-to-secs-wells-notice/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">issued</a> a Wells notice to Coinbase, signaling its intention to conduct enforcement actions against the exchange.</p>
<p>This prompted Coinbase to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-compels-sec-to-respond-to-rulemaking-petition-in-new-lawsuit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">file</a> a narrow action in federal court to compel the securities regulator to respond yes or no. In a federal court filing dated April 24, the company said it is &#8220;unreasonable for the SEC &#8211; an agency with over 4,500 employees &#8211; to take nine months (and counting) to complete that simple task.&#8221;</p>
<p>Grewal had previously commented,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;From the SEC’s public statements and enforcement activity in the crypto industry, it seems like the SEC has already made up its mind to deny our petition. But they haven’t told the public yet. So the action Coinbase filed today simply asks the court to ask the SEC to share its decision.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Since January, the SEC has been aggressively targeting crypto platforms such as Bittrex, Gemini, and lender Genesis, as well as several individual actors accused of manipulating crypto assets, including Tron&#8217;s Justin Sun and disgraced Terraform Labs founder Do Kwon. As a result, many firms are now looking to move their operations to friendlier jurisdictions.</p>
<h2>Global Push</h2>
<p>Amid the ongoing tribulations with the SEC, Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> a Bermuda-based marketplace for non-US institutional users. The San Francisco-based exchange will initially offer Bitcoin and Ethereum perpetual futures, with trades settled in the USDC stablecoin.</p>
<p>The announcement of the new venture follows regulatory approval from the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" rel="nofollow">SEC Ordered 10 Days to File Response to Coinbase&#8217;s Petition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Fails to Keep Up, Is a Crash Below $0.45 Coming? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-fails-to-keep-up-is-a-crash-below-0-45-coming-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249230</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price action has been relatively bearish recently, following a rejection from a significant resistance level. Currently, XRP is trading near a key support level, and its reaction would determine the short-term market trend. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart The price is ranging around the 50-day moving average, located near the $0.46 level. [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price action has been relatively bearish recently, following a rejection from a significant resistance level. Currently, XRP is trading near a key support level, and its reaction would determine the short-term market trend.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price is ranging around the 50-day moving average, located near the $0.46 level. A breakdown of this moving average would lead make the market retreat further towards the $0.4 support level and the 200-day moving average.</p>
<p>Conversely, a rebound from either of these support levels would result in another rally and potential breakout above the significant $0.6 resistance area. The RSI has also shown values below 50%, pointing to the bearish momentum in this timeframe, as well as boosting the probability of a deeper decline.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249460" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249460" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249460" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" alt="XRPUSDT Daily - May 4 2023" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249460" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the BTC paired chart, XRP has failed to break out from the sizeable descending channel once more and is creating lower highs and lows. The 50-day moving average has been broken to the downside, and the price is currently testing the 0.000015 support level.</p>
<p>In case this level is broken through, a plunge toward the 0.000012 level would be probable. The RSI is also trending below 50%, as the momentum is clearly bearish on this chart.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249461" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249461" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249461" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" alt="XRPBTC Daily - May 4 2023" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPBTC-Daily-May-4-2023-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249461" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-fails-to-keep-up-is-a-crash-below-0-45-coming-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Fails to Keep Up, Is a Crash Below $0.45 Coming? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Finds Bullish Momentum But Will $2K Finally Fall? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-finds-bullish-momentum-but-will-2k-finally-fall-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249234</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price has been making corrections following the rally over the last few months. However, there are plenty of support levels that could hold the price in the short term. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart Looking at the daily timeframe, the price has been on the decline over a period of several weeks [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has been making corrections following the rally over the last few months. However, there are plenty of support levels that could hold the price in the short term.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the daily timeframe, the price has been on the decline over a period of several weeks after failing to reach the $2200 resistance level. The 50-day moving average is currently holding the market around the $1900 level, with $1800 also providing support.</p>
<p>In case the price rebounds from this area, a rapid rise toward the $2200 level could be expected. On the other hand, a breakdown would result in a further correction towards the 200-day moving average, trending around the $1600 mark. The RSI continues to oscillate around the 50% threshold recently.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249452" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249452" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249452" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" alt="ETHUSDT 4H - May 4 2023" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-4H-May-4-2023-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249452" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, the price seems to be attempting to escape the range between the $1800 and $1900 levels. The $1900 resistance is currently being tested once more, and a bullish breakout would pave the way for a surge toward values above $2000.</p>
<p>However, another rejection could initiate a bearish move toward the $1800 support level and potentially even lower. The RSI indicator is trending above the 50% mark in this timeframe, indicating that the bulls are in control and a bullish breakout is more probable.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249458" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249458" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249458" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg" alt="ETHUSDT Daily - May 4 2023" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSDT-Daily-May-4-2023-1-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249458" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-finds-bullish-momentum-but-will-2k-finally-fall-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Finds Bullish Momentum But Will $2K Finally Fall? (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Senator Calls Banks &#8220;Sophisticated Ponzi Schemes&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-calls-banks-sophisticated-ponzi-schemes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 18:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Congress]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249439</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/john-kennedy-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/john-kennedy-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[No bank is safe from the panic of a bank run in today’s social communications age, says Senator John Kennedy. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Republican Senator John Kennedy of Louisiana called banks “sophisticated Ponzi schemes” while discussing the US banking crisis that’s claimed multiple crypto-supportive financial institutions in the past two months. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The politician also spoke on the state of inflation, which he believes the Federal Reserve will need to bring to at least 8% to cool down. </span></p>
<h2>Banks Are Ponzi Schemes?<b><br />
</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://twitter.com/CarlBMenger/status/1654506749590732807" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with CNBC that aired in full on Friday, Kennedy stressed that banks “exist on the basis of trust,” and have been made more vulnerable in the era of advanced communications technology. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“They’re really just – and don’t take this the wrong way – sophisticated Ponzi schemes,” he said. “They work when everybody trusts each other.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Given the speed at which banking panic can spread beginning from a single person’s iPhone, Kennedy said a herd can “panic and stampede” to the point where “anybody can go broke.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) was seized by the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) in March after a run on deposits rendered it unable to satisfy all customers’ claims. Depositors were quickly </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/european-regulators-blast-federal-reserve-for-svb-depositor-bailout/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">bailed out</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in full by both the FDIC and Federal Reserve.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The initial bank run began when SVB revealed that it had realized a $1.8 billion loss following a $21 billion bond portfolio sale to restructure its balance sheet. Panic spread over the following two days, with PayPal co-founder Pether Thiel encouraging companies to withdraw from SVB. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The surrounding panic also caused withdrawal demand to surge at other banks, including Signature Bank, which was placed into receivership shortly after SVB. Earlier this week, </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/from-very-good-bank-to-got-nothing-for-shareholders-jim-cramers-dubious-advice-for-first-republic/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">First Republic Bank</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> was also pushed to extinction, with most of its assets being sold to JP Morgan by the FDIC. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Federal Reserve reiterated on Wednesday that the banking system remains “sound and resilient.” Former Coinbase CTO Balaji Srinivasan, however, has </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/balaji-forfeits-and-settles-1-million-bitcoin-bet-but-stands-by-hyperinflation-thesis/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">argued</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the Treasury Department and Federal Reserve have a history of not warning markets of impending danger until a deep recession actually occurs. </span></p>
<h2>A Longer Inflation Fight</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to Kennedy, taming inflation will require raising interest rates much further, from its current 5% to 5.25% level to the realm of 8% to 10% – unless the problem is tackled from both a monetary and fiscal angle. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Powell’s gonna have to raise rates much higher than he normally would have if Congress would slow the stimulus of spending,” he <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/video/2023/05/03/jay-powell-may-have-to-raise-rates-8-10-percent-to-fight-inflation-says-sen-john-kennedy.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Rising interest rates are considered largely responsible for the cratered bond portfolios that caused banks like SVB to go insolvent in the first place. After the latest rise, however, market </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-showing-promising-rise-potential-after-fed-rate-decision-santiment/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">analysis</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> suggests that Bitcoin may not be so affected by tighter monetary policy as it was last year. </span></p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of The Washington Post</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-senator-calls-banks-sophisticated-ponzi-schemes/" rel="nofollow">US Senator Calls Banks &#8220;Sophisticated Ponzi Schemes&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Fires Back at Reuters Over Report About Confiscated Accounts Linked to Terrorism</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-fires-back-at-reuters-over-report-about-confiscated-accounts-linked-to-terrorism/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Israel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Money Laundering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249311</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Binance_Reuters.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Binance_Reuters.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance claimed that Reuters ignored "critical facts" to debunk the exchange.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of Israel have reportedly seized around 190 cryptocurrency accounts at Binance since 2021, saying some of those were tied to the terrorist groups &#8211; Hamas and Islamic State.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange claimed that Reuters (the media outlet that informed about the confiscation) is &#8220;deliberately leaving out critical facts to fit their narrative.&#8221; It asserted that anti-money laundering and preventing terrorist activities remain a key focus for the company.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Reuters/Binance Clash</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the news agency, all seized Binance crypto accounts </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-seized-binance-crypto-accounts-thwart-islamic-state-document-shows-2023-05-04/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">belonged</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to three Palestinian currency exchange firms designated by Israel as &#8220;terrorist organizations.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, Reuters maintained that two of the total addresses were linked to Islamic State, whereas companies controlled by Hamas owned a dozen others. A document released by Israel&#8217;s National Bureau for Counter Terror Financing (NBCTF) and seen by the media outlet showed that the accounts belonged to a 28-year-old Palestinian called Osama Abuobayada. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Islamic State and Hamas have claimed responsibility for numerous incidents in the past several years, while the USA, the European Union, and many others have ranked them as some of the deadliest terrorist entities. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Reuters has criticized Binance over the years, blaming it for failing to comply with anti-money laundering procedures. It went further, claiming the company has processed more than $10 billion in payments for criminals since 2017.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange was quick to react to the allegations, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/community/our-response-to-reuters-1363137884256691497" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">saying</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a certain reporter from the multimedia news provider is &#8220;deliberately leaving out critical facts&#8221; to present Binance in a bad light. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It assured that anti-money laundering policies and tackling cryptocurrency-based financing of terrorism are some of the utmost standards for the firm:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The bottom line is that we are not aware of any exchange – or other financial institution for that matter – that does more today to keep bad actors off their platform than Binance. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Our policies and processes comply with AMLD5/6 anti-money laundering and counter-terrorism financing requirements, and we have a robust compliance program that incorporates sophisticated anti-money laundering and global sanctions principles and tools to detect and address suspicious activity. We even have specialists on our team who have focused their entire careers on counter-terrorism.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance said it has collaborated with law enforcement agencies on the aforementioned seizures. It added that wrongdoers don&#8217;t register accounts under the names of their criminal groups. However, the company takes appropriate action once it discovers such bad behavior and freezes accounts if necessary.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, the exchange outlined that blockchain technology has &#8220;proven to be one of the most powerful tools for law enforcement&#8217;s anti-money laundering efforts&#8221; due to its immutable, public nature. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hamas Says &#8220;No&#8221; to Bitcoin Donations</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <em>CryptoPotato </em></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/hamas-armed-wing-to-stop-accepting-bitcoin-donations-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last month, the armed wing of Hamas &#8211; Al-Qassam Brigades &#8211; plans to stop accepting donations in BTC to protect the contributors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some economists, such as Mohammad Abu Jayyab, think that Israel&#8217;s agencies could track those transactions and see who has a connection to the Palestinian organization. Another suggestion is that Hamas has found more advanced options to fund its operations or has shifted back to traditional finance methods.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American authorities halted the efforts of Hamas, al-Qaeda, and Islamic State to raise funds through digital currencies and seized $2 million in crypto in 2020. The Palestinian entity has obtained most of its BTC donations from Muslim countries since most stand behind it in its war against Israel.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-fires-back-at-reuters-over-report-about-confiscated-accounts-linked-to-terrorism/" rel="nofollow">Binance Fires Back at Reuters Over Report About Confiscated Accounts Linked to Terrorism</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Coin Explodes 1200% Weekly While Crypto Markets Stagnate: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-explodes-1200-weekly-while-crypto-markets-stagnate-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249418</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE is the number one cryptocurrency by means of overall market performance, acquiring a market capitalization upwards of $1 billion in less than three weeks.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The broader cryptocurrency market failed to chart any notable changes in the past seven days, with the total capitalization remaining more or less what it was back then. This comes on the back of slight volatility in between, but nothing that could have been sustained. That said, there&#8217;s an obvious exception in the face of the freshly-minted and now-trending PEPE coin. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<p>Bitcoin is trading more or less where it was exactly seven days ago &#8211; at $29K. The cryptocurrency plunged toward $27,500 in the middle of the week, but the bears were unable to sustain the selling pressure and the price recovered. The momentum is shaky, and market participants are on their toes as the cryptocurrency is trading within a range between $27,000 and $30K. A breakout in either direction will likely dictate where the market will be headed in the short term.</p>
<p>Typically, it&#8217;s during times like these when an explosive move follows, so it&#8217;s important to keep an eye on the markets at all times.</p>
<p>Speaking of explosive moves&#8230; let&#8217;s talk about PEPE.</p>
<p>For those of you who haven&#8217;t been following the space recently, PEPE is a brand new memecoin minted less than three weeks ago. It first made the news back then, soaring toward a multi-million dollar market cap and producing a few success stories in the face of people who made hundreds of thousands of dollars on its back.</p>
<p>However, fast-forward to today, this brand new memecoin is now traded across all major exchanges, including Binance, and has managed to acquire a market cap of over a whopping $1 billion. This puts it in the top 50 coins by means of total market cap, and who knows how much higher can it go. Will it challenge SHIB and DOGE? If one thing is clear, it&#8217;s that anything can happen within the cryptocurrency market, so it&#8217;s very exciting to see how it will shape up in the next few days.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,257B | 24H Vol: $43B | BTC Dominance: 45.2%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $29,313 (-0.6%) | ETH: $1,949 (+2%) | BNB: $327 (-1.5%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-249423" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover.jpg" alt="pepe_logo_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/pepe_logo_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>PEPE’s Market Cap Soars Above $1 Billion Following Binance Listing. </strong>PEPE is this week&#8217;s highlight, and it&#8217;s the cryptocurrency that soared a whopping 1200% in seven days. This was only <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepes-market-cap-soars-above-1-billion-following-another-60-daily-surge/" data-wpel-link="internal">accelerated</a> following the decision of Binance to also list it for trading.</p>
<p><strong>Ethereum Median Gas Fee Hit 12-Month High Amid Memecoin Resurgence. </strong>Amid the ongoing meme hype, the gas fees on Ethereum also skyrocketed. They <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-median-gas-fee-hit-12-month-high-amid-memecoin-resurgence/" data-wpel-link="internal">reached</a> a 12-month high amid the incredibly memecoin resurgence.</p>
<p><strong>Coinbase Posts $79M Net Loss But Beats Expectations. </strong>Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal">posted</a> a $79 million net loss for the first quarter of 2024. Despite this, the results were reported to be not as bad as they initially expected, which could be attributed to the market recovery.</p>
<p><strong>SUI Faced Massive Volatility Minutes After Mainnet Launch. </strong>The newest contestant in the L1 field &#8211; SUI &#8211; saw its mainnet launch this week. Unfortunately for the native cryptocurrency of the protocol, this led to a massive <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sui-faced-massive-volatility-minutes-after-mainnet-launch/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash</a> in its price.</p>
<p><strong>Fed Announces 25bps Rate Hike to 5%, Bitcoin Remains Flat. </strong>Another month, another rate hike. This time, the US Federal Reserve <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fed-announces-25bps-rate-hike-to-5-bitcoin-remains-flat/" data-wpel-link="internal">increased</a> the rates by another 0.25 basis points, bringing it up to 5%. The cryptocurrency market failed to react.</p>
<p><strong>Biden Administration Pushes Congress to Pass 30% Tax on Bitcoin Mining. </strong>The administration of US President Joe Biden <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/biden-administration-pushes-congress-to-pass-30-tax-on-bitcoin-mining/" data-wpel-link="internal">proposed</a> a 30% tax on Bitcoin mining. The change is titled Digital Asset Mining Energy (DAME) excise tax.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, PEPE, and Tron– <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-5-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-trx/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-coin-explodes-1200-weekly-while-crypto-markets-stagnate-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Coin Explodes 1200% Weekly While Crypto Markets Stagnate: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis May-5: ETH, XRP, ADA, PEPE, TRX</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-5-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-trx/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRXBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TRXUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron (TRX) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249337</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Pepe, and Tron. Ethereum (ETH) This week, Ethereum has retested the support at $1,800. Buyers showed strength and did not allow the price to fall lower, which is why ETH is found at a similar level to last week due to low volatility. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Pepe, and Tron.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-249405" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231.jpg" alt="cryptopost_friday_0505231" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/cryptopost_friday_0505231-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>This week, Ethereum has retested the support at $1,800. Buyers showed strength and did not allow the price to fall lower, which is why ETH is found at a similar level to last week due to low volatility.</p>
<p>The current target for this cryptocurrency is $2,000, which is also a key psychological level. In April, ETH managed to break above it but quickly lost ground once sellers took over the price action. Another break above $2,000 would be quite bullish, but momentum is lacking at this time.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Ethereum has found a good foundation to gather strength in the coming week. If buyers return to the market, then a retest of the key resistance appears imminent.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249347" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249347" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249347" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27.png" alt="ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27" width="1814" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-05_16-38-27-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249347" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>XRP is in red and has closed the past seven days with a 1.5% loss. The price appears on its way to test the key support at 43 cents. This would be the second time XRP tests this support, and could turn out to be a bearish move if buyers don&#8217;t return.</p>
<p>The key resistance is quite some distance away at 48 cents. The momentum indicators, such as the MACD and RSI, are also bearish, with the RSI falling under 50 points. XRP&#8217;s failure to sustain its price above 50 cents in April was a bearish signal, and the market did not hesitate to react.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, bears appear to have the upper hand right now, and a break of the key support could see this cryptocurrency go to 40 cents next.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249346" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249346" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249346" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46" width="1814" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46-1024x453.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-05_16-38-46-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249346" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>Cardano formed a bearish head and shoulders formation, which is about to resolve soon. If confirmed, that would mean the price could break lower. ADA also lost 5.4% of its valuation this past week.</p>
<p>The key support at 38 cents is critical for this cryptocurrency as it will determine the price action in the weeks to come. The bears appear to have the upper hand right now, but things could still go either way.</p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking ahead</span></span>, expect volatility to increase as the price approaches the key support. If buyers cannot defend this critical level, then ADA could fall towards 35 cents next. The key resistance is at 41 cents should buyers suddenly return.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249345" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249345" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249345" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13" width="1814" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13-1024x453.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-05_16-39-13-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249345" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Pepe (PEPE) </span></p>
<p>The star of the past few weeks has been PEPE which experienced a parabolic rally not seen since the early days of Shiba Inu and Dogecoin. Only this past week, PEPE managed to increase by over 600%. This mind-blowing performance comes on top of the euphoria generated by meme coins.</p>
<p>Despite this performance, buyers should be extremely careful if they are late to buy, as no one knows for how long this bullish momentum can be sustained. Eventually, the market equilibrium will reverse, and then it will be a rush to the exit.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, PEPE will continue to be in the spotlight one way or another and has put a long shadow on other meme coins such as DOGE, SHIB, or FLOKI.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249344" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249344" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249344" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-05_16-40-10-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249344" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Tron (TRX)</span></p>
<p>Tron surprised market participants with an excellent performance this past week, booking a 6.3% price increase while most altcoins are in red. The current resistance is found at 8 cents, and the price could continue higher until it hits this level.</p>
<p>The uptrend for Tron started back in November 2022, and so far, it has managed to sustain its rally. The current support is at 6 cents, and the momentum indicators just turned positive. For example, the daily MACD did a bullish cross yesterday. This is significant.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, TRX might continue higher in the coming days. The resistance at 8 cents seems to be the next considerable obstacle.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249343" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249343" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-249343" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36.png" alt="TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TRXUSDT_2023-05-05_16-42-36-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249343" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-5-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-trx/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis May-5: ETH, XRP, ADA, PEPE, TRX</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
