<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 21:57:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase Sees UAE as a Strategic Hub for International Operations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sees-uae-as-a-strategic-hub-for-international-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UAE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249661</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinbase_UAE.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Coinbase_UAE.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase believes that its establishment in the UAE will expand its global footprint.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase is considering the United Arab Emirates (UAE) as a potential strategic hub for its international operations.</p>
<p>In a Monday <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/the-uae-recognising-the-transformative-potential-of-the-cryptoeconomy" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a>, Coinbase’s vice president for international and business development Nana Murugesan disclosed that the exchange is currently in talks with Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM) regulators to expand the licensing for the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">just-launched</a> Coinbase International Exchange.</p>
<h2>Coinbase to Make UAE a Hub</h2>
<p>The Coinbase executive team, including co-founder and CEO Brian Armstrong and Murugesan, are currently in the UAE for meetings with policymakers, Web3 and crypto founders, and clients. Armstrong is set to give a keynote speech at the ongoing Dubai Fintech Summit under the patronage of the Royal Highness, who is also the Deputy Prime Minister and the Minister of Finance.</p>
<blockquote><p>“And this week we are delighted to be on the ground in Dubai and Abu Dhabi meeting key local stakeholders and commending in person the role they have played in creating such a welcoming environment. There is no doubt that UAE has the potential to be a strategic hub for Coinbase, amplifying our efforts across the world,” Murugesan said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Coinbase is also working with Dubai’s Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) as the regulator works toward <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dubai-sets-regulatory-guidlines-on-crypto-marketing-to-safeguard-investors-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">creating</a> a comprehensive framework for crypto assets following economic sustainability and cross-border financial security principles.</p>
<p>The exchange believes the economic and technological opportunities provided by crypto and Web3 in the UAE will play an important part in achieving its goal of bringing one billion users to the nascent sector. The country, which serves as a bridge between Asia and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-eyes-europe-expansion-hires-four-new-executives/" data-wpel-link="internal">Europe</a>, will aid Coinbase in expanding its global footprint.</p>
<h2>A Welcoming Environment</h2>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase praised the UAE for creating an environment that is welcoming for crypto businesses and the development of the Web3 ecosystem. The existing and forthcoming rules align with the region’s objective of becoming a global leader in the blockchain space.</p>
<blockquote><p>“In short, the region is standing-out as a leader in the development of a web3 ecosystem, making it an attractive location to consider investing in. The vacuum created by other notable jurisdictions means that international counterparts, such as the UAE, are racing to fill the regulatory gap,” Murugesan added.</p></blockquote>
<p>While it remains unclear if Coinbase will eventually center its operations in the UAE due to the favorable regulatory environment, Armstrong has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-100-committed-to-the-us-despite-regulatory-uncertainty-brian-armstrong/" data-wpel-link="internal">clarified</a> that the exchange will remain 100% committed to the US.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-sees-uae-as-a-strategic-hub-for-international-operations/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Sees UAE as a Strategic Hub for International Operations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin’s Fees Explode Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Mania, Miners Benefit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 23:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249721</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/bitcoin_cover-8.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s blockchain was flooded with volume over the weekend by transactions involving so-called “BRC-20” Ordinals – an emergent standard for issuing fungible tokens on Bitcoin.   The surge caused network fees to skyrocket to the point where transaction fee revenue for miners briefly surpassed the natural block subsidy for the first time since 2017.  Meme Tokens [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin’s blockchain was flooded with volume over the weekend by transactions involving so-called “BRC-20” Ordinals – an emergent standard for issuing fungible tokens on Bitcoin.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The surge caused network fees to skyrocket to the point where transaction fee revenue for miners briefly surpassed the natural block subsidy for the first time since 2017. </span></p>
<h2>Meme Tokens on Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to data from </span><a href="https://dune.com/cryptokoryo/brc20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Dune Analytics</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, over 3.7 million BRC-20 Ordinals transactions have already occurred, versus just 631,630 non-BRC-20 Ordinals transactions. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A </span><a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">separate dashboard</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows that over 4.7 million Ordinals inscriptions are now on Bitcoin, most of which appeared within the past two weeks alone. This indicates that much of the recent activity isn’t so much related to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/taproot-usage-soars-amid-rising-interest-in-ordinals-on-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ordinals NFTs</a> as in early February, but to new fungible assets created by the BRC-20 standard. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">BRC-20 is a “fun experimental standard demonstrating that you can create off-chain balance states with inscriptions,” wrote Twitter author domodata on </span><a href="https://domo-2.gitbook.io/brc-20-experiment/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">gitbook</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, when </span><a href="https://twitter.com/domodata/status/1633658974686855168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1633658974686855168%7Ctwgr%5E6797f928b32a7ca6c6a92a0781ecc6ffe45fcbdf%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fmythbtc.xyz%2Fbrc-20-token-standard-bitcoin%2F" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">revealing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> the innovation on March 10th.  “this is an extremely dynamic experiment, and I strongly discourage any financial decisions to be made on the basis of its design.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The author added that the idea of issuing assets on Bitcoin is “not novel” and that <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lightning-labs-aims-to-bitcoinize-the-dollar-with-taros-alpha-release/" data-wpel-link="internal">Taro</a> – a lightning network-based solution for Bitcoin asset issuance – is “unequivocally a better solution.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite his personal reservations, BRC-20 hasn’t failed to pick up steam. Data from brc-20.io shows that the market cap for tokens of this standard has surpassed $720 million and that their cumulative trading volume over the past 24 hours is over $132 million. Leading the pack is a token called “ordi,” followed by a Bitcoin-based version of the memecoin </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">PEPE</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, and another called “meme.”</span></p>
<h2>Fees Skyrocket</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Transactions for these new memecoins are competing with ordinary BTC transfers for Bitcoin block space, creating a highly competitive fee market that makes the average transaction more expensive. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Data from </span><a href="https://ycharts.com/indicators/bitcoin_average_transaction_fee#:~:text=Basic%20Info,799.8%25%20from%20one%20year%20ago." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">ycharts</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> shows that the average Bitcoin transaction fee has skyrocketed to $19.21 as of Monday, up from just $2.90 last week. Meanwhile, according to mempool.space, over 460,000 transactions are still awaiting confirmation within the blockchain. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The spike is almost certainly related to BRC-20 Ordinals, since Glassnode data indicates that Taproot-related transactions have </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-75-of-daily-bitcoin-on-chain-transactions-used-taproot-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">shot up</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to 75% of all on-chain transactions, as opposed to just 1.5% at the start of the year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The congested network makes transactions with Bitcoin more expensive and slow, but has created a massive boost to miner revenue in recent days. In fact, at block 788695, the associated miner netted 6.7 BTC in fees, which is larger than the consistent 6.25 BTC reward that comes attached to each block. The last time a flip of this kind occurred was in 2017.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many in the Bitcoin community are enthusiastic that BRC-20 tokens are driving up fees in this manner, as it means that Bitcoin will boast a profitable fee market with mining incentives even after the block subsidy dwindles to near zero over the coming decades. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/IIICapital/status/1655579667955343362</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others, however, view the development as a denial of service attack on Bitcoin, making transactions unfeasible for less wealthy populations in developing countries. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Nodes can always decide to invalidate blocks by miners that include transactions they don&#8217;t consider valid,” suggested Bull Bitcoin CEO and Ordinals critic Francis Pouliot over Twitter. “Last resort and could be messy but it&#8217;s always possible.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-fees-explode-amid-brc-20-memecoin-mania-miners-benefit/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin’s Fees Explode Amid BRC-20 Memecoin Mania, Miners Benefit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OKX Expands its Global Reach With a Turkish Office</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/okx-expands-its-global-reach-with-a-turkish-office/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 21:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OKEx]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Turkey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249653</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OKX_Turkey.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/OKX_Turkey.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto exchange considers Türkiye as a "growing center of innovation and blockchain expertise" and is willing to open an office there. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the leading cryptocurrency exchanges &#8211; OKX &#8211; intends to open an office in Türkiye in the following months.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company has already interacted with the Turkish market, launching direct deposits and withdrawals in the country&#8217;s official currency &#8211; TRY. It also put its name among the numerous crypto platforms that sent aid packages to the nation when a devastating earthquake hit it in February.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another Expansion Step</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OKX&#8217;s President &#8211; Hong Fang &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/okx-to-expand-global-presence-with-turkiye-office-301818060.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the exchange has picked Türkiye as its next destination because it considers it an &#8220;important market:&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Opening an office in Türkiye will be a crucial step for OKX as we move from a trust-based system to one that is trustless and empowers users to take control of their financial future. Türkiye is an important market for us, and we&#8217;re excited to build strong relationships with our users and contribute to the development of its crypto ecosystem.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CIO Jason Lau highlighted the country as a &#8220;growing center of innovation and blockchain expertise with a user base that has a strong appetite for crypto.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Turkish people have indeed displayed huge interest in the digital asset universe lately. One possible reason could be the financial turmoil that looms across the nation and the depreciating official currency. The Turkish lira recently crossed a record low against the US dollar: an event that has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/turks-pile-into-bitcoin-and-tether-to-escape-plunging-lira-11641982077" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">triggered </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">an increased interest in bitcoin and stablecoins. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OKX has already taken steps regarding its upcoming expansion, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-launches-turkish-lira-deposits-and-withdrawals/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">enabling</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> deposits and withdrawals in Turkish Lira (TRY) in March this year. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Our goal is to become the leading crypto platform in Türkiye. This starts with listening to the community about their needs and investing in the market. We want to give the Turkish community a platform to explore, experiment, and dream up the future with us.</span></p>
<p>Perhaps we will see the next big thing come out of Türkiye with the support from us and other crypto companies,&#8221; the exchange&#8217;s CMO &#8211; Haider Rafique &#8211; said at the time.</p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm was also one of the multiple contributors that </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.okx.com/learn/crypto-wallet-for-turkiye-relief" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">helped</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Türkiye get back on its feet after the disastrous earthquake that hit the southern part of the nation in February and killed over 50,000 people. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stretching to Other Locations, too</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Türkiye is not the only place OKX has recently set up a base in. The company, whose main headquarters are in Seychelles, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-to-open-office-in-australia/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> it will soon open an office in Australia. The popular F1 driver who serves as OKX ambassador &#8211; Daniel Ricciardo &#8211; said:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I&#8217;m very excited to see OKX plan an office in my home country. I had a great time celebrating with the OKX team and the crypto community today. The future looks bright for OKX in Australia.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange further </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-to-apply-for-vasp-licence-in-hong-kong-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">displayed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its intention to apply for a VASP license in Hong Kong and, thus, strengthen its presence there. The special administrative region of China has emerged as a crypto hub lately after the local authorities announced plans to implement a friendly regulatory framework on the industry.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/okx-expands-its-global-reach-with-a-turkish-office/" rel="nofollow">OKX Expands its Global Reach With a Turkish Office</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Liechtenstein Could Embrace Bitcoin as a Payment Method for Gvmt Services, Says PM</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/liechtenstein-could-embrace-bitcoin-as-a-payment-method-for-gvmt-services-says-pm/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 19:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Switzerland]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249597</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Liechtenstein_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Liechtenstein_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[An upcoming legislation could allow the residents of Liechtenstein to settle government services in BTC. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Prime Minister of Liechtenstein &#8211; Daniel Risch &#8211; said the local lawmakers plan to enable bitcoin payments for various government services. However, he did not disclose whether the country will adopt the primary cryptocurrency as a legal tender. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another country that has turned its focus toward BTC is Liechtenstein&#8217;s western neighbor &#8211; Switzerland &#8211; and, more specifically, the city of Lugano. The domestic authorities have developed an infrastructure to make Bitcoin, Tether, and LVGA tokens official means of settlement in the region. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Payment Option is Coming</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Daniel Risch &#8211; the PM of Liechtenstein who also serves as Finance Minister &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.handelsblatt.com/politik/international/kryptowaehrung-liechtenstein-will-staatliche-dienstleistungen-kuenftig-auch-in-bitcoin-bezahlen-lassen/29134712.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the ruling body could allow citizens to settle government services in bitcoin. Once the payment is confirmed, the authorities will have the option to swap the crypto assets for Swiss francs (the official currency of the European microstate).<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249608" style="width: 600px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249608" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch.webp" alt="Daniel Risch" width="600" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch.webp 1200w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch-300x200.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch-1024x683.webp 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch-768x512.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Daniel-Risch-50x33.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249608" class="wp-caption-text">Daniel Risch, Source: Brussels Research Group</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that the politician failed to provide details on whether Liechtenstein intends to embrace BTC as a legal tender, similar to what El Salvador and the Central African Republic <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-months-later-bitcoin-now-officially-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">did</a> in 2021 and 2022, respectively. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is not the European nation&#8217;s first interaction with the cryptocurrency industry. The Liechtenstein Parliament </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.liechtensteinusa.org/article/liechtensteins-parliament-approves-blockchain-act-unanimously" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">passed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Token and Trusted Technology Service Provider Act, better known as the &#8220;Blockchain Act.&#8221; The legislation, which became official at the beginning of 2020, set clear standards in the sector, providing maximum protection to users.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The leading private bank in Liechtenstein – LGT Bank &#8211; has also jumped on the crypto bandwagon. It partnered with SEBA Bank in 2022 to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/liechtensteins-largest-private-bank-enables-direct-investments-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">enable</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> direct investments in digital currencies for its clients. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Cryptocurrencies are still in a stage of dynamic development. LGT, therefore first created the corresponding, necessary processes and framework for this type of investment,&#8221; CEO Matt said at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lugano&#8217;s Efforts</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Swiss city of Lugano, located less than 200 kilometers from Liechtenstein&#8217;s capital Vaduz, made the headlines in March 2022 by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swiss-city-lugano-to-make-bitcoin-and-tether-its-official-de-facto-currency/" data-wpel-link="internal">introducing</a> BTC, USDT, and its own LVGA Points token as legal tender. The initiative became possible after a collaboration between the authorities of the town and Tether (the company behind the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The firm&#8217;s CTO &#8211; Paolo Ardoino &#8211; praised El Salvador&#8217;s bitcoin forays, arguing Lugano could also benefit from the adoption:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;El Salvador&#8217;s GDP increased by 10% and its tourism by 30% after declaring Bitcoin a legal tender. Imagine what we can do in a city at the center of Europe.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The move, named Plan ₿, also aims to enable locals to pay taxes or public service fees via the aforementioned assets. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Tether </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/lugano-after-one-year-on-its-bitcoin-and-tether-standard/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">outlined</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in March this year that the initiative has been quite successful during the first year of its existence. According to the company, more than 150 domestic merchants have accepted BTC, USDT, and LVGA as payment methods, while the total number could surpass 2,500 by the end of 2023. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/liechtenstein-could-embrace-bitcoin-as-a-payment-method-for-gvmt-services-says-pm/" rel="nofollow">Liechtenstein Could Embrace Bitcoin as a Payment Method for Gvmt Services, Says PM</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO: US SEC is Acting Alone in its Crypto Regulation Efforts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-us-sec-is-acting-alone-in-its-crypto-regulation-efforts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249695</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Coinbase co-founder believes that the SEC’s stance on crypto regulation is different from the viewpoint of other regulators.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brian Armstrong, the co-founder and CEO of leading American cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, believes the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is on a lone crusade in the push for regulatory clarity in the country, as the agency’s stance on the matter is different from that of Congress and other federal regulators.</p>
<p>During a Monday <a href="https://twitter.com/CNBCMiddleEast/status/1655486443349848065?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with CNBC, the CEO insisted that SEC chair Gary Gensler is attempting to regulate the American digital asset industry from an anti-crypto perspective for some unknown reason.</p>
<h2>A Lone Crusader</h2>
<blockquote><p>“I think the broad consensus view in the U.S. government is that there should be a clear rule book, and this is going to require new legislation from Congress. The SEC is a bit of an outlier here. There’s kind of a lone crusade, if you will, with Gary Gensler, the chair there, and he has taken a more anti-crypto view for some reason,” the Coinbase CEO said.</p></blockquote>
<p>Armstrong stated that Gensler is not trying to regulate the crypto industry as much as he is curtailing it, with the number of lawsuits the SEC has filed. The Coinbase boss argued that the legal battles were unhelpful for the industry.</p>
<p>Recall that the securities regulator has served multiple lawsuits against several crypto exchanges. Coinbase also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-and-legal-officer-respond-to-secs-wells-notice/" data-wpel-link="internal">received</a> a Wells Notice from the agency indicating potential enforcement action despite the absence of a clear rule book for cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Armstrong noted that the absence of clear regulation allowed Coinbase to get clarity from the courts, a move the exchange commenced last year. As <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a>, the Third Circuit Court of Appeals recently ordered the SEC to respond to Coinbase’s rulemaking petition filed nine months ago within ten days.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Not Relocating Overseas</h2>
<p>Furthermore, the Coinbase CEO <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-100-committed-to-the-us-despite-regulatory-uncertainty-brian-armstrong/" data-wpel-link="internal">reiterated</a> his stance that the exchange would not move its operations to offshore regions amid the regulatory uncertainty in the U.S. However, he mentioned that the company would invest in areas like the U.K. and E.U., which have more thoughtful approaches to crypto.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Coinbase is not gonna relocate overseas. We’re always going to have a U.S. presence &#8230; But the U.S. is a little bit behind right now. I would say we’re seeing more thoughtful approaches. For instance, in the E.U. [European Union], they’ve actually already passed comprehensive crypto legislation,” Armstrong stated.</p></blockquote>
<p>Meanwhile, an earlier report confirmed that Coinbase is already considering the UAE as a hub for its international operations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-us-sec-is-acting-alone-in-its-crypto-regulation-efforts/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO: US SEC is Acting Alone in its Crypto Regulation Efforts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Web3.Conference Will Gather Web3 Builders and Creators this May in Amsterdam</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-web3-conference-will-gather-web3-builders-and-creators-this-may-in-amsterdam/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 16:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249697</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Frame_890_1683560309WGGwiqO8HB.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Frame_890_1683560309WGGwiqO8HB.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 8th, 2023] The Web3.Conference is the premier event to guide you around the fascinating world of Web3. Participants can explore, learn, network, and gain insights into the latest trends and use cases emerging within this new internet standard. With a lineup of famous speakers, industry leaders, marketers, developers, investors, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 8th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://bit.ly/3zEe0qg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">The Web3.Conference</a> is the premier event to guide you around the fascinating world of Web3. Participants can explore, learn, network, and gain insights into the latest trends and use cases emerging within this new internet standard. With a lineup of famous speakers, industry leaders, marketers, developers, investors, and entrepreneurs, the conference promises a day packed with insightful talks and networking.</p>
<p><strong>Key topics include:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>How Web3 projects will change the way we live</li>
<li>Web3 infrastructure: building Decentralized Autonomous Organizations</li>
<li>Web3 NFT use cases for business</li>
<li>Will Web3 make or break social media?</li>
<li>The role of the metaverse + gaming in the new Web3 reality</li>
<li>How to invest in Web3</li>
<li>AI&#8217;s role in shaping the future of Web3</li>
</ul>
<p>Web3 is a hot topic today because it represents the next generation of the internet in which decentralization, privacy, and user empowerment are at the forefront. Web3 represents a significant shift in the way we think about and use the internet, and its potential for innovation and disruption has captured the attention of investors, developers, and entrepreneurs.</p>
<p>The Web3.Conference opens its doors on May 19 in the vibrant city of Amsterdam. It’s rich in culture, with numerous museums, galleries, theaters and events. But that’s not all: during the time in Amsterdam, participants will experience amazing side events and an unforgettable afterparty just for the guests of The Web3.Conference.</p>
<p>Web3 builders, investors, marketers, creators, developers, CEOs, and numerous NFT projects will be there to share their knowledge and offer unique opportunities for further growth. The event will offer much more than just networking, leaving participants feeling inspired and motivated, through mixing with individuals and companies who share deep passion for Web3.</p>
<p>The organizers of this event, AroundB, have already held several events in Amsterdam. These include The Conference.Exchanges: How to DEX in 2022, which was held in the charming Vondel Church, done up in a Gothic revival style, and The Conference.Exchanges: DeFi Edition. Both events had tremendous success and were entirely sold out. The upcoming The Web3.Conference promises to repeat this feat on an even grander scale.</p>
<p>For people interested in collaboration and even support, AroundB has plenty of options for sponsors and partners. Interested speakers with relevant expertise can submit candidacy for a speaker slot.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s shape the Web3 future together!</p>
<p>Contact AroundB to receive a sponsorship deck and discuss further opportunities: <a href="mailto:hello@aroundb.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener">hello@aroundb.com</a></p>
<p>Follow: <a href="https://twitter.com/TheWeb3Conf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a> | <a href="https://t.me/theweb3conference" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Community</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-web3-conference-will-gather-web3-builders-and-creators-this-may-in-amsterdam/" rel="nofollow">The Web3.Conference Will Gather Web3 Builders and Creators this May in Amsterdam</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Traders Sell BAYC Below Floor Price to Buy PEPE</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nft-traders-sell-bayc-below-floor-price-to-buy-pepe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249619</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/BAYC_Floor.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/BAYC_Floor.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Traders used the funds from the sales (nearly $1.3 million worth of ETH) to purchase PEPE.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Certain traders have recently sold NFTs part of the Bored Ape Yacht Collection (BAYC) at a discount to invest in the now-trending memecoin &#8211; PEPE.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The asset has been among the best performers in the crypto market lately, as its price has surged by over 600% over the last two weeks before cooling off in the past 24 hours.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Shifting From NFTs to PEPE</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The popular Twitter user Cirrus <a href="https://twitter.com/cirrusnft/status/1655295076443238401" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> recently that some traders had sold 14 BAYC NFTs below their floor price during the weekend. They used the 672 ETH (worth over $1.2 million at the time) acquired from the deals to purchase PEPE.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The crypto community was somewhat divided on that move, with some arguing that dealing with the memecoin at the moment could turn quite profitable. Others believe the hype around the token has reached such a high level that an upcoming crash seems inevitable. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Cirrus has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/CirrusNFT/status/1654908749637885952" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that people are likely to part with their digital art below floor prices to enter PEPE&#8217;s ecosystem. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><em><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CryptoPotato</span></em><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-reasons-pepe-soared-90-in-the-past-24-hours/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last week, crypto whales have also shifted their attention toward the memecoin. One such holder swapped $590,000 worth of WBTC, $90,000 worth of CULT, $235,000 worth of UNI, and $37,000 worth of ETH (almost all their assets in this wallet) to get 1.72T PEPE. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">PEPE has turned into a real sensation in the world of crypto, boosting its market capitalization from less than a million dollars in mid-April (the launch date) to over $1.7 billion (according to CoinMarketCap) on May 5. It is worth mentioning that even celebrities joined the overall mania. One example is the American rapper DeAndre Cortez Way (better known as Soulja Boy), who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/souljaboy/status/1653971555456815104" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> he &#8220;done got rich off PEPE.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Has PEPE Started Losing Steam?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the massive PEPE craze and the almost daily price spikes, the asset has been on a downtrend for the past 24 hours. The decline comes a few days after Binance &#8211; the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepes-market-cap-soars-above-1-billion-following-another-60-daily-surge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">listed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the coin in its Innovation Zone. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">We are yet to see whether <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE</a> will mimic the performance of well-known memecoins, such as Dogecoin and Shiba Inu, which have attracted a substantial number of investors in the past few years. During its peak in 2021, DOGE skyrocketed to nearly $0.75 and reached a market cap of almost $90 billion. It is currently among the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, investors should keep in mind that the PEPE mania could be a temporary event, meaning that becoming rich overnight might not be the case (as most would wish).</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-traders-sell-bayc-below-floor-price-to-buy-pepe/" rel="nofollow">NFT Traders Sell BAYC Below Floor Price to Buy PEPE</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>TUSD Readies Operation Plan for International Transition</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tusd-readies-operation-plan-for-international-transition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249652</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Untitled_design_1683533207aWUKNNzxlO.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Untitled_design_1683533207aWUKNNzxlO.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, May 8th, 2023] TrueUSD (TUSD), a leading stablecoin provider, announced its intention to implement a plan for the international transition of its management services, reflecting an emerging industry trend of international expansion. Since its inception in 2018, TUSD has led industry innovation in the stablecoin sector with a strong emphasis [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, May 8th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>TrueUSD (TUSD), a leading stablecoin provider, announced its intention to implement a plan for the international transition of its management services, reflecting an emerging industry trend of international expansion. Since its inception in 2018, TUSD has led industry innovation in the stablecoin sector with a strong emphasis on client due diligence and regulatory compliance while growing its reserve portfolios in collaboration with a diversified network of financial institutions and fiduciaries. TrueUSD has proven to be one of the most trusted stablecoins during recent market volatility and disruption to the US banking sector.</p>
<p>The expansion and transition of TrueUSD’s operations was part of the intention around its acquisition in 2020 and conditions are now appropriate to begin this next phase of portfolio review, consolidation and growth. While TrueUSD remains committed to serving all members of its global community, this announcement signifies TUSD’s effort to further align itself with the development of the stablecoin sector against continued disruptions to the banking system and ongoing regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<h2>About TrueUSD</h2>
<p>TrueUSD (TUSD) is the first digital asset with live on-chain attestations by independent third-party institutions and is backed 1:1 with USD. So far, it has been listed on more than 100 trading platforms such as Binance and Huobi, and is live on 10+ mainstream public chains, including Ethereum, TRON, Avalanche, BNB Chain, Fantom, and Polygon. TrueUSD is attested in real-time by The Network Firm LLP, an independent, industry-specialized accounting firm in the U.S., to ensure the 1:1 ratio of its USD reserve to the circulating token supply and the 100% collateral rate. With the integration of Chainlink PoR, TrueUSD becomes the first USD-Backed stablecoin to secure minting and further ensure transparency and reliability. Users can access the relevant data via the official website <a href="http://tusd.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tusd.io</a> at any time. TUSD was granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the Commonwealth of Dominica on October 7th 2022.</p>
<p><a href="https://tusd.io" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Website</strong></a> | <a href="https://twitter.com/tusdio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Twitter</strong> </a><strong>| </strong><a href="https://trueusd.medium.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Medium</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="http://discord.gg/tusdio" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Discord</strong></a><strong> | </strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tusd-readies-operation-plan-for-international-transition/" rel="nofollow">TUSD Readies Operation Plan for International Transition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Someone Just Lost $120K in a Costly Mistake With ETH Fees</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/someone-just-lost-120k-in-a-costly-mistake-with-eth-fees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249646</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ethereum_shadow_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ethereum_shadow_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[As a result of memecoin renaissance, the gas fees on Layer 2 networks, especially chains built using zero-knowledge proofs, also shot up. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While the debate surrounding Ethereum&#8217;s high gas fees have been a major pain point, the latest spike comes amidst the PEPE memecoin hysteria that has put tremendous pressure on the network once again.</p>
<p>Traders are paying thousands of dollars for a transaction as Ethereum&#8217;s gas fees surged above a one-year high.</p>
<ul>
<li>In the latest development, a trader ended up paying 64 ETH for a single transaction on May 8th. According to an <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1655472148020961285" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a> from the blockchain tracker, &#8216;Whale Alert,&#8217; the user paid around $119,157 just to send 84 WETH.</li>
<li>It is important to note that transaction fees on Ethereum have climbed much higher levels ranging between $50 to $70 in 2021. But the figures have been low since the market crashed in May 2022.</li>
<li>The excitement surrounding PEPE can be attributed to the revival in gas fees.</li>
<li>As such, the average transaction fee <a href="https://etherscan.io/chart/avg-txfee-usd" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">surged</a> to $27.62 on May 5, a level that was last seen almost a year ago. Since the memecoin&#8217;s launch on April 18th, average gas fees have increased by a whopping 115%.</li>
<li>However, the mainnet isn&#8217;t the only network that has been hit by high gas fees. Layer 2s &#8211; which are designed to reduce transaction costs &#8211; were not spared as well as network demand shot up.</li>
<li>Notably, zero-knowledge proof-based (ZK) rollups <a href="https://twitter.com/healthymofin/status/1654291117016326147" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">witnessed</a> fees for swapping tokens surge between $2-$11 for solutions such as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-announces-polygon-bridge-for-its-zero-knowledge-rollup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Polygon zkEVM</a>, Starknet, and zkSync Era mainnet.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/someone-just-lost-120k-in-a-costly-mistake-with-eth-fees/" rel="nofollow">Someone Just Lost $120K in a Costly Mistake With ETH Fees</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chinese Supreme Court Clarifies Framework for Crypto Disputes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-supreme-court-clarifies-framework-for-crypto-disputes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 13:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249639</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/China.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/China.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although cryptocurrencies are now technically banned in China, the local system still provides a framework for legal disputes arising from their use.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since September 2021, China has banned cryptocurrency transactions and heavily curtailed crypto mining operations.</p>
<p>However, the ban has turned out to be, in practice, more of a general guideline. Since its implementation, Chinese policymakers have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-happening-with-china-and-its-crypto-approach/" data-wpel-link="internal">discussed</a> crypto taxation. Furthermore, a court <a href="https://www.theregister.com/2022/09/15/china_crypto_asset_trading_case/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">case</a> from 2022 clarified that although locals are not allowed to use crypto as a currency, they can still own them – as an investment asset.</p>
<p>As an asset, it can be taxed – leading to further deliberation on how Chinese courts should proceed when faced with lawsuits involving cryptocurrencies.</p>
<h2>Debts Can Be Settled With Crypto</h2>
<p>In a <a href="http://www.baotoulawyer.com/info/6080.jspx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a> made by members of the Chinese Supreme Court, policymakers declared that debts can be settled in cryptocurrency up to an undisclosed amount, provided a valid contract stipulating payment in such assets was already active and no other local laws take precedence.</p>
<p>However, it is reiterated that the cryptocurrencies used to settle the debt are not legal tender. If the aforementioned contract them as such, Chinese courts are to declare it <a href="https://wublock.substack.com/p/full-requirements-for-cryptocurrency" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">invalid</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Where a party uses virtual currency as a regular payment instrument to exchange legal tender or physical commodities under the guise of a basic transaction contract, the people&#8217;s court shall determine that the contract is invalid.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Platforms Liable Under Certain Conditions</h2>
<p>Leading up to the total ban on crypto trading in 2021, the Chinese government issued multiple warnings to citizens on the risk associated with trading in such assets. Although viewed as overbearing at the time, the events of 2022 have proven that those warnings were not completely unwarranted.</p>
<p>Chinese citizens who lost their assets during the crypto winter will not be protected in court by the government, according to the legal draft discussed.</p>
<p>However, Chinese citizens who participated in crypto trading before the 4th of September 2017 – the date of a legal document named “Notice on Preventing the Financing Risks of Token Issuance” – and lost their assets due to trading platforms failing to meet their contractual obligations will be allowed to pursue justice in court.</p>
<p>The document further outlines the way Chinese courts should treat disputes in which criminal activity is suspected or in which crypto mining is involved. Although crypto trading may technically be banned in China, the continued focus on the asset class could mean that the ruling will be lifted at some point in the future, considering that the nation has repeatedly changed its stance on digital assets in the past.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/chinese-supreme-court-clarifies-framework-for-crypto-disputes/" rel="nofollow">Chinese Supreme Court Clarifies Framework for Crypto Disputes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
