<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:56:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Father and Son Face up to 20 Years in Jail for Orchestrating a $10M Crypto Scam (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/father-and-son-face-up-to-20-years-in-jail-for-orchestrating-a-10m-crypto-scam-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 22:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260420</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Prison-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The men who stole investor funds to live like millionaires will most likely spend some years behind bars.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American authorities have reportedly arrested Brandon Austin and his father, Eugene &#8220;Hugh&#8221; Austin, over accusations that they run a massive crypto fraud, embezzling over $10 million from investors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brandon, who has already pleaded guilty, will hear his sentence on September 6.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Conning Investors to Fund a Lavish Lifestyle</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to recent <a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/father-son-duo-hugh-and-brandon-austin-accused-of-scamming-dollar10-million-in-crypto" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">coverage</a>, federal agents detained the 27-year-old Brandon Austin in April and his dad on July 5. US Attorney Damian Williams said the duo &#8220;victimized both sophisticated and novice cryptocurrency investors alike out of millions.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Specifically, the family encouraged people to purchase cryptocurrencies through them by promising great returns. However, they swindled every cent and used the money for their own benefit. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The officials claimed the wrongdoers stayed in posh hotels, bought luxurious cars, and visited expensive restaurants. They also gifted funds to their loved ones via wire transfers. Brandon sent $50,000 to the mother of his children and $32,000 to his girlfriend, while Hugh handed $10,000 to his dad and lover. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The duo went further, organizing glamorous trips to New York, Miami, and Europe, inviting investors as special guests who would later understand that those parties were thrown so the Austin family could amass new victims. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Each investor parted with a different sum, with one losing over $500,000. At one point, they got angry with Hugh, urging him to keep his promise and send him the assets and return on the investment. The alleged criminal replied plainly:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I w call u (sic) in about 25 minutes. Thanks, Hugh.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Brandon has pleaded guilty, agreeing to forfeit $3.4 million and to pay $2 million in restitution. The federal agents also confiscated a 2022 E-Pace P250 Jaguar that was said to be worth over $60,000.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The two men face up to 20 years in prison on charges like money laundering and wire fraud. The magistrates are expected to decide Brandon&#8217;s punishment on September 6.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Mini Version of OneCoin?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The aforementioned case looks similar to one of the biggest frauds in the history of crypto &#8211; OneCoin. The Ponzi scheme, orchestrated by Ruja Ignatova (a.k.a. &#8220;The Cryptoqueen&#8221;), ran between 2014 and 2016, draining approximately $4 billion from investors. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The head of the scam mysteriously disappeared shortly after the authorities launched an investigation against OneCoin. Ignatova was last spotted in Athens, Greece, in 2017, and her whereabouts have been the subject of conspiracy theories from that moment.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some believe she is hiding on a luxurious yacht in the Mediterranean Sea, away from the coast (where law enforcement agencies are unauthorized to arrest her).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other sources have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/was-fbis-most-wanted-cryptoqueen-brutally-murdered-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hinted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that Ignatova might have been brutally murdered in 2019 after a Bulgarian drug lord got burned from investing in her scheme. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/father-and-son-face-up-to-20-years-in-jail-for-orchestrating-a-10m-crypto-scam-report/" rel="nofollow">Father and Son Face up to 20 Years in Jail for Orchestrating a $10M Crypto Scam (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CZ Admits to Involuntary Terminations Within Binance But Disagrees With Reported Numbers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cz-admits-to-involuntary-terminations-within-binance-but-disagrees-with-reported-numbers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260809</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The numbers reported by CNBC and WSJ are "way off," said CZ.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Several traditional media outlets reported recently that Binance, the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, has or will have to dismiss thousands of employees in the wake of its legal battle with US regulators.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s CEO confirmed the layoffs but disagreed with the &#8220;FUD&#8221; reported numbers of terminated staff members.</p>
<h2>CNBC, WSJ Reports</h2>
<p>Citing a person familiar with the matter, the Wall Street Journal <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/binance-lays-off-over-1-000-employees-d59ff6ad" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claimed</a> on Friday that Binance had already dismissed over 1,000 people as it prepares for a lengthy and costly legal fight with US regulators.</p>
<p>Former company workers asserted that more layoffs will follow in the upcoming weeks, with the customer support team being hit the hardest.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;As we prepare for the next major bull cycle, it has become clear that we need to focus on talent density across the organization to ensure we remain nimble and dynamic. This is not a case of rightsizing, but rather, re-evaluating whether we have the right talent and expertise in critical roles,&#8221; &#8211; commented a Binance spokesperson.</p></blockquote>
<p>CNBC took it a step further, <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/14/binance-could-lay-off-thousands-in-response-to-doj-probe-source.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">indicating</a> that the overall cut-offs within the exchange could reach 3,000, which is almost half of the firm&#8217;s <a href="https://buybitcoinworldwide.com/binance-statistics/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> employees.</p>
<p>The media outlet&#8217;s source noted that the DOJ battle could change Binance &#8220;fundamentally,&#8221; as if the firm decides to settle, it could cost it billions of dollars.</p>
<h2>CZ Confirms But Not Everything</h2>
<p>Changpeng Zhao, CEO of Binance, started this year with a message for all of his followers that they should learn to ignore much of the FUD coming from traditional media outlets. In the next seven months or so, he had to use that phrase quite a lot.</p>
<p>When it came down to the layoff reports, CZ actually confirmed that his company had to undertake such actions, which he referred to as &#8220;involuntary terminations.&#8221; However, he said Binance is doing so as it strives for &#8220;talent density.&#8221;</p>
<p>Additionally, CZ strongly disagreed with the aforementioned number of laid-off employees.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As we continuously strive to increase talent density, there are involuntary terminations. This happens in every company. The numbers reported by media are all way off. 4 FUD.</p>
<p>On the bright side, they just can’t resist talking about us.</p>
<p>We are still hiring. <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f91d.png" alt="🤝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1679951762906595330?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-admits-to-involuntary-terminations-within-binance-but-disagrees-with-reported-numbers/" rel="nofollow">CZ Admits to Involuntary Terminations Within Binance But Disagrees With Reported Numbers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Can Ripple (XRP) Reach $1 in 2023? 4 Factors to Consider According to ChatGPT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/can-ripple-xrp-reach-1-in-2023-4-factors-to-consider-according-to-chatgpt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ChatGPT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260889</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/xrp_mu_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Let's see what ChatGPT thinks of XRP reaching $1 this year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s XRP has undoubtedly been the hottest story throughout the past few weeks. T</p>
<p>he legal battle between the company and the US Securities and Exchange Commission culminated last week when US Judge Analisa Torres ruled that secondary sales of XRP didn&#8217;t constitute investment contracts.</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe title="BREAKING: XRP PRICE EXPLODES as RIPPLE WINS HUGE VICTORY AGAINST SEC | CRYPTO WIN!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pUTDJAy0Kxs" width="743" height="418" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div></p>
<p>Expectedly, XRP <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-price-explodes-16-as-judge-rules-in-favor-of-ripple-in-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">exploded</a> by over 70% and is seemingly on its way to $1. The question is, will it be able to achieve this massive feat in 2023?</p>
<p>We decided to ask none other than the world&#8217;s most popular  AI-based chatbot. Here are four factors that ChatGPT outlined for XRP on its course to reaching $1 in 2023.</p>
<h2>Market Demand</h2>
<p>According to ChatGPT, &#8220;increased demand for XRP can drive its price higher.&#8221; Duh&#8230; the chatbot, however, takes it a bit further, outlining that &#8220;factors such as increased adoption by financial institutions, partnerships, and use cases that demonstrate the value of Ripple&#8217;s technology may generate greater demand for XRP.&#8221;</p>
<p>It&#8217;s also worth noting that many investors have been holding back when it comes to buying XRP because of the uncertainty regarding its legal status in the face of the US regulators.</p>
<p>While the battle with the SEC might not yet be over, and it might just be headed for trial, the fact is that the recent ruling of Judge Analisa Torres did scatter some of the uncertainty and provided fresh hope for Ripple.</p>
<h2>Regulatory Developments</h2>
<p>Speaking of regulatory clarity, ChatGPT puts it as number two on the list.</p>
<blockquote><p>Regulatory clarity and positive developments regarding cryptocurrencies, particularly regarding Ripple&#8217;s ongoing legal issues with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, could positively impact its price. Resolving regulatory concerns and gaining widespread acceptance may boost investor confidence.</p></blockquote>
<p>It appears that we saw a major step toward the above last week.</p>
<h2>Market Sentiment</h2>
<p>Market sentiment is detrimental to the performance of individual cryptocurrencies, and XRP is no exception.</p>
<p>The AI says:</p>
<blockquote><p>The overall sentiment within the cryptocurrency market can heavily influence individual coin prices. Positive market sentiment, driven by general optimism, favorable news, or positive industry developments, could contrbiute to an in crease in Ripple&#8217;s price.</p></blockquote>
<p>ChatGPT also added that the performance of other cryptocurrencies, as well as &#8220;the global economic climate, can impact Ripple&#8217;s price.&#8221;</p>
<p>In essence, if the overall market is bullish, the price of XRP has a better chance of reaching $1 in 2023.</p>
<h2>Technology Enhancements</h2>
<p>Last but not least, the chatbot determined that improvements or developments in Ripple&#8217;s core technology, including increased transaction speed, scalability, or adding new features, could also have a positive impact on attracting more investors.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/can-ripple-xrp-reach-1-in-2023-4-factors-to-consider-according-to-chatgpt/" rel="nofollow">Can Ripple (XRP) Reach $1 in 2023? 4 Factors to Consider According to ChatGPT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC Is a Win for the Entire Crypto Space, Says Brad Garlinghouse</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-is-a-win-for-the-entire-crypto-space-says-brad-garlinghouse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260797</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/BradGarlinghouse-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/BradGarlinghouse-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Garlinghouse also asserted that US Congress should pay attention to the judge's ruling. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The landmark decision by Judge Torres in the legal battle between Ripple and the US SEC could positively impact the entire crypto industry, said the former&#8217;s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse.</p>
<p>He also hopes that the ruling will serve as a wake-up call to US Congress for the upcoming regulations.</p>
<h2>A Win for Everyone</h2>
<p>Nearly three years after the SEC sued Ripple for allegedly selling its native cryptocurrency (XRP) as unregistered security, Judge Analisa Torres, presiding over the case, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled</a> earlier this week that almost all sales do not, in fact, constitute securities transactions.</p>
<p>This was considered a major win for the blockchain project, and the hype sent XRP flying to a 19-month peak at $0.95.</p>
<p>However, Ripple&#8217;s CEO <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1680005238017908736" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">believes</a> this landmark ruling could benefit the entire industry, and especially other assets, which were recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-partial-win-in-xrp-case-sparks-alt-rally-as-pos-coins-post-impressive-gains/" data-wpel-link="internal">put in the same boat</a> by the securities regulator in its latest lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;For the SEC is really an overreach to suggest, as the Chair has said many times, that basically, everything in the crypto space is a security. Well, you now have a judge who is very clearly saying that is just not true and very clearly saying XRP is not a security on exchanges and all these different use cases, which I think helps the whole industry, for sure. This is a win for Ripple, it&#8217;s also a win for the entire crypto industry.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Wake-Up Call</h2>
<p>Ripple, along with many other US-based crypto companies, has urged the US government to provide more regulatory clarity for years, but to no avail so far. Garlinghouse raised hopes that Judge Torres&#8217; ruling in the case against his company will be a &#8220;wake-up call&#8221; for the decision-makers in Washington and Congress will finally act.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Hoping yesterday’s decision is the wake-up call that Congress needs. This ruling directly undercuts the SEC’s claims that nearly all tokens are inherently securities – likely to set a positive precedent for other digital tokens in the US. <a href="https://t.co/ZlSXbTigxK" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/ZlSXbTigxK</a></p>
<p>— Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1680005238017908736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The US has dropped the ball when it comes down to regulating the crypto industry, and many other nations have taken more decisive steps. At the same time, the US Securities and Exchange Commission has gone out of its way to target multiple crypto projects, companies, and exchanges, but whether the agency has the legal right to do so is still undetermined.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-victory-over-sec-is-a-win-for-the-entire-crypto-space-says-brad-garlinghouse/" rel="nofollow">Ripple&#8217;s Victory Over SEC Is a Win for the Entire Crypto Space, Says Brad Garlinghouse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unpopular Opinion: Is the SEC the Key Behind the Next Crypto Bull Market?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/unpopular-opinion-is-the-sec-the-key-behind-the-next-crypto-bull-market/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 11:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260855</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin_SEC_Bull.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitcoin_SEC_Bull.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This is why the US securities regulator could actually be the inadvertent propeller for the next crypto bull market.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market has recovered a lot of the losses sustained in 2022, with BTC rising by over 80% YTD and many altcoins performing even better. This led to questions and analysis within the community about whether the bear market is over and the industry is preparing for yet another bull cycle.</p>
<p>Moreover, the BTC halving is scheduled to take place in less than a year, which is typically regarded as a catalyst for upcoming price increases. However, the recent developments from the US Securities and Exchange Commission could suggest that the agency might also have a role in a potential bull market.</p>
<h2>The SEC Impact</h2>
<p>Being among the most powerful regulators within the world&#8217;s largest economy, the SEC&#8217;s actions frequently have a direct impact on a relatively small market like crypto. As such, when the Commission decided to go after Ripple in late 2020, as well as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-did-investors-react-to-the-sec-binance-coinbase-fiasco-glassnode-reports/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase and Binance</a>, a few months ago, it harmed most digital assets&#8217; prices almost immediately.</p>
<p>While this doesn&#8217;t sound all that surprising that the SEC&#8217;s lawsuits could hurt projects and companies, there&#8217;s also the opposite angle. We saw it earlier this week when Judge Analisa Torres, presiding over the agency&#8217;s case against Ripple, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled in favor</a> of the blockchain project, indicating that almost all XRP sales did not constitute security transactions, something that the SEC has been trying to prove for years.</p>
<p>The judge&#8217;s decision had an<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/220m-in-shorts-liquidated-as-ripple-xrp-explodes-to-19-month-high-following-victory-over-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal"> immediate and massive impact</a> not only on XRP&#8217;s price but many other altcoins, which the SEC alleged to be unregistered securities.</p>
<p>Consequently, it&#8217;s safe to assume that the entire market could further surge should the agency lose its ongoing battles with the likes of Coinbase and Binance &#8211; two of the industry&#8217;s most prominent players.</p>
<h2>Spot Bitcoin ETF</h2>
<p>The other aspect on which the SEC&#8217;s actions have a direct impact is whether the US will (ever) have a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund. The regulator has rejected countless applications in the past decade from companies such as Grayscale, Ark Invest, Fidelity, WisdomTree, VanEck, and many others.</p>
<p>With the agency&#8217;s growing attacks against the industry with its latest series of lawsuits, many believed that such a product will not see the light of day, at least not any time soon.</p>
<p>However, the tides changed in mid-June when BlackRock, the world&#8217;s largest asset manager and arguably the most influential financial giant, filed to release a spot Bitcoin ETF &#8211; a move <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">mimicked</a> by several other companies. BlackRock has a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" data-wpel-link="internal">mindblowing success rate</a> when it comes down to ETF applications, with the SEC of 575 to just 1.</p>
<p>Its filing for a spot BTC ETF had a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-taps-31k-on-blackrocks-etf-refiling-aptos-jumps-10-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">profound effect</a> on the cryptocurrency&#8217;s price, which soared past $30,000 for the first time in months after being stuck at around $26,000 &#8211; $27,000 for weeks.</p>
<p>The SEC first dismissed all recent applications, deeming them &#8220;inadequate,&#8221; which triggered immediate price declines as well. However, BlackRock, as well as the rest of the ETF seekers, amended the filings. Moreover, the agency recently <a href="https://www.sec.gov/rules/sro/nasdaq.htm" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">accepted</a> BlackRock&#8217;s application, thus commencing the official review process.</p>
<p>Although that could that a long time, a potential approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF in the States could also have a colossal and immediate effect on the entire market. After all, BTC did chart its current ATH of $69,000 amid the approval of the first futures BTC ETF in the US back in late 2021.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/unpopular-opinion-is-the-sec-the-key-behind-the-next-crypto-bull-market/" rel="nofollow">Unpopular Opinion: Is the SEC the Key Behind the Next Crypto Bull Market?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Introducing ChainGPT Pad, an AI-focused Launchpad Released by ChainGPT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/introducing-chaingpt-pad-an-ai-focused-launchpad-released-by-chaingpt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 09:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260846</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/11.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/11.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] ChainGPT Pad, the IDO platform that will be enabling the next generation of startups in the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry, has just been released https://pad.chaingpt.org. ChainGPT, the provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the digital economy, has just launched the ChainGPT Pad, a platform that connects promising early-stage startups [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>ChainGPT Pad, the IDO platform that will be enabling the next generation of startups in the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry, has just been released <a href="https://pad.chaingpt.org" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://pad.chaingpt.org</a>.</p>
<p>ChainGPT, the provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the digital economy, has just launched the ChainGPT Pad, a platform that connects promising early-stage startups with the $CGPT community and enables a new era of initial DEX offerings.</p>
<p>Now projects of all calibers will have an environment to supercharge their social presence, bootstrap their communities, and bring their products to market with greater impact.</p>
<h2>What is the ChainGPT Pad?</h2>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad is an IDO platform and incubator for Web3 projects looking to bring their ideas to life and jumpstart their token ecosystems. As a means to uphold the standards of ChainGPT, the Pad conducts rigorous quality assurance tests and due diligence processes to vet incoming projects and is highly selective with who they allow to list.</p>
<p>The launchpad is coupled with the ChainGPT incubation program that provides a network of expert mentors (founders, venture capitalists, and CEOs of other successful projects) that provide support to all projects that meet a certain qualification criteria.</p>
<h2>What are some of the Platform Features?</h2>
<p>The ChainGPT Pad has been geared up with all of the leading innovations that contribute to successful, healthy, and effective IDO launches. Striking the perfect balance between opportunity and security the ChainGPT Pad has been carefully designed by a team of professionals with experience working on some of the industry&#8217;s leading launchpads.</p>
<p><strong>Two Round Structure</strong></p>
<p>Every IDO is given two rounds for the audience to participate; starting at the guaranteed allocations for round 1 (where the upper tiers of the $CGPT community members are given exclusive access). In order to participate in the guaranteed allocation, qualifying members must register their interests (info on registration here). Moving into round 2, the FCFC (first-come-first-serve) invites members of all tiers and partners.</p>
<p><strong>Staking &amp; Point System</strong></p>
<p>Tithed to the $CGPT token ecosystem, the Chain GPT Pad has a simple and effective structure for establishing tiers. One $CGPT token is equal to one Point, point multipliers are based on the staking pool durations. An in-depth guide to the Staking and Point logic systems can be found here.</p>
<p><strong>Fair Tier System</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/22.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260849" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/22.jpg" alt="ChainGPT2" width="512" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/22.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/22-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/22-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>A model of prioritization and inclusion based on a balanced point module that leverages staking the $CGPT token to signal commitment. Composed of four distinct grade categories, Bronze, Silver, Gold, and Diamond, the tier system provides a structure for the discerning user that looks for maximal benefits. To explore the benefits of each tier and understand the detailed scope of inclusion, please refer to the official post here.</p>
<p><strong>Flexible Refund Policy</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/33.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260850" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/33.jpg" alt="ChainGPT3" width="512" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/33.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/33-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/33-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>As a means to provide the highest possible grade of protection to the participants of ChainGPT Pad’s IDOs, a refund policy has been implemented that allows users up to 14 days of post-round considerations to finalize their commitments and lock in their allocations. More information about the refund policy can be found <a href="https://www.chaingpt.org/blog/chaingpt-launch-pad-refund-policy" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p>For questions pertaining to how projects can register, how users can join, restrictions of countries, requirements to signal interest, and everything in between, ChainGPT has provided a dedicated F.A.Q. for the Pad, which can be accessed <a href="https://www.chaingpt.org/blog/chaingpt-launchpad-f-a-q-s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Upcoming IDOs on ChainGPT Pad</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/44.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260851" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/44.jpg" alt="ChainGPT4" width="512" height="310" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/44.jpg 512w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/44-300x182.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/44-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" /></a></p>
<p>Immediately upon launch, ChainGPT orchestrated a world-class lineup of three startups that have been going through the incubation program and have prepared to launch their IDOs in the months of July-August. With three projects already establishing their technical aptitude and social presence, here is who will be launching through the ChainGPT pad: DexCheck, TradeTomato, and Solidus AI Tech.</p>
<p><strong>What is DexCheck:</strong></p>
<p>DexCheck is an analytics platform augmenting the user experience with an AI-powered toolkit. From whale tracking and leaderboard monitoring to mirror trading and even arbitrage scanning, DexCheck is the future of on-chain intelligence.</p>
<p><strong>What is Tradetomato:</strong></p>
<p>Tradetomato is using artificial intelligence to fuel its decentralized trading platform and portfolio management ecosystem. Catering to a wide audience through modular trading algorithms, a social marketplace, unique wallet aggregators, and other elements from its stack of advanced tooling, Tradetomato is an end-to-end solution for the automation of on-chain finance.</p>
<p><strong>What is Solidus AI Tech:</strong></p>
<p>Providing AI infrastructure solutions for enterprises through its suite of SaaS, BaaS, AIaaS, AI marketplace, and HPC (high-performance computing), Solidus AI Tech is taking the Web3 industry by storm with its own 8,000-square-foot facility.</p>
<h2>What is the ChainGPT Incubation Program?</h2>
<p>Providing support, guidance, and accelerating excellence, the ChainGPT Incubation program is an extensive, in-depth, multi-month-long program of intense, close collaboration between ChainGPT and promising projects that are looking to launch into Web3.</p>
<p>Revealed in May of 2023, the incubation program aims to attract teams of innovators who have identified unique pain points of the digital economy; and equip them with the knowledge, tools, and connections to realize their visions. You can find a dedicated blog post here that provides an overview of the rationale behind the Incubation programs and an introduction to the mentorship network.</p>
<h2>About ChainGPT</h2>
<p>ChainGPT is the leading provider of AI-powered Infrastructure for the crypto, blockchain, and Web3 industry. From automated smart contract generation and auditing, to autonomous community management, advanced Web3 AI chatbot, AI-powered news aggregation, and NFT generation, ChainGPT is the most sophisticated, end-to-end AI solution on the market.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/introducing-chaingpt-pad-an-ai-focused-launchpad-released-by-chaingpt/" rel="nofollow">Introducing ChainGPT Pad, an AI-focused Launchpad Released by ChainGPT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekend Watch: Bitcoin (BTC) Defends $30K, Cardano (ADA) Drops 4% Daily</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-bitcoin-btc-defends-30k-cardano-ada-drops-4-daily/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260838</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_Cardano_mw.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bitcoin_Cardano_mw.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lido DAO has also dumped hard in the past 24 hours, losing nearly 7% of value. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin dipped toward $30,000 but managed to bounce off that level and stands a few hundred dollars above it now as well.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are also slightly in the red today, with ADA, SOL, MATIC, and DOT dropping the most from the larger caps.</p>
<h2>BTC Defends $30K</h2>
<p>The primary cryptocurrency experienced enhanced volatility at the end of the business week, alongside the rest of the market, following Ripple&#8217;s landmark victory against the SEC. Following the judge&#8217;s ruling that almost all XRP sales do not constitute security transactions, BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-add-70b-daily-as-xrp-sol-ada-xlm-soar-by-double-digits-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">jumped</a> from under $30,500 to a new 13-month peak of over $31,800.</p>
<p>However, it failed to keep this momentum going and retraced by several hundred dollars by Friday. Then came a more violent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-btc-rejected-at-31k-again-ripple-xrp-dumps-8-daily-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">rejection</a> that pushed it south to just under $30,000 for the third time that week.</p>
<p>The bulls stepped up once more and helped BTC reclaim that round-numbered milestone by Saturday. The weekend, as usual, is significantly less eventful, but bitcoin still dipped to $30,050 (on Bitstamp) earlier today.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, it managed to maintain that level and now sits around $300 above it. Its market cap and its dominance have remained the same as yesterday at $590 billion and 48.5%, respectively.</p>
<figure id="attachment_260839" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-260839" style="width: 1835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-260839" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1835" height="867" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15.png 1835w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15-1024x484.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15-768x363.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15-1536x726.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTCUSD-15-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1835px) 100vw, 1835px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-260839" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>ADA Leads the Way Down</h2>
<p>As expected, most altcoins soared as well following the SEC-Ripple ruling, especially XRP. It almost <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/220m-in-shorts-liquidated-as-ripple-xrp-explodes-to-19-month-high-following-victory-over-sec/" data-wpel-link="internal">doubled</a> in value in the hours and spiked to a 19-month high at $0.95. However, it also failed there and retraced quite a bit in the next few days to its current level of just over $0.7.</p>
<p>ETH spiked above $2,000 but now stands at $1,930 after a two-day decline as well. BNB is back under $250.</p>
<p>The past 24 hours brought more pain to ADA, which is down by more than 4%, SOL (-4%), DOGE (-2%), MATIC (-3%), and DOT (-3%).</p>
<p>Lido DAO&#8217;s native token has dumped the most, by over 6.5%. As a result, LDO now sits below $2.3.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has remained relatively still at around $1.210 trillion on CMC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_260840" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-260840" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-260840" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="841" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11-300x134.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11-1024x458.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11-768x344.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11-1536x687.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allcoins-11-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-260840" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-bitcoin-btc-defends-30k-cardano-ada-drops-4-daily/" rel="nofollow">Weekend Watch: Bitcoin (BTC) Defends $30K, Cardano (ADA) Drops 4% Daily</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man Charged With Stealing NFTs and Crypto by Spoofing OpenSea in 2021 </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/man-charged-with-stealing-nfts-and-crypto-by-spoofing-opensea-in-2021/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259932</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/OpenSea_Phishing.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/OpenSea_Phishing.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The defendant got his victim through an ad for the fake OpenSea website on a popular search engine.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US prosecutors have charged Soufiance Oulahya, presently in legal custody in Morocco, with stealing cryptocurrencies and NFTs worth $450,000 from a victim in Manhattan by creating a fake OpenSea marketplace in 2021.  </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A release from the United States Attorney’s Office Southern District of New York said the defendant illegally obtained the seed phrase of the victim by spoofing and used it to steal their collection of digital art. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Details of the Case</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Oulahya stole four NFTs from the victim’s OpenSea account. These were one each from Bored Ape Yacht Club, Meebit, Bored Ape Kennel Club, and Crypto Dad series. Besides, the defendant also stole cryptocurrencies from the Manhattan victim’s compromised wallet. The indictment said the victim had paid approximately $448,923 to obtain these digital assets.  </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">“As alleged, Soufiane Oulahyane used a common cybercrime technique to steal victim cryptocurrency and NFTs. ‘Spoofing’ is one of the oldest tricks in the criminal playbook. Oulahyane adapted this old tool for use in a new and developing arena – the crypto space,” Attorney Damian Williams said in the release.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to the indictment, prepared by the US Department of Justice (DoJ) and the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Oulahyane used paid advertisement on a popular search engine to entice the victim to the spoofed OpenSea website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The moment the victim entered the seed phrase on the spoofed website, it got transferred to an email id controlled by Oulahyane, who immediately accessed the former&#8217;s wallet and transferred the NFTs and cryptocurrencies to his wallet. The prosecutors have not named the victim or the search engine where Oulahyane put out the advertisement. </span></p>
<h2>Cyber Attacks on the Rise</h2>
<p>Spoofing is one of the many social engineering techniques where cybercriminals launch a malicious attack by enticing and convincing potential victims to click links, reveal passwords, download attachments, etc.</p>
<p>In April 2022, a BYAC owner was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-a-bayc-owner-was-tricked-into-swapping-his-bored-ape-nft-worth-570k-for-worthless-jpegs/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">cheated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> of BAYC #1584, MAYC #13168, and MAYC #13169 — worth $570K in a swapping deal on the Swap Kiwi platform. The scammer used weak verification and anti-spoofing features in its checkmarks to create fake BAYC NFTS. But they were nothing more than photoshopped Jpegs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In October 2022, the BNB Chain suffered a security breach and compromised cryptocurrencies worth millions of dollars. While freezing, recovering, and normalization were still going on, a fresh spoofing <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bnb-hack-inu-how-someone-stole-60-eth-following-the-bnb-chain-hack/" data-wpel-link="internal">attack</a> made the network suffer a loss of 60 ETH. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/man-charged-with-stealing-nfts-and-crypto-by-spoofing-opensea-in-2021/" rel="nofollow">Man Charged With Stealing NFTs and Crypto by Spoofing OpenSea in 2021 </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Wallet Users Hit by Suspicious Activity Caused by Low Entropy Mnemonic</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-wallet-users-hit-by-suspicious-activity-caused-by-low-entropy-mnemonic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 19:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260375</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto_wallet.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Crypto_wallet.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The affected wallets were reportedly created using an old and weak pseudorandom number generator (PRNG) algorithm. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A crypto wallet service &#8211; Klever &#8211; revealed that an already known exploit caused by low entropy mnemonic affected several users. The incident first came to light when users reported suspicious activity within their wallets earlier this week.</p>
<p>As per the company&#8217;s update, the algorithm called Random Generation, used by Bip39 implementation, was previously used by numerous cryptocurrency wallet providers. However, a flaw in the algorithm compromised the security and unpredictability of the generated keys, thereby making wallets susceptible to unauthorized access or malicious activities.</p>
<ul>
<li>Addressing the incident, Klever <a href="https://twitter.com/klever_io/status/1679267565434986501" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a> all affected wallets were imported into Klever Wallet K5.</li>
<li>These wallets had not been originally created using Klever Wallet K5 but were previously built using an outdated and ineffective pseudorandom number generator (PRNG) method as their entropy source.</li>
<li>According to the company, this algorithm was widely used in early versions of various crypto wallet providers, which relied on the Javascript platform.</li>
<li>It also highlighted that such a weak PRNG algorithm can significantly compromise the security and unpredictability of the generated keys, potentially making them more vulnerable to attacks or unauthorized access.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>On the Klever platform, the core codes responsible for entropy and mnemonic generation that utilize the PRNG algorithm are implemented with robust security measures and are native to the operating system.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Klever said the incident is similar to the one reported by the TrustWallet explorer extension earlier in April.</li>
<li>The company advised users currently possessing any old wallets that were created before Klever Wallet to promptly move to new ones created on Klever Wallet K5 or Klever Safe.</li>
<li>Initial investigation <a href="https://klever.org/en/blog/klever-alert-external-security-incident" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">suggested</a> that the suspicious activity was not exclusive to Klever and that users of multiple wallet providers are affected.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-wallet-users-hit-by-suspicious-activity-caused-by-low-entropy-mnemonic/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Wallet Users Hit by Suspicious Activity Caused by Low Entropy Mnemonic</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Why Robert Kiyosaki Sticks With Real Assets Like Bitcoin and Gold</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-robert-kiyosaki-sticks-with-real-assets-like-bitcoin-and-gold/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 17:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260795</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Robert_Kiyosaki.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The author of the Rich Dad, Poor Dad outlined the recent US crisis about the debt ceiling.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert Kiyosaki, the author of several best-seller books, continues to display his support for bitcoin, gold, and silver above all other assets.</p>
<p>In his latest tweet on the matter, he praised the aforementioned three assets while warning that the rich will get richer in the wake of the US government&#8217;s policies.</p>
<h2>Sticking With BTC</h2>
<p>The largest US stock market indexes registered some gains over the week, with the Dow jumping by over 3% and the S&amp;P 500 by just shy of that percentage. The renowned author, businessman, and entrepreneur commented on the matter, as he believes these increases are only because of the removal of the US debt ceiling.</p>
<p>Recall that the world&#8217;s largest economy faced a major crisis until June when President Biden <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/biden-signs-bill-lifting-us-debt-limit-2023-06-03/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">signed</a> a bill that suspended the country&#8217;s $31.4 trillion debt ceiling, thus avoiding the nation&#8217;s first-ever default.</p>
<p>Kiyosaki, though, who recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-explode-to-120k-in-2024-the-us-dollar-will-die-rober-kiyosaki/" data-wpel-link="internal">predicted</a> that BTC will tap $120,000 soon, believes the government&#8217;s decision will only benefit the rich and harm America because the US national debt will increase, just like the stock market. As such, he doubled down on his support for what he referred to as &#8220;real assets&#8221; &#8211; bitcoin, silver, and gold.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">WHY is stock market taking off? Because “Debt Ceiling” removed. Means national debt to rise with stock market. Rich get richer as America gets poorer. Sad. Sticking with real money &amp; real assets: Gold, Silver, Bitcoin.</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1679915869340848129?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>BTC Vs. Gold Vs. Silver YTD</h2>
<p>Although Kiyosaki keeps praising the two precious metals as well as BTC, it&#8217;s worth exploring their performance as of late, especially on a year-to-date basis.</p>
<p>Silver entered the new year at $23,75 per ounce and jumped to over $26 at one point. However, it since retraced to $22 before climbing back to $24.9 to close on Friday, which gives it a modest 4.84% YTD increase.</p>
<p>Gold&#8217;s performance has been rather identical as it started 2023 at $1,827 before it shot up to a yearly peak at $2,080 on May 4. However, it couldn&#8217;t maintain its run and fell back down to $1,955 as of Friday&#8217;s closing hours. As such, the yellow metal is up by 7% so far this year.</p>
<p>Bitcoin, on the other hand, started the year on a positive note after the devastating 2022 bear market. It quickly surged from its January 1 price of $16,700 to over $20,000 and just this week tapped a 13-month peak at $31,850.</p>
<p>Despite losing some ground and currently trading at $30,300, the cryptocurrency&#8217;s YTD gains stand at just over 80%, making it the best-performing asset so far this year.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-why-robert-kiyosaki-sticks-with-real-assets-like-bitcoin-and-gold/" rel="nofollow">This Is Why Robert Kiyosaki Sticks With Real Assets Like Bitcoin and Gold</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
