<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Fund Pledges $5 Million to Bitcoin Developers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorseys-fund-pledges-5-million-to-bitcoin-developers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 23:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255702</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/jackdorsey_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/jackdorsey_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Twitter’s co-founder is committing to another round of financial support for Bitcoin’s decentralized group of developers. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Billionaire Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey plans to allocate more capital to the Bitcoin ecosystem after pledging $5 million to the network’s core developers through his grantmaking organization Start Small.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The firm will distribute the funds to the Bitcoin development non-profit, Brink, over the next five years in $1 million annual installments. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to its </span><a href="https://brink.dev/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">website</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Brink exists to “support the Bitcoin developer community through funding, education, and mentoring.” </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">“We are 100% funded by donations from individuals and organizations who wish to support the open-source Bitcoin network and protocol,” the site states.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike many blockchain projects, Bitcoin lacks any committed founder, foundation, or company with a financial stake in the protocol’s success. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">As such, donations and charity are largely required to support the developers who maintain its codebase, who often </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-bitcoin-core-maintainer-steps-down-after-7-years/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">rotate</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Brink is very grateful for this extended pledge to support our Bitcoin developer funding efforts,” said Brink co-founder Mike Schmidt. “We can help make Bitcoin development a sustainable career for the talented developers that are building, securing, testing, and reviewing the Bitcoin Core codebase.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Last year, Jack Dorsey launched a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorsey-starts-a-new-fund-to-provide-legal-defense-to-bitcoin-developers/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">legal defense fund</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to defend Bitcoin developers to fight back against lawsuits from self-proclaimed Bitcoin founder Craig Wright. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">In 2021, he </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jay-z-and-twitters-jack-dorsey-set-up-500-btc-trust-for-bitcoin-developers-in-africa-and-india/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">teamed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with Jay-Z to launch a 500 BTC blind trust to assist Bitcoin development teams in Africa and India.  </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">On Thursday, Dorsey’s payment company Block </span><a href="https://bitkey.build/beta/?ref=nobsbitcoin.com" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">unveiled</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> the beta for its self-custody Bitcoin wallet Bitkey, which will feature special integrations with Coinbase and CashApp. </span></li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Bitcoin and nostr are the only two truly censorship resistant technologies at scale. <a href="https://t.co/0O1oihSRaz" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/0O1oihSRaz</a></p>
<p>— jack (@jack) <a href="https://twitter.com/jack/status/1669697334240837632?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/jack-dorseys-fund-pledges-5-million-to-bitcoin-developers/" rel="nofollow">Jack Dorsey&#8217;s Fund Pledges $5 Million to Bitcoin Developers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock&#8217;s ETF Success Rate With the SEC Is 575 to 1, What About its Bitcoin Application?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255776</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BlackRock_Bitcoin_ETF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BlackRock_Bitcoin_ETF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BlackRock's only unsuccessful ETF attempt dates back to almost a decade ago. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest asset manager made a massive step towards its involvement in the cryptocurrency industry this week by filing for a Bitcoin Spot ETF with the US Securities and Exchange Commission.</p>
<p>With so many previous applications for such a product by other companies failing before, the community wondered whether BlackRock&#8217;s attempt seems doomed from the get-go. However, the behemoth&#8217;s success rate with the SEC has been rather unmatched so far.</p>
<h2>History to Repeat But for Which Side?</h2>
<p>The COVID-19 pandemic, the subsequent central bank monetary policies, and BTC&#8217;s price surge in 2020 and 2021 changed the game in a way that very few were brave enough to envision prior to that moment. Numerous institutions started looking more seriously toward the cryptocurrency industry, and BTC in particular.</p>
<p>Back then, it was almost expected that a new institution or individual legacy investor will announce their bitcoin purchase on a weekly basis. BlackRock, despite being hesitant at first, started with minor <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/world-largest-asset-manager-blackrock-reveals-360k-bitcoin-gains-through-cme-futures/" data-wpel-link="internal">investments</a> through CME, as well as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-can-become-a-great-asset-class-says-blackrock-ceo/" data-wpel-link="internal">encouraging comments</a> from some of its executives.</p>
<p>While many institutions backed off during the 2022 bear market, especially in the wake of the loud collapses of the Terra ecosystem and FTX, BlackRock doubled down with a few more initiatives, including a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/investment-behemoth-blackrock-introduces-blockchain-etf-in-europe-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Blockchain ETF</a> in Europe.</p>
<p>In June 2023, though, the behemoth made its largest bet on the industry by <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> for a Bitcoin Spot ETF in the States alongside Coinbase, which will be the custodian for the funds.</p>
<p>The move had an immediate positive effect on BTC and its price, which jumped by over $2,000 in the first few days after the filing. The long-term consequences could be even more beneficial for the entire industry should that ETF be approved.</p>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1669691447996456963" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">According</a> to Eric Balchunas &#8211; Bloomberg&#8217;s senior ETF analyst &#8211; the chances are quite high, at least historically speaking. BlackRock has a mindblowing success rate when it comes down to its ETF applications with the SEC &#8211; 575 approved against just a single rejected one.</p>
<p>Moreover, the Commission <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/sec-etf-transparency-idUSL2N0SH1ZE20141022" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reportedly</a> denied that application for an actively managed ETF because it didn&#8217;t require the participants to disclose their holdings on a daily basis.</p>
<figure id="attachment_91560" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-91560" style="width: 827px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-91560" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min.jpg" alt="BlackRock Building. Source: FT" width="827" height="601" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min.jpg 827w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min-300x218.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min-768x558.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BlackRock-min-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 827px) 100vw, 827px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-91560" class="wp-caption-text">BlackRock Building. Source: FT</figcaption></figure>
<h2>What About BTC ETF in the States?</h2>
<p>While the SEC has greenlighted a few Bitcoin Futures ETFs, it has rejected countless Spot ETF applications. In fact, the never-ending denials pushed Grayscale, which tries to convert its flagship BTC product into an exchange-traded fund, to sue the securities regulator.</p>
<p>The agency&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ark-21shares-bitcoin-etf-rejected-by-the-sec-once-again/" data-wpel-link="internal">justification</a> has always been the same, claiming that the proposed ETFs fail to demonstrate how they will prevent market manipulation and fraud.</p>
<p>Additionally, the SEC has now gone after multiple crypto exchanges and tokens, alleging that most assets are unregistered securities. Nevertheless, even its skeptic Chair &#8211; Gary Gensler &#8211; has admitted in the past that BTC is a commodity.</p>
<p>In any case, BlackRock&#8217;s timing is quite intriguing, given the SEC&#8217;s overall negative stance toward the industry. Being one of the most influential financial players, though, it begs the question of whether BlackRock knows something we don&#8217;t that will help it continue with its spectacular success rate or if it will register its second L(oss).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrocks-etf-success-rate-with-the-sec-is-575-to-1-what-about-its-bitcoin-application/" rel="nofollow">BlackRock&#8217;s ETF Success Rate With the SEC Is 575 to 1, What About its Bitcoin Application?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>USDC Dethrones USDT as the Most Liquid Stablecoin on Centralized Exchanges: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-dethrones-usdt-as-the-most-liquid-stablecoin-on-centralized-exchanges-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255671</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/USDC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/USDC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[USDC has dethroned USDT as the most liquid stablecoin on centralized exchanges.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An analysis by crypto market data provider Kaiko revealed that USD Coin (USDC) is currently the most liquid stablecoin on centralized exchanges (CEXs), with approximately $38 million bids preventing a .1% price deviation of the asset.</p>
<p>USDC’s liquidity is followed by that of Tether (USDT), Binance USD (BUSD), True USD (TUSD), and Dai (DAI). The data <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1669674320921018368?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">compiled</a> by Kaiko includes the .1% bid-side depth across all markets that use USDC as a base asset.</p>
<h2>USDC &#8211; the Most Liquid on CEXs</h2>
<p>Kaiko <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1669674320921018368?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">noted</a> that while stablecoin issuers like Circle and Tether ensure their tokens maintain their parity, de-pegging could still occur on spot markets. This has made stablecoin spot markets essential for price discovery.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Theoretically, stablecoin issuers maintain their peg. However, de-pegging can still happen on spot markets, especially considering #USDT redemptions start at $100k. Stablecoin spot markets are thus extremely important for price discovery. This data aggregates .1% bid-side market depth across all markets that include the stablecoin as a base asset,” Kaiko <a href="https://twitter.com/KaikoData/status/1669674322632294401?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a>.</p></blockquote>
<p>The latest development is significant for USDC, as USDT has always been in the lead. At the start of the year, USDC and DAI had very little usage on CEXs. They were mostly traded within the decentralized finance (DeFi) ecosystem, <a href="https://blog.kaiko.com/trade-volume-soars-as-btc-crosses-28-4ea2d581f574" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Kaiko.</p>
<p>Toward the end of Q1 2023, a potential U.S. banking crisis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/why-did-usdc-depeg-circle-ceo-gives-the-inside-story/" data-wpel-link="internal">caused</a> USDC to lose its dollar parity and fall 13% to levels below $0.88. However, the stablecoin has stabilized and is striving to remain in the $1 price range, per data from CoinMarketCap.</p>
<h2>Coinbase Increases USDC Rewards to 4%</h2>
<p>USDC’s dominance on CEXs can be attributed to crypto exchange Coinbase raising the rewards with the asset to 4%. The trading platform <a href="https://twitter.com/coinbase/status/1669480042924228609?t=Xj8nlQ-0EVSeskDP6T6n_A&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> in a June 15 tweet that it is increasing its incentive for USDC holders from 2% to 4%, a move aimed at luring more users and boosting its position in the market.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, USDT, now the second most liquid stablecoin on centralized exchanges with approximately $26 million bids, traded below the $1 price range during the week. The asset was worth $0.99 at writing time, per data from CoinMarketCap, due to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-founder-repays-1-3m-usdt-of-aave-loan-to-reduce-liquidation-risk-data/" data-wpel-link="internal">ongoing</a> Curve-Aave loan saga.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-dethrones-usdt-as-the-most-liquid-stablecoin-on-centralized-exchanges-data/" rel="nofollow">USDC Dethrones USDT as the Most Liquid Stablecoin on Centralized Exchanges: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring CBDCs: Crucial Social Experiment or Digital Enslavement</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/exploring-cbdcs-crucial-social-experiment-or-digital-enslavement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255742</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/CBDC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/CBDC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The privacy factor of CBDCs will ultimately prove to be the biggest bone of contention. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Central Bank Digital Currencies (CBDCs) are slowly becoming a reality. The initial hype may have faded, but to crypto advocates&#8217; disdain, these digitized versions of legal tenders appear to be inevitable. So far, 100 countries are reported to be exploring the concept in some form or the other.</p>
<p>Despite not yet being rolled out full-fledged, CBDCs have managed to attract numerous narratives.</p>
<h2>Social Experiment?</h2>
<p>Project Rosalind &#8211; a central bank digital currency (CBDC) initiative with the Bank of England, in joint participation <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-16/bank-of-england-s-project-rosalind-finds-support-for-cbdc-digital-pound-britcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">run</a> by the BIS Innovation Hub London Centre &#8211; developed 33 API functionalities and successfully explored more than 30 retail CBDC use cases covering a broad range of domains for both individuals and businesses.</p>
<p>Ripple also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-partners-with-colombias-banco-de-la-republica-to-enhance-payment-system-with-blockchain/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">teamed up</a> with Colombia&#8217;s central bank, Banco de la República, to pilot CBDC.</p>
<p>The recent events demonstrate that CBDCs have emerged as a powerful indicator of blockchain technology&#8217;s increasing importance, maturing beyond its initial perception as a fleeting craze, according to KuCoin. A spokesperson for the crypto exchange told <em>CryptoPotato</em>,</p>
<blockquote><p>“With the rapid development of the Internet, e-commerce and online transactions have become more prevalent. Whether it&#8217;s CBDCs in various countries or blockchain-based cryptocurrencies, I think it&#8217;s all a great social experiment &#8211; bringing humanity into a new digital world.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>He further said these explorations deserve recognition and praise &#8220;as they will contribute to the progress of society and the building of a better world for mankind.”</p>
<p>One of the main factors that have driven conversion surrounding counterparty risk and the necessity to have a trusted service provider in an effectively regulated jurisdiction that is comprehensive, transparent, and logical is the abrupt collapse of Sam Bankman-Fried crypto empire &#8211; FTX.</p>
<p>To that extent, David Newns, Head of SIX Digital Exchange (SDX), believes CBDC initiatives across the world serve as empirical evidence that institutions prioritize fraud prevention, focusing on licensed service providers and currencies backed by the issuing central bank or government.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;After all, one of the main benefits of CBDCs against other cryptocurrencies is their higher level of safety, stability, and regulatory compliance. Using a high-quality, safe, and stable CBDC for the settlement of digital asset transactions would unleash the potential of the emerging digital assets ecosystem while reducing the overall risk profile of such transactions.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Digital Enslavement</h2>
<p>While many experts think CBDCs should be viewed as something positive for the blockchain community as they highlight government interest in the technology being used to mitigate global payment risk, many privacy advocates beg to differ. Their main argument is digital enslavement.</p>
<p>Speaking with <em>CryptoPotato</em> about the matter, Vineeth Bhuvanagiri, Managing Director of EMURGO Fintech, said if CBDCs are enacted properly, they have the potential to be a massive real-world use case for the technology.</p>
<p>However, it is important for the governments that are exploring this &#8220;need to fully understand what the technology is good for, and where it doesn’t add value, because I think a lot of the skepticism surrounding CBDCs is the intent to use them as a mechanism of capital control.&#8221; The exec went on to add,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This would go against the core ethos of blockchain. The core value proposition of blockchain technology is uncensorable financial freedom and if the intent of the government is to impose more control, blockchain technology is not the proper tool to do so.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>To address this aspect, The Treasury Department’s Assistant Secretary for Financial Institutions, Graham Steele, said minimizing illegal transactions while maintaining user privacy is a major feature of a retail CBDC. He spoke about including Privacy Enhancing Technologies to protect user anonymity.</p>
<p>Steele laid out both benefits as well as risks of a possible CBDC, highlighting that it could promote a competitive payment environment. But the pushback from Presidential candidates Robert F. Kennedy Jr and Ron DeSantis has been substantial. The duo maintains that such a payment system would let the government have too much control.</p>
<h2>Legal Challenges</h2>
<p>Still in its infancy, SDX&#8217;s Newns said the main legal challenges will come in the context of global adoption and will depend on the perspective of the harmonization of regulatory frameworks and cooperation amongst central banks across the world to support interoperability and cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>Moving forward, the legal debates surrounding CBDCs will ultimately boil down to the privacy conversations and what limitations the government wants to put on them, as per EMURGO&#8217;s Bhuvanagiri. He said if the government treats CBDCs like cash, then once they are issued, they are free to move anywhere in the world. Such a scenario is deemed ideal as it would take advantage of the suite of benefits that blockchain technology brings.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;People would have the ability to hold custody over their own assets and transact with them as they choose, leading to increased financial freedom at the cost of increased risk of those funds being used for nefarious purposes. How the government monitors the transactions or limits them would be the hot topic of debate.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/exploring-cbdcs-crucial-social-experiment-or-digital-enslavement/" rel="nofollow">Exploring CBDCs: Crucial Social Experiment or Digital Enslavement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Halving Effect on Asset&#8217;s Behavior Still Unclear: Coinbase</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-halving-effect-on-assets-behavior-still-unclear-coinbase/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 11:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255696</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/bitcoin-halving-nedir.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/bitcoin-halving-nedir.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Getting a clear picture of the crypto market's reaction to the halving would require disentangling the effects of several external factors, according to Coinbase. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report by America&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase revealed that the effect of Bitcoin halving events on the asset&#8217;s performance is still unclear as several exogenous factors play significant roles in the market&#8217;s behavior.</p>
<p>While the halving is viewed positively because it is believed to enhance BTC&#8217;s prospective scarcity and support its supply-demand dynamics, getting a clear picture of the market&#8217;s reaction would require disentangling the effects of U.S. dollar movements, interest rates, and global liquidity.</p>
<h2>Unclear Effect of BTC Halving</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s halving happens every four years or every 210,000 blocks. During the event, the block rewards for BTC mining are reduced by 50%. The first halving happened in 2012, and the next, the fourth, is expected to occur between April and May 2024. The upcoming one will reduce BTC&#8217;s block rewards from 6.25 BTC to 3.125 BTC per block.</p>
<p>David Duong, Head of Institutional Research at Coinbase, <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/institutional/research-insights/research/monthly-outlook/bitcoin-halvings-and-liquidity-problem-june-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">explained</a> in the report that with only three halving events, evidence of the market&#8217;s reaction is still limited, as they all took place alongside some significant monetary and fiscal developments.</p>
<p>In 2012, the Federal Reserve Board began to buy mortgage-backed securities and long-dated Treasuries for the third round of quantitative easing (QE3). During the second halving in 2016, Brexit stirred fiscal concerns in the E.U. and U.K., leading to increased BTC purchases. When the third halving <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-halving-aftermath-btc-transaction-fees-on-the-rise-as-miners-seek-higher-incentives/" data-wpel-link="internal">occurred</a> in 2020, central banks and governments responded to the COVID-19 pandemic &#8220;with unprecedented levels of stimulus,&#8221; which drove global liquidity higher.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Detrending bitcoin price action from the movements in such factors helps elucidate the situation somewhat. However, outside of the third halving, evidence that these halving events supported bitcoin price action is not entirely clear cut,&#8221; Duong said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Getting a Clear Picture</h2>
<p>Duong further emphasized that removing the influence of global liquidity on BTC&#8217;s price behavior would reveal a clear picture of the asset&#8217;s performance within different economic regimes.</p>
<p>As the next halving <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-will-be-bitcoins-price-during-the-next-halving-according-to-planbs-s2f-model/" data-wpel-link="internal">approaches</a>, Duong said it is important to note that the current surge in global liquidity will obscure the net effect on bitcoin&#8217;s price behavior, as the crypto market has been tracking global liquidity movements since the unfavorable market events that took place in May-June 2022.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We think it&#8217;s possible that the next bitcoin halving in 2Q24 could have a positive impact on the token&#8217;s performance. However, the limited supporting evidence makes this relationship still somewhat speculative, in our view,&#8221; the Coinbase research head added.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-halving-effect-on-assets-behavior-still-unclear-coinbase/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Halving Effect on Asset&#8217;s Behavior Still Unclear: Coinbase</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aptos (APT) Explodes 20% Weekly, Bitcoin (BTC) Stalls at $26.5K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-apt-explodes-20-weekly-bitcoin-btc-stalls-at-26-5k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255768</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Aptos-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Aptos-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aptos the among the best performers on both a weekly and daily scale in the top 100 crypto assets. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has finally calmed and remained relatively stagnant on a daily scale at around $26,500 after the massive volatility experienced during the business week.</p>
<p>Most altcoins are in a similar state with insignificant daily gains or declines, aside from APT, which is up by 6% today.</p>
<h2>BTC Stalls at $26.5K</h2>
<p>Last weekend was quite uneventful for the primary cryptocurrency, aside from a brief pump and dump at around $26,000. As such, the asset entered the working week in a calm manner, which continued for a few more days.</p>
<p>The US CPI numbers from Wednesday didn&#8217;t really change that, as BTC remained in a tight range at just over $26,000. The Fed&#8217;s decision to pause its interest rate hiking policy also didn&#8217;t affect bitcoin, but only at first.</p>
<p>The asset dumped hard just a few hours after the Fed&#8217;s announcement and plummeted to a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-drops-to-3-month-low-below-25000-where-to-next/" data-wpel-link="internal">three-month low</a> of under $24,800 on Friday. As the markets shed billions of dollars in days and fear returned, the bulls finally intervened and didn&#8217;t allow any further declines.</p>
<p>Perhaps fueled by BlackRock&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> for a Bitcoin Spot ETF, the cryptocurrency bounced off by a grand at first before it <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-markets-add-60b-in-2-days-as-btc-eth-jump-4-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">skyrocketed</a> to a weekly high at $26,800 on Saturday morning.</p>
<p>It has lost some traction since then but still trades at around $26,500. Its market cap stands at $515 billion, and its dominance over the alts is just above 48%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255770" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255770" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255770" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-17-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255770" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>APT Steals the Show</h2>
<p>The alternative coins went through similar volatility during the week but recovered most losses during yesterday&#8217;s run-up. Ethereum, for instance, had declined to just over $1,600, which was a four-month low. It pumped to $1,750 on Saturday but has slipped by 1% since then.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, which was harmed the most following the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against Binance, charted a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-coin-bnb-dumps-to-6-month-low-bitcoin-btc-fails-at-26k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">six-month low</a> at $222 a few days back but is close to $250 now.</p>
<p>Ripple and Polkadot are slightly in the green from the larger-cap alts, while Cardano, Dogecoin, Tron, Solana, Polygon, and Litecoin are with minor losses. Shiba Inu has pumped by over 4%.</p>
<p>Aptos has gained the most from the top 100. APT is up by 6% and trades above $7.</p>
<p>The total crypto market cap has remained relatively still since yesterday at $1.070 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_255771" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-255771" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-255771" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="852" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11-1024x464.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11-768x348.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11-1536x696.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-11-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-255771" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aptos-apt-explodes-20-weekly-bitcoin-btc-stalls-at-26-5k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Aptos (APT) Explodes 20% Weekly, Bitcoin (BTC) Stalls at $26.5K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform&#8217;s Do Kwon Claims He Didn&#8217;t Know His Passport Was Fake (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/terraforms-do-kwon-claims-he-didnt-know-his-password-was-fake-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 04:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255736</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Do_Kwon1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/Do_Kwon1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[He also asserted that the person he was caught with was innocent. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do Kwon, who was recently arrested in Montenegro after evading authorities for months, claimed that he had no idea the Costa Rican passport he was traveling with was fake.</p>
<p>He admitted that he received the passport from an agency in Singapore.</p>
<ul>
<li>Ever since the catastrophic collapse of the Terra ecosystem a year ago, Do Kwon, the person behind the protocol, has been blamed by many for his role. Although he claimed he was not trying to escape from the authorities, his location was unknown until recently when he was apprehended in the European country &#8211; Montenegro &#8211; while carrying a fake passport.</li>
<li>His time spent in a local jail has been somewhat controversial as his bail application for $400,000 was first granted before being denied and then <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/montenegrin-basic-court-reapproves-do-kwons-430k-bail-request/" data-wpel-link="internal">re-approved</a>.</li>
<li>Another <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwons-detention-in-montenegro-could-be-extended-by-another-6-months-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">report</a> from days ago asserted that Kwon&#8217;s custody could be extended by six months before the authorities decide on whether to extract him to the US or South Korea.</li>
<li>During a <a href="https://www.yna.co.kr/view/AKR20230616160000109" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">hearing</a> at the Podorica District Court in Montenegro&#8217;s capital on June 16, Kwon explained that he received the Costa Rican passport he was caught with through an agency in Singapore &#8220;recommended by a friend.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;I traveled all over the world with a Costa Rican passport. If I had suspected that it was a fake passport, I would not have traveled to many countries.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>He also tried getting a Granada passport but was rejected. However, when asked about the name of that agency, Kwon said he didn&#8217;t remember it, and he only knew it was Chinese.</li>
<li>According to the report, Kwon also had a Belgian passport when he was arrested. Prosecutor Harris Chabotich said the two passports had different names and different dates of birth, which made it clear that they &#8220;were created with bad intentions. Please punish it appropriately.&#8221;</li>
<li>Kwon also urged the judge to punish just him for being caught with a fake passport, as Terraform&#8217;s former Chief Financial Officer who was with him &#8211; Han Chang-joon &#8211; was innocent.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terraforms-do-kwon-claims-he-didnt-know-his-password-was-fake-report/" rel="nofollow">Terraform&#8217;s Do Kwon Claims He Didn&#8217;t Know His Passport Was Fake (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salesforce Ventures Lead $6M Seed Extension Investment in NFT Intelligence Firm Mnemonic</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/salesforce-ventures-lead-6m-seed-extension-investment-in-nft-intelligence-firm-mnemonic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 23:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255217</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bitcoin_Funding.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/Bitcoin_Funding.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Mnemonic offers NFT data, analytics and insights to help developers and enterprises create Web3 products via its APIs. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NFT data firm Mnemonic has secured a $6 million seed extension round led by Salesforce Ventures. Other participants of the fundraiser include Polygon Ventures, Orange DAO, FIN Capital, and FJ Labs.</p>
<p>The latest capital infusion will be deployed to accelerate the product roadmap of Mnemonic amid rising demand for deeper on-chain insights by expanding the suite of APIs.</p>
<ul>
<li>Mnemonic&#8217;s CEO and Co-founder, Andrii Yasinetsky, revealed that the capital funds the company&#8217;s &#8220;ambitious vision to unlock Web3&#8217;s full potential&#8221; to drive &#8220;exceptional experiences, personalized rewards, and sticky communities for enterprises of all sizes.&#8221;</li>
<li>As part of the deal, Salesforce plans to tap Mnemonic&#8217;s technology to power its Web3-related CRM products in a bid to assist customers in making better data-driven decisions on critical aspects such as partner selection, Web3 product pricing, and audience targeting for airdrop.</li>
<li>Following the development, Laura Rowson, a senior associate at Salesforce Ventures, was <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/06/14/salesforce-ventures-leads-6-million-round-for-web3-data-analytics-firm-mnemonic/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">quoted</a> saying,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Increasingly, we’ve seen a lot of interest from enterprises who want to understand and tap into Web3 to build trusted digital communities, and turn relevant data into actionable insights.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The funding follows Mnemonic&#8217;s announcement of Polygon and Optimism support. The NFT intelligence provider also added support for Coinbase&#8217;s Base testnet.</li>
<li>Mnemonic previously raised $4 million from Kenetic Capital, Monochrome Capital, Sound Ventures, and Tribe Capital, alongside angel investors Coinbase, IntoTheBlock, and People.ai., in a seed round announced in December 2021.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/salesforce-ventures-lead-6m-seed-extension-investment-in-nft-intelligence-firm-mnemonic/" rel="nofollow">Salesforce Ventures Lead $6M Seed Extension Investment in NFT Intelligence Firm Mnemonic</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CoinEx Settles With NYAG, Banned From Operating in New York</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinex-settles-with-nyag-banned-from-operating-in-new-york/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 20:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255516</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/NewYork.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/NewYork.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[CoinEx will pay fines and make refunds worth more than $1.7M, and will not be allowed to operate in New York nor accept new customers from the US.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">After being sued for operating illegally in February 2023, CoinEx, a Hong Kong-based cryptocurrency exchange, has reached an agreement with the office of the New York Attorney General, which includes a payment of over $1.7 million and a ban from offering its services in New York.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The recovered funds will go into penalties and refunds to New York investors.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">CoinEx to Refund Over $1 Million</h2>
<p dir="ltr">In a <a href="https://ag.ny.gov/press-release/2023/attorney-general-james-recovers-17-million-cryptocurrency-platform-operating" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">press release</a> from the New York Attorney General&#8217;s (NYAG) office CoinEx agreed to pay back more than $1.1 million to over 4,600 New York investors and further pay penalties worth $600,000 to the state of New York. The refund will happen over the next 90 days when users can be paid back in crypto directly from the exchange.</p>
<p>The agreement between CoinEx and the NYAG&#8217;s office will also prohibit the crypto firm from offering, selling, or buying securities and commodities in New York and ban the company from opening new accounts for customers in the U.S. The firm is also mandated to apply geoblocking to restrict access to the CoinEx platform for New York IP addresses.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Commenting on the latest development, NYAG Letitia James said:</p>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">“Today’s agreement should serve as a warning to crypto companies that there are hefty consequences for ignoring New York’s laws. My office will continue to crack down on crypto companies that brazenly disregard the law, mislead investors, and put New Yorkers at risk.”</p>
</blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">The office of the NYAG recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coin-cafe-to-pay-4-3-million-restitution-to-defrauded-investors-nyag/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> Coin Cafe to refund over $4 million to users on the grounds that the crypto firm defrauded investors with its &#8220;free&#8221; bitcoin wallet storage service, which was not free.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">NYAG Wants Tougher Crypto Regulations</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The development between CoinEx and the office of the NYAG settles a lawsuit brought by the latter against the firm in February 2023. As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ny-attorney-general-sues-coinex-for-selling-securities-without-a-license/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the New York regulator alleged that CoinEx falsely represented itself as a cryptocurrency exchange and sold tokens labeled as securities and commodities without proper registration.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Shortly after the lawsuit, CoinEx announced that it was withdrawing its services from the US market.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In May, Attorney General James proposed legislation called the Crypto Regulation, Protection, Transparency, and Oversight (CRPTO) Act that would see more stringent regulatory policies for the cryptocurrency industry. James believes the lack of robust crypto rules makes the industry prone to fraud and other criminal activities.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinex-settles-with-nyag-banned-from-operating-in-new-york/" rel="nofollow">CoinEx Settles With NYAG, Banned From Operating in New York</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Scam in Texas Led to Lawsuit Between a Bitcoin ATM Operator and a Local Sheriff: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scam-in-texas-led-to-lawsuit-between-a-bitcoin-atm-operator-and-a-local-sheriff-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255416</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Texas.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Texas.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Sheriff McNamara supposedly remained unfazed by the legal battle started by Bitcoin Depot, saying the company "can go to hell."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Lux Vending &#8211; doing business as Bitcoin Depot &#8211; has reportedly filed a lawsuit against the sheriff&#8217;s office of McLennan County, Texas, accusing it of unlawfully seizing $15,000 from a BTC automated teller machine (ATM).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities confiscated the amount to compensate an elderly victim who had become a victim of a cryptocurrency scam.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bitcoin Depot &#8216;Can Go to Hell&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to local </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.kwtx.com/2023/06/13/elderly-woman-scammed-into-converting-15k-into-bitcoin-sparks-legal-battle-between-crypto-kiosk-manager-mclennan-county-sheriffs-office/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the whole drama started at the end of April when an 82-year-old Crawford woman was browsing the Internet for a cooking recipe. While online, she received an email stating she had accidentally activated a &#8220;Ransomware&#8221; computer virus.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The woman contacted &#8220;customer support,&#8221; where she was redirected to a specially-designated &#8220;fraud investigator.&#8221; The latter claimed all her personal data had been compromised, adding that someone had written a $15,000 check to a mysterious construction firm using her details. The wrongdoer advised the victim to make a $15K cash withdrawal from her bank and deposit the money into a bitcoin ATM in Waco, Texas. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The woman said she followed the instructions and that the guy stayed on the phone with her the entire time. The woman said she deposited $15,000, $100 at a time,&#8221; the affidavit reads. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Shortly after, she reported the fraud to the sheriff&#8217;s office, which issued a search warrant on Bitcoin Depot, seized the funds, and returned them to the woman. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The $15,000 she put in the machine was still in the wallet that she had put it in. So we retrieved that $15,000 and brought it back to the office. We photographed it, put it into evidence, and ultimately got it back to the victim so she wouldn&#8217;t be further traumatized by these creeps,&#8221; Sheriff Parnell McNamara asserted. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He described the firm as &#8220;a bunch of vultures&#8221; that wanted to take money that rightfully belonged to the elderly person. The sheriff went even further, saying Bitcoin Depot &#8220;can go to hell.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">For its part, the company&#8217;s team maintained that the sheriff&#8217;s office had the right to confiscate the funds but not return them to the woman. The lawsuit also states that Bitcoin Depot was not the scammer, meaning they did not lure the victim into depositing the money. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A hearing has not yet been scheduled. Bitcoin Depot&#8217;s attorney &#8211; MacVane &#8211; said the entity &#8220;pledged to cooperate in any way possible&#8221; to help the investigators in the case. According to the sheriff, the fraudsters are located in another country.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Missouri Citizen Who Shot a BTC ATM</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The aforementioned case of the elderly Texas resident is not the only baffling one involving a Bitcoin ATM. The Missouri citizen Matthew Klinger recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/missouri-citizen-sentenced-to-5-years-of-probation-after-shooting-a-bitcoin-atm-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">received </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">five years of supervised probation after firing five rounds into such a machine. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His reason behind the act remained unclear, however, he said he destroyed the device &#8220;so that it could not take money from anyone else.&#8221; </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-scam-in-texas-led-to-lawsuit-between-a-bitcoin-atm-operator-and-a-local-sheriff-report/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Scam in Texas Led to Lawsuit Between a Bitcoin ATM Operator and a Local Sheriff: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
