<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:39:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>SEC Wins Lawsuit Filed Against Hydrogen Technology Corporation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wins-lawsuit-filed-against-hydrogen-technology-corporation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 23:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Security Tokens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247679</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/sec.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/sec.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This lawsuit was filed due to allegations of price manipulation schemes, which were proven to be substantial.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Last September, the SEC took the Hydrogen Technology Corporation and its CEO, Michael Ross Kane, to court for the alleged price manipulation of the firm&#8217;s proprietary token, HYDRO.</p>
<h2>Proven Manipulation Of Market Value</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-targets-the-hydrogen-related-entities-over-crypto-securities-market-manipulation/" data-wpel-link="internal">charges</a>, Kane used services offered by Moonwalkers Trading Ltd, a South African company, without a clear legitimate business purpose in order to conduct bogus trades using the HYDRO token.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We announced charges against The Hydrogen Technology Corporation, its former CEO, Michael Ross Kane, and CEO of Moonwalkers Trading Limited, Tyler Ostern, for unregistered offers, sales, and manipulation of crypto asset securities called “Hydro.”</p>
<p>— U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (@SECGov) <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov/status/1575897008476504066?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">September 30, 2022</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>This caused the price of HYDRO tokens to soar way above their actual worth, netting everyone involved about $1.5 million worth of illegitimate profits.</p>
<p>Tyler Ostern, the CEO of Moonwalkers Ltd., was also charged in the lawsuit. However, his role as a hired party was not as important to the SEC, and he quickly settled with them for $41,000.</p>
<p>On April 20th, the courts reached a final decision regarding the fate of Hydrogen Corp. and its CEO.</p>
<p>According to court <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/65383136/20/us-securities-and-exchange-commission-v-the-hydrogen-technology/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">documents</a>, Hydrogen Technology and Michael Kane have up to a year to pay over $2.6 million in fines and disgorgement fees, the latter being the legal term for restitution of unlawfully made profits.</p>
<p>Hydrogen Technology Corporation currently owes the SEC more than $1.5 million in disgorgement, prejudgement interest worth over $244k, and a civil penalty of over $1 million. Michael Ross Kane has also been ordered to pay a separate civil penalty of over $260k for his coordinating role in the scheme.</p>
<h2>Banned From Crypto-Related Business Ventures</h2>
<p>The judge presiding over the case also informed Kane that he and any business entities he may control are forbidden from participating in further offerings of crypto assets, effectively barring him from business deals that involve cryptocurrencies forever.</p>
<p>However, Kane is permitted to buy, sell and invest in cryptocurrencies from his personal account(s).</p>
<blockquote><p>Defendants Hydrogen and Kane each are permanently restrained and enjoined from participating, directly or indirectly, including, but not limited to, through any entity controlled by defendants, in any offering of crypto asset securities, provided, however, that such injunction shall not prevent Kane from purchasing or selling crypto asset securities for his own personal account.</p></blockquote>
<p>Furthermore, Kane has been ordered to burn – or remove from the market by other means – all HYDRO tokens in his personal accounts and the accounts his company controls.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wins-lawsuit-filed-against-hydrogen-technology-corporation/" rel="nofollow">SEC Wins Lawsuit Filed Against Hydrogen Technology Corporation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zimbabwe to Launch Gold-Backed Cryptocurrency</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/zimbabwe-to-launch-gold-backed-cryptocurrency/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 21:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zimbabwe]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247654</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Zimbabwe.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Zimbabwe.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The central bank of Zimbabwe has announced a new digital asset that will be backed by gold.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On April 23, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ) said the gold-backed digital asset will be used as legal tender in the African nation.</p>
<p>The move is part of an effort to stabilize the country’s economy and local currency’s continued depreciation against the U.S. dollar.</p>
<p>According to <a href="https://www.sundaymail.co.zw/rbz-introduces-gold-backed-digital-currency" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">reports</a> in local media, the move will allow those holding small amounts of Zimbabwean dollars to exchange their money for digital tokens. This will help them store value and hedge against currency volatility.</p>
<p>RBZ Governor Dr. John Mangudya said the current exchange rate volatility was caused by “expectations of increased foreign currency supply.”</p>
<p>This is due to the start of the tobacco season when farmers receive receiving payments in USD.</p>
<h2>Distancing From The Dollar</h2>
<p>It is not the first time Zimbabwe has turned to gold to address currency volatility issues. Last year, gold coins were introduced to stabilize the local currency. It should officially trade at around $Z1,000 to the dollar but often changes hands for as much as $Z1,750 on the streets.</p>
<p>Zimbabwe abandoned its currency in 2009, replacing it mainly with the US dollar. This followed a period of extreme <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-crypto-the-perfect-and-immediate-solution-to-zimbabwes-hyperinflation/" data-wpel-link="internal">hyperinflation</a> rendering the local money worthless. In 2019, it reintroduced the Zimbabwe dollar to revive the local economy, but volatility ensued again. It has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zimbabwe-refutes-plans-to-embrace-bitcoin-btc-as-legal-tender/" data-wpel-link="internal">not considered</a> adopting Bitcoin as a legal tender but has mulled a CBDC (central bank digital currency).</p>
<p>Details on the technical aspects of the blockchain of the new digital currency were not provided.</p>
<p>Gold is a relatively stable commodity when compared to currencies. Gold prices have been increasing this year as another impending U.S. banking crisis has resulted in a flight to store of value assets.</p>
<h2>Gold&#8217;s Performance YTD</h2>
<p>Since the beginning of the year, gold prices have increased by 8.25%. Furthermore, they hit an all-time high of $2,040 USD/oz on April 13, according to <a href="https://goldprice.org/gold-price-chart.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Gold Price</a>. However, the yellow metal has retreated since and is currently around $1,980/oz.</p>
<p>Comparatively, Bitcoin prices have surged this year, gaining around 70% since January 1.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/zimbabwe-to-launch-gold-backed-cryptocurrency/" rel="nofollow">Zimbabwe to Launch Gold-Backed Cryptocurrency</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase and Gemini Join Bid Race for Celsius Network’s Assets: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-and-gemini-join-bid-race-for-celsius-networks-assets-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 19:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247683</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Celsius_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[An unnamed source disclosed that the new bidders are most likely to win the auction as they are established crypto operators.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Leading cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase and Gemini are parts of the two consortiums set to bid for bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network&#8217;s assets at an auction scheduled for Tuesday, the 25th of April, 2023, according to a court filing and report from Fortune.</p>
<p class="p2">The court <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174904222380000000030.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">document</span></a> revealed that the auction would be held at the New York offices of Kirkland and Ellis, the law firm handling Celsius’ bankruptcy, from 2 pm EPT.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Coinbase and Gemini to Bid for Celsius’ Assets</b></h2>
<p class="p2">One consortium seeking to take over Celsius is Fahrenheit, a group backed by blockchain-based venture capital firm Arrington Capital and its founder Michael Arrington, alongside US Data Mining Group. Other backers include Proof Group Capital Management, former Algorand CEO Steven Kokinos, and investment banker Ravi Kaza.</p>
<p class="p2">In a Saturday tweet, Arrington mentioned Coinbase’s participation while <a href="https://twitter.com/arrington/status/1649877931966038021?t=DV21LeRe9dAnlDScZtWx3w&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">discussing</span></a> Fahrenheit’s involvement in the bidding process. The famous venture capitalist deleted the tweet for unknown reasons, and <span class="s1">Coinbase</span> failed to comment.</p>
<p class="p2">On the other hand, the second consortium is called Blockchain Recovery Investment Committee. It is backed by <span class="s1">Gemini Trust</span>, a company co-owned by the Winklevoss twins, fund manager Van Eck, Bitcoin mining firm Global X Digital, and Plutus Lending.</p>
<p class="p2">The two consortiums will participate in the auction alongside asset manager NovaWulf, the stalking horse bidder. A stalking horse bidder is the first bidder for a bankrupt company that sets the bar for other bidders ahead of an auction.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>New Bidders Most Likely to Win</b></h2>
<p class="p2">NovaWulf’s proposed plan will see Celsius general Earn creditors, who deposited less than $5,000 on the platform, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-customers-will-receive-up-to-72-5-of-their-crypto-back/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">receive</span></a> about 70% of their funds in liquid crypto assets. Users with Earn claims of more than $5,000 will receive liquid crypto assets and tokenized equity on the new Celsius platform wholly owned by the creditors.</p>
<p class="p2">People familiar with the matter <a href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/04/23/celsius-auction-set-for-tuesday-coinbase-and-gemini-join-bidding-for-bankrupt-firm/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">told</span></a> Fortune that one of the two consortiums is most likely to win the auction because they are backed by well-known crypto entities that could extract more value by operating instead of liquidating the bulk of Celsius’ assets, unlike NovaWulf.</p>
<p class="p2">The assets include holdings in several venture capital-backed startups, a loan book, and many crypto mining machines that could generate immediate returns for their new owner.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-and-gemini-join-bid-race-for-celsius-networks-assets-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase and Gemini Join Bid Race for Celsius Network’s Assets: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>South Korean Court Rules Luna Is Not a Security: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-court-rules-luna-is-not-a-security-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247714</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Terra_Korea.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Terra_Korea.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[A Korean Court has deemed LUNA not to be a security, making it the first time a court has been clear on the supposed properties of the token.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">A South Korean District Court has declared that LUNA, the native token of the Terra ecosystem, is not a security.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The court also dismissed prosecutors&#8217; requests to confiscate properties belonging to Singapore-based Terraform Labs co-founder Shin Hyun-Seong, and also arrest him along with other executives of the Singapore-based project.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">LUNA Is Not a Security Token</h2>
<p dir="ltr">The Seoul Southern District Court categorically stated that LUNA is not considered a security, according to a <a href="https://m.ilyo.co.kr/?ac=article_view&amp;entry_id=450928" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> by a local media outlet, ilyo on April 24. The court, in its ruling, said, &#8220;It is difficult to view LUNA Coin as a financial investment product regulated by the Capital Markets Act.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the latest ruling is notable in that other courts have not been clear on whether Luna is a securities token or not.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Also, the court rejected multiple requests from prosecutors to issue an arrest warrant for the Terraform Lab&#8217;s co-founder and other executives, as stated by Shin&#8217;s lawyer. In addition, the Southern District Court in Seoul dismissed the prosecution&#8217;s claims to confiscate Shin&#8217;s properties, stating that &#8220;it is difficult to see that the property subject to the claim is a property acquired by a crime or an asset derived from it.&#8221;</p>
<p dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-daniel-shin-interrogated-in-court-about-the-luna-ust-crash-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the Terraform Labs co-founder appeared for interrogation in the Seoul District Court regarding his involvement in the collapse of LUNA and algorithmic stablecoin UST, which resulted in losses worth $40 billion for users.</p>
<p dir="ltr">According to South Korean authorities, Shin allegedly violated the Capital Markets Act and the Electronic Financial Transactions Act, along with other offenses. However, the former executive claimed that he left Terraform Labs two years before the LUNA/UST collapse in 2022.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr">Do Kwon&#8217;s Fate Undecided</h2>
<p dir="ltr">While LUNA is not seen as a security, according to the South Korean District Court, regulators in the United States have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-sues-terraform-labs-and-do-kwon-for-crypto-fraud-involving-ust-and-luna/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued</a> Terraform Labs and co-founder Do Kwon for securities violation. As stated in a lawsuit by the Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), both parties offered and sold unregistered securities through crypto.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Do Kwon, on the other hand, who has been reportedly evading authorities, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-reportedly-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested</a> in Montenegro. There were also reports that Kwon <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwon-transferred-7-million-to-a-law-firm-shortly-before-the-terra-crash-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">transferred</a> approximately $7 million to a law firm before Terra&#8217;s crash.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korean-court-rules-luna-is-not-a-security-report/" rel="nofollow">South Korean Court Rules Luna Is Not a Security: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s the Critical Support for ETH Following a 14% Weekly Plunge (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-critical-support-for-eth-following-a-14-weekly-plunge-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247697</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After a prolonged period of consolidation without a clear direction, the cryptocurrency market has finally undergone a correction, with most coins decreasing in value. Ethereum was no exception, as its price has plunged by 14%, hitting a significant support zone. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Ethereum recently surpassed its prior major swing high [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After a prolonged period of consolidation without a clear direction, the cryptocurrency market has finally undergone a correction, with most coins decreasing in value. Ethereum was no exception, as its price has plunged by 14%, hitting a significant support zone.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum recently surpassed its prior major swing high at $2K due to its impulsive uptrend, providing a significant bullish sentiment by indicating a positive trend reversal. However, the price quickly formed a head-and-shoulder reversal pattern and was rejected, resulting in a 14% plummet.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the price has now arrived at a crucial support region comprising the 50-day moving average of $1800 and the 100-day moving average of $1705.</p>
<p>Therefore, the price action within the $1.7K-$1.8K range must be closely monitored since a breakout from this critical support zone will likely determine Ethereum&#8217;s near future direction. If the cryptocurrency falls below this vital area, its previous major swing low at $1.4K will serve as the primary support for the price in the mid-term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247702" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247702" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-247702 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2404231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-Daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247702" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>According to the 4-hour timeframe, Ethereum’s price rally came to an end when it attempted to break out of the channel&#8217;s upper trendline at $2.1K. As a result of an impulsive decline, Ethereum&#8217;s price has now reached the middle boundary of the channel, a significant support/resistance region, and is struggling to break it downward.</p>
<p>If the price falls below this level, it could trigger a downtrend toward the $1.7K mark. However, if the cryptocurrency finds support and reverses the downtrend, a rally toward the upper threshold will be the most probable scenario for Ethereum in the short term.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247703" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247703" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-247703 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_2404232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/ETH-4H-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247703" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-critical-support-for-eth-following-a-14-weekly-plunge-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s the Critical Support for ETH Following a 14% Weekly Plunge (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Days Left Until Litecoin&#8217;s Third Halving: What Do You Need to Know?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/100-days-left-until-litecoins-third-halving-what-do-you-need-to-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247718</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Litecoin_Halving.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Litecoin_Halving.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The third Litecoin halving event is close by; here are some important things you need to know.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Litecoin&#8217;s third halving is officially 100 days away, with the event expected to occur on August 2, 2023, at block 2,520,000. However, the date may change due to the network&#8217;s hash rate fluctuations.</p>
<p class="p2">Halving is a mechanism in which the rewards that crypto miners receive for validating transactions on a blockchain are cut in half. This is done to slow down the rate at which new units of a digital asset are created, thereby creating scarcity and potentially boosting the asset&#8217;s value, according to the principles of supply and demand.</p>
<p class="p2">By reducing the number of coins in circulation, halving is intended to counteract inflation and encourage a sustainable and stable growth trajectory for the cryptocurrency.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>The Effect of Halving on the Litecoin Network</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Litecoin&#8217;s halving occurs every four years after 840,000 blocks, with miners receiving 50% fewer coins than before. The blockchain has undergone two halving events since its launch in 2011, and miners are currently receiving 12.5 LTC as rewards.</p>
<p class="p2">Litecoin&#8217;s block mining rewards will be cut to 6.25 LTC with the upcoming halving event. At Litecoin&#8217;s genesis, miners received 50 LTC, but after the first halving on August 25, 2015, at block height 840,000, the reward was slashed to 25 LTC. On August 5, 2019, the second halving occurred at block height 1,680,000, and the reward was further reduced by half.</p>
<p class="p2">Currently, about 576 blocks are mined on the Litecoin network each day, creating 7,200 LTC. However, after the third halving, the daily LTC production will be reduced to 3,600. As a result, the supply rate of LTC will decrease, potentially triggering a surge in demand from investors. This could positively impact the overall value of the assets.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>How Will Litecoin&#8217;s Third Halving Affect LTC?</b></h2>
<p class="p2">There has been much speculation about the impact of the halving event on Litecoin&#8217;s price. While some members of the crypto community believe the asset&#8217;s value will increase following the event, others think the halving will have no impact as it has been already priced in.</p>
<p class="p2">The optimistic outlook regarding Litecoin&#8217;s halving event is rooted in the historical price trends of Bitcoin following its own halving, which also takes place every four years. Like Litecoin, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/51-attack-and-higher-transaction-fees-what-are-the-risks-post-bitcoin-halving-2020" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">Bitcoin&#8217;s halving </span></a>helps reduce the inflation rate and cuts miners&#8217; block rewards by 50%.</p>
<p class="p2">Given Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance, its halvings have historically caused significant disruptions in the market. Following Bitcoin&#8217;s halving in 2016 and 2020, the market experienced rallies that resulted in many crypto assets reaching new all-time highs in the years that followed.</p>
<p class="p2">However, on-chain data shows that Litecoin&#8217;s previous halving events have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-price-analysis-bears-take-control-despite-recent-litecoin-halving/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">failed</span></a> to produce the same effects. LTC prices in 2015 and 2019 were, for the most part, unresponsive to the network&#8217;s halving. Before the most recent halving, Litecoin&#8217;s value <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoin-price-analysis-2-days-before-halving-will-ltc-overcome-100/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">declined</span></a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/following-litecoins-halving-the-ltc-hash-rate-crashing-70-to-its-yearly-low/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">continued</span></a> after the event. Therefore, it is uncertain which direction Litecoin&#8217;s price will move after the halving.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/100-days-left-until-litecoins-third-halving-what-do-you-need-to-know/" rel="nofollow">100 Days Left Until Litecoin&#8217;s Third Halving: What Do You Need to Know?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert Kiyosaki Doubles Down on Bitcoin Support, Warns Gold Could Tumble to $1000</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/robert-kiyosaki-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-support-warns-gold-could-tumble-to-1000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gold]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247687</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BitcoinGold-min-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/BitcoinGold-min-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, the Rich Dad, Poor Dad author continues to bet on the precious metal.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By quoting Portfolio Shield&#8217;s inventor, Steven Van Metre, Robert Kiyosaki warned that gold prices could be heading toward a massive correction that could slash the value in half.</p>
<p>At the same time, he reaffirmed his stance that &#8220;cash is trash&#8221; and his belief in the yellow metal as well as bitcoin.</p>
<h2>Gold to Drop Hard?</h2>
<p>The precious metal has been long praised as the go-to safe haven investment tool, given its history and positive performance in times of economic uncertainty. The past few years have indeed been uncertain, to say the least, with a global pandemic breaking out, a war in Ukraine, and galloping worldwide inflation.</p>
<p>The bullion skyrocketed when during the early days of the COVID-19 pandemic and topped $2,000 to chart a new all-time high. Its performance since then, though, has been somewhat shaky. It dropped below $1,700 a few months down the line, tried its hand at $2,000 once again in 2022 before another correction brought it back down to $1,600 last November.</p>
<p>Nevertheless, the gold bugs propelled a new price surge that helped the asset near its ATH. It failed to breach it and currently sits under $2,000/oz. According to Van Metre&#8217;s latest <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vCS0H8_upnM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">analysis</a> on the SPDR Gold Shares, their price is poised to correct further as the RSI has declined recently, while the MACD shows a &#8220;negative cross.&#8221;</p>
<p>By outlining the triple top, which had less and less volume during each consecutive attempt, Van Metre concluded that gold could go down by up to $1,000, which would essentially cut its USD value in half.</p>
<h2>Kiyosaki on Gold and BTC</h2>
<p>Rich Dad, Poor Dad&#8217;s author has been a long-time advocate of the yellow metal, as well as silver, and bitcoin, since more recently. However, even he warned that Van Metre&#8217;s doomsday scenario for gold could play out as investors and markets are &#8220;tired of waiting&#8221; for the bullion to go higher.</p>
<p>Should gold indeed plummet by up to 50% from its current position, Kiyosaki said he would buy more as he is an investor, not a trader. At the same time, he reaffirmed his belief in BTC, for which he recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-dad-poor-dad-author-explains-why-he-loves-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">explains</a> why he loves it, while also dismissing keeping any cash as it is &#8220;trash.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">GOLD to CRASH. Steve Van Meter whom I respect predicts gold to crash to $1000. He states markets are tired of waiting for gold to go higher. If gold drops to $1000 I will buy more. I am an investor not a trader. To me, Gold, Silver, &amp;Bitcoin are real money. To me Cash is trash.</p>
<p>— Robert Kiyosaki (@theRealKiyosaki) <a href="https://twitter.com/theRealKiyosaki/status/1650275580561223680?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 23, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robert-kiyosaki-doubles-down-on-bitcoin-support-warns-gold-could-tumble-to-1000/" rel="nofollow">Robert Kiyosaki Doubles Down on Bitcoin Support, Warns Gold Could Tumble to $1000</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum ICO Participant Wakes Up to $4.42M in ETH After 8 Years</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-ico-participant-wakes-up-to-4-42m-in-eth-after-nearly-eight-years/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247671</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ETHWhales.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ETHWhales.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Ethereum ICO address now holds 2,363 ETH, valued at $4.37 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A wallet that participated in Ethereum&#8217;s initial coin offering (ICO) in 2016, which remained dormant since then, has finally woken up after seven years and seven months.</p>
<p class="p2">According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1650336537496920064?s=46&amp;t=yoL7WJcO9vZ3TjSE2j6FRQ" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">tweet</span></a> by on-chain analysis firm Lookonchain, the address transferred one ether (ETH) to a new address about 13 hours ago, marking its first transaction. The crypto community speculates that it is a test transaction. However, the ICO wallet has not made any other transactions since.</p>
<ul>
<li class="p2">At the time of the ICO, the wallet received 2,365 ETH, valued at around $733.51, as the token sale price was $0.311. However, the assets are worth roughly $4.36 million at the current market price of ETH, signaling nearly 600,000% ROI.</li>
<li class="p2">The ICO participant has joined the list of previously inactive addresses that have suddenly come to life and started transferring their assets. In December, two Ethereum addresses that had been dormant since October 2018 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/for-the-first-time-in-four-years-these-ethereum-whales-transfer-over-27m-worth-of-eth/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">made</span></a> significant transfers of 22,982 ETH for the first time.</li>
<li class="p2">Aside from Ethereum, there have also been reports of dormant Bitcoin (BTC) addresses becoming active again.</li>
<li class="p2">One striking example is a wallet that received 6,071 BTC in 2013 and recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dormant-btc-whale-wakes-up-sends-60-million-for-the-first-time-in-9-years/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">sent</span></a> 2,071 BTC to a new address. At the time of the initial transaction, the value of one BTC was $663, and the total worth of the wallet was over $4 million.</li>
<li class="p2">However, by April 2023, when it was reactivated, the value of the stash had skyrocketed to $176 million, and $60 million worth of assets were transferred out.</li>
<li class="p2">In March 2022, another Bitcoin address was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/satoshi-era-bitcoin-address-with-20-million-worth-of-btc-activated-after-11-years/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">activated</span></a> for the first time in 11 years. The address held 489 BTC worth merely $50 in 2010. By the activation date, the assets were worth over $20 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-ico-participant-wakes-up-to-4-42m-in-eth-after-nearly-eight-years/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum ICO Participant Wakes Up to $4.42M in ETH After 8 Years</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Struggles Above $27K, Injective (INJ) Nosedives 12% Daily: Market Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-struggles-above-27k-injective-inj-nosedives-12-daily-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 08:57:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247668</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BTC_MW_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/03/BTC_MW_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market took a beating in the past 24 hours, with Injective (INJ) plunging over 12% and BTC dropping toward $27K.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The weekend saw the broader correction within the cryptocurrency market continue, and most projects failed to stage any sort of recovery.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is declining toward $27K and, at the time of this writing, is trading slightly above it. The past 24 hours offered no relief to altcoins as well, with most of them continuing their downfall. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Price Struggling Around $27K</h2>
<p>The beginning of the new week has done little to help Bitcoin in its attempt to recover. In fact, the price continues declining, and it looks like $27K is the next level that the cryptocurrency will visit.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247669" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247669" style="width: 1182px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247669" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21.png" alt="BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21" width="1182" height="491" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21.png 1182w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21-300x125.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21-1024x425.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21-768x319.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/BTCUSDT_2023-04-24_11-38-21-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1182px) 100vw, 1182px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247669" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that BTC attempted to reclaim $28,000 but was abruptly stopped at around $27.8K, where the bears took complete control. Every hourly candle since then has been red.</p>
<p>This previous week saw BTC lose the most value in five months. It&#8217;s down roughly 10% compared to where it was trading seven days ago.</p>
<h2>Altcoins Continue Suffering</h2>
<p>The altcoin market also failed to produce any meaningful recovery during the past 24 hours. Ethereum is trending towards $1.8K, down 2.1% on the day, much like the majority of the major alts by means of total market capitalization.</p>
<p>As seen in the heatmap below, it&#8217;s not looking very pretty.</p>
<figure id="attachment_247674" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-247674" style="width: 1490px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-247674" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231.jpg" alt="crypto_heatmap_2404231" width="1490" height="785" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231.jpg 1490w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231-300x158.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231-1024x539.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231-768x405.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/crypto_heatmap_2404231-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1490px) 100vw, 1490px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-247674" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>Injective Protocol (INJ) is the worst performer from the past 24 hours, losing over 12% in the period. The cryptocurrency is now down over 30% in the past seven days alone. Trailing right behind is Arbitrum&#8217;s ARB, which also lost around 10% today.</p>
<p>On the other end of the spectrum, there&#8217;s Kaspa (KAS) and Bitget Token (BGB), both of which are up over 6% in the past 24 hours. Apart from them, though, it&#8217;s all red.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-struggles-above-27k-injective-inj-nosedives-12-daily-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Struggles Above $27K, Injective (INJ) Nosedives 12% Daily: Market Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>KuCoin&#8217;s Twitter Account Hack Led to Asset Losses Worth Over $22,000</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kucoins-twitter-account-hack-led-to-asset-losses-worth-over-22000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 06:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[KuCoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=247656</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/KuCoin_Hack.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/KuCoin_Hack.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[KuCoin became the latest victim of a Twitter hack, which resulted in the loss of assets worth over 22,000 USDT for its users.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">KuCoin&#8217;s Twitter account was briefly compromised, causing the platform&#8217;s users to lose over 22,000 USDT to hackers through fake activity.</p>
<p dir="ltr">The crypto exchange was able to recover its account and promised to reimburse affected users.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">KuCoin <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1650336619730436099?t=4qo2Gc_xjnhXkqLCOGYGqg&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">revealed</a> that hackers took over its Twitter account for 45 minutes to promote a fake activity on Monday, April 24. While the incident was brief, the company said that it identified 22 transactions in connection with the fraudulent activity, including ETH and BTC, with the value of the losses totaling 22,628 USDT.</li>
<li dir="ltr">The crypto exchange has since recovered its Twitter account but stressed that it was the only channel that was affected, implying that the website and other social media accounts were safe.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Following the incident, KuCoin promised to reimburse affected users while it is carrying out investigations and blocking suspicious addresses. The platform also said it would boost security to prevent a similar incident in the future.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">5/ In addition to Twitter&#8217;s existing 2FA, the KuCoin team will implement additional security measures to fortify the protection of our social media accounts. We are also conducting a thorough investigation of the incident with Twitter to prevent similar occurrences in the future.</p>
<p>— KUCOIN (@kucoincom) <a href="https://twitter.com/kucoincom/status/1650336628349763585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">April 24, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, the latest development shows how hackers continue to use prominent Twitter accounts to post fake giveaways to steal people&#8217;s money.</li>
<li dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/circle-executives-twitter-account-hacked-to-promote-fake-usdc-airdrop/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, hackers hijacked a Twitter account belonging to Circle&#8217;s Chief Strategy Officer Dante Disparte, to promote a fake USDC airdrop. Rogue actors also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-hackers-promote-fake-xrp-airdrop-on-news24-twitter-account/" data-wpel-link="internal">took over</a> News24&#8217;s Twitter handle to push an XRP airdrop. Robinhood was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhoods-twitter-hacked-used-to-promote-scam-token/" data-wpel-link="internal">another victim</a>, which saw its Twitter account being used to announce a token purportedly created by the platform.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Crypto holders are advised not to send tokens to anyone promising to multiply returns and should also carry out due diligence to avoid opening suspicious links trying to impersonate the real ones.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kucoins-twitter-account-hack-led-to-asset-losses-worth-over-22000/" rel="nofollow">KuCoin&#8217;s Twitter Account Hack Led to Asset Losses Worth Over $22,000</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
