<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:24:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Russia&#8217;s State Duma Approvea National CBDC Project</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/russias-state-duma-approvea-national-cbdc-project/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260143</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Russia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Russia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The legislation will become official once the Federal Council and the President of Russia give their approval.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Russia&#8217;s State Duma &#8211; the lower chamber of the local parliament &#8211; passed the digital ruble bill. The legislation defines rules surrounding the nation&#8217;s upcoming central bank digital currency, outlining the Bank of Russia as &#8220;the operator&#8221; of the project.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The institution will also establish a range of users of the digital ruble platform, adjust their type of transactions, </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">and set specific thresholds by the end of 2024.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Few More Steps Before Becoming Official</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">State Duma </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="http://duma.gov.ru/news/57491/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the adoption of a law on the release of a CBDC and on &#8220;the implementation of cashless payments using this form of national currency.&#8221; According to the bill, the project will consist of a &#8220;digital ruble platform,&#8221; &#8220;digital ruble platform rules,&#8221; &#8220;digital ruble platform participants,&#8221; &#8220;digital ruble platform users,&#8221; and &#8220;digital accounts (wallets).&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legislation (if officially accepted) will prohibit consumers from using the CBDC in deposits. &#8220;In the event of the bankruptcy of the debtor, digital rubles will be part of the bankruptcy estate,&#8221; the parliament&#8217;s lower chamber explained. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unsurprisingly, the central bank will play a main role in the project, overseeing the whole process and ensuring the platform works properly. The institution will also be responsible for the safety of the financial product and the correct accounting of information on such transactions.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legislation will now move to the upper chamber of the Russian parliament &#8211; the Federation Council. The last step is a signature from President Vladimir Putin. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CBDC Could be Used for International Payments</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The launch of a CBDC has been one of the central bank&#8217;s missions in the past few years. Elvira Nabiullina &#8211; Governor of the Bank of Russia &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/russia-plans-to-use-digital-ruble-for-international-settlements/" data-wpel-link="internal">described</a> </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the digital ruble as a top priority for the institution, raising hopes that it could be employed in international settlements.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The digital ruble is among the priority projects. We have fairly quickly created a prototype … now we are holding tests with banks, and next year, we will gradually have pilot transactions,&#8221; Nabiullina stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the wealthiest Russians &#8211; Vladimir Potanin &#8211; is also in favor of the digital ruble. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cbdc-can-replace-bitcoin-claims-russias-second-richest-man/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">views</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Bitcoin and the alternative coins as risky, &#8220;unreliable products&#8221; that the watchdogs can not monitor. As such, CBDCs (controlled by the authorities) could be the appropriate financial solution to stimulate Russia&#8217;s economy, he argued.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/russias-state-duma-approvea-national-cbdc-project/" rel="nofollow">Russia&#8217;s State Duma Approvea National CBDC Project</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ConsenSys Unveils zkEVM Rollup Network &#8216;Linea&#8217;</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-unveils-zkevm-rollup-network-linea/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ConsenSys]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259976</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Consensys.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Consensys.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The company warned users that advertisements of an existing or imminent Linea token sale or drop are scams and the network will instead use ETH as its native currency. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum layer-2 ecosystem is heating up with the space seeing yet another entry by ConsenSys, an already established player in the industry. ConsenSys, the firm behind MetaMask, announced the launch of its layer-2 network &#8211; Linea &#8211; to the main Ethereum blockchain this week. It will soon begin onboarding partners as well.</p>
<p>The new layer-2 scaling solution is a zkEVM rollup network leveraging zero-knowledge proofs while making it an Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) equivalent.</p>
<h2>ConsenSys&#8217;s zkEVM Rollup Network &#8211; Linea</h2>
<p>ConsenSys is the latest company to ride the growing trend of zkEVM with its new offering Linea that has already witnessed a successful testnet phase with 5.5 million unique wallets conducting more than 46 million transactions. According to the company, Linea has emerged as one of the largest and fastest-growing projects in Goerli.</p>
<p>Before hitting the mainnet at ETHCC, Linea will begin onboarding its launch partners starting this week.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Linea combines the power of zero-knowledge proofs with full Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) equivalence, allowing builders to create scalable decentralized applications (dapps) or migrate existing ones without the hassle of changing code or rewriting smart contracts.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>As per ConsenSys&#8217;s announcement, the alpha release provides faster throughput while lowering the transaction fees up to 15x lower than Ethereum layer-1. The firm also said that the release will allow deeper integrations with its crypto wallet MetaMask.</p>
<p>Linea will be made available to users next week once partners have had an opportunity to onboard their dApps and infrastructure. The company also confirmed that the network uses Ether as its native currency, which is bridged directly from the Ethereum Mainnet. It urged users to remain cautious about fraudulent advertisements of an existing or imminent Linea token sale or drop.</p>
<h2>zkEVM Popularity</h2>
<p>A zkEVM is an EMV-compatible rollup that is secured by zero-knowledge proofs. By pooling in ZKPs with EVM compatibility, zkEVMs offer the security and privacy-preserving features of zk-Rollups while simultaneously enhancing Ethereum interoperability by protecting EVM compatibility. Such a system helps zkEVMs to be interoperable with smart contracts and decentralized applications (dApps) used on Ethereum.</p>
<p>The first zkEVM to be publicly available was zkSync&#8217;s solution called &#8216;zkSync Era,&#8217; which went live to much fanfare in March. Days later, Polygon announced the final mainnet for its zkEVM product and added subsequent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-announces-polygon-bridge-for-its-zero-knowledge-rollup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">optimizations</a> a month later.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-unveils-zkevm-rollup-network-linea/" rel="nofollow">ConsenSys Unveils zkEVM Rollup Network &#8216;Linea&#8217;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former FTX Exec Under Investigation for Possible Violations of Campaign Finance Law (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-exec-under-investigation-for-possible-violations-of-campaign-finance-law-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 22:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260069</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_legal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_legal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This is Salame's second dispute with the American authorities after the FBI raided his home in April.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">US prosecutors have reportedly targeted Ryan Salame &#8211; ex-CEO of FTX&#8217;s Bahamian subsidiary &#8211; over a possible breach of the law when donating funds to his then-girlfriend&#8217;s political campaign in 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Previous sources have informed that Michelle Bond (the woman in question) has received at least $400,000 in consulting fees from FTX Digital Markets &#8211; the entity that Salame ran. According to The New York Times, the American personally donated $1.5 million to the GMI super PAC (a newly-formed committee that supported crypto-friendly candidates), which in turn used some of the funds to popularize Bond&#8217;s campaign.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Salame Takes Another Punch</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/former-ftx-executive-linked-to-campaign-finance-probe-of-new-york-gop-race-c2b50252" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">reported</a> by The Wall Street Journal, Federal prosecutors in Manhattan have launched an investigation against Salame to examine the donations that he handed to his then-girlfriend Michelle Bond. She ran for the Republican nomination for a congressional seat in New York last year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX executives, including the former CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, have made generous donations to politicians from both the Democratic and Republican parties prior to the collapse of the exchange.<br />
</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the probe, the pair was not accused of wrongdoing. Their lawyers and the US Attorney&#8217;s office in Manhattan have not yet spoken on the matter. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FBI has also put Salame under its radar, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-boss-ryan-salames-house-raided-by-the-fbi-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">raiding</a> his house in Potomac, Maryland, at the end of April. The exact reason behind the search remained unclear. However, some speculations emerged claiming it could be connected to the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX crash </a>that shook the entire crypto industry in November 2022. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Salame took a central role in the scandal after he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-15/ftx-executive-ryan-salame-tipped-off-bahamian-regulators-to-possible-fraud?in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">told</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Bahamian regulators that the once-prominent platform might have misappropriated billions of dollars in customers&#8217; funds and transferred them to Alameda Research.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Investigation Has no Relation to SBF</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The coverage further informed that the most recent probe against Salame is being treated separately from the case against SBF. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous regulators and authorities have accused the former CEO of conducting several crimes, such as wire fraud and conspiracy to commit money laundering. However, he has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-pleads-not-guilty-trial-date-set/" data-wpel-link="internal">pleaded</a> not guilty and refused to be blamed as the main culprit behind the meltdown of the company he founded.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">SBF spent a brief time in a Bahamian jail before being deported to the USA. The American magistrates <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal">allowed</a> him to live with his parents until the trial on October 2 under a whopping $250 million bond. He could receive a 115-year prison sentence if found guilty.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-ftx-exec-under-investigation-for-possible-violations-of-campaign-finance-law-report/" rel="nofollow">Former FTX Exec Under Investigation for Possible Violations of Campaign Finance Law (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>LBRY Token Crashes 14% After Company Firm Behind Project Announces Shutdown</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lbry-token-crashes-14-after-company-firm-behind-project-announces-shutdown/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 21:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260266</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Lawsuit-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LBRY wasn’t forced to shutter operations, but has been compelled to pay a fine and stop issuing unregistered securities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LBRY Inc – the firm responsible for developing the LBRY protocol – has announced it will close operations after receiving a final judgment in its case with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Since the announcement, LBRY token (LBC) has collapsed 14% in value.</p>
<ul>
<li>A federal judge sided with the SEC in <a href="https://www.dropbox.com/scl/fi/tn88lu25f8xg96algkj60/SEC-v-LBRY-Final-Judgment.pdf?dl=0&amp;rlkey=la5au9jor0ev4ae0qcq9uwao2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">ruling</a> that LBRY violated Section 5 of the Securities Act of 1933 in its issuance of LBC.</li>
<li>As such, it has permanently restrained and enjoined from further issuance of any “security” unless registered with the commission in advance.</li>
<li>LBRY is also required to pay a $111,614 fee for its violation within the next thirty days. This is a massive <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-knocks-lbrys-22-million-fine-down-to-111k/" data-wpel-link="internal">reduction</a> from the SEC’s original fee request, which was $22 million</li>
<li>Over Twitter, LBRY confirmed that it will be completely winding down its operations, with the community free to decide how to make use of its LBC token.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The final judgement in SEC vs LBRY is out.</p>
<p>In accordance with the court&#39;s order and our promises, we expect to spend the next several months winding LBRY Inc. down entirely.</p>
<p>As to what happens to LBRY from here, well, that&#39;s up to you. <a href="https://t.co/cU8O3nATT6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/cU8O3nATT6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; LBRY <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f680.png" alt="🚀" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@LBRYcom) <a href="https://twitter.com/LBRYcom/status/1678866789407551489?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<ul>
<li>LBRY is a decentralized content platform known for its video-sharing platform, Odyssey. The platform leveraged LBC as the internal currency with which creators could charge viewers for streaming their content, or earn tips.</li>
<li>Throughout the case, the SEC noted that one of LBRY’s explicitly stated uses for LBC was to “financially support its operations,” which is one of the hallmarks of a security under the Howey Test.</li>
<li>Ultimately, Judge Paul Barbadoro <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-wins-case-against-lbry-what-does-it-mean-for-ripple/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled</a> in November that “no reasonable trier of fact could reject the SEC’s contention that LBRY offered LBC as a security.”</li>
<li>The case is thought to set a dangerous precedent for other crypto creators, who fear their token issuance models may have been illegal in the SEC’s view.</li>
<li>In June, the agency alleged that multiple top cryptos were securities in a lawsuit against Coinbase, including Cardano (ADA), Solana (SOL) and Polygon (MATIC).</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lbry-token-crashes-14-after-company-firm-behind-project-announces-shutdown/" rel="nofollow">LBRY Token Crashes 14% After Company Firm Behind Project Announces Shutdown</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dump Incoming? US Government Moves Another 9,000 BTC From Silk Road</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dump-incoming-us-government-moves-another-9000-btc-from-silk-road/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260261</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/UnitedStates.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Department of Justice (DOJ) appears to be continuing its 50,000 BTC sale that began earlier this year. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blockchain data shows that the Department of Justice (DOJ) is moving another massive batch of seized Bitcoin (BTC) connected to Silk Road – the defunct darknet marketplace launched by Ross Ulbricht in 2011.</p>
<p>The government has already confirmed plans to sell its Silk Road-related BTC throughout the year, meaning the latest transfers could signal its intention to soon dump more.</p>
<h2>Silk Road Sale: Round 2</h2>
<p>As <a href="https://twitter.com/WuBlockchain/status/1679132502886162436" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweeted</a> by Wu Blockchain on Wednesday, two Silk Road BTC addresses suspected to have been seized by the Justice Department moved over 9,825 BTC in aggregate in the past 24 hours. The <a href="https://www.oklink.com/btc/address/bc1qmxjefnuy06v345v6vhwpwt05dztztmx4g3y7wp?tab=commonTx" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">first</a> moved ~825 BTC, while the <a href="https://www.oklink.com/btc/address/bc1qe7nk2nlnjewghgw4sgm0r89zkjzsurda7z4rdg" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">second</a> moved ~9000 BTC.</p>
<p>Previous movements from these wallets were seen in March when the second wallet <a href="https://www.oklink.com/btc/tx/d43068e021701606724af16aeb8197a3530021d45a16d5b830b465da6c5ce9e6" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">sent</a> over 9,800 BTC to Coinbase, where it was later sold. Both addresses now hold 0 BTC, with the remaining ~30,174 BTC from Silk Road sitting at a <a href="https://www.oklink.com/btc/address/bc1qf2yvj48mzkj7uf8lc2a9sa7w983qe256l5c8fs" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">third address</a>, from which they still haven’t moved.</p>
<p>The 9,825 BTC moved on Wednesday are currently worth $300 million – up roughly 50% in value from September 7, when the department initially announced that it had <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-doj-seized-over-50000-btc-related-to-silk-road/" data-wpel-link="internal">seized</a> the 51,351 BTC. At the time, the DOJ indicted James Zhong for hacking Silk Road back in 2012 and creating nine accounts to hide his identity and trigger the release of all Bitcoin from the marketplace</p>
<p>The government later <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brandonkochkodin/2023/03/31/us-government-sells-bitcoin-seized-from-silk-road-case-netting-over-215-million/?sh=48f164492888" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> that it sold 9,861 BTC on March 14, 2023, for an average price of $21,877. Many in the crypto community mocked the government following the reveal given that Bitcoin’s price had already surged roughly 25% since the actual sale and that it had paid $215,000 in transaction fees alone.</p>
<p>The DOJ’s only financial seizure larger than Silk Road relates to another crypto hack. Early last year, authorities claimed 119,754 BTC related to the 2016 Bitfinex hack, worth $3.6 billion at the time.</p>
<h2>Total Bitcoin Held By USG</h2>
<p>In total, data from <a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/metrics?a=BTC&amp;c=native&amp;m=distribution.BalanceUsGovernment&amp;resolution=24h" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Glassnode</a> shows that the government held 204,013 BTC prior to its most recent wallet transfers. This makes it the largest known individual holder of Bitcoin (excluding exchanges and custodians that hold BTC on behalf of thousands of customers).</p>
<p>It’s unclear if an upcoming BTC sale with heavily impact the market. Data from CoinGecko shows that Bitcoin’s daily trading volume is over $12.7 billion, meaning the market may be able to absorb the sale without significant trouble.</p>
<p>It’s also unclear if the coins will be sold all at once or in smaller batches over the course of a few weeks, the latter of which would have an even smaller impact. In a Glassnode <a href="https://insights.glassnode.com/the-week-onchain-week-28-2023/?utm_campaign=woc_28__2023&amp;utm_medium=woc_newsletter&amp;utm_source=email" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> this week, the firm explained that Bitcoin’s price had formed a “firm foundation” under $30,000 based on the number of coins traded in that price region.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dump-incoming-us-government-moves-another-9000-btc-from-silk-road/" rel="nofollow">Dump Incoming? US Government Moves Another 9,000 BTC From Silk Road</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Attracts Strong Community Interest</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-attracts-strong-community-interest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260246</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alex_gamefi_banner_16891634719Ivvd8V7pI.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Alex_gamefi_banner_16891634719Ivvd8V7pI.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Frankfurt, Germany, July 12th, 2023] The presale for memecoin Alex The Doge (ALEX) is currently live, and has seen strong demand from the crypto community already. The presale offers a chance to participate in the ALEX ecosystem from the outset and to stake a claim in the MiracleVerse. Built on Polygon&#8217;s blockchain, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Frankfurt, Germany, July 12th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>The presale for memecoin <a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Alex The Doge</a> (ALEX) is currently live, and has seen strong demand from the crypto community already. The presale offers a chance to participate in the ALEX ecosystem from the outset and to stake a claim in the MiracleVerse.</p>
<p>Built on Polygon&#8217;s blockchain, which provides speed, scalability, and security, Alex The Doge integrates DeFi i to allow value to transfer throughout the ecosystem and provide liquidity for trading and gaming.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency has a unique use case that is focused on the gaming industry. The Alex The Doge (ALEX) team has created a gaming world called the MiracleVerse, where gamers can participate in challenges and earn tokens with monetary value outside the ecosystem. The platform will unite communities via cross-chain compatibility and integrate popular gaming services into the platform to improve interoperability in gaming.</p>
<p>The ALEX team is focused on improving the user experience compared to other P2E projects and meme tokens, with the focal point being the smooth transition between gaming credits and digital assets to be used within the everyday world.</p>
<p>The presale offers 349,190,374 ALEX tokens for purchase with a starting price of 0.0084 USD. Following the presale, ALEX will be available on the Uniswap v3 platform for trading. Community members will need to include a compatible Polygon receiving address to ensure tokens are airdropped to their account on launch.</p>
<p>The ALEX team is striving to optimize user experience and create a fluid transition between gaming, social, and trading. Users will be able to join social trading groups on the ALEX platform, bridging the gap between diverse trading communities and introducing ALEX to multiple crypto and gaming groups.</p>
<p>ALEX&#8217;s unique features, including cross-chain compatibility and the MiracleVerse, set it apart from other P2E gaming platforms. The community is excited about the opportunity to join the ALEX presale and participate in the future of MiracleVerse.</p>
<p><strong>About ALEX</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ALEX</a> is the newest Doge on the block, Welcome to the future of Play-To-Earn Gaming and Social-Fi! Alex The Doge is a community project with a focal point on the end user experience, ALEX will revolutionize P2E gaming and expand our ecosystem to alternative gaming communities using cross-chain compatibility and creating a fluid transition between gaming credits and digital assets.</p>
<p><strong>For more information about Alex The Doge (ALEX) presale: </strong><a href="https://alexthedoge.live/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Website</strong></a><strong> | </strong><a href="https://t.me/alexthedoge" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Telegram</strong></a><strong> |</strong> <a href="https://twitter.com/AlexTheDoge_p2e" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><strong>Twitter</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/alex-the-doge-alex-presale-attracts-strong-community-interest/" rel="nofollow">Alex The Doge (ALEX) Presale Attracts Strong Community Interest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Struct Finance Transforms DeFi Landscape on Avalanche With the Launch of Tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Vaults</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260226</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC_USDC_1689175623JHb650OWHh.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/BTC_USDC_1689175623JHb650OWHh.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[Press Release &#8211; Tortola, British Virgin Islands, July 12th, 2023] In its ongoing journey to reshape the crypto investing landscape, Struct Finance, a DeFi platform that enables investors to engage with tailored interest rate products linked to digital assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of the BTC.B-USDC Vaults. The tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Interest Rate Product [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[Press Release &#8211; Tortola, British Virgin Islands, July 12th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>In its ongoing journey to reshape the crypto investing landscape, Struct Finance, a DeFi platform that enables investors to engage with tailored interest rate products linked to digital assets, is thrilled to announce the launch of the BTC.B-USDC Vaults.</p>
<p>The tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Interest Rate Product was made possible by effectively leveraging Avalanche’s BTC.B (Bridged Bitcoin) for DeFi applications. The new vault beautifully complements Struct Finance’s Genesis USDC Vaults, heralding an exciting era in DeFi yield opportunities. Struct Finance built the new vault on top of GMX&#8217;s Liquidity Provider Token (GLP) to generate predictable yields for BTC in the form of fixed returns, and USDC in the form of variable returns, while still leveraging a secure asset and minimizing volatility and exposure to other risks.</p>
<p>“Our BTC.B-USDC Vaults represent an innovative application of Bitcoin in DeFi. We&#8217;re taking full advantage of Avalanche&#8217;s Bridged Bitcoin (BTC.B) to bring about a fresh wave of opportunities in the digital asset space,” said Ersin Dalkali, the Co-founder of Struct Finance.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin continues to dominate the market, its inherent lack of a DeFi layer has traditionally made native yield generation quite challenging. Avalanche has unlocked new possibilities for Bitcoin in DeFi with BTC.B (Bridged Bitcoin). Unlike WBTC that relied on centralized bridges, BTC.B is minted via Avalanche Core — a decentralized bridge — and can be trustlessly bridged across networks using the Layer Zero bridge.</p>
<p>At present, Bitcoin investments in prominent lending pools yield between 0.2–0.5%. Even the stable swap pools offering wBTC-BTC.B products only manage to deliver returns of about 2%. Struct’s BTC.B-USDC product shatters these limitations, offering significantly higher yields.</p>
<p>The purpose of BTC.B is to empower BTC holders to explore DeFi opportunities on the Avalanche blockchain, without the need to acquire secondary tokens or rely on centralized bridges. BTC.B represents BTC coins transferred to the Avalanche blockchain in the form of ERC-20 tokens. With over 6000 BTC bridged and a fully diluted value of $180 million, BTC.B is carving a niche for itself in the crypto arena.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin ETF applications by BlackRock, WisdomTree, and Invesco – three of the world’s leading asset managers – are not just a mere submission. It is a signal that the traditional financial realm is ready to embrace Bitcoin on a new level. Recently, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) gave the green light to a 2X leveraged Bitcoin ETF, sparking an enthusiastic wave of speculation and anticipation for approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<h2>Delta hedging</h2>
<p>Amid the highly volatile crypto industry, Struct Finance’s Interest Rate Products allow anyone to split and repackage the risk of any yield-bearing DeFi assets in different parts to fit their risk profile through an innovative process called “tranching.” Every Interest Rate Product is a single vault split into two portions, or tranches that have different return configurations:</p>
<ol>
<li>A Fixed-return Tranche for conservative investors looking for consistent returns</li>
<li>A Variable-return Tranche for investors with a higher risk appetite seeking superior returns</li>
</ol>
<p>The yield from the underlying asset flows into the fixed tranche first to ensure predictable returns. The remainder is then allocated to the variable tranche, which gets enhanced exposure to the underlying yield-bearing asset. Compared to the fixed tranche, the variable tranche might accrue more yield, less yield, or no yield.</p>
<p>As part of its BTC.B-USDC Vaults, Struct Finance has implemented a unique approach to managing investment risk: delta hedging. While the fixed tranche takes center stage with its high yield, the variable side of the product offers an additional layer of intriguing complexity and potential.</p>
<p>Upon deployment of funds into the vault, the BTC.B in the fixed tranche gets converted into GMX’s GLP token, setting up a position that’s short Bitcoin against GLP and contributing a negative delta. In contrast, the USDC on the variable side is converted into GLP, which inherently carries a positive delta.</p>
<p>This innovative delta-hedged product design achieves a fine balance between the positive and negative delta forces. It results in a robust strategy that allows investors to confidently navigate the crypto market’s inherent volatility.</p>
<p>This artful interplay of the fixed and variable sides within the vaults opens the doors for investors to tap into the potential of Bitcoin investments like never before. By catering to a diverse range of risk appetites, Struct Finance ensures that both retail and institutional investors can tailor their strategies to maximize their returns, regardless of market conditions.</p>
<h2>About Struct Finance</h2>
<p>Struct Finance is at the forefront of the DeFi revolution, with a vision to transform the design and utility of financial products. It empowers users to design their own financial instruments, harnessing the power of tokenized, yield-bearing positions to unlock a world of diverse investment opportunities. Moreover, its cutting-edge financial products adopt a tranche-based system, smartly distributing yield between different investor classes. This balanced approach guarantees a steady yield for risk-averse investors while also offering the prospect of heightened returns to the more adventurous. Initially available on Avalanche, Struct Finance plans to go multichain in the near future.</p>
<p><strong>For more information, visit</strong>: <a href="https://www.struct.fi/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Website</a>  |  <a href="https://twitter.com/structfinance" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a>  |  <a href="https://discord.gg/kngan3PD" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a>  |  <a href="https://t.me/struct_finance_announcements" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a></p>
<p class="ql-align-center"><strong>Disclaimer: This release is for informational purposes only and should not be construed as financial promotion.</strong></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/struct-finance-transforms-defi-landscape-on-avalanche-with-the-launch-of-tranche-based-btc-b-usdc-vaults/" rel="nofollow">Struct Finance Transforms DeFi Landscape on Avalanche With the Launch of Tranche-based BTC.B-USDC Vaults</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Litecoin&#8217;s Social Chatter Intensfies to New Yearly Peak Ahead of Halving: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/litecoins-social-chatter-intensfies-to-new-yearly-peak-ahead-of-halving-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260134</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Litecoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Litecoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After the much-anticipated halving, miners will receive just 6.25 LTC per block.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Litecoin (LTC) search trend has hit a new yearly peak, according to the blockchain analytic platform, IntoTheBlock. The upcoming halving event &#8211; which is currently set for August 2nd &#8211; is likely to be a key driver for the heightened interest.</p>
<p>Halving events have been known to generate tremendous interest in the days leading up to the fact, as they increase the scarcity, which typically boots the value. Hence, the chatter around the crypto asset intensifying is a given.</p>
<ul>
<li>ITB&#8217;s latest <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1679077427903971328" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> depicts a rising search trend for Litecoin amidst what experts consider the longest bear market in the history of the crypto industry.</li>
<li>In fact, its price spikes in the past couple of weeks have <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1676645794089439233" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">coincided</a> with peaks in social activity volume.</li>
<li>Such a trend is common, especially ahead of halving, and if history repeats, the crypto asset is poised for a more upward breakout.</li>
<li>Data suggest that its market cap <a href="https://twitter.com/coinfeeds_ai/status/1676746993773977600" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">increased</a> by nearly 3x nine months following the last halving in 2019. With the crypto markets maturing, the upcoming halving could exert even more upward price pressure.</li>
<li>For one, Litecoin re-entered the top 10 digital assets by market cap in July. Over the past month alone, it has gained over 26%. The crypto asset was currently trading at $97.05, up by more than 37% YTD.</li>
<li>The current price trajectory, coupled with <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/13-of-all-litecoin-ltc-in-circulation-unmoved-for-5-years-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">increased</a> holding behavior demonstrated by long-term LTC holders, signals a potential acceleration in the crypto asset&#8217;s price.</li>
<li>Meanwhile, the network activity has been picking up all year and more significantly since the beginning of April.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-bitcoin-ordinals-are-now-on-litecoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">introduction</a> of LTC 20 &#8211; an experimental standard of NFTs &#8211; could be another catalyst for such a trend.</li>
<li>The LTC-20 standard has attracted more than 90,000 users, inscribing over a million ordinals.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/litecoins-social-chatter-intensfies-to-new-yearly-peak-ahead-of-halving-data/" rel="nofollow">Litecoin&#8217;s Social Chatter Intensfies to New Yearly Peak Ahead of Halving: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How This Dogecoin Trade Made a Crypto Investor a Millionaire: Could These Meme Coins Explode Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 18:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260227</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hankey_thuglife_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/hankey_thuglife_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Dogecoin ($DOGE) remains the most talked-about meme coin in the crypto market – and for good reason. The coin has made fortunes for numerous astute investors, and the tale of one trader, in particular, has caught people&#8217;s interest. However, with Dogecoin’s heyday seemingly behind it, meme coin enthusiasts are now seeking out alternative coins with [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dogecoin ($DOGE) remains the most talked-about meme coin in the crypto market – and for good reason.</p>
<p>The coin has made fortunes for numerous astute investors, and the tale of one trader, in particular, has caught people&#8217;s interest.</p>
<p>However, with Dogecoin’s heyday seemingly behind it, meme coin enthusiasts are now seeking out alternative coins with colossal price potential – and Mr. Hankey Coin ($HANKEY) and Thug Life ($THUG) have emerged as viable candidates in this regard.</p>
<h2>Reddit User Becomes Crypto Millionaire by Betting on Dogecoin</h2>
<p>Dogecoin needs no introduction, as the coin’s exponential price increase in 2021 was what sparked the meme coin niche into life.</p>
<p>Between January and May 2021, $DOGE exploded by over 7,500%, marking the first time meme-based crypto had gained mainstream attention.</p>
<p>The remarkable surge in Dogecoin&#8217;s value captured the public&#8217;s imagination and fueled a frenzy of interest and speculation.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-13.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260237" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-13.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="288" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-13.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-13-300x144.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-13-50x24.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Amidst this frenzy, many crypto traders emerged and seized the opportunity presented by the coin&#8217;s rising value.</p>
<p>One of these traders, Glauber Contessoto, made a fortune investing in Dogecoin by using his life savings to purchase $DOGE.</p>
<p>According to a 2021 <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/14/technology/hes-a-dogecoin-millionaire-and-hes-not-selling.html" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">article</a> from The New York Times, Contessoto&#8217;s decision to invest his life savings in Dogecoin drew skepticism from friends and family members, but it paid off immensely.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-13.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260236" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-13.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="296" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-13.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-13-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-13-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Contessoto’s first investment amounted to around $250,000 and was made in February 2021, just before $DOGE took off.</p>
<p>At the time, $DOGE was trading for just $0.045, yet Contessoto believed in the inherent price potential of the coin, thanks to discussions on platforms like Reddit.</p>
<p>Within two months, Contessoto’s investment soared, turning him into a crypto millionaire.</p>
<p>At the peak of Dogecoin’s rally, Contessoto’s $DOGE holdings amounted to a staggering $3 million – representing a 12x return on his initial investment.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260235" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="611" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7-296x300.jpg 296w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-7-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Interestingly, Contessoto claimed he would sell when $DOGE reached $1, highlighting his unwavering support for the coin.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, this price point was not achieved. Dogecoin&#8217;s value crashed throughout the second half of 2021, leaving many HODLers (including Contessoto) out of pocket.</p>
<p>However, the good news for the so-called &#8220;Dogecoin millionaire&#8221; is that he has now carved out a niche on social media, boasting a <a href="https://twitter.com/ProTheDoge?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter audience</a> of over 280,000 people.</p>
<p>Ultimately, Contessoto’s story serves as a testament to the unpredictable nature of the crypto market and its incredible potential.</p>
<h2>Which Meme Coins Could Explode Next?</h2>
<p>While Dogecoin&#8217;s remarkable rise captivated the world, it is not the only meme coin that has seen such huge gains, with Pepe being one of the most recent examples.</p>
<p>Other meme coins, like Mr. Hankey Coin and Thug Life, have also emerged &#8211; aiming to ride the wave of internet culture and provide similar investment opportunities.</p>
<h2>Mr. Hankey Coin Generating Huge Excitement Ahead of ICO This Week</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Mr. Hankey Coin ($HANKEY)</a> is a fresh entrant into the meme coin universe that’s generating huge hype before it’s even launched. It draws inspiration from the beloved South Park character that shares its name and is embracing the shitcoin status.</p>
<p>$HANKEY’s social media traction in the past few days has been remarkable – within just 24 hours of being launched, the Mr. Hankey Coin <a href="https://twitter.com/MrHankeythecoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter account</a> saw a whopping 4,300 people become followers.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260234" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-3.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="602" height="259" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-3-300x129.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture5-3-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This impressive response underscores the viral potential that $HANKEY has, which is bolstered even further by the fact that the creators are gearing up to launch a limited-time presale phase on 13 July.</p>
<p>During this presale phase, 40% of the total $HANKEY supply will be made available, with a modest hard cap of $500,000.</p>
<p>This was a key ingredient in Dogecoin’s success story – and it seems that $HANKEY is taking a leaf from that playbook. There are also rumors that the team behind Mr. Hankey Coin is the same behind the $SPONGE token, which rose over 100x earlier this year.</p>
<p>Prominent crypto YouTuber Jacob Bury has even taken note of Mr. Hankey Coin’s debut, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rxL79EydSMI" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">expressing</a> that it could be the next “10x potential meme coin”. All in all, although $HANKEY may be at the beginning of its journey, the growing enthusiasm around the token indicates it&#8217;s already making its mark.</p>
<p>The exact drop time has not yet been announced, but interested traders can join the presale now to get notified and ensure they don’t miss out</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Mr. Hankey Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>High-Flying Meme Coin Thug Life Raises Over $1.1m &amp; Looks Set to Go Viral</h2>
<p>Another meme coin that has the potential to provide exponential returns is <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Thug Life ($THUG)</a>.</p>
<p>Harnessing the power of hip-hop nostalgia, this fresh addition to the meme coin niche is already piquing the interest of traders worldwide.</p>
<p>$THUG’s recently-launched presale has already generated over $1.1 million within just two weeks, highlighting the hype around the token.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-260233" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-2.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="602" height="413" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-2.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-2-300x206.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-2-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>With the presale set to conclude in under five days, or once the hard cap of $2.05 million is hit, there’s now a rush as investors clamor to get their hands on $THUG before its open market debut.</p>
<p>Importantly, 70% of the total 4.2 billion $THUG supply has been earmarked for presale investors, with tokens priced at just $0.0007.</p>
<p>Not only that, but Thug Life’s <a href="https://thuglifetoken.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a> notes that 15% of the supply will be used for community rewards – which could include giveaways and token airdrops.</p>
<p>This attractive tokenomics setup has helped foster a strong community base right from the get-go, with nearly 4,000 people now following the official <a href="https://twitter.com/thug_life_token" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter page</a>.</p>
<p>Given its significant following and rapidly increasing presale investment, the signs that Thug Life could be the next meme coin to explode are undoubtedly promising.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_thuglife_33357?referrer=how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Thug Life Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-this-dogecoin-trade-made-a-crypto-investor-a-millionaire-could-these-meme-coins-explode-next/" rel="nofollow">How This Dogecoin Trade Made a Crypto Investor a Millionaire: Could These Meme Coins Explode Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Hits ATH Against EGP on Binance Amid Egypt&#8217;s Economic Crisis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-hits-ath-against-egp-on-binance-amid-egypts-economic-crisis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260179</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/egypt_bitcoin-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/egypt_bitcoin-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The depreciation of the Egyptian pound against the US dollar is the main reason for the development.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Egypt is yet another country that currently copes with severe financial difficulties and galloping inflation, which have harmed the local currency. As such, the price of bitcoin against EGP has surged notably lately, exceeding 1,200,000 EGP on Binance, which is a record high.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that the valuation is not that high on other cryptocurrency exchanges, such as Coinbase.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Outcome of the Monetary Disruption</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite Egypt&#8217;s GDP gradually growing in the past years, the standard of living in the country has been on a downtrend, with high inflation decreasing the purchasing power of the national currency.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some experts claim the financial problems started after the bloody <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2011_Egyptian_revolution" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">2011 revolution</a> when approximately two million people flooded the streets protesting against the reign of President Hosni Mubarak. Egypt entered a turbulent political period in the following years, unable to sustain a stable government until 2014.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The COVID-19 global pandemic and the military conflict between Russia and Ukraine are other factors that worsened the issues. Egypt depends on imported wheat and grain from the Black Sea region, and logically, those deliveries have been interrupted. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The condition of the Egyptian pound is quite worrying since it has depreciated by nearly 40% against the US dollar in the last year. The decline has prompted locals to convert their savings into foreign currency or seek alternative investment options like cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The domestic currency has shrunk so much that the price of bitcoin measured in EGP has reached an all-time high on some cryptocurrency exchanges, such as Binance and Changelly.<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_260197" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-260197" style="width: 645px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-260197" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance.png" alt="BTC Against EGP" width="645" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance.png 737w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-300x186.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Binance-50x31.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 645px) 100vw, 645px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-260197" class="wp-caption-text">BTC Against EGP, Source: Binance</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The previous record was in mid-November 2021, when the primary cryptocurrency reached its highest valuation against all fiat currencies, including the greenback, at $69,000.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that other crypto platforms display different prices. Coinbase, for one, <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/price/bitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">shows</a> that one BTC is currently worth around 950,336 EGP. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Similar Situation in Other Countries</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trends are similar in Turkey and Argentina, where residents also have to cope with record inflation and monetary chaos. Bitcoin is currently worth around 806,000 TRY on <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/price/bitcoin" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Binance</a></span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.binance.com/en/price/bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">close to the ATH measured a few days ago. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Turkish residents have shown an increasing interest in digital assets over the years. Some have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/turkey-residents-turn-to-crypto-amid-another-lira-collapse-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">converted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> their funds to the stablecoin USDT as a protection against the never-ending depreciation of the lira. Ebru Güven – university lecturer and former banker &#8211; explained in detail:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Investing in stablecoins allows people to keep the value of their wealth; it&#8217;s one of the ways to hold on to some value when inflation is this high. This is the only motivation for people to buy stablecoins right now.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some Argentines have also lost their trust in the peso. The political calamity that has reigned in the South American nation for decades, the three-digit inflation rate marked earlier this year, and many more problems have triggered a huge appetite for crypto. Similar to the Turks, Argentines have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/argentines-embrace-crypto-following-resignation-of-economy-minister/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shifted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> their focus to the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin &#8211; USDT.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-hits-ath-against-egp-on-binance-amid-egypts-economic-crisis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Hits ATH Against EGP on Binance Amid Egypt&#8217;s Economic Crisis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
