<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:57:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Cathie Wood Explains How Bitcoin Can Reach $1.5 Million By 2030</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-wood-explains-how-bitcoin-can-reach-1-5-million-by-2030/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ark Invest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261298</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/cathiewood_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Cathie Wood has grown even more bullish on Bitcoin as an insurance policy since the U.S. regional banking crisis in March.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood said on Tuesday that she and her fund are now more confident in their “bull case” for Bitcoin (BTC): $1.5 million by 2030.</p>
<p>The investment manager’s boost of confidence stems from Bitcoin’s positive response to the United States regional banking crisis in March.</p>
<h2>The Bear, Base, and Bull Case</h2>
<p>Ark published a bear, base, and bull <a href="https://research.ark-invest.com/hubfs/1_Download_Files_ARK-Invest/Big_Ideas/ARK%20Invest_013123_Presentation_Big%20Ideas%202023_Final.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">thesis</a> for where Bitcoin would be in 2030 back in January. All price targets were many multiple higher than Bitcoin’s price today, sitting at $258,500, $682,800, and $1.48 million respectively.</p>
<p>Each case put forward different estimates for the total market share of various financial use cases that Bitcoin could gobble up. The bull case rested largely on Bitcoin absorbing $50% of gold’s market cap, while also claiming 6.5% of the institutional asset base and 10% of the M2 money supply in emerging markets.</p>
<p>In an <a href="https://twitter.com/Pledditor/status/1681044467904655362" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a> with Bloomberg on Monday, Wood said that ARK’s confidence in the bull case had “increased” in March when regional banks including Silvergate Bank, Signature Bank, and Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) all collapsed after facing overwhelming withdrawal pressure.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">ARKK&#39;s Cathie Wood: on <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#bitcoin</a> &quot;is an insurance policy against two things: the confiscation of wealth, either directly or by inflation, or in the deflation world, what is it a hedge against? It&#39;s a hedge against counterparty risk. We won&#39;t have an &#39;08-&#39;09 with bitcoin&quot; <a href="https://t.co/jk9hR0Lsid" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/jk9hR0Lsid</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pledditor (@Pledditor) <a href="https://twitter.com/Pledditor/status/1681044467904655362?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 17, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>“As regional banks are going bankrupt and the stocks are imploding across the board, Bitcoin rallied from $19,000 to $30,000,” Wood said. In Wood’s view, this rally signaled a “flight to safety” among investors that “everyone” will eventually want.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin As Insurance</h2>
<p>For one, Wood said that Bitcoin insures against both direct and indirect confiscation of wealth. Whereas direct confiscation means stealing one’s assets by force, indirect confiscation is inflation – the devaluation of a national currency, particularly one whose supply has been astronomically inflated through money printing.</p>
<p>Bitcoin’s supply is programmatically capped at 21 million units, making inflation of this style impossible. Yet even in a deflationary environment for fiat, Wood said Bitcoin presents a hedge against counterparty risk.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We won’t have an 08’ / 09’ with Bitcoin,” she said. “Everything is decentralized, and transparent.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Wood isn’t the only billionaire with a hyper-bullish long-term thesis for Bitcoin. Michael Saylor, Executive Chairman of MicroStrategy, has predicted that Bitcoin’s market cap could soar to $100 million – implying a BTC price of $4.7 million per coin.</p>
<p>Other bulls are confident that Bitcoin will perform strongly over the next 18 months. This year, both Rich Dad Poor Dad author <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-will-explode-to-120k-in-2024-the-us-dollar-will-die-rober-kiyosaki/" data-wpel-link="internal">Robert Kiyosaki</a> and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/banking-giant-standard-chartered-sees-bitcoin-tapping-50k-in-2023-and-120k-in-2024-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">Standard Chartered Bank</a> have called for a $120,000 per coin price by 2025.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-wood-explains-how-bitcoin-can-reach-1-5-million-by-2030/" rel="nofollow">Cathie Wood Explains How Bitcoin Can Reach $1.5 Million By 2030</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFi Platform Struct Finance Sees 129% Gains in 7-Day TVL, Ranks First on Avalanche</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defi-platform-struct-finance-sees-129-gains-in-7-day-tvl-ranks-first-on-avalanche/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 23:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Avalanche]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261147</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The milestone has made Struct Finance the fastest-growing Avalanche-based DeFi platform in the past week.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Struct Finance recorded over 129% gains in its total value locked (TVL) over the past week, according to data from DeFi TVL aggregator DeFiLlama.</p>
<p>Struct Finance’s TVL more than <a href="https://defillama.com/protocol/struct-finance" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">doubled</a> between July 11 and July 18 from $350,820 to $800,000, and at the time of writing, the TVL was at $806,314. When measured in Avalanche’s native token AVAX, the TVL has soared from 25,800 AVAX to 57,553 AVAX.</p>
<h2>Struct Finance Gains Over 100% in TVL</h2>
<p>In the past week, Struct’s growth earned it the number-one spot as the fastest-growing DeFi platform on Avalanche in less than a month of its mainnet launch. The protocol currently ranks first for both one-day and seven-day TVL gain on the network.</p>
<p>Struct now <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Avalanche" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">ranks</a> as the 34th largest Avalanche-based platform by TVL. While the protocol’s growth is significant, it still trails far behind Benqi and Aave, the first and second largest Avalanche-based platforms, with TVLs of $232 million and $214 million, respectively.</p>
<p>Struct Finance, which launched its mainnet on June 21, 2023, offers investors customizable structured financial products that give exposure to digital assets. During the mainnet launch announcement, the platform unveiled a tranching mechanism and innovative Interest Rate Vaults that enable users to invest in products according to risk tolerance and earn predictable returns.</p>
<h2>Struct Bags $3.9 Million in Funding</h2>
<p>As <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-platform-struct-finance-introduces-new-interest-rate-products/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a>, the Avalanche-based DeFi platform allows clients to split the risk of any yield-bearing asset into different parts so it can fit into all strategies. Investors can choose between a fixed but lower return and a higher-risk variable return on their investments.</p>
<p>The returns from the underlying assets are first distributed to the fixed tranche while the remainder is moved to the variable tranche, giving them additional exposure to the initially-picked investment.</p>
<p>In addition, Struct’s unique features allow liquidity providers to earn fixed yields during stable market conditions, regardless of market fluctuations.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the project <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-based-defi-platform-struct-finance-raises-3-9m-in-seed-funding/" data-wpel-link="internal">bagged</a> $3.9 million in March 2022 during a funding round led by Avalanche ecosystem’s Blizzard Fund, Bison Fund, Bixin Ventures, Double Peak, FBG Capital, and AVentures Dao, among others.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-platform-struct-finance-sees-129-gains-in-7-day-tvl-ranks-first-on-avalanche/" rel="nofollow">DeFi Platform Struct Finance Sees 129% Gains in 7-Day TVL, Ranks First on Avalanche</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Terminates its Collaboration With Argentina&#8217;s National Soccer Team</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-terminates-its-collaboration-with-argentinas-national-soccer-team/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 21:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Argentina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261132</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/sky-1281701_1280-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/sky-1281701_1280-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite cutting ties with the AFA, Binance has no intentions to push the brake in Argentina.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance &#8211; ended its partnership with the Argentine Football Association (AFA), claiming the latter has not &#8220;fully met its contractual obligations.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agreement, which turned the platform into the Global Main Sponsor of Argentina&#8217;s national soccer team, was supposed to last until 2027.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Parting Ways</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance and the AFA </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-becomes-the-new-global-sponsor-of-argentinas-national-soccer-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">signed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the deal in January 2022, several months before the start of the World Cup in Qatar, which saw Argentina lifting the trophy. The partnership was considered a significant achievement for the exchange since it was its first collaboration with a national soccer team. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/BinanceArg/status/1680971083904700416" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">tweet</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, though, Binance maintained that the AFA has not complied with its agreement responsibilities. As such, it cut ties with the entity as this goes against its &#8220;business values and association principles.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Binance has decided to end its association with the AFA (Argentine Football Association). We regularly evaluate the results of our partnerships around the world, and unfortunately, despite being offered time and opportunity, AFA has not fully met its contractual obligations, which goes against our business values ​​and our association principles,&#8221; the announcement reads.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, Binance remains committed to strengthening its presence in Argentina. It said it will continue to engage with domestic partners, such as prestigious universities, to &#8220;expand educational efforts and strategic business alliances.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Recall that the exchange </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.forbesargentina.com/money/binance-asocia-una-universidad-argentina-llevar-crypto-academia-n34234" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">teamed up</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the Austral University in May to provide a five-month training program focused on cryptocurrencies, blockchain technology, Web3, and the Metaverse.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Argentina&#8217;s Soccer Team has Another Crypto Sponsor</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance was not the only cryptocurrency partner of the AFA, as the Association previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-becomes-the-global-main-sponsor-of-argentinas-national-soccer-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">inked</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a deal with Bybit. The marketplace serves as the Global Main Sponsor for all soccer selections, whereas its logo is displayed on the training apparel of Lionel Messi (the captain of Argentina) and his teammates. </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bybit and the AFA announced their collaboration in November 2021, revealing that it will last 24 months. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that the big star of Argentina &#8211; &#8220;Leo&#8221; Messi &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitget-partners-with-leo-messi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">collaborated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the cryptocurrency exchange Bitget in October last year. The winner of a record seven Ballon d&#8217;Or Awards became a brand ambassador for the platform, while his responsibilities include introducing the company&#8217;s products and services to sports fans, brands, and organizations.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Messi is among the most influential athletes, having nearly 480 million followers on Instagram. His biggest rival &#8211; Cristiano Ronaldo (who has </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-partners-with-soccer-legend-cristiano-ronaldo-to-launch-exclusive-nft-collections/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">partnered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with Binance) &#8211; has almost 600 million. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-terminates-its-collaboration-with-argentinas-national-soccer-team/" rel="nofollow">Binance Terminates its Collaboration With Argentina&#8217;s National Soccer Team</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Reaches $25 Million Settlement with Series B Holders for GK8 Sale Proceeds Allocation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-reaches-25-million-settlement-with-series-b-holders-for-gk8-sale-proceeds-allocation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celsius Network (CEL)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261182</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Celsius_Dark_Times.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Celsius_Dark_Times.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Israel-based GK8 was initially acquired by Celsius for $115 million in 2021.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bankrupt cryptocurrency lender Celsius, its creditors, and its Series B holders have reached a settlement with regard to the distribution of $25 million in proceeds from the sale of crypto custodian GK8.</p>
<p>According to the filing, the settlements seek to deploy $24 million for legal expenses while allocating the rest of $1 million among the Series B holders. The court document also states that the settlement agreement was born out of the &#8220;mutual desire&#8221; to prevent costly legal disputes and an extensive confirmation process, which would lead to higher professional fees.</p>
<ul>
<li>The agreement between the Debtors, the Committee, and the Initial Consenting Series B Preferred Holders is said to have been &#8220;thoughtfully negotiated and is eminently reasonable.&#8221;</li>
<li>The <a href="https://cases.stretto.com/public/x191/11749/PLEADINGS/1174907182380000000004.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> read,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Settlement brings an end to nearly a year of highly contentious litigation and removes one of the largest obstacles to confirmation and emergence in exchange for a $25 million cash settlement from the proceeds of the GK8 sale and a mutual release of claims between the Initial Consenting Series B Preferred Holders and the Estate Parties.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>GK8 was initially acquired by Celsius for an unknown amount, which was later disputed to be $115 million, in November 2021.</li>
<li>However, as Celsius filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection last summer following the collapse of Terra&#8217;s ecosystem, Mike Novogratz-led Galaxy Digital agreed to purchase the Israel-based company as part of bankruptcy proceedings.</li>
<li>The former Celsius CEO, Alex Mashinsky, was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ex-celsius-ceo-alex-mashinsky-arrested-sec-files-against-celsius/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested</a> last week and charged with wire fraud and other crimes.</li>
<li>US prosecutors also alleged that the exec pumped up the price of his company&#8217;s cryptocurrency to lure customers to the platform.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/celsius-reaches-25-million-settlement-with-series-b-holders-for-gk8-sale-proceeds-allocation/" rel="nofollow">Celsius Reaches $25 Million Settlement with Series B Holders for GK8 Sale Proceeds Allocation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Pump and Dump, Sell the News, or Massively Bullish: Analysts on Potential Approval of Spot BTC ETF</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-pump-and-dump-sell-the-news-or-massively-bullish-analysts-on-potential-approval-of-spot-btc-etf/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 18:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261276</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/bitcoin_cover-9.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[How will the market actually react to a Bitcoin spot ETF – even if it gets approved?]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest influx of Bitcoin (BTC) spot ETF applications in the United States is certainly generating hype, but some analysts are split on whether that excitement is warranted.</p>
<p>While many claim approval will invite a new wave of investor capital into the asset, others think it may only amount to a sell-the-news event.</p>
<h2>The Bearish Case for a Bitcoin Spot ETF</h2>
<p>In an interview with <a href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitcoin-etf-hype-threatens-another-sell-the-news-fizzle-1.1947277" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>, FLX Networks Managing Director Jillian DelSignore questioned whether a Bitcoin spot ETF will attract significant capital beyond the first few days from its launch.</p>
<p>She cited the ProShare Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) as an example – a Bitcoin Futures ETF which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/first-bitcoin-futures-etf-generates-1-billion-in-trade-volume-on-first-day/" data-wpel-link="internal">listed</a> on the NYSE in October 2021. While Bitcoin spot ETF backs its shares with actual BTC, a futures ETF is backed by Bitcoin futures contracts.</p>
<p>BITO had the second-largest opening day in BITO history, attracting over $1 billion, but mostly stopped absorbing capital after a few days.</p>
<p>“I think we’ll definitely see multiple billions of dollars come in,” said DelSignoreregarding a potential spot ETF. “I do think it will be a very early momentum-driven asset growth, and then the question mark for me is what happens from there. Does it quiet down?”</p>
<p>JP Morgan strategist Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou happens to agree. In a memo this month, the strategist <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-07/jpmorgan-says-a-bitcoin-etf-wouldn-t-be-an-industry-game-changer?in_source=embedded-checkout-banner" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">said</a> that spot ETFs have already existed in Canada and Europe for years, and have failed to attract much capital, “failing to benefit from investor outflows from gold ETFs.”</p>
<p>While conceding that there may be some benefits to having a spot ETF, the strategist predicted that they would be “rather marginal.”</p>
<h2>The Positives of a Spot ETF</h2>
<p>Contrarily, Bloomberg Intelligence ETF analysts including Athanasios Psarofagis and James Seyffart see great potential for a spot ETF.</p>
<p>When looking at Canada’s existing crypto ETFs, analysts note that they’ve attracted 1% of the ETF market in the country already. If a roughly similar share of the United States’s ETF capital rushed into a U.S. Bitcoin spot ETF, that would amount to $54 billion.</p>
<p>For context, the total US commodity ETF market amounts to $137 billion. Furthermore, Glassnode analysts say that roughly $13.5 billion worth of BTC actively participates in price discovery right now.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Nate Geraci – president of the advisory firm “The ETF Store” – thinks a spot ETF provides meaningful benefit to investors above a futures ETF, noting that the latter doesn’t perfectly track BTC’s price. While BITO is down 63% since launch, BTC has dropped just 53% since that time.</p>
<p>“Investors want the real deal,” he said. “They don’t want to hassle with potentially significant tracking error.”</p>
<p>Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) – the world’s largest Bitcoin fund holding over 650,000 BTC under management – also faces a tracking error issue. Its share price currently trades 26% below the value of its underlying BTC, due to an inability to redeem shares easily for coins the way an ETF can do.</p>
<p>The fund is embroiled in a legal battle with regulators to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-calls-out-sec-for-approving-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-while-denying-spot/" data-wpel-link="internal">transition</a> into a spot ETF, in which case its share price will immediately restore to parity with its BTC.</p>
<p>BlackRock’s entry into the Bitcoin ETF race last month was alone able to boost Bitcoin’s price over the past few weeks, raising optimism that a spot ETF might finally be approved. The firm’s CEO Larry Fink, who was once a Bitcoin skeptic, said last week that Bitcoin may have the power to “transcend any one currency.”</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-pump-and-dump-sell-the-news-or-massively-bullish-analysts-on-potential-approval-of-spot-btc-etf/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Pump and Dump, Sell the News, or Massively Bullish: Analysts on Potential Approval of Spot BTC ETF</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DEX Top Performer Token TET Listed on MEXC Exchange on July 18th, 3 PM UTC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dex-top-performer-token-tet-listed-on-mexc-exchange-on-july-18th-3-pm-utc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261258</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/f1u9ravayaaejxj_1689697687fkga3SjIKw.jpeg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/f1u9ravayaaejxj_1689697687fkga3SjIKw.jpeg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, July 18th, 2023] We are thrilled to announce that $TET, the top-performing token on Uniswap, has been listed on the esteemed MEXC Exchange. This listing represents a significant milestone for the Tectum project and opens up exciting opportunities for investors and traders worldwide. The highly anticipated listing on MEXC Exchange [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Mahe, Seychelles, July 18th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>We are thrilled to announce that $TET, the top-performing token on Uniswap, has been listed on the esteemed MEXC Exchange. This listing represents a significant milestone for the Tectum project and opens up exciting opportunities for investors and traders worldwide.</p>
<p>The highly anticipated listing on MEXC Exchange took place on July 18th at 3 pm UTC. MEXC Exchange is renowned for its robust trading infrastructure, high liquidity, and wide range of trading pairs. With this strategic move, $TET aims to provide its community with enhanced trading capabilities and a seamless trading experience.</p>
<p>TET has garnered significant attention in the DEX space due to its exceptional performance on Uniswap, innovative features of the SoftNote, and strong community support. The team hopes that the token&#8217;s consistent growth and positive market sentiment will continue due to its global long-term utility.</p>
<p>By listing on MEXC Exchange, TET gains exposure to a vast network of traders, institutional investors, and crypto enthusiasts. This increased visibility and accessibility will contribute to the further expansion of the $TET ecosystem and its adoption within the broader crypto community.</p>
<p>The $TET team has been working diligently to ensure a smooth listing process on MEXC Exchange. The team is committed to providing ongoing support and maintaining transparent communication channels with the community throughout this exciting phase.</p>
<p>For more information about TET and the upcoming listing on MEXC Exchange, please visit the official website, <a href="https://www.softnote.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">www.softnote.com</a>. Stay tuned for further updates on social media channels, including <a href="https://twitter.com/tectumsocial" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://t.me/tectumglobal" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Telegram</a>, and <a href="https://discord.gg/TXREkPY8C7" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Discord</a>.</p>
<h2>About Tectum:</h2>
<p>From the Cybersecurity company CrispMind, The Tectum SoftNote is the ultimate Bitcoin/Crypto Layer 2 solution that overcomes the pitfalls of the lightning network. It is built on the Layer 1 Blockchain, Tectum, which is the fastest blockchain in the world and transacts at 1.3 million TPS. With SoftNote, users can enjoy instant, trustless, anonymous, and decentralized crypto payments for free. With a strong community backing and a commitment to innovation, $TET aims to shape the future of the crypto payments for private and retail transactions and revolutionize the blockchain industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dex-top-performer-token-tet-listed-on-mexc-exchange-on-july-18th-3-pm-utc/" rel="nofollow">DEX Top Performer Token TET Listed on MEXC Exchange on July 18th, 3 PM UTC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The US Will Become a &#8216;Highly Competitive Market&#8217; Once it Embraces Crypto, Circle CEO Says</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-will-become-a-highly-competitive-market-once-it-embraces-crypto-circle-ceo-says/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Circle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261174</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Jeremy-Allaire.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Blockchain technology will be among the key factors to transform commerce and trade in the following decade, Allaire added.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jeremy Allaire &#8211; Chief Executive Officer of Circle &#8211; believes American regulators should open arms to the cryptocurrency industry to prevent falling behind other nations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He said the US government was among the first to propose recommendations regarding stablecoin regulation, adding that the White House, the Federal Reserve, and the Treasury Department are all focused on that mission. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;The US may be Late to the Party&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/07/18/future-of-finance-circle-jeremy-allaire-crypto-regulations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Allaire </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">regretted that the American government has not been as supportive of the digital asset industry over the years as other countries. In his view, this could push talent abroad and affect &#8220;where capital will go.&#8221; Still, he raised hopes that the US will quickly catch up once it enforces a regulatory framework due to the size of its economy and implement certain policies &#8220;in an election year:&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The US may be late to the party in terms of getting these policies done, but it is the biggest economy and has the biggest technology industry and the biggest financial system in the world. And when the US does lay down its rules, it&#8217;s going to be a highly competitive market.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_261204" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261204" style="width: 607px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261204" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg" alt="Jeremy Allaire" width="607" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-300x198.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-1024x675.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-768x506.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-1536x1012.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-2048x1350.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Allaire-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 607px) 100vw, 607px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261204" class="wp-caption-text">Jeremy Allaire, Source: The Boston Globe</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Allaire </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/regulatory-uncertainty-and-banking-crisis-could-push-investors-outside-the-us-circle-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">argued</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> earlier this year that the regulatory chaos and the banking crisis in America could prompt local investors to move abroad.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also gave his two cents on the numerous financial giants that have recently filed to launch spot Bitcoin ETFs in the States, such as the world&#8217;s largest asset manager <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">BlackRock</a>. According to him, one factor behind the increasing interest from such companies is the end of the turbulence caused by<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal"> the FTX implosion</a> last year. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;But we&#8217;re well past that, and at the same time, the technological progress just keeps cranking along,&#8221; he maintained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Circle&#8217;s CEO suggested the current condition of the crypto sector is much similar to the market after the Dot-com crash in the late 1990s. Back then, phrases like &#8220;e-commerce&#8221; or &#8220;consumer internet&#8221; were frowned upon due to the high uncertainty. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Nonetheless, &#8220;the next generation of browser technology, the next generation of digital media technology, broadband infrastructure, Wi-Fi infrastructure, mobile devices&#8221; lit up &#8220;a whole new era,&#8221; Allaire concluded.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">What Does the Future Hold?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Allaire described the next five to ten years as &#8220;the programable money era,&#8221; where blockchain technology, AI, smart contracts, and entrepreneurship will reshape trade and commerce.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He went further, saying the financial system will transform the way smartphones are modified after the success of the iPhone.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It&#8217;s similar to when you lit up broadband for everyone, and you enabled Wi-Fi-connected devices—what became possible, right? Television was reinvented; gaming was reinvented,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-us-will-become-a-highly-competitive-market-once-it-embraces-crypto-circle-ceo-says/" rel="nofollow">The US Will Become a &#8216;Highly Competitive Market&#8217; Once it Embraces Crypto, Circle CEO Says</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase CEO to Meet US House Democrats on Crypto Legislation: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-to-meet-us-house-democrats-on-crypto-legislation-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261215</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Brian_Armstrong.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brian Armstrong, the chief executive officer of America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase, will privately meet with Democrats from the House of Representatives on Wednesday morning.</p>
<p>According to a Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-07-17/coinbase-ceo-brian-armstrong-set-to-meet-with-house-democrats?sref=3REHEaVI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, Democratic aides disclosed that the meeting would focus on crypto legislation and related issues like taxes, privacy, and national security.</p>
<h2>Coinbase CEO to Meet With House Democrats</h2>
<p>The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House that is made up of 100 members who are committed to pro-economic growth, pro-innovation, and fiscally responsible policies.</p>
<p>Armstrong’s meeting with the New Democratic Coalition comes as Coinbase faces a lawsuit from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over allegations of securities law violations. Recall that the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">accused</a> the crypto exchange of operating as an unregistered national securities exchange, clearing agency, and broker last month.</p>
<p>While Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-welcomes-sec-legal-battle-well-get-the-job-done/" data-wpel-link="internal">fights</a> the SEC’s allegations, Armstrong launched a campaign seeking clearer crypto rules in the U.S. Before the lawsuit, Coinbase petitioned the agency in July 2022, asking for clarity on crypto regulation. After ignoring the exchange’s request, the agency finally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-responds-to-coinbase-request-for-crypto-clarity-wants-more-time/" data-wpel-link="internal">asked</a> for more time to file a concrete response.</p>
<h2>Armstrong Seeks Clear Crypto Rules</h2>
<p>The Coinbase chief has urged U.S. lawmakers to consider two crypto bills that have been circulating and promise to provide guidance on which regulators will oversee digital assets. Lawmakers from the House and Senate introduced the bills to provide clarity on crypto regulation.</p>
<p>The first one, <a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=100652X1574425&amp;isjs=1&amp;jv=15.4.2-stackpath&amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coindesk.com%2Fpolicy%2F2023%2F06%2F02%2Fus-house-republicans-push-for-crypto-oversight-with-bill-to-make-sec-play-ball%2F&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Ffinancialservices.house.gov%2Fnews%2Fdocumentsingle.aspx%3FDocumentID%3D408838&amp;xs=1&amp;xtz=-60&amp;xuuid=e221d84af2894b01674d9afbd13b765a&amp;xjsf=other_click__auxclick%20%5B2%5D" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">proposed</a> by Republican chairs of the House Financial Services Committee and the House Committee on Agriculture, would enable crypto exchanges to register with the SEC and trade digital securities, commodities, and stablecoins all in one place.</p>
<p>The second, introduced by crypto-friendly Senator Cynthia Lummis and Senator Kirsten Gillibrand, would require the Commodity Futures Trading Commission to oversee exchanges while regulated depository institutions handle stablecoin issuers. The bill was initially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-cynthia-lummis-bill-and-what-does-it-mean-for-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">proposed</a> in June 2022 but <a href="https://www.lummis.senate.gov/wp-content/uploads/Lummis-Gillibrand-2023.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">re-introduced</a> last week.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Coinbase’s COIN stock is up over 25% since a federal court <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripples-secondary-sales-of-xrp-not-an-investment-contract-judge-rules-following-over-3-year-long-legal-battle/" data-wpel-link="internal">ruled</a> in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit with the SEC concerning XRP’s recognition as a security or investment contract. The partial victory was considered a win for the crypto industry at large. The closed-door gathering will be with lawmakers from the New Democrat Coalition, one of the largest caucuses in the House.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-ceo-to-meet-us-house-democrats-on-crypto-legislation-report/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase CEO to Meet US House Democrats on Crypto Legislation: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Meme Token Evil Pepe Coin Launches Presale &#8211; Next $PEPE Rival to Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261239</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evil_pepe_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/evil_pepe_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The meme coin market has a new contender looking to challenge the dominance of $PEPE – Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE). Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE) This brand-new project launched its presale phase today, aiming to capture the meme coin hype with an edgy twist on the popular Pepe the Frog character. With the frenzy around meme [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The meme coin market has a new contender looking to challenge the dominance of $PEPE – Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE).</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Evil Pepe Coin ($EVILPEPE)</a> This brand-new project launched its presale phase today, aiming to capture the meme coin hype with an edgy twist on the popular Pepe the Frog character.</p>
<p>With the frenzy around meme coins showing no signs of dissipating, $EVILPEPE could be the next viral hit when it makes its open market debut in the coming weeks.</p>
<h2>Evil Pepe Coin Unleashes Exciting Opportunity to Harness Meme Coin Magic</h2>
<p>Evil Pepe Coin has burst onto the scene with an appealing presale phase, generating excitement throughout the crypto scene.</p>
<p>This presale offers a golden opportunity for investors and meme enthusiasts, with 90% of the total $EVILPEPE supply on offer.</p>
<p>Priced at just $0.000333, $EVILPEPE beckons investors to embrace their dark side and engage in the exciting world of meme culture.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261246" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="256" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21-300x128.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture2-21-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Early investors have the option to purchase tokens using $ETH or $USDT, without the constraint of any minimum or maximum investment size.</p>
<p>Per the project’s <a href="https://evilpepecoin.com/assets/documents/whitepaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper</a>, the presale&#8217;s hard cap is just $1,996,002, hastening the token&#8217;s debut on the open market.</p>
<p>Although 90% of the total $EVILPEPE supply has been set aside for the presale, the remaining 10% will be used for decentralized exchange (DEX) liquidity – a solid foundation for the token&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p>Importantly, this liquidity will be locked for one month, helping stabilize the price and prevent a dreaded rug pull from occurring.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Evil Pepe Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Evil Pepe Coin Looks to Challenge Dominance of Meme King $PEPE</h2>
<p>As indicated by its name, Evil Pepe Coin seeks to capitalize on the triumphant performance of the enormously successful meme coin Pepe ($PEPE).</p>
<p>$PEPE experienced a meteoric rise of over 10,000% earlier this year, kickstarting the meme coin frenzy that has been sustained until this day.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261245" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="309" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21-300x154.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture3-21-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Evil Pepe Coin looks to tap into the existing enthusiasm surrounding $PEPE, which has demonstrated the massive potential (and profitability) of low-cap cryptos.</p>
<p>However, $EVILPEPE puts its own spin on things with a rebellious nature and dark branding – providing scope to attract investors who missed out on the original $PEPE’s ascent.</p>
<p>Describing itself as &#8220;unapologetic and audacious,&#8221; Evil Pepe Coin looks primed and ready to ride the hype wave and offer huge gains potential for early adopters.</p>
<h2>Ambitious $EVILPEPE Roadmap Hints at Token’s Future Potential</h2>
<p>Given $EVILPEPE’s stable price point throughout its presale phase, many members of the token’s <a href="https://t.me/Evilpepetoken" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram community</a> believe that it&#8217;s positioned for a remarkable take-off once it hits exchanges.</p>
<p>Importantly, $EVILPEPE will only be listed on a decentralized exchange (DEX) initially – a decision that has been taken to promote community engagement.</p>
<p>This is because a DEX listing aligns with the project’s vision of inclusivity, allowing for broader access to $EVILPEPE.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-261244" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg" alt="Picture4" width="602" height="141" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14-300x70.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture4-14-50x12.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>As such, by launching exclusively on a DEX, the project&#8217;s creators ensure everyone has an equal opportunity to engage with the token and contribute to its growth.</p>
<p>With this solid foundation of inclusivity and community engagement, Evil Pepe Coin&#8217;s roadmap seeks to drive the project towards ambitious goals.</p>
<p>These goals include high-profile marketing campaigns, strategic partnerships, and a lofty market cap of $100 million.</p>
<p>All in all, Evil Pepe Coin&#8217;s roadmap reflects a vision of embracing the devilish side of meme culture – positioning $EVILPEPE as a potentially prominent player in the crypto landscape.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_1ecf342c.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Evil Pepe Coin Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-meme-token-evil-pepe-coin-launches-presale-next-pepe-rival-to-watch/" rel="nofollow">New Meme Token Evil Pepe Coin Launches Presale &#8211; Next $PEPE Rival to Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Unable to Breach $2,000 as Bulls Running Out of Steam: Ethereum Price Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2000-as-bulls-running-out-of-steam-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 14:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=261190</guid>
		<media:content url="" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price rally has slowed down in recent weeks. The price has yet to break above the $2,000 level, which is making many market participants worried. Ethereum Price Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily timeframe, the price has been forming higher highs and higher lows since rebounding from the 200-day moving [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price rally has slowed down in recent weeks. The price has yet to break above the $2,000 level, which is making many market participants worried.</p>
<h2><strong>Ethereum Price Technical Analysis</strong></h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily timeframe, the price has been forming higher highs and higher lows since rebounding from the 200-day moving average earlier in June.</p>
<p>However, there is a clear lack of bullish momentum, as the ETH price keeps pulling back towards the 50-day moving average located around the $1,900 mark. In case it breaks, there are two close support levels available: the $1,800 static level and the 200-day moving average close to the same price mark.</p>
<p>Therefore, while the momentum is seemingly fading, there is still hope that a rebound from either of these levels would initiate the next rally higher.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261196" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261196" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261196 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1807231" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jul-18-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261196" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Recent PA developments become clearer on the 4-hour chart.</p>
<p>The ETH price has broken above the $1,930 resistance level a couple of times since the beginning of July but has failed in both instances, as it has rapidly dropped back below the level.</p>
<p>Currently, the price is seemingly targeting the $1,850 short-term support level once again, with the $1,750 level available as the next target in line in case the former level fails to hold. The RSI indicator, while previously signaling the potential fake breakout and drop, is offering little insight at the moment, as it is oscillating around the 50% value. This behavior confirms the indecisiveness of the market participants and the equilibrium in momentum.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261194" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261194" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261194 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_1807232" width="2560" height="1464" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-768x439.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-2048x1171.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/ETHUSDT-4H-Jul-18-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261194" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>Ethereum Coinbase Premium Index</h3>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has remained relatively stagnant over the past few months, consolidating around the $2,000 level. However, interesting activity has been going on in the background.</p>
<p>The chart displays the Ethereum Coinbase premium gap, which is calculated based on the gap between ETH&#8217;s price on Coinbase and Binance, two of the largest exchanges in the world. This metric shows whether US investors are buying or selling on aggregate compared to other investors. Positive values indicate buying pressure from the United States.</p>
<p>As the image demonstrates, there has been a significant shift in the US market sentiment, as the premium gap index has mostly been positive. Considering that many US investors are wealthy individuals or institutions, this could be a positive signal for ETH, pointing out that it might be in the accumulation phase at the beginning of a new bull market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_261195" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-261195" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-261195 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_coinbase_premium_index_chart_1807231" width="2560" height="1619" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-300x190.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-1024x647.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-768x486.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-1536x971.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-2048x1295.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Ethereum-Coinbase-Premium-Index-Jul-18-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-261195" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-unable-to-breach-2000-as-bulls-running-out-of-steam-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Unable to Breach $2,000 as Bulls Running Out of Steam: Ethereum Price Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
