<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Pumps Up 7% in 7 Days – Where is BTC Heading Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-pumps-up-7-7-days-where-btc-heading-next.htm</link><description>In the past week, Bitcoin's price has experienced an impressive 7% increase, raising questions about the cryptocurrency's future trajectory. As investors and market analysts eagerly assess the factors driving this surge, many are left wondering where Bitcoin is heading next and what potential obstacles it may face along the way....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-pumps-up-7-7-days-where-btc-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Pumps Up 7% in 7 Days – Where is BTC Heading Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-pumps-up-7-7-days-where-btc-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112577/272123/30-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="509586"/></item><item><title>Think Like a Hacker: OPSEC Tips To Ensure Crypto Security</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/think-like-hacker-opsec-tips-ensure-crypto-security.htm</link><description>Ron Stoner is the Head of Security at US-based crypto security specialist Casa.__________  &lt;br /&gt;
Operational security, or OPSEC, is the process of performing risk management by defining what information you are trying to secure, what is required to achieve that goal, and then taking the practical steps required.  &lt;br /&gt;
The philosophy behind OPSEC primarily focuses on thinking like your attacker, understanding who that attacker may be, and what steps they may take to exploit you....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/think-like-hacker-opsec-tips-ensure-crypto-security.htm"&gt;Read More: Think Like a Hacker: OPSEC Tips To Ensure Crypto Security&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Opinions</category><category>Casa</category><category>Security</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Hack</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Transactions</category><category>Privacy</category><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/think-like-hacker-opsec-tips-ensure-crypto-security.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112252/271396/adobestock-weerasak-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="120037"/></item><item><title>Lightning Labs Unveils Upgrade to Boost Bitcoin Accessibility for Billions of People – Here's How it Works</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lightning-labs-unveils-upgrade-boost-bitcoin-accessibility-for-billions-of-people-heres-how-it-works.htm</link><description>Bitcoin infrastructure firm Lightning Labs has released an update to Litd, its node management tool, in order to make it easier for people to use the Lightning Network. &lt;br /&gt;
The new update adds automated fee management, custodial accounts, finer-grained LNC permissions, and the Pool Order Board to Litd, Lightning Labs head of product growth Michael Levan said in a recent blog post....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lightning-labs-unveils-upgrade-boost-bitcoin-accessibility-for-billions-of-people-heres-how-it-works.htm"&gt;Read More: Lightning Labs Unveils Upgrade to Boost Bitcoin Accessibility for Billions of People – Here's How it Works&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Lightning Network</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lightning-labs-unveils-upgrade-boost-bitcoin-accessibility-for-billions-of-people-heres-how-it-works.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112567/272086/adobestock-24k-production.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="78825"/></item><item><title>Generative AI: Legal Challenges and Opportunities in the Crypto World</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/generative-ai-legal-challenges-and-opportunities.htm</link><description>Artificial Intelligence has been very much in the news lately, and it seems that every day we hear about new amazing things that can be done with this technology. Yet with great power come great challenges. There are currently legal questions regarding A.I. content, that once sorted out, will open up brave new venues for using it, particularly in the crypto sector....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/generative-ai-legal-challenges-and-opportunities.htm"&gt;Read More: Generative AI: Legal Challenges and Opportunities in the Crypto World&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 08:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/generative-ai-legal-challenges-and-opportunities.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112541/272082/ai.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="387612"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price &amp; Ethereum Forecast: BTC and ETH See Modest 0.5% Shift - Is a Breakout on the Horizon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-forecast-btc-and-eth-see-modest-05-shift-is-a-breakout-on-the-horizon.htm</link><description>In the world of cryptocurrencies, Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) have experienced a relatively calm period, with both digital assets seeing a modest 0.5% movement in recent trading sessions. With such stable price action, market participants may be wondering if a breakout is just around the corner for these leading cryptocurrencies....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-forecast-btc-and-eth-see-modest-05-shift-is-a-breakout-on-the-horizon.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price &amp; Ethereum Forecast: BTC and ETH See Modest 0.5% Shift - Is a Breakout on the Horizon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-ethereum-forecast-btc-and-eth-see-modest-05-shift-is-a-breakout-on-the-horizon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112565/272080/30-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="527236"/></item><item><title>US House Financial Services Committee Says Crypto Bill Coming in "Next Two Months" – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-says-crypto-bill-coming-next-two-months-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The US House Financial Services Committee and House Agriculture Committee are set to introduce comprehensive legislation to oversee the cryptocurrency sector in the next two months. &lt;br /&gt;
Before unveiling the new bill, the two committees will hold a joint public hearing, which is scheduled to start in May, Representative Patrick McHenry, chair of the House Financial Services Committee, said during Consensus 2023 conference. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-says-crypto-bill-coming-next-two-months-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: US House Financial Services Committee Says Crypto Bill Coming in "Next Two Months" – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><category>law</category><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-says-crypto-bill-coming-next-two-months-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112542/271978/gavel-g1658266f2-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="217806"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Forecast as Cardano Becomes Top 3 Project for Development Activity – Can ADA 10x in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-cardano-becomes-top-3-project-for-development-activity-can-ada-10x-2023.htm</link><description>Cardano has established itself as a top project for developer activity, consistently appearing among the top three.  &lt;br /&gt;
As a result of this trend, more investors and analysts are paying close attention to the price changes of Cardano to gauge its potential in the future. &lt;br /&gt;
Cardano (ADA) had a terrible year with massive price fluctuation like the rest of the cryptocurrency market.  &lt;br /&gt;
It ended the year at $0.2456, and notably, it has grown to reach its current price of $0.4017. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-cardano-becomes-top-3-project-for-development-activity-can-ada-10x-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Forecast as Cardano Becomes Top 3 Project for Development Activity – Can ADA 10x in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 11:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-as-cardano-becomes-top-3-project-for-development-activity-can-ada-10x-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112510/271890/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="289990"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Developers Tease New Metaverse Launch – SHIB Pump Incoming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-developers-tease-new-metaverse-launch-shib-pump-incoming.htm</link><description>SHIB, the token powering the second most popular meme coin ecosystem, Shiba Inu is still hanging loosely on the cliff’s edge. However, there is a higher probability of the outcome flipping bullish bolstered by the soon-to-launch metaverse....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-developers-tease-new-metaverse-launch-shib-pump-incoming.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Developers Tease New Metaverse Launch – SHIB Pump Incoming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba Inu Price Prediction</category><category>SHIB</category><category>SHIB/USD</category><category>Shib Price</category><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-developers-tease-new-metaverse-launch-shib-pump-incoming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112538/271976/shibusd-2023-04-29-13-31-34.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="494001"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Approaches $30,000 Resistance – What is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-30000-resistance-what-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>As Bitcoin inches closer to the $30,000 resistance level, investors and traders eagerly anticipate its next move. In this Bitcoin price prediction, we will explore various price predictions and analyze the factors that could influence its trajectory.  &lt;br /&gt;
Will BTC break through this significant barrier and continue its upward trend, or will it face a pullback? Let's dive into the possible scenarios and targets for the world's largest cryptocurrency by market cap....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-30000-resistance-what-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Approaches $30,000 Resistance – What is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-approaches-30000-resistance-what-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112535/271975/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1214343"/></item><item><title>Crypto is 'Dead in America', Binance.US Says ‘Bye Voyager’, Countries Say ‘Hi CBDC’ and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-dead-in-america-binanceus-says-bye-voyager-countries-say-hi-cbdc-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-dead-in-america-binanceus-says-bye-voyager-countries-say-hi-cbdc-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto is 'Dead in America', Binance.US Says ‘Bye Voyager’, Countries Say ‘Hi CBDC’ and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/crypto-is-dead-in-america-binanceus-says-bye-voyager-countries-say-hi-cbdc-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112360/271715/web3-0-memes-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="347245"/></item><item><title>Ethereum (ETH) Price Set to Roar as These Two Key Deflationary Tailwinds Pick Up</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-eth-price-set-roar-as-these-two-key-deflationary-tailwinds-pick-up.htm</link><description>Post-“shapella” upgrade optimism that briefly lifted the Ether (ETH) price to 11-month highs in the mid-$2,150s earlier this month has mostly faded. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether, the token that powers the smart-contract-enabled Ethereum blockchain, was last trading close to $1,900, still up around 4% for the month, but over 11% below earlier monthly peaks....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-eth-price-set-roar-as-these-two-key-deflationary-tailwinds-pick-up.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum (ETH) Price Set to Roar as These Two Key Deflationary Tailwinds Pick Up&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Deflation</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-eth-price-set-roar-as-these-two-key-deflationary-tailwinds-pick-up.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112520/271963/eth-6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6975908"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 28 April – Cronos, Render, Internet Computer</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-28-april-cronos-render-internet-computer.htm</link><description>As the month of May approaches, the financial world finds itself at the crossroads of several pivotal economic events. &lt;br /&gt;
The decisions and data emerging from these events are expected to leave a lasting impact on both equity and cryptocurrency markets. &lt;br /&gt;
Given this uncertain macroeconomic backdrop, what are the best cryptos to buy now?  &lt;br /&gt;
One of the most anticipated events is the meeting of the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC), an essential arm of the Federal Reserve. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-28-april-cronos-render-internet-computer.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 28 April – Cronos, Render, Internet Computer&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>AI</category><category>LHINU</category><category>Love Hate Inu</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>Internet Computer</category><category>ICP</category><category>Render Token</category><category>RNDR</category><category>CRO</category><category>Cronos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-28-april-cronos-render-internet-computer.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112519/271958/5aae0107-31f2-4907-ae67-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="336747"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price Pauses Below $30K, Here is Where it Could Be Headed Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-pauses-below-30k-here-where-it-could-headed-next.htm</link><description>The Bitcoin (BTC) price is largely unchanged in the mid-$29,000s on Friday. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency found decent support earlier in the session when it briefly fell to test the $29,000 level and 21-Day Moving Average just above it. &lt;br /&gt;
But the Bitcoin bulls seem to be taking a breather ahead of the psychologically important $30,000 level, as key macro events including a rate decision from the US Federal Reserve next week loom....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-pauses-below-30k-here-where-it-could-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin (BTC) Price Pauses Below $30K, Here is Where it Could Be Headed Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-btc-price-pauses-below-30k-here-where-it-could-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112518/271951/btc-6.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="255668"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Target $30,000 Level – Is the Bear Market Over</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-target-30000-level-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>In this Bitcoin price prediction, we'll explore the possibility of bulls targeting the $30,000 level and discuss whether the recent momentum could signal the end of the bear market. With the cryptocurrency market witnessing a resurgence in optimism, it's essential to assess the underlying factors contributing to these trends and consider the potential outlook for Bitcoin's price trajectory....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-target-30000-level-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Target $30,000 Level – Is the Bear Market Over&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-target-30000-level-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112472/271784/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1173235"/></item><item><title>JPMorgan Pursues Tokenization Plans Despite Crypto Downturn and Regulatory Hurdles</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-pursues-tokenization-plans-despite-crypto-downturn-regulatory-hurdles.htm</link><description>Major Wall Street investment bank JPMorgan is moving forward with its push to tokenize traditional financial assets despite last year’s market downturn. &lt;br /&gt;
According to Tyrone Lobban, the head of JPMorgan’s digital asset and tokenization platform Onyx, the bank has already processed close to $700 billion in short-term loans on Onyx, with more to come in the near future....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-pursues-tokenization-plans-despite-crypto-downturn-regulatory-hurdles.htm"&gt;Read More: JPMorgan Pursues Tokenization Plans Despite Crypto Downturn and Regulatory Hurdles&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>JPMorgan</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/jpmorgan-pursues-tokenization-plans-despite-crypto-downturn-regulatory-hurdles.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112484/271806/jpmorgan.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="66879"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as New Neo-Banking App Adds Support for SHIB – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-new-neo-banking-app-adds-support-for-shib-time-to-buy.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the Ethereum blockchain-issued ERC-20 crypto token that powers the Shiba Inu web3 ecosystem, continues to struggle to gain traction, with prices remaining capped under the 200-Day Moving Average just above $0.000010. &lt;br /&gt;
As a result, near-term price predictions remain pessimistic. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-new-neo-banking-app-adds-support-for-shib-time-to-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as New Neo-Banking App Adds Support for SHIB – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Love Hate Inu</category><category>LHINU</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-new-neo-banking-app-adds-support-for-shib-time-to-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112513/271894/shib-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="711217"/></item><item><title>UK Considers Taxation Revisions for DeFi Lending and Staking Activities – Here's The Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-considers-taxation-revisions-for-defi-lending-staking-activities-heres-latest.htm</link><description>According to a consultation document, the UK government is seeking views on tax modification for decentralized finance (DeFi) lending and staking.  &lt;br /&gt;
The government has initiated an open consultation to gather insights for drafting improved tax legislation on DeFi transactions. &lt;br /&gt;
The consultation aims to establish a framework that aligns taxation on crypto assets involved in DeFi transactions with their underlying economic substance....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-considers-taxation-revisions-for-defi-lending-staking-activities-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: UK Considers Taxation Revisions for DeFi Lending and Staking Activities – Here's The Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/uk-considers-taxation-revisions-for-defi-lending-staking-activities-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112504/271865/judge-g76ff89d7f-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185047"/></item><item><title>FTX's Final Days: SkyBridge Founder Scaramucci Discusses Meeting with Bankman-Fried in Bahamas</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftxs-final-days-skybridge-founder-scaramucci-discusses-meeting-with-bankman-fried-in-bahamas.htm</link><description>SkyBridge Capital founder Anthony Scaramucci has spoken about his visit to the Bahamas to meet Sam Bankman-Fried, the disgraced CEO of now-defunct crypto exchange FTX, during the firm's final days. &lt;br /&gt;
In early November last year, Scaramucci flew to the Bahamas to personally talk to Bankman-Fried after it was revealed that the now-bankrupt exchange might be on shaky financial grounds, he said during Consensus 2023 conference on Thursday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftxs-final-days-skybridge-founder-scaramucci-discusses-meeting-with-bankman-fried-in-bahamas.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX's Final Days: SkyBridge Founder Scaramucci Discusses Meeting with Bankman-Fried in Bahamas&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftxs-final-days-skybridge-founder-scaramucci-discusses-meeting-with-bankman-fried-in-bahamas.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112505/271859/sam-bankman-fried-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2601250"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Binance to Begin Japan Operations, Millennials are Dominant Crypto Enthusiast Group, Canadian Police Issue Warnings After a $7.5M Scam, Hamas Stops Crypto Donations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-binance-begin-japan-operations-millennials-are-dominant-crypto-enthusiast-group-canadian-police-issue-warnings-after-75m-scam-hamas-stops-crypto-donations.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-binance-begin-japan-operations-millennials-are-dominant-crypto-enthusiast-group-canadian-police-issue-warnings-after-75m-scam-hamas-stops-crypto-donations.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Binance to Begin Japan Operations, Millennials are Dominant Crypto Enthusiast Group, Canadian Police Issue Warnings After a $7.5M Scam, Hamas Stops Crypto Donations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Japan</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Canada</category><category>Scam</category><category>Police</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Donations</category><category>Palestine</category><category>JPMorgan</category><category>Federal Reserve</category><category>AI</category><category>Market</category><category>FBI</category><category>FTX</category><category>Mining</category><category>Core Scientific</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-crypto-binance-begin-japan-operations-millennials-are-dominant-crypto-enthusiast-group-canadian-police-issue-warnings-after-75m-scam-hamas-stops-crypto-donations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112481/271807/adobestock-andranik123-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="75079"/></item><item><title>Anna Stone, Web3 at eToro and Director of GoodDollar.org, on Universal Basic Income (UBI) and Web3 | Ep. 225</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/anna-stone-web3-at-etoro-director-of-gooddollarorg-universal-basic-income-ubi-web3-ep-225.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com ,Anna Stone, Web3 at eToro and Director of GoodDollar.org, talks about universal basic income, Web3 Open source code, and the future of financial inclusion....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/anna-stone-web3-at-etoro-director-of-gooddollarorg-universal-basic-income-ubi-web3-ep-225.htm"&gt;Read More: Anna Stone, Web3 at eToro and Director of GoodDollar.org, on Universal Basic Income (UBI) and Web3 | Ep. 225&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/anna-stone-web3-at-etoro-director-of-gooddollarorg-universal-basic-income-ubi-web3-ep-225.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/112493/271836/anna-stone-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="112696"/></item></channel></rss>
