<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:29:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Launches Bitcoin Transaction Accelerator and Teases Layer-2 Solution</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-launches-bitcoin-transaction-accelerator-and-teases-layer-2-solution/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNB Chain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255545</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/binance_bitcoin_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The world’s largest crypto exchange Binance launched a transaction accelerator for Bitcoin miners.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Binance is also preparing a BNB Chain layer-2 scaling solution to improve network transaction speeds and costs.</p>
<p>Separately, the firm announced on June 15 that Binance Pool has launched a “Bitcoin Transaction Accelerator.”</p>
<p>The new solution will allow users to confirm their transactions on the Bitcoin network quicker regardless of any potential network congestion issues, it <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/binance-pool-launches-btc-transaction-accelerator-98c505511bfc489997cf3eb2318c7953" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">noted</a>.</p>
<p>Binance Pool is the exchange’s service platform dedicated to improving the income of BTC miners.</p>
<h2>Binance Teasing a Layer-2</h2>
<p>The Bitcoin network has struggled under demand for block space recently amid the BRC-20 memecoin minting and ordinal inscriptions craze.</p>
<p>In May, regular users suffered from high transaction fees and a backlog of unconfirmed transactions in the Bitcoin mempool.</p>
<p>The new transaction accelerator will only be available for verified Binance Pool users.</p>
<p>Also on June 15, BNB Chain posted a short video teasing a new layer-2 solution. It said the new offering would be “coming soon” on June 19, but no further details were provided.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="und">19.6.23 <a href="https://t.co/R8ZLTNt4kS" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/R8ZLTNt4kS</a></p>
<p>— BNB Chain (@BNBCHAIN) <a href="https://twitter.com/BNBCHAIN/status/1669253419587227649?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 15, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Some in the crypto community <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoExpert101/status/1669269753335017475" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">suggested</a> that BNB Chain will <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/polygon-launches-zkevm-scaling-solution-for-web3-adoption/" data-wpel-link="internal">emulate Polygon</a> and launch a zkEVM for layer-2 chains.</p>
<p>A zero-knowledge Ethereum Virtual Machine is a fully compatible layer-2 solution that can seamlessly integrate with Ethereum’s smart contract ecosystem.</p>
<p>Binance is currently embroiled in a battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, which sued the firm last week for violating securities laws, among other alleged misdemeanors.</p>
<h2>BNB Price Outlook</h2>
<p>The Binance native token BNB has had a roller-coaster ride since the company came under fire from <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-coinbase-and-binance-lawsuits-super-bullish-for-btc-and-eth-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">American regulators</a>.</p>
<p>The asset fell to an intraday low of $231 before recovering to trade at $236 at the time of writing. It has lost 22.6% since the SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-ceos-see-wealth-crushed-after-secs-twin-lawsuits/" data-wpel-link="internal">sued the firm</a> on June 6.</p>
<p>BNB is currently down 65.5% from its all-time high of $686 on May 10, 2021. Despite the regulatory war on exchanges, BNB has fared much better than a lot of its brethren. Many of the altcoins, especially those related to DeFi, are down 90% from their peak prices.</p>
<p>Crypto markets, in general, remain flat on the day, with total capitalization at $1.07 trillion at the time of writing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-launches-bitcoin-transaction-accelerator-and-teases-layer-2-solution/" rel="nofollow">Binance Launches Bitcoin Transaction Accelerator and Teases Layer-2 Solution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Kwon&#8217;s Detention in Montenegro Could be Extended by Another 6 Months (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwons-detention-in-montenegro-could-be-extended-by-another-6-months-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 21:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255560</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/ezgif.com-gif-maker.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/ezgif.com-gif-maker.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[There could be some relief for the Korean developer, though, as his lawyers tried to drop charges filed by the US SEC.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of Montenegro reportedly consider extending Do Kwon&#8217;s custody in the country for another six months before taking an official decision on his possible extradition. The homeland of Terraform Labs&#8217; co-founder &#8211; South Korea &#8211; and the world&#8217;s biggest economy &#8211; the United States of America &#8211; have both requested his deportation.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Montenegrin police arrested the 31-year-old developer in March this year after he was supposedly on the run for several months, changing multiple hiding locations. He faces numerous fraud charges and is accused of having a hand in last year&#8217;s LUNA/UST collapse. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Kwon&#8217;s Stay in Europe to Be Extended?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Marija Rakovic &#8211; adviser for public relations of the High Court of Montenegro &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.slobodnaevropa.org/a/kralj-kriptovaluta-pritvor-crna-gora/32460870.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">confirmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to a local media outlet that Kwon received a detention order of half a year. During that period, the magistrates will decide whether to extradite the former crypto tycoon to South Korea. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities of the Asian country have insisted on his deportation, alleging he played a significant role in </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/here-is-what-happened-to-luna-and-why-the-price-can-continue-crashing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">the Terra crash</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> last year that prompted multi-billion dollar losses and undermined the entire digital asset sector. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The USA has also requested Kwon&#8217;s extradition. The US SEC previously asserted that Terraform Labs and its co-founder had orchestrated a massive crypto scam by offering and selling unregistered securities through the use of digital currencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">American prosecutors </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-accused-of-running-a-crypto-fraud-by-american-prosecutors-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">pressed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> charges, too, labeling Kwon as the main culprit behind the catastrophe. The officials accused him of committing securities fraud, commodities fraud, as well as conspiracy and demanded a proper punishment.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The legal problems for the South Korean do not stop here. Upon his arrest at the Podgorica airport in March, he was carrying a falsified passport and forged travel documents. A hearing on the matter held in the Basic Court of Podgorica is scheduled for June 16. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, Kwon will have to answer questions regarding his possible connection with Milojko Spajic &#8211; former Minister of Finance of Montenegro and current leader of the political party Europe Now. The National Security Council disclosed that the individuals had been friends for years, and Kwon financed some of Spajic&#8217;s political campaigns.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Could the US SEC Drop Charges?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The law firm Dentons, which represents Terraform Labs, recently tried to alleviate some of Kwon&#8217;s troubles by eliminating its legal battle with the US SEC. The attorneys filed a motion, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IV7nIPmmdfi3nIPfbS5PtKq0XsVxV6szC4cI7t3PL9Q/edit" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claiming</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that UST (the algorithmic stablecoin developed by the blockchain firm) is not a security, meaning the regulator should dismiss charges. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The defense, represented by Douglas Henkin, maintained the asset was designed for &#8220;practical purposes and commerce, not as an investment.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;By design &#8230; it&#8217;s pegged one to one to the dollar; it&#8217;s designed not to fluctuate. That&#8217;s for commerce &#8230; that&#8217;s a consumptive use.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The attorney went further, comparing the stablecoin to Bitcoin, suggesting UST was &#8220;controlled by a decentralized group through the LUNA token.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Devon Staren &#8211; a representative of the SEC &#8211; said the agency has been &#8220;simply enforcing existing laws.&#8221; She noted that the analysis of tokens expands beyond them and touches upon the ecosystems they are part of. Staren also gave her two cents on LUNA, claiming it is &#8220;merely a piece of code.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Judge Rakoff&#8217;s decision on whether the motion will be approved or dismissed is expected in mid-July.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/do-kwons-detention-in-montenegro-could-be-extended-by-another-6-months-report/" rel="nofollow">Do Kwon&#8217;s Detention in Montenegro Could be Extended by Another 6 Months (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Resorts to Job Cuts as It Prepares for Long and Costly Litigation With SEC: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-resorts-to-job-cuts-as-it-prepares-for-long-and-costly-litigation-with-sec-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 18:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255580</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The regulator insists on a rulebook for crypto exchanges and their compliance with security laws.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a letter to employees, Binance said it foresees protracted and expensive litigation with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and asked Binance.US management to reduce the size of its workforce across the division.</p>
<p>The job-cut decision is likely to affect about 50 employees.</p>
<h2>Job Cuts at Binance.US</h2>
<p>A Bloomberg <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-15/binance-us-fires-workers-in-anticipation-of-costly-sec-fight" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> noted that a number of employees at Binance’s US affiliate have been laid off. While a firm spokesperson confirmed the lay-offs, the exact number of employees affected by the decision was not mentioned.</p>
<p>However, a Reuters report outlined that about 50 staff members have been affected.</p>
<p>Early this month, Binance.US said it was being cut off from the banking and payments partners. On June 9, the crypto exchange serving only American customers <a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleWire/status/1667002820258668545" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">suspended</a> USD deposits and asked users to withdraw their dollar deposits right away, given the SEC’s “extremely aggressive and intimidating tactics.”</p>
<p>More recently, Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao dismissed the notion that the company sold BTC and BNB and termed such <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-refutes-rumors-claiming-binance-sold-btc-bnb/" data-wpel-link="internal">rumors</a> on social media as FUD. CZ asserted that the firm even holds its “bag of FTT.”</p>
<h2>In a Crosshair With the SEC</h2>
<p>In its June 5 lawsuit, the SEC requested the court to freeze the assets and operations of Binance.US. However, the authorities <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-rejects-secs-request-to-freeze-binance-us-assets-orders-parties-to-compromise/" data-wpel-link="internal">denied</a> the SEC’s motion on June 14 and asked Binance.US and the agency to engage with each other and find a solution.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Shutting it down completely would create significant consequences not only for the company but for the digital asset markets in general. (Work it out) – The nitty-gritty of it is better handled by you than by me,” the court said.</p></blockquote>
<p>These developments signify that the sudden hardening of US regulators’ stance following the collapse of FTX in November 2022 has finally caught up with the industry’s top players. The US SEC filed lawsuits against Binance and Coinbase on June 5 and June 6, respectively.</p>
<p>The Commission&#8217;s charges against the duo included functioning as exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing houses without proper licenses. It charged Binance with running two unregistered securities – BNB and BUSD &#8211; and commingling customers&#8217; funds. The SEC argued that Binance and Coinbase allow trading in crypto tokens, which are unregistered securities.</p>
<p>The regulator wants the exchanges and tokens to abide by the guidelines that apply to securities. It means following the rulebook and making sufficient disclosure that help investors mitigate risks and make informed decisions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-resorts-to-job-cuts-as-it-prepares-for-long-and-costly-litigation-with-sec-report/" rel="nofollow">Binance.US Resorts to Job Cuts as It Prepares for Long and Costly Litigation With SEC: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Race: DAI Surpasses BUSD Amid Binance-SEC Regulatory Row</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-race-dai-surpasses-busd-amid-binance-sec-regulatory-row/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 17:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance USD (BUSD)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255573</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BUSD_DAI.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BUSD_DAI.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DAI is now the third-largest stablecoin trailing behind Tether (USDT) and USDC Coin (USDC). ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DAI stablecoin, with a circulation of around $4.6 billion, has surpassed BUSD amidst mounting legal troubles for the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange, Binance.</p>
<p>The market capitalization of BUSD has declined to $4.3 billion following the regulatory drama that started earlier this year.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from CoinMarketcap, BUSD circulation is down over 70% since the beginning of the year. During the same period, the circulation of DAI has also retraced but by only 20%.</li>
<li>BUSD was launched in 2019 under the umbrella of Binance’s &#8216;Project Venus.&#8217; Although the crypto exchange does not issue the stablecoin, it has been on a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-will-happen-to-binance-if-sec-manages-to-kill-busd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">downward</a> spiral for several months now.</li>
<li>The first major blow to BUSD&#8217;s trajectory was Paxos&#8217; move to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-paxos-will-stop-minting-binance-usd-busd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">stop</a> minting the stablecoin at the end of February at the direction of the US New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS).</li>
<li>In March, the Commodities Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) filed suit against the exchange for improper licensure and offering US consumers the wrong financial products.</li>
<li>The subsequent lawsuit by the SEC against Binance forced the crypto exchange to <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1668142704105259009" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">delist</a> eight BUSD trading pairs from its margin trading platform.</li>
<li>While BUSD has shown impressive resilience in the face of turbulence as it managed to maintain its position among the top three most dominant stablecoins for several months, however, the recent surge in burn rate finally pushed its supply below that of DAI.</li>
<li>Zooming out, the persistent regulatory attacks on the industry have translated into a decline in the whole stablecoin market, which can be viewed as a sign of capital draining from the digital asset space and a troubling trend.</li>
<li>This week&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-cto-paolo-ardoino-alleviates-usdt-de-peg-scares/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">deviation</a> of USDT from the $1 peg further fueled FUD narratives, but Tether&#8217;s CTO reassured users that the company is ready to redeem any amount.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stablecoin-race-dai-surpasses-busd-amid-binance-sec-regulatory-row/" rel="nofollow">Stablecoin Race: DAI Surpasses BUSD Amid Binance-SEC Regulatory Row</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlackRock Files for Bitcoin Spot ETF, BTC Dropped to 3-Month Low as Fed Pauses Interest Rate Hikes: This Week’s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-for-bitcoin-spot-etf-btc-dropped-to-3-month-low-as-fed-pauses-interest-rate-hikes-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 15:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlackRock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255665</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin_United_States.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BTC slumped to a three-month low after the Fed's latest move on the interest rates, but several altcoins have plummeted by over 20% weekly. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There aren&#8217;t too many favorable developments within the cryptocurrency community lately. It all started last Monday when the US SEC decided to begin a legal battle against Binance and doubled down on its crackdown against large crypto exchanges by suing Coinbase the very next day as well.</p>
<p>Expectedly, these rather unexpected events led to massive price crashes for the majority of crypto assets. Nevertheless, many managed to recover most losses by the end of last week, but it all changed precisely seven days ago.</p>
<p>As Friday came to its end and Saturday approached, numerous digital assets, mostly altcoins that were mentioned in the SEC&#8217;s lawsuits for being unregistered securities, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bloodbath-the-reasons-behind-sol-matic-ada-sand-crash-today/" data-wpel-link="internal">dumped</a> by double digits during a massive weekend bloodbath.</p>
<p>BTC and ETH were spared to an extent, perhaps because they were not in the SEC&#8217;s filings. However, after a relatively quiet week in which even the US CPI <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-spikes-toward-26-5k-as-us-cpi-clocks-4-for-may/" data-wpel-link="internal">numbers</a> from Wednesday and the Fed&#8217;s decision to halt the interest rate hikes on Thursday didn&#8217;t shake the primary cryptocurrency &#8211; at first.</p>
<p>That all changed on Thursday evening when BTC slumped from over $26,000 to just below $24,800 to chart its <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-drops-to-3-month-low-below-25000-where-to-next/" data-wpel-link="internal">lowest price position in three months</a>. Most alts followed suit, with some, such as BNB, posting six-month lows.</p>
<p>Bitcoin managed to bounce off after the first positive news of the week. The cryptocurrency spiked by over a grand once the world&#8217;s largest asset manager &#8211; BlackRock &#8211; filed documents to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF in the States.</p>
<p>Looking at the charts on a weekly scale, though, the landscape seems quite painful. While bitcoin is down by a more modest 4%, some alts, such as EOS, ApeCoin, Flow, Polygon, Chiliz, Axie Infinity, THORChain, PEPE, The Sandbox, and many others, have shed double digits, dumping by up to 35% in seven days.</p>
<h2><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-201301" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg" alt="bears_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/bears_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Market Cap: $1,072B | 24H Vol: $33B | BTC Dominance: 46.1%</em></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>BTC: $25,500 (-4.2%) | ETH: $1,663 (-10%) | BNB: $235 (-10.1%)</em></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Better Not Miss</h2>
<p><strong>BlackRock Files Bitcoin Spot ETF Application, Taps Coinbase</strong>. As mentioned above, the positive highlight of the week came when the US behemoth BlackRock <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-bitcoin-spot-etf-application-taps-coinbase/" data-wpel-link="internal">filed</a> documents to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF in the States. Given the SEC&#8217;s views on the matter, though, the community doesn&#8217;t really hold its breath.</p>
<p><strong>Brazil’s President Empowers the Central Bank as Crypto Regulator</strong>. While the United States still fails to provide clear guidelines on the crypto industry and even which regulator is supposed to do so, Brazil&#8217;s president <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazils-president-empowers-the-central-bank-as-crypto-regulator/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> the nation&#8217;s central bank to begin supervising the digital asset space.</p>
<p><strong>Miami Bitcoin-Loving Mayor Joins the US Presidential Race</strong>. The US presidential race is heating up, with new candidates popping up weekly. The latest <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/miami-bitcoin-loving-mayor-joins-the-us-presidential-race/" data-wpel-link="internal">to do so</a> is Francis Suarez &#8211; the current mayor of Miami, who is a keen supporter of BTC and has even invested in the asset.</p>
<p><strong>CZ Refutes Reports That Binance’s French Branch Was Under Investigation</strong>. CZ had a busy week having to quash false rumors. First, he refuted the speculations that his company began selling BTC and BNB. Just on Friday, he had to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-refutes-reports-that-binances-french-branch-was-under-investigation/" data-wpel-link="internal">rebut</a> a report that French authorities had started investigating Binance&#8217;s local branch.</p>
<p><strong>Judge Rejects SEC’s Request to Freeze Binance.US Assets, Orders Parties to Compromise</strong>. The first sparks on the Binance-SEC front began this week. The SEC requested an emergency asset freeze of Binance.US&#8217; holdings, but a US judge <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-rejects-secs-request-to-freeze-binance-us-assets-orders-parties-to-compromise/" data-wpel-link="internal">rejected</a> the motion and ordered both parties to find a more fitting solution.</p>
<p><strong>Bitcoin Trades Flat After Federal Reserve Pauses Rate Hikes</strong>. As many expected, the US Federal Reserve decided to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-trades-flat-after-federal-reserve-pauses-rate-hikes/" data-wpel-link="internal">pause</a> the interest rate hike policy after numerous consecutive increases. While BTC indeed remained relatively flat at first, the asset tumbled in the following hours.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blackrock-files-for-bitcoin-spot-etf-btc-dropped-to-3-month-low-as-fed-pauses-interest-rate-hikes-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">BlackRock Files for Bitcoin Spot ETF, BTC Dropped to 3-Month Low as Fed Pauses Interest Rate Hikes: This Week’s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CZ Refutes Reports That Binance&#8217;s French Branch Was Under Investigation</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cz-refutes-reports-that-binances-french-branch-was-under-investigation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[France]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255647</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BinanceFrance.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/BinanceFrance.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance's French division remains the company's "flagship center in Europe," reassured CZ.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Changpeng Zhao, alongside another company spokesperson, refuted the recent reports from French media that Binance was under investigation in the country for alleged money laundering.</p>
<p>The company&#8217;s CEO explained that such &#8220;surprise inspections&#8221; are the norm in the European country for both banks and now crypto businesses.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the <a href="https://www.lemonde.fr/pixels/article/2023/06/16/binance-principale-plate-forme-mondiale-d-echange-de-cryptomonnaies-visee-par-une-enquete-en-france_6177876_4408996.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> from local media Le Monde, Binance has gone under the scope of the French authorities for failing in its anti-money laundering obligations as well as canvassing local customers before receiving its regulatory license.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The investigation is about, on one hand, the unauthorized practice of the profession of virtual assets service provider, and, on the other, about aggravated money-laundering,&#8221; &#8211; reads a statement seen by Le Monde.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In his typical style, Binance&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Changpeng Zhao &#8211; posted the well-known &#8220;4&#8221; on Twitter, suggesting the latest developments are yet more fake and sensational news targeting his company.</li>
<li>He explained that such &#8220;no advance notice on-site inspections of regulated businesses are the norm, for banks, and now for crypto, too.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. FUD.</p>
<p>In France, surprise (no advanced notice) on-site inspections of regulated businesses are the norm, for banks, and now for crypto too.</p>
<p>The surprise visit for Binance France happened a couple of weeks ago. It&#8217;s not &#8220;news&#8221;. Binance France cooperated fully.</p>
<p>Binance also… <a href="https://t.co/xdbLc5jXBW" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/xdbLc5jXBW</a></p>
<p>— CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f536.png" alt="🔶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Binance (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1669690219329716224?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 16, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>The other massage coming from the official Binance Twitter channel said the company had such an on-site visit last week. However, Binance continues to be &#8220;fully collaborative&#8221; with the relevant authorities.</li>
<li>The company has been put under the scope of US watchdogs as the SEC filed a lawsuit against it last week. More recently, the firm had to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-exits-netherlands-after-failing-to-secure-vasp-license/" data-wpel-link="internal">wind down</a> its business operations in The Netherlands after failing to secure the needed license.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-refutes-reports-that-binances-french-branch-was-under-investigation/" rel="nofollow">CZ Refutes Reports That Binance&#8217;s French Branch Was Under Investigation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presale Token CHANCER Raises Impressive $214K During the First 24 Hours</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/presale-token-chancer-raises-impressive-214k-during-the-first-24-hours/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255469</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-12.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-12.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Chancer has entered the fast-paced worlds of blockchain and online betting with an innovative new project that recently launched its presale. The uptake of tokens has been so fast among online betting fans and crypto investors that the first 24 hours of the CHANCER presale raised an impressive $214K. Hoping to raise $15 million during [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chancer has entered the fast-paced worlds of blockchain and online betting with an innovative new project that recently launched its presale. The uptake of tokens has been so fast among online betting fans and crypto investors that the first 24 hours of the CHANCER presale raised an impressive $214K.</p>
<p>Hoping to raise $15 million during the 12-stage presale event, Chancer has gotten off to an impressive start. Investors are flocking in droves to take advantage.</p>
<h2><strong>The Chancer Presale: What You Need to Know</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=cryptopotato" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Chancer</a> is offering bettors a new way to participate in online prediction markets with its fully decentralized peer-to-peer (P2P) model, which will place control of betting markets in the hands of the users. To enable this, the platform won’t rely on a centralized body such as a bookmaker to set markets and odds. Instead, the platform will empower users to create bespoke markets that aren’t slanted in the bookies’ favor.</p>
<p>To further illustrate the potential of the Chancer presale, the betting industry — valued at $60 billion in 2022 — is projected to grow to more than <a href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/press-release/global-online-gambling-market" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$150 billion by 2030</a>. Chancer&#8217;s team believes their platform is ideally positioned to grab a share of this growing market by offering a different approach in the online betting world.</p>
<p>During the Chancer presale, the token price will climb from its launch price of $0.01 to $0.021. Interested investors, therefore, have a limited time to grab their tokens at the lowest possible price. What can they expect for their money?</p>
<h2><strong>What is Chancer?</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=cryptopotato" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Chancer</a> is the world’s first decentralized online betting predictions market platform that will enable users to create small bets with friends and work colleagues or join huge, global, crowdfunded bets. Chancer facilitates and supports users in creating, taking on, managing, and fulfilling custom bets on bespoke markets of their choosing.</p>
<p>All users will have the opportunity to create odds on any number of potential outcomes and events, marking out the revolutionary nature of the Chancer platform. This is made possible by harnessing the power of blockchain technology. The platform’s foundations will have complete transparency, including open-source platform code and a public ledger that records transactions and enables a comprehensive trustless P2P online betting platform.</p>
<p>There are no bookmakers setting markets and weighing the odds in their favor. This means that Chancer’s users can deal directly with others, participating with the knowledge that they have the power in their hands.</p>
<h2><strong>How Does CHANCER Work?</strong></h2>
<p>The native CHANCER token fuels the entire ecosystem, from functionality to development. The token is used to create, lay, and settle all bets and also provides users with the currency for depositing and withdrawing funds. All transactions are executed by the platform’s slick Certik-verified smart contracts protocol.</p>
<p>The Chancer platform has been designed with the integration of Google’s cutting-edge <a href="https://webrtc.org/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">WebRTC</a> software which enables users to keep track of their bets in real-time while communicating with other users worldwide.</p>
<p>To ensure fairness, all bets are overseen by a team of impartial moderators, meaning that users can play safe knowing that any bets will be fully paid out free from disputes. This opens up a massive world of possibilities for the P2P predictions marketplace.</p>
<p>Chancer claims to offer investors and online gamblers something unique in the market thanks to its P2P capability. It also removes the centralized “house,” or bookmaker, that stands to profit substantially from other online betting apps. Allowing users to access custom bets and lay directly against each other on various markets is supposed to make Chancer an appealing platform for a much more diverse audience than those purely attracted to sports betting.</p>
<p>With extensive utility and eventual governance rights delivered to token holders, CHANCER combines deflationary tokenomics with a total fixed supply. The result will be that supply will be scarcer.</p>
<p>Chancer is unique in many ways, not least because it stands at the apex of two vastly growing industries, Web3, and online betting. If the platform’s appeal and community grows, the expected high daily volume levels could also drive the value of CHANCER higher.</p>
<p>The Chancer presale represents an investment opportunity in an exciting sector that can also serve as means of portfolio diversification.</p>
<p><strong>You can take part in the CHANCER presale </strong><a href="https://chancer.com/?utm_source=media&amp;utm_medium=artc&amp;utm_campaign=cryptopotato" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>here</strong></a><strong>.</strong></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/presale-token-chancer-raises-impressive-214k-during-the-first-24-hours/" rel="nofollow">Presale Token CHANCER Raises Impressive $214K During the First 24 Hours</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arthur Hayes Claims Removal of US Retail Investors From Crypto Capital Market is Misplaced</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arthur-hayes-claims-removal-of-us-retail-investors-from-crypto-capital-market-is-misplaced/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BitMEX]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[China]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255557</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Arthur_Hayes-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Arthur_Hayes-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder pointed out the irrelevancy of US crypto traders and why the bull market baton will shift from the US to China.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ongoing regulatory enforcement actions are threatening to drive US crypto businesses offshore. The implications of such a shift for the country&#8217;s economy are significant, something that has translated into declining crypto prices, making investors even more jittery.</p>
<p>While the market&#8217;s concerns regarding the potential removal of the US retail investor from the crypto capital markets are palpable, Arthur Hayes believes the fear is misplaced.</p>
<h2>Elimination of US Retail Investors From Crypto</h2>
<p>In a recent <a href="https://blog.bitmex.com/fungible/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">blog post,</a> the former BitMEX CEO Arthur Hayes said retail investors selling crypto alongside US-domiciled institutions is not wise. He explained that it is completely irrelevant whether the mass affluent and below can own or trade Bitcoin or a subset of &#8220;shitcoins.&#8221; Even if brokerage platform Robinhood still allowed them to trade &#8220;XYZ shitcoin,&#8221; they wouldn’t have the available capital to purchase it anyway.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The capital of the rich, on the other hand, is much more plentiful, and it’s fungible across the entire globe &#8211; all thanks to a host of intermediaries that cater to the American wealthy and will dutifully do whatever they are told as long as they receive a phat commission.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Hayes pointed out that the US population accounts for approximately 4% of that of the world. While &#8220;this is an extremely small slice of the pie,&#8221; the percentage of wealthy individuals relative to everyone else across the globe is quite high. Hence, investors care about what such a small population does with their money.</p>
<p>If the US government decides to distribute another round of &#8220;freshly printed money&#8221; &#8211; as they did with the COVID stimulus but in the form of interest &#8211; it will not go to the mass affluent, who have little to no savings. Hayes said the funds will instead flow straight to the top 10%, or just the top 1%, who hold the majority of wealth in America. This money will then be deployed into &#8220;various forms of hard assets and stores of value.&#8221;</p>
<p>This rich cohort, which the BitMEX founder deems as &#8220;the most overbanked people in the world,&#8221; has access to any and all financial assets traded globally, even if they are American. This essentially means that they can easily buy it from firms Cumberland, NYDIG, and the OTC trading desks of the US-domiciled crypto exchanges like Coinbase and Kraken, which specializes in selling crypto to &#8220;rich folks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Hayes said selling crypto when the market is at the bottom after buying on top is unwise because it&#8217;s important to look into Asia, as China and Japan’s silent currency war for export competitiveness is going to drive a significant amount of credit issuance by the second largest economy. This credit issuance is expected to ultimately weaken the yuan and prompt some of China’s mass affluent to transfer their capital elsewhere, including crypto.</p>
<h2>In Comes China</h2>
<p>Despite China&#8217;s blanket ban on cryptocurrencies, traders are slowly making a comeback through the financial pipes of Hong Kong. Earlier this month, the city-state&#8217;s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-to-launch-hong-kong-venue-on-june-1-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">began</a> accepting applications for crypto trading platform licenses.</p>
<p>A Hong Kong lawmaker even invited San Francisco-based Coinbase to come and register in the region. More recently, the Hong Kong Monetary Authority was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hong-kong-pressures-banks-to-accept-crypto-exchanges-as-clients-ft/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> to have been pressuring major financial institutions such as &#8211; HSBC, Standard Chartered, and Bank of China &#8211; to accept crypto clients.</p>
<p>The act of laying out the red carpet for global crypto exchanges that have been facing regulatory scrutiny in the West is yet another factor that Hayes believes will reignite the market at the same time the &#8220;broke-ass American mass affluent are effectively shut out.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arthur-hayes-claims-removal-of-us-retail-investors-from-crypto-capital-market-is-misplaced/" rel="nofollow">Arthur Hayes Claims Removal of US Retail Investors From Crypto Capital Market is Misplaced</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>WIN NFT HERO Coming Soon to the APENFT Launchpad with Limited Release of New HERO Mystery Box</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/win-nft-hero-coming-soon-to-the-apenft-launchpad-with-limited-release-of-new-hero-mystery-box/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255633</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1_1686913383XXqJfKzbhl.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/image1_1686913383XXqJfKzbhl.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, June 16th, 2023] WIN NFT HERO, a strategy game built on Tron, has been garnering a lot of attention. Following the official launch of the game’s v2.0 and the new HERO system in April 2023, WIN NFT HERO officially launched v2.1 with an open beta test on June 1. Along [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, June 16th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p>WIN NFT HERO, a strategy game built on Tron, has been garnering a lot of attention. Following the official launch of the game’s v2.0 and the new HERO system in April 2023, WIN NFT HERO officially launched v2.1 with an open beta test on June 1. Along with that news, an official announcement was made that the S1 Million Dollar Season event will be launched on June 15.</p>
<p>According to the official announcement, WIN NFT HERO S1 season game scenario is a PvP points tournament. Only players with 3N and above quality heroes can participate. WIN NFT HERO&#8217;s S1 season event includes an abundance of $NFT, $WIN, $WNH and high-quality NFT rewards.</p>
<p>New players who want to participate in the WIN NFT HERO S1 season must first obtain a HERO NFT. The cost of the WIN NFT HERO depends upon what version it is. There are 5 qualities to choose from, ranging from low to high: N (green), R (blue), SR (purple), SSR (orange), and UR (red). The higher the quality of the HERO, the stronger the HERO is.</p>
<p>Currently, the WIN NFT HERO game contains a total of 58 heroes in 11 lineups, 19 of which are new heroes added when v2.0 was launched. Since the new heroes have different attributes, skills, bond effects, etc., players with new heroes will be able to experiment with more strategic combinations as well as have a greater advantage in matchmaking.</p>
<p>To celebrate the upcoming S1 season and help players achieve better scores, WIN NFT HERO announced that a new Hero Mystery Box sale will go live on APENFT Launchpad on June 16, 2023. 200 Hero Mystery Boxes will be available, priced at 10 USDD per box. Each box will include five new heroes, distributed according to rarity.</p>
<p>These limited v2.1 HERO Mystery Boxes are exclusive to the APENFT Launchpad. As the S1 season approaches, expect these highly scarce new HERO NFTs to be even more popular.</p>
<h2>About WIN NFT HERO</h2>
<p>WIN NFT HERO is a &#8220;GameFi + NFT&#8221; strategy game built on the TRON blockchain. It offers all kinds of heroes, equipment, and other NFT in-game assets for individual players to enjoy as they play, earn, and collect.</p>
<p>WIN NFT HERO requires players to match different strategic formations according to hero attributes in order to win on the battlefield. The goal of WIN NFT HERO is simple – to unite players around the world through blockchain gaming with a shared economy that transcends real-world values. This “GameFi + NFT” game provides players with an unprecedented experience in immersive entertainment.</p>
<p>Learn more about WIN NFT HERO at their:</p>
<p><strong>Website</strong>：<a href="https://www.winnfthero.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://www.winnfthero.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>Twitter</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/winnfthero" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://twitter.com/winnfthero</a></p>
<h2>About APENFT Marketplace</h2>
<p>APENFT Marketplace is an NFT trading platform native to the TRON blockchain, launched by the APENFT Foundation, with additional support from the world’s largest distributed storage system BitTorrent File System (BTFS). It provides a range of NFT-related services, including NFT minting, trading, and creation. By converting more artworks as NFTs and bringing more GameFi projects on the blockchain, APENFT Marketplace not only makes art unique and eternal but also boosts transparency in the exchange and transmission. With higher speed and zero transaction fees, APENFT Marketplace helps boost a more diverse ecosystem and a stronger community.</p>
<p>The APENFT utility token ($NFT) is the official governance token issued by the APENFT Foundation. It is a decentralized digital asset that is backed by TRC-20 protocols and serves as proof of rights on APENFT. With the designation of TRON as the national blockchain for the Commonwealth of Dominica, $NFT has been granted statutory status as authorized digital currency and medium of exchange in the country, effective on October 7th, 2022. Currently, $NFT is traded on over 27 CEXs and DEXs, including OKX, Huobi, KuCoin, Bybit, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and SunSwap.</p>
<p>Learn more about APENFT at their:</p>
<p><strong>Website</strong>: <a href="https://apenft.io/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://apenft.io/</a></p>
<p><strong>Twitter</strong>: <a href="https://twitter.com/apenftorg" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">https://twitter.com/apenftorg</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/win-nft-hero-coming-soon-to-the-apenft-launchpad-with-limited-release-of-new-hero-mystery-box/" rel="nofollow">WIN NFT HERO Coming Soon to the APENFT Launchpad with Limited Release of New HERO Mystery Box</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BetFury and BurgerCities Collaboration Allows Users to Get 100 Free NFTs</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/betfury-and-burgercities-collaboration-allows-users-to-get-100-free-nfts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 10:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255618</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] On June 13, the partnership between BetFury, an ecosystem of crypto products for entertainment and additional income, and BurgerCities, a blockchain-enabled play-to-earn game, was launched. Anyone who joins the event can receive special: prizes, branded NFTs, promo codes, and bonuses. During the event on the BurgerCities platform, everyone will [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>On June 13, the partnership between BetFury, an ecosystem of crypto products for entertainment and additional income, and BurgerCities, a blockchain-enabled play-to-earn game, was launched. Anyone who joins the event can receive special: prizes, branded NFTs, promo codes, and bonuses.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255620" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury.png" alt="BetFury" width="3840" height="2160" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury.png 3840w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-300x169.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-1024x576.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-768x432.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-1536x864.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-2048x1152.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BetFury-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 3840px) 100vw, 3840px" /></a></p>
<p>During the event on the BurgerCities platform, everyone will be able to relax at the Burger Bar, chat with friends, and see the exhibition prepared by partners.</p>
<p>BetFury platform will become a part of the game with BetFury-related activities that organizers won’t disclose. But participants will be able to find out during the gameplay.</p>
<p>At the end of the collaboration, BetFury will organize a giveaway where users will have a chance to win 1 of 100 branded NFTs. Their owners will receive not only unique content but also additional prizes. The platform will credit free spins and bets to the holders&#8217; balance. Rewards will be transferred automatically to users registered at BetFury.</p>
<p>In the future, the collaboration will bring informative AMA sessions and many other interesting features.</p>
<p>You can find out how to get additional promo codes for 20 Free Spins and Free Bet on BetFury and BurgerCities social networks</p>
<h2>About BetFury</h2>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://betfury.io/promo/welcome-pack-bonus?utm_source=media&amp;&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;&amp;utm_campaign=burgercities_pr" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BetFury</a> &#8211; an ecosystem of crypto products for entertainment and additional income.</li>
<li>The platform provides BFG staking APY up to 50% and 50+ cryptocurrencies for playing.</li>
<li>The company regularly holds events with impressive prize pools, distributes bonuses on social media, and is constantly working on earning opportunities on the platform.</li>
<li><a href="https://betfury.io/promo/welcome-pack-bonus?utm_source=media&amp;&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;&amp;utm_campaign=burgercities_pr" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Sign up</a> for 1,000 Free Spins and $3,500.</li>
</ul>
<h2>About BurgerCities</h2>
<p><a href="https://burgercities.org/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">BurgerCities</a> is a one-stop MetaFi platform with a wide range of features, including its native token BURGER, a Decentralized Exchange (DEX), and Non-Fungible Tokens (NFT), which are made up of Heroes, Props, and Lands.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/betfury-and-burgercities-collaboration-allows-users-to-get-100-free-nfts/" rel="nofollow">BetFury and BurgerCities Collaboration Allows Users to Get 100 Free NFTs</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
