<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:51:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[5 Thrilling Augmented Reality Games Available To Play Right Now]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/5-thrilling-augmented-reality-games-available-to-play-right-now</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-257.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/5-thrilling-augmented-reality-games-available-to-play-right-now</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The interactive monster-collecting app Pokemon Go was a global phenomenon that increased awareness of the potential of augmented reality games, inspiring millions of people around the world to grab their mobile device and set off into the great outdoors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since then, the AR gaming genre has grown to encompass quite a few fresh ideas. AR games work by using the device&rsquo;s camera to superimpose 3D graphical elements onto the real world, as viewed on its display. The idea is to incorporate the user&rsquo;s physical surroundings into the gameplay, creating a surreal mixed reality experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AR games involve mapping the user&rsquo;s surroundings in order to overlay 3D virtual objects onto it. In the case of Pokemon Go, it meant users could get out and about, exploring their town or city in order to hunt for collectible Pokemon creatures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One key advantage of AR games is that they can be played on even the cheapest mobile phone, so there&rsquo;s no need to invest in an expensive and bulky VR headset. Simply grab your phone, switch the game on and explore your surroundings to try and complete the objectives.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world. Here&rsquo;s some of the hottest new AR games you can try today!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Angry Birds AR: Isle of Pigs
<p>This is pretty much as you would imagine an augmented reality version of the popular Angry Birds game to be. Launch the game and it sets up a structure on a nearby table that can be viewed through your phone&rsquo;s camera. Then, you use a slingshot to shoot those colorful, loveable Angry Birds at the structure in an attempt to destroy it and kill those nasty green pigs hiding inside. There are 70 different levels on the game, and many of the original characters from the popular franchise appear in it. The game is a couple of years old, but it works well and provides a very different and entertaining take on the classic Angry Birds experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Ingress Prime
<p>Created by Niantic, the developer of the original AR hit Pokemon Go, Ingress Prime is widely considered to be one of the best AR games ever made. In the game, the discovery of an unknown, transdimensional force known as Exotic Matter by a team of scientists at CERN resulted in the creation of two factions, the Enlightened and the Resistance. The Enlightened faction seeks to harness and embrace the power of XM to transcend humanity to a higher dimension. Meanwhile the Resistance sees XM as humanity&rsquo;s biggest threat, and is sworn to defend mankind by resisting the efforts of the Enlightened faction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ingress Prime uses your device&rsquo;s GPS to locate and interact with &ldquo;portals&rdquo; in real-world locations, found at points of interest where human creativity is expressed, such as statues, monuments, unique architecture and historic buildings. Players choose a faction then use the map to find nearby portals, and are tasked with &ldquo;hacking&rdquo; them and building them up so the other team can&rsquo;t get them. The game uses the portals as elements of a science fiction backstory along with a continuous open narrative provided through various forms of media.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;
Peer
<p>Launching this summer, Peer is the creator of a unique social network that&rsquo;s overlaid onto the real world, where users can explore physical locations and find information and digital objects amid their surroundings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s an extremely ambitious project that aims to bring AR to the masses by overlaying 3D graphics atop of the entire world. In some ways, it can be considered an enhanced version of Google Maps, enabling users to search for nearby restaurants for example. When they arrive at their chosen restaurant to grab a bite to eat, they may be able to pick up a coupon placed outside by the restaurant owner, entitling them to a free coffee. Peer can also be used by creators, such as NFT artists, tasking people to visit different locations to mint digital collectibles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Alternatively, a dinosaur museum can create huge, 3D dinosaurs that roam around the physical world outside their premises, enticing people to come and visit its exhibits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Jurassic World Alive
<p>Staying with the dinosaur theme, Jurassic World Alive enables players to get outside in the real world searching for various dinosaurs they need to collect. In some ways it&rsquo;s similar to Pokemon Go, with users having to search different locations to discover the most difficult to find dinosaurs. Once they collect a dinosaur, they can train it and breed it to create hybrid dinosaurs, and then use them to fight battles with other players nearby.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the game initially had a few bugs, the developer has seemingly ironed most of them out and it has built up a loyal player base. Players can even subscribe to the game to earn rewards, instead of spending money on in-app purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Zombies, Run!&nbsp;
<p>The extremely original Zombies, Run! is not so much a game as a gamified fitness app that uses AR to simulate zombies and scare people into running away from them. To play the game, you&rsquo;ll need some earbuds or headphones to listen to the audio as it narrates the story and tasks you with completing various missions while you're out and about on your daily jog. As the story progresses, there will be occasional interruptions by flesh-eating zombies that jump out of the shadows and chase after you, forcing you to start sprinting to outrun them. The game also works just as well on a treadmill.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Zombies, Run! cleverly merges AR elements with an enthralling audio story to motivate people to keep moving and it has proven incredibly effective and popular. The first four missions are available to play for free, and new ones can be unlocked either by paying for them, or by completing various challenges each week.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The interactive monster-collecting app Pokemon Go was a global phenomenon that increased awareness of the potential of augmented reality games, inspiring millions of people around the world to grab their mobile device and set off into the great outdoors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Since then, the AR gaming genre has grown to encompass quite a few fresh ideas. AR games work by using the device&rsquo;s camera to superimpose 3D graphical elements onto the real world, as viewed on its display. The idea is to incorporate the user&rsquo;s physical surroundings into the gameplay, creating a surreal mixed reality experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>AR games involve mapping the user&rsquo;s surroundings in order to overlay 3D virtual objects onto it. In the case of Pokemon Go, it meant users could get out and about, exploring their town or city in order to hunt for collectible Pokemon creatures.&nbsp;</p>
<p>One key advantage of AR games is that they can be played on even the cheapest mobile phone, so there&rsquo;s no need to invest in an expensive and bulky VR headset. Simply grab your phone, switch the game on and explore your surroundings to try and complete the objectives.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The potential of AR games has yet to be fully realized, but developers have already created lots of highly original apps to enhance our experiences in the physical world. Here&rsquo;s some of the hottest new AR games you can try today!&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Angry Birds AR: Isle of Pigs
<p>This is pretty much as you would imagine an augmented reality version of the popular Angry Birds game to be. Launch the game and it sets up a structure on a nearby table that can be viewed through your phone&rsquo;s camera. Then, you use a slingshot to shoot those colorful, loveable Angry Birds at the structure in an attempt to destroy it and kill those nasty green pigs hiding inside. There are 70 different levels on the game, and many of the original characters from the popular franchise appear in it. The game is a couple of years old, but it works well and provides a very different and entertaining take on the classic Angry Birds experience.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Ingress Prime
<p>Created by Niantic, the developer of the original AR hit Pokemon Go, Ingress Prime is widely considered to be one of the best AR games ever made. In the game, the discovery of an unknown, transdimensional force known as Exotic Matter by a team of scientists at CERN resulted in the creation of two factions, the Enlightened and the Resistance. The Enlightened faction seeks to harness and embrace the power of XM to transcend humanity to a higher dimension. Meanwhile the Resistance sees XM as humanity&rsquo;s biggest threat, and is sworn to defend mankind by resisting the efforts of the Enlightened faction.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Ingress Prime uses your device&rsquo;s GPS to locate and interact with &ldquo;portals&rdquo; in real-world locations, found at points of interest where human creativity is expressed, such as statues, monuments, unique architecture and historic buildings. Players choose a faction then use the map to find nearby portals, and are tasked with &ldquo;hacking&rdquo; them and building them up so the other team can&rsquo;t get them. The game uses the portals as elements of a science fiction backstory along with a continuous open narrative provided through various forms of media.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
&nbsp;
Peer
<p>Launching this summer, Peer is the creator of a unique social network that&rsquo;s overlaid onto the real world, where users can explore physical locations and find information and digital objects amid their surroundings.&nbsp;</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s an extremely ambitious project that aims to bring AR to the masses by overlaying 3D graphics atop of the entire world. In some ways, it can be considered an enhanced version of Google Maps, enabling users to search for nearby restaurants for example. When they arrive at their chosen restaurant to grab a bite to eat, they may be able to pick up a coupon placed outside by the restaurant owner, entitling them to a free coffee. Peer can also be used by creators, such as NFT artists, tasking people to visit different locations to mint digital collectibles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Alternatively, a dinosaur museum can create huge, 3D dinosaurs that roam around the physical world outside their premises, enticing people to come and visit its exhibits.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Jurassic World Alive
<p>Staying with the dinosaur theme, Jurassic World Alive enables players to get outside in the real world searching for various dinosaurs they need to collect. In some ways it&rsquo;s similar to Pokemon Go, with users having to search different locations to discover the most difficult to find dinosaurs. Once they collect a dinosaur, they can train it and breed it to create hybrid dinosaurs, and then use them to fight battles with other players nearby.&nbsp;</p>
<p>While the game initially had a few bugs, the developer has seemingly ironed most of them out and it has built up a loyal player base. Players can even subscribe to the game to earn rewards, instead of spending money on in-app purchases.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
Zombies, Run!&nbsp;
<p>The extremely original Zombies, Run! is not so much a game as a gamified fitness app that uses AR to simulate zombies and scare people into running away from them. To play the game, you&rsquo;ll need some earbuds or headphones to listen to the audio as it narrates the story and tasks you with completing various missions while you're out and about on your daily jog. As the story progresses, there will be occasional interruptions by flesh-eating zombies that jump out of the shadows and chase after you, forcing you to start sprinting to outrun them. The game also works just as well on a treadmill.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Zombies, Run! cleverly merges AR elements with an enthralling audio story to motivate people to keep moving and it has proven incredibly effective and popular. The first four missions are available to play for free, and new ones can be unlocked either by paying for them, or by completing various challenges each week.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Mainstream media blackout on introduction of new BRICS currency]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/mainstream-media-blackout-on-introduction-of-new-brics-currency</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/brics.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 10:08:34 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/mainstream-media-blackout-on-introduction-of-new-brics-currency</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Despite the earth shattering development of a new BRICS currency to rival the dollar, Western mainstream news media is generally silent on the matter.</p>
A rival reserve currency
<p>The hegemony of the US dollar as the world&rsquo;s reserve currency has remained intact since the Bretton Woods agreement in 1944. However, the average citizen in the West is probably not aware that a group of countries termed the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) is about to announce a new rival reserve currency, with the likelihood that it will be backed by gold.</p>
<p>The announcement is expected to take place at the BRICS summit, in late August, only a matter of weeks away, and none of the mainstream media outlets in the West have reported on what has the potential to be the biggest monetary change since Bretton Woods.</p>
Backlash against the dollar
<p>The weaponisation of the dollar in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine was seen by many countries as a move that could potentially be used against them in the future, and so a move away from the dollar has begun.</p>
<p>This rebellion against US hegemony has undoubtedly been led by Putin, but has the backing of the other BRICS nations and countries that are in the process of joining them, including Saudi Arabia, and the Gulf Cooperation Council among others.</p>
Gold backing
<p>Originally, the BRICS currency was to be backed by a basket of commodities, which included gold, but according to Alistair Mcleod, Head of Research at GoldMoney.com, this would probably not work, and therefore gold on its own is likely to be that backing.</p>
<p>Therefore, the flow of gold from West to East over recent decades can certainly be accounted for, along with the increase of gold mining production in China and Russia.</p>
<p>With as many as 41 countries either joining or expressing interest in joining the BRICS trading bloc, the combined populations and GDP would be equal to more than half of the world and would be far bigger than that of the Western alliance.</p>
The West needs to wake up
<p>This introduction of a new rival reserve currency is not likely to usurp the dollar&rsquo;s position any time soon. However, the attraction of a currency that is actually backed by a real asset, instead of the dollar, which is printed out of thin air and has no backing at all, might be anticipated to grow steadily over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Such a development should greatly alarm the West. Media blackouts on the situation should not be the alternative to free and open dialogues on such a critical evolution in the global monetary system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite the earth shattering development of a new BRICS currency to rival the dollar, Western mainstream news media is generally silent on the matter.</p>
A rival reserve currency
<p>The hegemony of the US dollar as the world&rsquo;s reserve currency has remained intact since the Bretton Woods agreement in 1944. However, the average citizen in the West is probably not aware that a group of countries termed the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China, South Africa) is about to announce a new rival reserve currency, with the likelihood that it will be backed by gold.</p>
<p>The announcement is expected to take place at the BRICS summit, in late August, only a matter of weeks away, and none of the mainstream media outlets in the West have reported on what has the potential to be the biggest monetary change since Bretton Woods.</p>
Backlash against the dollar
<p>The weaponisation of the dollar in response to the Russian invasion of Ukraine was seen by many countries as a move that could potentially be used against them in the future, and so a move away from the dollar has begun.</p>
<p>This rebellion against US hegemony has undoubtedly been led by Putin, but has the backing of the other BRICS nations and countries that are in the process of joining them, including Saudi Arabia, and the Gulf Cooperation Council among others.</p>
Gold backing
<p>Originally, the BRICS currency was to be backed by a basket of commodities, which included gold, but according to Alistair Mcleod, Head of Research at GoldMoney.com, this would probably not work, and therefore gold on its own is likely to be that backing.</p>
<p>Therefore, the flow of gold from West to East over recent decades can certainly be accounted for, along with the increase of gold mining production in China and Russia.</p>
<p>With as many as 41 countries either joining or expressing interest in joining the BRICS trading bloc, the combined populations and GDP would be equal to more than half of the world and would be far bigger than that of the Western alliance.</p>
The West needs to wake up
<p>This introduction of a new rival reserve currency is not likely to usurp the dollar&rsquo;s position any time soon. However, the attraction of a currency that is actually backed by a real asset, instead of the dollar, which is printed out of thin air and has no backing at all, might be anticipated to grow steadily over time.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Such a development should greatly alarm the West. Media blackouts on the situation should not be the alternative to free and open dialogues on such a critical evolution in the global monetary system.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Pressure Congress To Pass Crypto Law]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-lawmakers-pressure-congress-to-pass-crypto-law</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/america-tax-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:02:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/us-lawmakers-pressure-congress-to-pass-crypto-law</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Following SEC's victory over Ripple, several US lawmakers have called on Congress for regulatory clarity regarding the crypto industry.</p>
<p>As one of the lawmakers stated, &ldquo;Gary Gensler&rsquo;s SEC cannot continue to pursue its regulation by enforcement approach, which only harms investors and creates uncertainty.&rdquo;</p>
The Ripple vs SEC Case
<p>Following a lengthy 3-year court battle, the SEC-Ripple case has finally ended with a "partial victory" for the latter. As per the Southern District of New York Court's ruling, all XRP sales fall under three buckets &ndash;&nbsp; institutional sales, programmatic sales, and other distributions. While the SEC prevailed in the case of institutional sales, Ripple secured a favorable outcome regarding programmatic sales and other distributions. It should be noted that t the SEC still has the option to appeal the court's decisions in the future.</p>
The Lawmakers Respond
<p>Following the ruling, the Chairman of the House Financial Services Committee, Patrick McHenry (NC-10), and the Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee, Glenn &ldquo;GT&rdquo; Thompson (PA-15), issued a joint statement.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This decision underscores the need for Congress to provide clear rules of the road for the digital asset ecosystem&mdash;it&rsquo;s misguided to think otherwise. The ruling gives large institutional investors greater protections than everyday Americans. Outcomes like this happen when regulators force courts to make policy instead of Congress. Our comprehensive market structure legislation will give all investors, customers, and market participants the same longstanding protections found in traditional financial markets."</p>

<p>The lawmakers also noted the flaws in the Gensler-led SEC's regulatory approach since digital assets may not &ldquo;be inherently securities, but can be offered as part of an investment contract in certain circumstances, which our legislation acknowledges." The SEC's one-size-fits-all approach creates uncertainty and harms investors.</p>
The Lummis-Gillibrand Crypto Bill
<p>Echoing her colleagues' sentiments, Senator Cynthia Lummis urged to pass the Lummis-Gillibrand Responsible Financial Innovation Act, emphasizing the need for regulatory clarity. The bill primarily aims to pass authority over crypto regulation from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the Commodities Future Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following SEC's victory over Ripple, several US lawmakers have called on Congress for regulatory clarity regarding the crypto industry.</p>
<p>As one of the lawmakers stated, &ldquo;Gary Gensler&rsquo;s SEC cannot continue to pursue its regulation by enforcement approach, which only harms investors and creates uncertainty.&rdquo;</p>
The Ripple vs SEC Case
<p>Following a lengthy 3-year court battle, the SEC-Ripple case has finally ended with a "partial victory" for the latter. As per the Southern District of New York Court's ruling, all XRP sales fall under three buckets &ndash;&nbsp; institutional sales, programmatic sales, and other distributions. While the SEC prevailed in the case of institutional sales, Ripple secured a favorable outcome regarding programmatic sales and other distributions. It should be noted that t the SEC still has the option to appeal the court's decisions in the future.</p>
The Lawmakers Respond
<p>Following the ruling, the Chairman of the House Financial Services Committee, Patrick McHenry (NC-10), and the Chairman of the House Agriculture Committee, Glenn &ldquo;GT&rdquo; Thompson (PA-15), issued a joint statement.</p>

<p>&ldquo;This decision underscores the need for Congress to provide clear rules of the road for the digital asset ecosystem&mdash;it&rsquo;s misguided to think otherwise. The ruling gives large institutional investors greater protections than everyday Americans. Outcomes like this happen when regulators force courts to make policy instead of Congress. Our comprehensive market structure legislation will give all investors, customers, and market participants the same longstanding protections found in traditional financial markets."</p>

<p>The lawmakers also noted the flaws in the Gensler-led SEC's regulatory approach since digital assets may not &ldquo;be inherently securities, but can be offered as part of an investment contract in certain circumstances, which our legislation acknowledges." The SEC's one-size-fits-all approach creates uncertainty and harms investors.</p>
The Lummis-Gillibrand Crypto Bill
<p>Echoing her colleagues' sentiments, Senator Cynthia Lummis urged to pass the Lummis-Gillibrand Responsible Financial Innovation Act, emphasizing the need for regulatory clarity. The bill primarily aims to pass authority over crypto regulation from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to the Commodities Future Trading Commission (CFTC).</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[QED: A zk-Native blockchain capable of serving millions of concurrent users]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/qed-a-zk-native-blockchain-capable-of-serving-millions-of-concurrent-users</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/QED_1600-900_16893407309PBZdzJexR.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:00:50 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/qed-a-zk-native-blockchain-capable-of-serving-millions-of-concurrent-users</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Startup Open Asset Standards has recently announced QED, the world's first ZK 2.0 blockchain protocol. Unlike existing zero-knowledge blockchain protocols, QED has a novel state model which is horizontally scalable, meaning it is no longer limited by TPS restrictions that have previously prevented adoption of blockchain technologies in Web2 use cases such as social networks, traditional finance, and gaming.</p><p>Enabled by advances in fast recursive zero-knowledge proofs, QED is able to achieve this scale without compromising security or decentralization and proves all transactions end-to-end using proof recursion (verifying a zero-knowledge proof in a zero-knowledge proof ). This process of decentralized recursive proving culminates in a single block proof that can be verified by an Ethereum smart contract, making the protocol only reliant on the Proof of Math itself, rather than an incentive based consensus system vulnerable to collusion, hacking and misaligned incentives.</p><p>As the first blockchain capable of serving billions of users in a single block, QED does away with the need for a zk-VM by compiling smart contract functions directly to zero knowledge circuits, making it the first zk-Native blockchain. QED&rsquo;s novel approach to ZKP allows users to prove their own transactions on their own device in milliseconds, enabling a new privacy-centric internet where transactions are private by default and sensitive data never has to leave a user&rsquo;s device.</p><p>With its announcement of the QED Protocol, Open Asset Standards unveiled QED's official Dapen Smart Contract IDE. With Dapen, Web2 developers can write zk Smart Contracts in the world's 2 most popular programming languages, JavaScript and Python, which have a developer market share 357 times larger than the Solidity community which only makes up a miniscule 0.1% of the world&rsquo;s developers.</p><p>In addition to making blockchain accessible to more developers than ever before, Dapen has integrated support for Markdown smart contracts which allow even non-technical users to write smart contracts in English using their integration with several large language AI models (LLMs) including ChatGPT.</p><p>Backed by Animoca Brands' fund Sparkle Ventures whose General Partners include Sebastien Borget, Co-founder of Sandbox, and Yat Siu, Co-founder of Animoca Brands, QED is set to see major adoption within the gaming space which regularly support millions of concurrent gamers playing at once. Due to its horizontal scaling model, QED is able to add transaction processing capacity by simply adding more proving nodes to its network, allowing large-scale gaming to integrate with blockchain technologies such as dynamic NFTs for the first time.</p><p>Headed up by Founder and CEO Carter Feldman, a former childhood hacking prodigy and reverse engineer, the QED core team is made up of a diverse team from both Web2 tech giants and Web3 titans including Binance, reflecting the protocol's mission to unite Web2 and Web3.</p><p>About QED</p><p>QED is the world's first zk-Native blockchain protocol, built to scale trustless computation and privacy for the next generation of the internet.</p><p>Twitter: Official | Founder&nbsp;</p>ContactQED Protocolnews@qedprotocol.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong, China, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Startup Open Asset Standards has recently announced QED, the world's first ZK 2.0 blockchain protocol. Unlike existing zero-knowledge blockchain protocols, QED has a novel state model which is horizontally scalable, meaning it is no longer limited by TPS restrictions that have previously prevented adoption of blockchain technologies in Web2 use cases such as social networks, traditional finance, and gaming.</p><p>Enabled by advances in fast recursive zero-knowledge proofs, QED is able to achieve this scale without compromising security or decentralization and proves all transactions end-to-end using proof recursion (verifying a zero-knowledge proof in a zero-knowledge proof ). This process of decentralized recursive proving culminates in a single block proof that can be verified by an Ethereum smart contract, making the protocol only reliant on the Proof of Math itself, rather than an incentive based consensus system vulnerable to collusion, hacking and misaligned incentives.</p><p>As the first blockchain capable of serving billions of users in a single block, QED does away with the need for a zk-VM by compiling smart contract functions directly to zero knowledge circuits, making it the first zk-Native blockchain. QED&rsquo;s novel approach to ZKP allows users to prove their own transactions on their own device in milliseconds, enabling a new privacy-centric internet where transactions are private by default and sensitive data never has to leave a user&rsquo;s device.</p><p>With its announcement of the QED Protocol, Open Asset Standards unveiled QED's official Dapen Smart Contract IDE. With Dapen, Web2 developers can write zk Smart Contracts in the world's 2 most popular programming languages, JavaScript and Python, which have a developer market share 357 times larger than the Solidity community which only makes up a miniscule 0.1% of the world&rsquo;s developers.</p><p>In addition to making blockchain accessible to more developers than ever before, Dapen has integrated support for Markdown smart contracts which allow even non-technical users to write smart contracts in English using their integration with several large language AI models (LLMs) including ChatGPT.</p><p>Backed by Animoca Brands' fund Sparkle Ventures whose General Partners include Sebastien Borget, Co-founder of Sandbox, and Yat Siu, Co-founder of Animoca Brands, QED is set to see major adoption within the gaming space which regularly support millions of concurrent gamers playing at once. Due to its horizontal scaling model, QED is able to add transaction processing capacity by simply adding more proving nodes to its network, allowing large-scale gaming to integrate with blockchain technologies such as dynamic NFTs for the first time.</p><p>Headed up by Founder and CEO Carter Feldman, a former childhood hacking prodigy and reverse engineer, the QED core team is made up of a diverse team from both Web2 tech giants and Web3 titans including Binance, reflecting the protocol's mission to unite Web2 and Web3.</p><p>About QED</p><p>QED is the world's first zk-Native blockchain protocol, built to scale trustless computation and privacy for the next generation of the internet.</p><p>Twitter: Official | Founder&nbsp;</p>ContactQED Protocolnews@qedprotocol.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Flipster to give away huge 1,500,000 USDT worth of Bonus]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/flipster-to-give-away-huge-1500000-usdt-worth-of-bonus</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Scene_Unlock-Opportunity_v02b_1689499027AWX7V2Ki90.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:43:22 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/flipster-to-give-away-huge-1500000-usdt-worth-of-bonus</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>seychelles, seychelles, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As part of Flipster's (formerly AQX) name launch, the business today announced an additional 1,500,000 USD worth of bonus rewards to encourage new users to join and trade on their exchange. Until the rewards are fully distributed, the futures exchange will run at least one campaign per week to encourage new users to signup and trade derivatives on the Flipster platform. Under the old name the exchange has already made available more than 400,000USDT worth bonus in past campaigns.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The first promotion in the series kicked off on the 17th of July, 2023 (running for seven days). A massive 110,000 USDT in bonuses has been allocated. 10,000 USDT to reward new users when completing identity verification with a 10 USDT Bonus. The remaining 100,000 USDT bonus is to incentivise and reward high volume traders that give the platform a chance. The top performer by trading volume will be rewarded with 10,000 USDT in Bonus at the end of the weekly campaign.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Flipster has reimagined futures trading with a mobile-first approach to appeal to casual crypto traders with limited experience in derivatives trading (or, as they say, Flipping).&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The method is to specialize in derivatives trading, stripping back the app experience to make it faster to learn and easier to use. Novice traders can open, close and monitor positions from any location. Potentially meaning some users may make more money on the bus to work, than from their days Labor. Beyond ease of use, the portable experience makes trading fun and feels less like a technical task.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The flip to a mobile-first approach came after initially having a web experience similar to other futures exchanges. The traditional UI for futures trading has a steep learning curve and is considerably more technical, which strongly contrasts with the UI that most contemporary apps users have become familiar with. The data concluded that users new to derivatives were not attracted to this experience as it had been built for experienced traders. The Flipster team discovered a few alternative UIs for future trading and none that have successfully been created to onboard new users to crypto futures trading at scale.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">While the focus is on simplicity, Flipster has features that will spark the interest of experienced traders as well. The exchange regularly adds new perpetual swap contracts, and as of today, over 120 assets can be traded with leverage, making Flipster a competitive exchange for traders to consider. Amongst their assets are tokens not found for futures on other exchanges and some even with low visibility in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>CEO Yongjin Kim said, "The team has been working very hard on bringing this new vision for futures trading to life, and now is the right time to incentivise users to trade with us. Once users start trading on our platform, they will be coming back again and again. Rather than just copying what every other exchange has done, we are doing something fresh, and I believe the market is ready for some injection of new ideas. To our existing users, I want to thank you for being with us, and to the new guys coming in now, Welcome".&nbsp;<p class="ql-align-justify">Get started by creating a Flipster account flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Flipster</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Flipster (ex AQX) is the industry's easy-to-use crypto derivatives trading platform. It offers users an all-in-one platform trading more than 120 tokens with leverage up to 50x. Get started at flipster.xyz to join online or download the app and play store. For media enquiries including interviews with the team reach out at pr@flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information follow Flipater on Twitter.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactHead of MarketingBen RogersPrex Ltdbenrogers@prestlabs.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>seychelles, seychelles, July 17th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">As part of Flipster's (formerly AQX) name launch, the business today announced an additional 1,500,000 USD worth of bonus rewards to encourage new users to join and trade on their exchange. Until the rewards are fully distributed, the futures exchange will run at least one campaign per week to encourage new users to signup and trade derivatives on the Flipster platform. Under the old name the exchange has already made available more than 400,000USDT worth bonus in past campaigns.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The first promotion in the series kicked off on the 17th of July, 2023 (running for seven days). A massive 110,000 USDT in bonuses has been allocated. 10,000 USDT to reward new users when completing identity verification with a 10 USDT Bonus. The remaining 100,000 USDT bonus is to incentivise and reward high volume traders that give the platform a chance. The top performer by trading volume will be rewarded with 10,000 USDT in Bonus at the end of the weekly campaign.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Flipster has reimagined futures trading with a mobile-first approach to appeal to casual crypto traders with limited experience in derivatives trading (or, as they say, Flipping).&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The method is to specialize in derivatives trading, stripping back the app experience to make it faster to learn and easier to use. Novice traders can open, close and monitor positions from any location. Potentially meaning some users may make more money on the bus to work, than from their days Labor. Beyond ease of use, the portable experience makes trading fun and feels less like a technical task.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The flip to a mobile-first approach came after initially having a web experience similar to other futures exchanges. The traditional UI for futures trading has a steep learning curve and is considerably more technical, which strongly contrasts with the UI that most contemporary apps users have become familiar with. The data concluded that users new to derivatives were not attracted to this experience as it had been built for experienced traders. The Flipster team discovered a few alternative UIs for future trading and none that have successfully been created to onboard new users to crypto futures trading at scale.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">While the focus is on simplicity, Flipster has features that will spark the interest of experienced traders as well. The exchange regularly adds new perpetual swap contracts, and as of today, over 120 assets can be traded with leverage, making Flipster a competitive exchange for traders to consider. Amongst their assets are tokens not found for futures on other exchanges and some even with low visibility in spot markets.&nbsp;</p>CEO Yongjin Kim said, "The team has been working very hard on bringing this new vision for futures trading to life, and now is the right time to incentivise users to trade with us. Once users start trading on our platform, they will be coming back again and again. Rather than just copying what every other exchange has done, we are doing something fresh, and I believe the market is ready for some injection of new ideas. To our existing users, I want to thank you for being with us, and to the new guys coming in now, Welcome".&nbsp;<p class="ql-align-justify">Get started by creating a Flipster account flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About Flipster</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Founded in 2021, Flipster (ex AQX) is the industry's easy-to-use crypto derivatives trading platform. It offers users an all-in-one platform trading more than 120 tokens with leverage up to 50x. Get started at flipster.xyz to join online or download the app and play store. For media enquiries including interviews with the team reach out at pr@flipster.xyz</p><p class="ql-align-justify">For more information follow Flipater on Twitter.</p><p></p><p></p>ContactHead of MarketingBen RogersPrex Ltdbenrogers@prestlabs.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Another Test of 30281 - 17 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-another-test-of-30281-17-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-16-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-another-test-of-30281-17-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Again Tests 30281:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lacked clear technical direction early in the Asian session as the pair again bounced higher from the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area. &nbsp;&nbsp;Buying pressure emerged around the 30145.47 area during a pullback, a move lower that represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp;&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30499.23 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30481.11.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Again Tests 30281:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 17 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) lacked clear technical direction early in the Asian session as the pair again bounced higher from the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area. &nbsp;&nbsp;Buying pressure emerged around the 30145.47 area during a pullback, a move lower that represented a test of the 23.6% retracement of the recent depreciating range from 31525.10 to 29715.87.&nbsp;&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30499.23 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30481.11.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Elected Below 30147 - 16 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-30147-16-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-30147-16-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 30147:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained confined to an extremely tight range early in the Asian session as the pair encountered minor technical buying pressure around the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30482.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30473.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 30147:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) remained confined to an extremely tight range early in the Asian session as the pair encountered minor technical buying pressure around the 30142.85 level, right around the 23.6% retracement of a recent narrow appreciating range from the 29715.87 area to the 30456 area.&nbsp; Stops were elected below the 31003.83, 30739.19, 30474.55, and 30147.11 areas during the recent acute depreciation, downside price objectives linked to recent selling pressure around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, and 34658 areas.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29920, 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels. &nbsp;Upside price objectives related to historical buying activity include the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 levels.&nbsp; Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460. &nbsp;Downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure include the 29849 and 29331 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30482.21 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30473.71.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Weekly Roundup: $XRP Soars After SEC Victory And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-xrp-soars-after-sec-victory-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/crypto-weekly-roundup-new.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-weekly-roundup-xrp-soars-after-sec-victory-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The most exciting news in the industry this week has been Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in the SEC case. Experts are opining that it could shake the market out of its rut. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Judge Analise Torres of the Southern District of New York handed a partial win over to Ripple Labs after its three-year-long battle with the SEC.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p>Europe&rsquo;s highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin ETF is finally set to debut later this year amidst huge anticipation surrounding its imminent arrival.</p>
<p>The US Department of Justice is finally moving the BTC reserves it seized from the Silk Road, the notorious online marketplace predominantly used for illicit activities.</p>
<p>Vanguard Group, which manages $7.2 trillion in assets, has significantly ramped up its investments in the bitcoin mining sector, with its total stake now exceeding $560 million.</p>
<p>The UK&rsquo;s FCA has shut down 26 cryptocurrency ATMs this year following a coordinated investigation with other law enforcement agencies.</p>
<p>Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021.</p>
<p>Satoshis are now being given out as rewards on Satlantis, a unique Bitcoin-themed Minecraft server.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated that he has not invested in Bitcoin, even though financial records prove otherwise.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>The transactions per second on the Etheruem blockchain will receive a significant boost now that Starknet&rsquo;s Quantum Leap upgrade has been deployed on the Ethereum mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Aave community members will be voting on whether to finally deploy gho ($GHO) on the Ethereum chain.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol, Rodeo Finance, lost $1.53 million in Ethereum due to a code vulnerability exploitation in its Oracle.</p>
<p>ConsenSys has announced the launch of its layer-2 network Linea, as the Ethereum ecosystem welcomed yet another scaling solution.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>20-year-old Argentinian Federico Jaime has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p>Kain Warwick, the founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p>Uniswap users can now start swapping their Avalanche tokens on the Uniswap website, as the decentralized exchange has now launched on the Avalanche network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000.</p>
Altcoins
<p>The pronouncement by the SDNY judge that XRP can only be partially classed as a security led to a massive market surge.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Polygon, the prominent Ethereum layer 2 scaling solution, is making strides towards a significant upgrade, changing its token from $MATIC to $POL.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p>Coinbase has launched an encrypted messaging service on its self-custodial wallet app, using the open-source Web3 messaging network of Texas-based startup XMTP.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month.</p>
<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After a significant downturn in the crypto market, it appears that in the first half of 2023, the venture investment market, much like the price of Bitcoin, has found its bottom.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin has surpassed 2 million sign-ups for its World ID program in half the time it took to reach the first million sign-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX recently launched its claims portal, allowing users from around the world to file a claim.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto data firm Arkham Intelligence is under fire after privacy-conscious users discovered that the firm has been irresponsible about user data.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP skyrocketed by around 70% in the 24 hours after its landmark partial win over the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Australian crypto investment firm, Monochrome Asset Management is working to introduce spot Bitcoin ETF on the Australian Securities Exchange.</p>
<p>Coinbase has paused its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the SEC can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
NFT
<p>Starbucks&rsquo; Web3 loyalty program Odyssey has announced a collaboration with the Aku NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>Blockchain security and analytics firm Chainalysis has suggested that the multimillion-dollar exploit of the Multichain Protocol could be indicative of a rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam after users reported receiving "fake approval" requests that led to exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The most exciting news in the industry this week has been Ripple&rsquo;s partial win in the SEC case. Experts are opining that it could shake the market out of its rut. Let&rsquo;s find out more.&nbsp;</p>
Bitcoin
<p>Judge Analise Torres of the Southern District of New York handed a partial win over to Ripple Labs after its three-year-long battle with the SEC.</p>
<p>Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p>Europe&rsquo;s highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin ETF is finally set to debut later this year amidst huge anticipation surrounding its imminent arrival.</p>
<p>The US Department of Justice is finally moving the BTC reserves it seized from the Silk Road, the notorious online marketplace predominantly used for illicit activities.</p>
<p>Vanguard Group, which manages $7.2 trillion in assets, has significantly ramped up its investments in the bitcoin mining sector, with its total stake now exceeding $560 million.</p>
<p>The UK&rsquo;s FCA has shut down 26 cryptocurrency ATMs this year following a coordinated investigation with other law enforcement agencies.</p>
<p>Standard Chartered Bank has presented an optimistic forecast for Bitcoin, suggesting that the leading cryptocurrency could touch the $50,000 milestone by the end of 2021.</p>
<p>Satoshis are now being given out as rewards on Satlantis, a unique Bitcoin-themed Minecraft server.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr had recently stated that he has not invested in Bitcoin, even though financial records prove otherwise.&nbsp;</p>
Ethereum
<p>The transactions per second on the Etheruem blockchain will receive a significant boost now that Starknet&rsquo;s Quantum Leap upgrade has been deployed on the Ethereum mainnet.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Aave community members will be voting on whether to finally deploy gho ($GHO) on the Ethereum chain.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol, Rodeo Finance, lost $1.53 million in Ethereum due to a code vulnerability exploitation in its Oracle.</p>
<p>ConsenSys has announced the launch of its layer-2 network Linea, as the Ethereum ecosystem welcomed yet another scaling solution.&nbsp;</p>
DeFi
<p>20-year-old Argentinian Federico Jaime has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p>Kain Warwick, the founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p>Uniswap users can now start swapping their Avalanche tokens on the Uniswap website, as the decentralized exchange has now launched on the Avalanche network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DeFi platform Arcadia Finance has reportedly been the victim of an exploit which allowed hackers to drain roughly $455,000.</p>
Altcoins
<p>The pronouncement by the SDNY judge that XRP can only be partially classed as a security led to a massive market surge.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Polygon, the prominent Ethereum layer 2 scaling solution, is making strides towards a significant upgrade, changing its token from $MATIC to $POL.&nbsp;</p>
Technology
<p>Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p>Coinbase has launched an encrypted messaging service on its self-custodial wallet app, using the open-source Web3 messaging network of Texas-based startup XMTP.&nbsp;</p>
Business
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month.</p>
<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>After a significant downturn in the crypto market, it appears that in the first half of 2023, the venture investment market, much like the price of Bitcoin, has found its bottom.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin has surpassed 2 million sign-ups for its World ID program in half the time it took to reach the first million sign-ups.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX recently launched its claims portal, allowing users from around the world to file a claim.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Crypto data firm Arkham Intelligence is under fire after privacy-conscious users discovered that the firm has been irresponsible about user data.&nbsp;</p>
Regulation
<p>Ripple&rsquo;s XRP skyrocketed by around 70% in the 24 hours after its landmark partial win over the SEC.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Australian crypto investment firm, Monochrome Asset Management is working to introduce spot Bitcoin ETF on the Australian Securities Exchange.</p>
<p>Coinbase has paused its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p>Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the SEC can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
NFT
<p>Starbucks&rsquo; Web3 loyalty program Odyssey has announced a collaboration with the Aku NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
Security
<p>Blockchain security and analytics firm Chainalysis has suggested that the multimillion-dollar exploit of the Multichain Protocol could be indicative of a rug pull.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Approval management platform Revoke introduced a new feature to combat a new crypto scam after users reported receiving "fake approval" requests that led to exuberant transaction fees.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Face Difficulty Ahead of Halving, JP Morgan Warns]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-miners-face-difficulty-ahead-of-halving-jp-morgan-warns</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/jp-morgan-btc-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-miners-face-difficulty-ahead-of-halving-jp-morgan-warns</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report suggests that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees need to rise substantially to balance the reduced block reward.</p>
Unsettling Times Ahead for Miners
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The analysis predicts potential difficulties for Bitcoin miners as the hash rate, representing the computational power used to mine cryptocurrency, hits new highs. Factors such as fluctuating electricity costs and intensified competition among miners are expected to increase the cost of production. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The halving event, which takes place approximately every four years, will cut miners' rewards by half. "The upcoming bitcoin halving event in April/May 2024 could be a stress test for Bitcoin miners," states the report, co-authored by JP Morgan analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This event will lower the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, effectively reducing miners&rsquo; revenue while concurrently increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost. The report explains that while Bitcoin halving typically has a positive impact on the Bitcoin price given that the production cost has historically acted as a floor, it presents a considerable challenge for miners.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[The halving] would reduce the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, implying a reduction in miners&rsquo; revenue, effectively increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost at the same time [...] As a result, while Bitcoin halving is seen as having a positive effect on the bitcoin price given the production cost acted historically as a floor, it poses a challenge for bitcoin miners," the report indicated.</p>

Hash Rate Volatility and Energy Costs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Based on a global average electricity cost of $0.05/kWh, it presently costs around $20,000 to mine a Bitcoin, currently valued at around $30,000 according to public blockchain explorer data. JP Morgan highlighted the hash rate's volatility, suggesting a range of energy sources and potential advantages for miners who have access to lower-priced power.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm revealed that a one-cent increase in the cost per kilowatt-hour translates into a $4,300 increase in Bitcoin production costs. After the halving event, this sensitivity is expected to double, thereby escalating the risk and susceptibility for higher-cost producers (in simpler terms, they will effectively be "priced out" of the competitive sphere for Bitcoin mining).</p>
Institutional Support and the Importance of Rising Bitcoin Prices
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report also points to growing institutional interest in Bitcoin mining as a source of support for struggling miners, citing investments in mining rigs from companies like Galaxy Digital and Grayscale Investments. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"It seems unlikely that the Bitcoin hash rate will continue to rise at the same pace post the April/May 2024 halving event without any sustained rise in the Bitcoin price above its production cost or a large increase in transaction fees that could offset the reduction in issuance rewards."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite this, however, to offset the lower block reward, JP Morgan stresses that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees must see substantial growth. The analysts furtherl noted that declining enthusiasm around cryptocurrencies could pose an additional challenge for miners' revenues, if indeed the trend in terms of declining interest in crypto proves to be a long-term trend.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bitcoin miners may face significant challenges due to the upcoming halving event, according to a new report by analysts from banking and finance firm JP Morgan.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report suggests that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees need to rise substantially to balance the reduced block reward.</p>
Unsettling Times Ahead for Miners
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The analysis predicts potential difficulties for Bitcoin miners as the hash rate, representing the computational power used to mine cryptocurrency, hits new highs. Factors such as fluctuating electricity costs and intensified competition among miners are expected to increase the cost of production. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The halving event, which takes place approximately every four years, will cut miners' rewards by half. "The upcoming bitcoin halving event in April/May 2024 could be a stress test for Bitcoin miners," states the report, co-authored by JP Morgan analyst Nikolaos Panigirtzoglou.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This event will lower the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, effectively reducing miners&rsquo; revenue while concurrently increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost. The report explains that while Bitcoin halving typically has a positive impact on the Bitcoin price given that the production cost has historically acted as a floor, it presents a considerable challenge for miners.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"[The halving] would reduce the issuance rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 BTC, implying a reduction in miners&rsquo; revenue, effectively increasing Bitcoin&rsquo;s production cost at the same time [...] As a result, while Bitcoin halving is seen as having a positive effect on the bitcoin price given the production cost acted historically as a floor, it poses a challenge for bitcoin miners," the report indicated.</p>

Hash Rate Volatility and Energy Costs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Based on a global average electricity cost of $0.05/kWh, it presently costs around $20,000 to mine a Bitcoin, currently valued at around $30,000 according to public blockchain explorer data. JP Morgan highlighted the hash rate's volatility, suggesting a range of energy sources and potential advantages for miners who have access to lower-priced power.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The firm revealed that a one-cent increase in the cost per kilowatt-hour translates into a $4,300 increase in Bitcoin production costs. After the halving event, this sensitivity is expected to double, thereby escalating the risk and susceptibility for higher-cost producers (in simpler terms, they will effectively be "priced out" of the competitive sphere for Bitcoin mining).</p>
Institutional Support and the Importance of Rising Bitcoin Prices
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report also points to growing institutional interest in Bitcoin mining as a source of support for struggling miners, citing investments in mining rigs from companies like Galaxy Digital and Grayscale Investments. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The report stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"It seems unlikely that the Bitcoin hash rate will continue to rise at the same pace post the April/May 2024 halving event without any sustained rise in the Bitcoin price above its production cost or a large increase in transaction fees that could offset the reduction in issuance rewards."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite this, however, to offset the lower block reward, JP Morgan stresses that Bitcoin's price and transaction fees must see substantial growth. The analysts furtherl noted that declining enthusiasm around cryptocurrencies could pose an additional challenge for miners' revenues, if indeed the trend in terms of declining interest in crypto proves to be a long-term trend.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Claims SEC Case May Take Years To Appeal $XRP]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-claims-sec-case-may-take-years-to-appeal-xrp</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ripple-case-update-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ripple-ceo-claims-sec-case-may-take-years-to-appeal-xrp</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to an interview from Garlinghouse with Bloomberg on July 15, the executive estimates that the SEC's opportunity for appeal could take "years." No other precise detail in terms of this claim was disclosed, however.</p>
Judge's Ruling on XRP
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On July 13, Judge Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit initiated by the SEC in 2020. The judgement states that the XRP token, with respect to retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not a security. However, Judge Torres ruled that XRP qualifies as a security when sold to institutional investors, in accordance with the criteria of the Howey Test.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse emphasized that the ruling about institutional sales represents "the smallest piece" of the lawsuit. He believes that if the SEC decides to appeal the ruling regarding retail sales, it would only "further solidify" Judge Torres' decision.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"As a matter of law, the law of the land right now is that XRP is not a security. Until there is an opportunity for the SEC to file an appeal, which would take years, frankly, we are very optimistic.&rdquo;</p>

SEC Accused of Bullying Tactics
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse also took the opportunity to criticize the SEC, alleging it acted as a "bully" by targeting "weak players" in the crypto industry incapable of mounting a strong defense. He indicated that the Ripple lawsuit marked the first defeat for the SEC in a "crypto case."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple CEO noted the SEC's lawsuit initially led to uncertainty among U.S. crypto exchanges, causing a wait-and-see attitude due to market confusion. According to Garlinghouse, the SEC deliberately fostered this confusion to increase its power, thereby stifling innovation in the U.S.</p>
Impact on the Crypto Market
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse argued that the SEC's power play and political manoeuvring have overshadowed sound policy and clear regulatory guidelines. This stance, he says, has hampered U.S. entrepreneurs and investors from fully participating in the crypto market and embracing blockchain technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the recent performance of XRP may be impacted by these developments, the broader implications revolve around regulatory clarity in the crypto industry, and this is something that requires closer attention in terms of how it evolves and becomes more complex with each new case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse recently made statements which predicted a long wait before the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) can file an appeal following Judge Torres' ruling on the Ripple case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to an interview from Garlinghouse with Bloomberg on July 15, the executive estimates that the SEC's opportunity for appeal could take "years." No other precise detail in terms of this claim was disclosed, however.</p>
Judge's Ruling on XRP
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On July 13, Judge Torres partially ruled in favor of Ripple Labs in a lawsuit initiated by the SEC in 2020. The judgement states that the XRP token, with respect to retail sales on digital asset exchanges, is not a security. However, Judge Torres ruled that XRP qualifies as a security when sold to institutional investors, in accordance with the criteria of the Howey Test.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse emphasized that the ruling about institutional sales represents "the smallest piece" of the lawsuit. He believes that if the SEC decides to appeal the ruling regarding retail sales, it would only "further solidify" Judge Torres' decision.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse said:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"As a matter of law, the law of the land right now is that XRP is not a security. Until there is an opportunity for the SEC to file an appeal, which would take years, frankly, we are very optimistic.&rdquo;</p>

SEC Accused of Bullying Tactics
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse also took the opportunity to criticize the SEC, alleging it acted as a "bully" by targeting "weak players" in the crypto industry incapable of mounting a strong defense. He indicated that the Ripple lawsuit marked the first defeat for the SEC in a "crypto case."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ripple CEO noted the SEC's lawsuit initially led to uncertainty among U.S. crypto exchanges, causing a wait-and-see attitude due to market confusion. According to Garlinghouse, the SEC deliberately fostered this confusion to increase its power, thereby stifling innovation in the U.S.</p>
Impact on the Crypto Market
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Garlinghouse argued that the SEC's power play and political manoeuvring have overshadowed sound policy and clear regulatory guidelines. This stance, he says, has hampered U.S. entrepreneurs and investors from fully participating in the crypto market and embracing blockchain technologies.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While the recent performance of XRP may be impacted by these developments, the broader implications revolve around regulatory clarity in the crypto industry, and this is something that requires closer attention in terms of how it evolves and becomes more complex with each new case.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polkadot Eyeing Resource Allocation Shifts For Parachains $DOT]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/polkadot-eyeing-resource-allocation-shifts-for-parachains-dot</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polkadot-parachain-proposal-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polkadot-parachain-proposal-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polkadot-parachain-proposal-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/polkadot-eyeing-resource-allocation-shifts-for-parachains-dot</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This initiative, referred to as Polkadot 2.0, reimagines the network's architecture as a conglomerate of sovereign chains connected by treaty-like 'accords.'</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">During the fourth Decoded conference, Wood illustrated his vision, likening Polkadot's journey of discovery to Ethereum's, another project he co-founded.</p>
Rethinking Polkadot's Infrastructure
<p class="md-end-block md-p">After launching Polkadot in May 2020, Wood transitioned from his CEO role at Parity Technologies to the network's chief architect in October 2022. Polkadot's core primitive, the parachain auctions, was not unveiled until November 2021, amidst the previous crypto bull market. The move caused a sharp price surge in Polkadot's native token, DOT, but later faced issues due to the competitive and fluctuating environment of parachain auctions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">From Parachains to Cores</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Wood sees Polkadot as a multicore computer, with reserved cores for the parachains. However, the core of Polkadot 2.0's vision lies in a shift from a focus on chains to one on 'space' or resources that chains need. Wood highlighted the necessity of a more agile system, noting that the slot auction model, whcile appealing, presented both perceived and real barriers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Under the proposed framework, 'core time' would be allocated via a marketplace. This marketplace would cater to both on-demand (instantaneous) and long-term (bulk) needs. Wood suggested that these monthly blocks of core time would be represented by NFTs, which can be fractionalized, letting owners of bulk time allocarte computation on a Polkadot core.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This means that all currently existing leases would continue under the new system, with the bulk pricing requiring initialization by governance.</p>
Shifting to an Application-Centric Model
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polkadot 2.0 proposal is all about application-centricity as opposed to chain-centricity. Wood pointed out that Polkadot is ultimately a platform for building applications for users, and these applications should ideally span across chains seamlessly, both from a user and developer perspective.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The robust nature of Polkadot's infrastructure allows deploying a pseudo network rather than just an application, which demands additional care regarding collators and network uptime. In some instances, it might be preferable to deploy smart contracts directly on cores, thus entirely bypassing the parachain concept.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The proposed Polkadot 2.0 initiative represents a significant evolution of the blockchain network, focusing more on resources (space) over chains. By redesigning its resource allocation model, Polkadot hopes to make the system more agile, with a focus on applications and user experience.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polkadot's founder, Gavin Wood, has proposed a major shift in how the blockchain network allocates resources.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This initiative, referred to as Polkadot 2.0, reimagines the network's architecture as a conglomerate of sovereign chains connected by treaty-like 'accords.'</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">During the fourth Decoded conference, Wood illustrated his vision, likening Polkadot's journey of discovery to Ethereum's, another project he co-founded.</p>
Rethinking Polkadot's Infrastructure
<p class="md-end-block md-p">After launching Polkadot in May 2020, Wood transitioned from his CEO role at Parity Technologies to the network's chief architect in October 2022. Polkadot's core primitive, the parachain auctions, was not unveiled until November 2021, amidst the previous crypto bull market. The move caused a sharp price surge in Polkadot's native token, DOT, but later faced issues due to the competitive and fluctuating environment of parachain auctions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">From Parachains to Cores</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Wood sees Polkadot as a multicore computer, with reserved cores for the parachains. However, the core of Polkadot 2.0's vision lies in a shift from a focus on chains to one on 'space' or resources that chains need. Wood highlighted the necessity of a more agile system, noting that the slot auction model, whcile appealing, presented both perceived and real barriers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Under the proposed framework, 'core time' would be allocated via a marketplace. This marketplace would cater to both on-demand (instantaneous) and long-term (bulk) needs. Wood suggested that these monthly blocks of core time would be represented by NFTs, which can be fractionalized, letting owners of bulk time allocarte computation on a Polkadot core.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This means that all currently existing leases would continue under the new system, with the bulk pricing requiring initialization by governance.</p>
Shifting to an Application-Centric Model
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Polkadot 2.0 proposal is all about application-centricity as opposed to chain-centricity. Wood pointed out that Polkadot is ultimately a platform for building applications for users, and these applications should ideally span across chains seamlessly, both from a user and developer perspective.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The robust nature of Polkadot's infrastructure allows deploying a pseudo network rather than just an application, which demands additional care regarding collators and network uptime. In some instances, it might be preferable to deploy smart contracts directly on cores, thus entirely bypassing the parachain concept.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The proposed Polkadot 2.0 initiative represents a significant evolution of the blockchain network, focusing more on resources (space) over chains. By redesigning its resource allocation model, Polkadot hopes to make the system more agile, with a focus on applications and user experience.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Indonesia Set To Launch National Crypto Exchange in July]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/indonesia-set-to-launch-national-crypto-exchange-in-july</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/indonesia-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/indonesia-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/indonesia-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 16:43:19 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/indonesia-set-to-launch-national-crypto-exchange-in-july</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month. </p>
<p>The Indonesian government will finally launch its national crypto exchange this month and expects the platform to begin trading in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Local news agency Tempo reported the country&rsquo;s Commodity Futures Trading Supervisory Agency, commonly known as Bappebti, plans to launch the exchange this month after several delays.</p>
<p>Bappebti&rsquo;s head Didid Noordiatmoko said once the exchange launches, all crypto transactions can only be conducted via its platform. Five hundred and one cryptocurrencies have been approved to be traded on the exchange.</p>
Exchange Will Go Live After Several Delays
<p>Noordiatmoko said Bappebti agreed on the stock exchange rules adding that its discussions involved KYC procedures. The official also noted that trading on the exchange would be offered through an integrated application, which Bappebti had already tested.</p>

<p>"Yesterday we conducted system integration tests between traders, exchanges, clearing, and depository," Didid said.</p>

<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s national exchange was slated to launch by December 2022 but was delayed to June 2023.</p>
<p>Noordiatmoko also said the regulator plans to restrict crypto sales to local transactions while keeping them in line with international market developments and standards.</p>
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Trade Minister, Zulkifli Hasan, has been informed of the exchange&rsquo;s progress. If all goes to plan and no further instructions are given, the regulator will sign a permit giving licensed traders one month to join the platform.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Futures and Commodity Trading Regulatory Agency will launch a national cryptocurrency exchange this month. </p>
<p>The Indonesian government will finally launch its national crypto exchange this month and expects the platform to begin trading in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>Local news agency Tempo reported the country&rsquo;s Commodity Futures Trading Supervisory Agency, commonly known as Bappebti, plans to launch the exchange this month after several delays.</p>
<p>Bappebti&rsquo;s head Didid Noordiatmoko said once the exchange launches, all crypto transactions can only be conducted via its platform. Five hundred and one cryptocurrencies have been approved to be traded on the exchange.</p>
Exchange Will Go Live After Several Delays
<p>Noordiatmoko said Bappebti agreed on the stock exchange rules adding that its discussions involved KYC procedures. The official also noted that trading on the exchange would be offered through an integrated application, which Bappebti had already tested.</p>

<p>"Yesterday we conducted system integration tests between traders, exchanges, clearing, and depository," Didid said.</p>

<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s national exchange was slated to launch by December 2022 but was delayed to June 2023.</p>
<p>Noordiatmoko also said the regulator plans to restrict crypto sales to local transactions while keeping them in line with international market developments and standards.</p>
<p>Indonesia&rsquo;s Trade Minister, Zulkifli Hasan, has been informed of the exchange&rsquo;s progress. If all goes to plan and no further instructions are given, the regulator will sign a permit giving licensed traders one month to join the platform.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Monochrome Targets ASX with Proposed Bitcoin ETF $BTC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/monochrome-targets-asx-with-proposed-bitcoin-etf</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/monochrome-bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/monochrome-bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/monochrome-bitcoin-etf-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 15:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/monochrome-targets-asx-with-proposed-bitcoin-etf</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Monochrome Asset Management, an Australian-based cryptocurrency investment firm, recently updated its application, targeting the introduction of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Monochrome is working in partnership with Vasco Trustees on this endeavor. The proposed ETF, dubbed the Monochrome Bitcoin ETF, aims to provide Australian retail investors with direct exposure to Bitcoin and Ether (ETH), according to a company announcement on July 14.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Monochrome's CEO, Jeff Yew explain the firm's intents, emphasizing that the need for Australian retail investors to be able to access Bitcoin within a regulated environment, promoting greater freedom to engage with the asset class within an established regulatory framework. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Yew pointed out the security advantages of a regulated ETF over unregulated exchanges. With a regulated ETF, investor protection is assured, while unregulated exchanges may lack such safeguards. This added protection will likely inspire confidence and increase participation in the crypto market among retail investors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Impact and Future Expectations</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Partnering with Vasco, Monochrome is well-positioned to offer regulated exposure to cryptocurrencies for retail investors. Vasco, functioning as Monochrome's "Responsible Entity Partner," holds the required authorization under an Australian Financial Services Licence to do so. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Yew further noted that a Bitcoin ETF on the ASX could significantly change the perception of traditional investors, marking an end to the unregulated "Wild West" phase. The structured, familiar, and secure environment provided by an ETF could boost investor confidence in the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposal of a Bitcoin ETF on the ASX indicates significant progress towards mainstream adoption and regulatory acceptance of cryptocurrencies in Australia. This updated application aligns with the recent global trend of increasing interest in spot Bitcoin ETFs, evidenced by filings from financial behemoths like Fidelity, Invesco, Wisdom Tree, Valkyrie, and BlackRock.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The introduction of the Monochrome Bitcoin ETF would provide investors with "direct exposure" to Bitcoin, according to the company's official statement. This represents a notable milestone as the first filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF on the ASX under the country's new crypto regulations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As such, on the outset, forthcoming decisions regarding Monochrome's Bitcoin ETF application could set an important precedent for future crypto asset investment vehicles.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Monochrome Asset Management, an Australian-based cryptocurrency investment firm, recently updated its application, targeting the introduction of a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Australian Securities Exchange (ASX).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Monochrome is working in partnership with Vasco Trustees on this endeavor. The proposed ETF, dubbed the Monochrome Bitcoin ETF, aims to provide Australian retail investors with direct exposure to Bitcoin and Ether (ETH), according to a company announcement on July 14.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Monochrome's CEO, Jeff Yew explain the firm's intents, emphasizing that the need for Australian retail investors to be able to access Bitcoin within a regulated environment, promoting greater freedom to engage with the asset class within an established regulatory framework. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Yew pointed out the security advantages of a regulated ETF over unregulated exchanges. With a regulated ETF, investor protection is assured, while unregulated exchanges may lack such safeguards. This added protection will likely inspire confidence and increase participation in the crypto market among retail investors.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Impact and Future Expectations</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Partnering with Vasco, Monochrome is well-positioned to offer regulated exposure to cryptocurrencies for retail investors. Vasco, functioning as Monochrome's "Responsible Entity Partner," holds the required authorization under an Australian Financial Services Licence to do so. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Yew further noted that a Bitcoin ETF on the ASX could significantly change the perception of traditional investors, marking an end to the unregulated "Wild West" phase. The structured, familiar, and secure environment provided by an ETF could boost investor confidence in the crypto market.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposal of a Bitcoin ETF on the ASX indicates significant progress towards mainstream adoption and regulatory acceptance of cryptocurrencies in Australia. This updated application aligns with the recent global trend of increasing interest in spot Bitcoin ETFs, evidenced by filings from financial behemoths like Fidelity, Invesco, Wisdom Tree, Valkyrie, and BlackRock.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The introduction of the Monochrome Bitcoin ETF would provide investors with "direct exposure" to Bitcoin, according to the company's official statement. This represents a notable milestone as the first filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF on the ASX under the country's new crypto regulations. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As such, on the outset, forthcoming decisions regarding Monochrome's Bitcoin ETF application could set an important precedent for future crypto asset investment vehicles.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Suspends Staking Services In Four U.S. States]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinbase-suspends-staking-services-in-four-us-states</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinbase-suspends-staking-services-in-four-us-states</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">The cryptocurrency giant pauses its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The United States-based crypto exchange is again in the news following the fierce back-and-forth between itself and the United States&rsquo; Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In a blog post yesterday July 14, the exchange announced a temporary suspension of its staking operations in the four states following preliminary orders by local state regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These states have laws enabling these agencies to issue preliminary orders even before legal proceedings begin.</p>
Other Fronts In Legal Action For Coinbase
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Apart from the aforementioned states, the exchange is also facing legal action from regulators in Maryland, Vermont, Kentucky, Illinois, Alabama, and Washington. Unlike the previous four states however, Coinbase&rsquo;s staking services are unaffected and customers &ldquo;remain eligible to stake crypto just as they were before.&rdquo;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These string of events comes after the SEC finally filed a lawsuit against the exchange last June 6. In the lawsuit, the agency alleged that the exchange acted as an unregistered broker, which the exchange has vehemently denied. Almost immediately, the respective regulatory bodies of the above-mentioned states initiated their own legal proceedings against Coinbase.</p>
Taking a Stand
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase however, remains unfazed by the lawsuit and the subsequent legal actions by local state regulators. It has reiterated its position that staking services are not securities and calls on the SEC to enact reasonable crypto policies instead of its current path of regulation-by-enforcement.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;It might be the easier path to simply cut off staking services in the ten states that have initiated proceedings against us, but we believe that would be wrong as a matter of law, wrong for our customers, and wrong for the future of the cryptoeconomy,&rdquo; the exchange said. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">After these statements, the exchange reiterated its call for the crypto community to come together for pro-crypto policies and make the U.S. a hub for crypto.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">The cryptocurrency giant pauses its staking operations in California, New Jersey, South Carolina, and Wisconsin as it continues discussions with their respective regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The United States-based crypto exchange is again in the news following the fierce back-and-forth between itself and the United States&rsquo; Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In a blog post yesterday July 14, the exchange announced a temporary suspension of its staking operations in the four states following preliminary orders by local state regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These states have laws enabling these agencies to issue preliminary orders even before legal proceedings begin.</p>
Other Fronts In Legal Action For Coinbase
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Apart from the aforementioned states, the exchange is also facing legal action from regulators in Maryland, Vermont, Kentucky, Illinois, Alabama, and Washington. Unlike the previous four states however, Coinbase&rsquo;s staking services are unaffected and customers &ldquo;remain eligible to stake crypto just as they were before.&rdquo;</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">These string of events comes after the SEC finally filed a lawsuit against the exchange last June 6. In the lawsuit, the agency alleged that the exchange acted as an unregistered broker, which the exchange has vehemently denied. Almost immediately, the respective regulatory bodies of the above-mentioned states initiated their own legal proceedings against Coinbase.</p>
Taking a Stand
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase however, remains unfazed by the lawsuit and the subsequent legal actions by local state regulators. It has reiterated its position that staking services are not securities and calls on the SEC to enact reasonable crypto policies instead of its current path of regulation-by-enforcement.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">&ldquo;It might be the easier path to simply cut off staking services in the ten states that have initiated proceedings against us, but we believe that would be wrong as a matter of law, wrong for our customers, and wrong for the future of the cryptoeconomy,&rdquo; the exchange said. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">After these statements, the exchange reiterated its call for the crypto community to come together for pro-crypto policies and make the U.S. a hub for crypto.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Alleged Hacker Behind $200m Euler Finance Exploit Arrested $EUL]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/alleged-hacker-behind-200m-euler-finance-exploit-arrested-eul</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/euler-finance-exploit-hacker-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/euler-finance-exploit-hacker-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/euler-finance-exploit-hacker-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/alleged-hacker-behind-200m-euler-finance-exploit-arrested-eul</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Federico Jaime, a 20-year-old from Argentina, has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The alleged hacker gave an interview from a French prison, where he is currently held for what he describes as a "small money-laundering case." The funds in question, totalling &euro;200,000, reportedly comprise profits from an IT business he operates with his father and a portion of the cryptocurrency that Euler allegedly allowed him to keep post-exploit.</p>
Deconstructing the Heist
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Euler Finance, a decentralized finance (DeFi) lending protocol developed by UK-based Euler Labs, suffered a significant loss on March 13. The alleged hacker, Jaime, reportedly exploited a vulnerability in the protocol's code, enabling him to redirect investor deposits into his personal wallets. Euler Labs has yet to comment on these recent developments. The company previously stated that the hacker had returned all the recoverable funds.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite his open admission of involvement, Jaime's story is not without contradictions. He maintains that the &euro;200,000 cash he was found with on his person was a combination of legitimate earnings and a portion of the cryptocurrency spoils from the hack that Euler permitted him to retain. According to Jaime, Euler deemed these assets tainted due to their passage through Tornado Cash, a coin mixer sanctioned by the U.S. government last year.</p>
Legal Fallout
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although Jaime currently faces charges related to money laundering in France, his potential involvement in the $200 million exploit could lead to more serious allegations. Interestingly, Jaime is reportedly held in a minimum-security prison in Nanterre, a Parisian suburb. However, verifying this information is challenging due to France's lack of a public prisoner database.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a bid to clarify his actions and possibly salvage his image, Jaime has made his intentions to help Euler regain its previous Total Value Locked (TVL) known. As of now, Euler's TVL stands at around $76,000, a substantial drop from its pre-hack value of over $300 million. The protocol has disclosed plans for a newer version (dubbed Euler V2) as well as plans for constructing a decentralized exchange called EulerSwap.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Regardless of his expressed remorse and willingness to help Euler recover, the ongoing legal proceedings and the severity of the accusations Jaime faces could significantly impact his future. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Federico Jaime, a 20-year-old from Argentina, has publicly claimed responsibility for the $200 million Euler Finance exploit and is now under arrest in a Paris prison.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The alleged hacker gave an interview from a French prison, where he is currently held for what he describes as a "small money-laundering case." The funds in question, totalling &euro;200,000, reportedly comprise profits from an IT business he operates with his father and a portion of the cryptocurrency that Euler allegedly allowed him to keep post-exploit.</p>
Deconstructing the Heist
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Euler Finance, a decentralized finance (DeFi) lending protocol developed by UK-based Euler Labs, suffered a significant loss on March 13. The alleged hacker, Jaime, reportedly exploited a vulnerability in the protocol's code, enabling him to redirect investor deposits into his personal wallets. Euler Labs has yet to comment on these recent developments. The company previously stated that the hacker had returned all the recoverable funds.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite his open admission of involvement, Jaime's story is not without contradictions. He maintains that the &euro;200,000 cash he was found with on his person was a combination of legitimate earnings and a portion of the cryptocurrency spoils from the hack that Euler permitted him to retain. According to Jaime, Euler deemed these assets tainted due to their passage through Tornado Cash, a coin mixer sanctioned by the U.S. government last year.</p>
Legal Fallout
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Although Jaime currently faces charges related to money laundering in France, his potential involvement in the $200 million exploit could lead to more serious allegations. Interestingly, Jaime is reportedly held in a minimum-security prison in Nanterre, a Parisian suburb. However, verifying this information is challenging due to France's lack of a public prisoner database.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a bid to clarify his actions and possibly salvage his image, Jaime has made his intentions to help Euler regain its previous Total Value Locked (TVL) known. As of now, Euler's TVL stands at around $76,000, a substantial drop from its pre-hack value of over $300 million. The protocol has disclosed plans for a newer version (dubbed Euler V2) as well as plans for constructing a decentralized exchange called EulerSwap.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Regardless of his expressed remorse and willingness to help Euler recover, the ongoing legal proceedings and the severity of the accusations Jaime faces could significantly impact his future. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BlockFi CEO Disregarded Warnings About FTX, Ignored Risk Team]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/blockfi-ceo-disregarded-warnings-about-ftx-ignored-risk-team</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/blockfi-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 08:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/blockfi-ceo-disregarded-warnings-about-ftx-ignored-risk-team</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By the time it filed for bankruptcy, BlockFi had around $1.2 billion in assets tied to FTX and Alameda.&nbsp;</p>
Warnings Ignored&nbsp;
<p>The document revealing the details was filed on behalf of former customers of BlockFi. According to the document, Prince disregarded and blatantly ignored several warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team over lending to FTX&rsquo;s sister entity, Alameda Research. However, Price allegedly dismissed all concerns from the team, with BlockFi lending Alameda Research around $217 million by August 2021. The risk management team had also flagged several risks associated with the FTT token used to secure the loans if they required liquidation. However, these warnings were also ignored. The filing stated that the risk management team flagged concerns as early as 2021.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As early as August 2021, BlockFi&rsquo;s risk management team was advised that Alameda&rsquo;s balance sheet was largely comprised of &lsquo;~7bb unlocked FTT and 11bb total including locked tokens based on unaudited financials. This set off alarms at BlockFi. Mr. Prince dismissed the concerns, urging the risk team to learn to &lsquo;get comfortable [with Alameda] being a three arrows size borrower, just with FTT and other collateral types instead of GBTC shares.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In January 2022, the risk management team stopped issuing warnings to Prince about loaning to Alameda Research. Instead, discussions moved to Slack, where the CEO occasionally acknowledged BlockFi&rsquo;s exposure to FTX and Alameda. BlockFi had around $1.2 billion in assets tied to Alameda and FTX when it filed for bankruptcy. Subsequently, BlockFi halted withdrawals on the 10th of November, 2022, citing the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
Bad Business Practices&nbsp;
<p>When BlockFi filed for bankruptcy, it stated that it had significant exposure to FTX and its associated entities. Furthermore, FTX US received a $400 million credit line from BlockFi, further deepening their association.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;BlockFi recalled its loans from Alameda [in June 2022], and Alameda repaid its outstanding balance to almost zero. BlockFi then could have walked away from the relationship. Instead, it re-lent Alameda nearly $900 million (between July and September 2022), almost exclusively collateralized by FTT.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The filing further stated that while the FTX collapse triggered BlockFi&rsquo;s downfall, poor decision-making and bad business practices were the ultimate reason behind BlockFi&rsquo;s bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It may be true that Alameda/FTX&rsquo;s downfall triggered BlockFi&rsquo;s downfall, but BlockFi&rsquo;s demise was rooted in business practices and decisions well preceding Alameda/FTX&rsquo;s bankruptcy filing.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The filing described BlockFi&rsquo;s functioning as a &ldquo;flawed business model&rdquo; and that the company took an unnecessary and unreasonable risk, leading to cataclysmic losses. It also added that BlockFi was not a regulated lending institution and challenged claims that BlockFi debtors are in a better position compared to FTX debtors.&nbsp;</p>
BlockFi Disagrees&nbsp;
<p>A representative from BlockFi responded to the filing, stating the company disagrees with the report, adding that the report cherry-picked statements and does not deliver an objective analysis. BlockFi blamed direct exposure to FTX as the reason for its bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Ultimately, BlockFi failed because FTX and Alameda were and are fraudulent enterprises, and the Special Committee [of independent directors] has not uncovered any evidence that the Released Parties knew, should have known, or reasonably could have known, about FTX&rsquo;s and Alameda&rsquo;s true nature.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Meanwhile, FTX and other companies have opposed BlockFi&rsquo;s bankruptcy plans in court filings, leading to delays in the execution of those plans. BlockFi currently owes between $1 billion to $10 billion to creditors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Court documents have revealed that Zac Prince, CEO of bankrupt crypto lending firm BlockFi, ignored warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team regarding exposure to FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By the time it filed for bankruptcy, BlockFi had around $1.2 billion in assets tied to FTX and Alameda.&nbsp;</p>
Warnings Ignored&nbsp;
<p>The document revealing the details was filed on behalf of former customers of BlockFi. According to the document, Prince disregarded and blatantly ignored several warnings from the company&rsquo;s risk management team over lending to FTX&rsquo;s sister entity, Alameda Research. However, Price allegedly dismissed all concerns from the team, with BlockFi lending Alameda Research around $217 million by August 2021. The risk management team had also flagged several risks associated with the FTT token used to secure the loans if they required liquidation. However, these warnings were also ignored. The filing stated that the risk management team flagged concerns as early as 2021.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;As early as August 2021, BlockFi&rsquo;s risk management team was advised that Alameda&rsquo;s balance sheet was largely comprised of &lsquo;~7bb unlocked FTT and 11bb total including locked tokens based on unaudited financials. This set off alarms at BlockFi. Mr. Prince dismissed the concerns, urging the risk team to learn to &lsquo;get comfortable [with Alameda] being a three arrows size borrower, just with FTT and other collateral types instead of GBTC shares.&rdquo;</p>

<p>In January 2022, the risk management team stopped issuing warnings to Prince about loaning to Alameda Research. Instead, discussions moved to Slack, where the CEO occasionally acknowledged BlockFi&rsquo;s exposure to FTX and Alameda. BlockFi had around $1.2 billion in assets tied to Alameda and FTX when it filed for bankruptcy. Subsequently, BlockFi halted withdrawals on the 10th of November, 2022, citing the collapse of FTX and Alameda Research.&nbsp;</p>
Bad Business Practices&nbsp;
<p>When BlockFi filed for bankruptcy, it stated that it had significant exposure to FTX and its associated entities. Furthermore, FTX US received a $400 million credit line from BlockFi, further deepening their association.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;BlockFi recalled its loans from Alameda [in June 2022], and Alameda repaid its outstanding balance to almost zero. BlockFi then could have walked away from the relationship. Instead, it re-lent Alameda nearly $900 million (between July and September 2022), almost exclusively collateralized by FTT.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The filing further stated that while the FTX collapse triggered BlockFi&rsquo;s downfall, poor decision-making and bad business practices were the ultimate reason behind BlockFi&rsquo;s bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It may be true that Alameda/FTX&rsquo;s downfall triggered BlockFi&rsquo;s downfall, but BlockFi&rsquo;s demise was rooted in business practices and decisions well preceding Alameda/FTX&rsquo;s bankruptcy filing.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The filing described BlockFi&rsquo;s functioning as a &ldquo;flawed business model&rdquo; and that the company took an unnecessary and unreasonable risk, leading to cataclysmic losses. It also added that BlockFi was not a regulated lending institution and challenged claims that BlockFi debtors are in a better position compared to FTX debtors.&nbsp;</p>
BlockFi Disagrees&nbsp;
<p>A representative from BlockFi responded to the filing, stating the company disagrees with the report, adding that the report cherry-picked statements and does not deliver an objective analysis. BlockFi blamed direct exposure to FTX as the reason for its bankruptcy.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Ultimately, BlockFi failed because FTX and Alameda were and are fraudulent enterprises, and the Special Committee [of independent directors] has not uncovered any evidence that the Released Parties knew, should have known, or reasonably could have known, about FTX&rsquo;s and Alameda&rsquo;s true nature.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Meanwhile, FTX and other companies have opposed BlockFi&rsquo;s bankruptcy plans in court filings, leading to delays in the execution of those plans. BlockFi currently owes between $1 billion to $10 billion to creditors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Binance Reportedly Cuts 1,000 Staff After Executives Exit Firm]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/binance-reportedly-cuts-1000-staff-after-executives-exit-firm</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-4.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-4.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/binance-1920-4.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 08:23:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/binance-reportedly-cuts-1000-staff-after-executives-exit-firm</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Binance reportedly laid off several staff members after a number of executives left the firm. </p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has cut its staff after an exodus of executives hit the firm, Reuters reports. The Wall Street Journal first reported the news, indicating more than 1,000 staff were let go over the past few weeks.</p>
CZ Disputes Media Reports
<p>The layoffs at Binance come after a wave of regulatory scrutiny in the US caused doubt in the industry&rsquo;s future. Binance and its rival Coinbase were sued by the US Securities and Exchange Commission for allegedly violating securities laws.</p>
<p>The SEC accused Binance and its CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao of operating a &ldquo;web of deception.&rdquo; The exchange vehemently denied the accusations and said it would defend itself vigorously.</p>
<p>Zhao took to Twitter to clarify media reports and said the numbers being reported are inaccurate. The exchange continues to appoint new staff.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As we continuously strive to increase talent density, there are involuntary terminations. This happens in every company. The numbers reported by media are all way off. 4 FUD. On the bright side, they just can&rsquo;t resist talking about us.We are still hiring. </p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) July 14, 2023
<p>

</p>
Executives Leave Binance
<p>Last week, Reuters reported a string of executives left Binance. The exchange&rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, Patrick Hillman, said in a tweet that he would be leaving the firm for personal reasons.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Apologies for any typos, but I was not expecting to be tweeting about this today. It&rsquo;s true that I am leaving @Binance, but I&rsquo;m doing so on good terms. I continue to respect and support @cz_binance and am grateful for having had the incredible opportunity to work under his&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) July 6, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Steven Christie, a compliance officer at the exchange, also announced via Twitter that he was leaving the firm. Christie said:</p>

<p>I usually don&rsquo;t tweet much and try and keep a low profile, but wanted to clear the air about a couple of articles that were printed today. I can confirm that I am indeed leaving @binance, but the reasons for my departure are very different than what was reported.</p>

<p>General Counsel for Binance, Hon Ng, also left the firm along with Yibo Ling, Binance&rsquo;s US-based chief business officer.</p>
<p>CZ also commented on reports of the executive exodus:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the &ldquo;news&rdquo; are completely wrong.As an organization that has grown from 30 to 8000 people in 6 years, from 0 to the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange in less than 5 months&hellip;</p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) July 6, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Binance told Reuters:</p>

<p>Over the last six years, we have grown from 30 to a team of almost 8,000 across the globe. As we prepare for the next major bull cycle, it has become clear that we need to focus on talent density across the organization to ensure we remain nimble and dynamic.</p>

Binance.US Lays Off Staff
<p>Soon after the SEC filed suit against Binance, Binance&rsquo;s US arm reportedly conducted a round of layoffs.</p>
<p>Sources said that around 50 people, or 10%, in the exchange&rsquo;s legal, compliance, and risk departments were dismissed.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto exchange Binance reportedly laid off several staff members after a number of executives left the firm. </p>
<p>Cryptocurrency exchange Binance has cut its staff after an exodus of executives hit the firm, Reuters reports. The Wall Street Journal first reported the news, indicating more than 1,000 staff were let go over the past few weeks.</p>
CZ Disputes Media Reports
<p>The layoffs at Binance come after a wave of regulatory scrutiny in the US caused doubt in the industry&rsquo;s future. Binance and its rival Coinbase were sued by the US Securities and Exchange Commission for allegedly violating securities laws.</p>
<p>The SEC accused Binance and its CEO Changpeng &ldquo;CZ&rdquo; Zhao of operating a &ldquo;web of deception.&rdquo; The exchange vehemently denied the accusations and said it would defend itself vigorously.</p>
<p>Zhao took to Twitter to clarify media reports and said the numbers being reported are inaccurate. The exchange continues to appoint new staff.&nbsp;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">As we continuously strive to increase talent density, there are involuntary terminations. This happens in every company. The numbers reported by media are all way off. 4 FUD. On the bright side, they just can&rsquo;t resist talking about us.We are still hiring. </p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) July 14, 2023
<p>

</p>
Executives Leave Binance
<p>Last week, Reuters reported a string of executives left Binance. The exchange&rsquo;s Chief Strategy Officer, Patrick Hillman, said in a tweet that he would be leaving the firm for personal reasons.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Apologies for any typos, but I was not expecting to be tweeting about this today. It&rsquo;s true that I am leaving @Binance, but I&rsquo;m doing so on good terms. I continue to respect and support @cz_binance and am grateful for having had the incredible opportunity to work under his&hellip;</p>
&mdash; Patrick Hillmann (@PRHillmann) July 6, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Steven Christie, a compliance officer at the exchange, also announced via Twitter that he was leaving the firm. Christie said:</p>

<p>I usually don&rsquo;t tweet much and try and keep a low profile, but wanted to clear the air about a couple of articles that were printed today. I can confirm that I am indeed leaving @binance, but the reasons for my departure are very different than what was reported.</p>

<p>General Counsel for Binance, Hon Ng, also left the firm along with Yibo Ling, Binance&rsquo;s US-based chief business officer.</p>
<p>CZ also commented on reports of the executive exodus:</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">4. More FUD about some departures. Yes, there is turnover (at every company). But the reasons dreamed up by the &ldquo;news&rdquo; are completely wrong.As an organization that has grown from 30 to 8000 people in 6 years, from 0 to the world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange in less than 5 months&hellip;</p>
&mdash; CZ  Binance (@cz_binance) July 6, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>A spokesperson for Binance told Reuters:</p>

<p>Over the last six years, we have grown from 30 to a team of almost 8,000 across the globe. As we prepare for the next major bull cycle, it has become clear that we need to focus on talent density across the organization to ensure we remain nimble and dynamic.</p>

Binance.US Lays Off Staff
<p>Soon after the SEC filed suit against Binance, Binance&rsquo;s US arm reportedly conducted a round of layoffs.</p>
<p>Sources said that around 50 people, or 10%, in the exchange&rsquo;s legal, compliance, and risk departments were dismissed.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Celsius Founder Alex Mashinsky Pleads Not Guilty $CEL]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-pleads-not-guilty-cel</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-network-case-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-network-case-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/celsius-network-case-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 23:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/celsius-founder-alex-mashinsky-pleads-not-guilty-cel</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The court session marks the latest twist in a long and complex narrative that has unfolded within the crypto lending industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">An Array of Charges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On the day of his arraignment, Mashinsky, 57, turned up to the Manhattan federal court in an understated gray polo shirt and jeans, and without handcuffs. He was arrested following a slew of lawsuits initiated by several federal regulatory agencies, including the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As reported by Reuters, the charges against Mashinsky and Celsius revolve around allegations that they "misled customers and artificially inflated the value of [Celsius's] propriety crypto token." In total, Mashinsky was charged with seven criminal counts, an indictment that was unsealed on the same day of his court appearance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A High-Profile Case</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This case isn't the first legal challenge Celsius and Mashinsky have faced. Earlier this year, New York state's attorney general also accused Mashinsky of fraud. Notably, Mashinsky's arrest comes at a time of increased scrutiny for the crypto industry, with numerous other platforms facing similar allegations. As Reuters puts it, the industry is undergoing "a reckoning after a slump in crypto prices led to the collapse of several companies."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a public statement, U.S. Attorney Damian Williams made his stance clear:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Whether it's old-school fraud or some new-school crypto scheme, it doesn't matter one bit. It's all fraud to us."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Accusations and Counterarguments</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Celsius Network, founded by Mashinsky in 2017, promised easy loan access and high interest rates to depositors, with the company lending out tokens to institutional investors with the intention of profiting from the difference. But the company filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in July 2022 after a wave of customer withdrawal requests during a downturn in crypto prices. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC's lawsuit against Mashinsky and Celsius alleges that the firm misled investors about the company's financial health, even as it pursued increasingly risky strategies to deliver high promised returns. Despite the significant loss of funds as customers rushed to withdraw, Mashinsky and Celsius continued to assert that the company was financially stable and had sufficient funds to meet withdrawals, the SEC claimed.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Awaiting What's Next</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the mounting allegations and legal challenges, Mashinsky and his legal team remain defiant. His attorneys, Benjamin Alee and Jonathan Ohring, have signaled their intent to challenge the charges, stating that Mashinsky "looks forward to vigorously defending himself in court against these baseless charges."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the case proceeds, the world will watch closely, considering the potential implications not just for Mashinsky and Celsius, but also for the broader crypto industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Alex Mashinsky, the former CEO of cryptocurrency lending platform Celsius Network, appeared in federal court last week, pleading not guilty to numerous charges, including securities fraud, commodities fraud, and wire fraud.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The court session marks the latest twist in a long and complex narrative that has unfolded within the crypto lending industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">An Array of Charges</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">On the day of his arraignment, Mashinsky, 57, turned up to the Manhattan federal court in an understated gray polo shirt and jeans, and without handcuffs. He was arrested following a slew of lawsuits initiated by several federal regulatory agencies, including the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As reported by Reuters, the charges against Mashinsky and Celsius revolve around allegations that they "misled customers and artificially inflated the value of [Celsius's] propriety crypto token." In total, Mashinsky was charged with seven criminal counts, an indictment that was unsealed on the same day of his court appearance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A High-Profile Case</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This case isn't the first legal challenge Celsius and Mashinsky have faced. Earlier this year, New York state's attorney general also accused Mashinsky of fraud. Notably, Mashinsky's arrest comes at a time of increased scrutiny for the crypto industry, with numerous other platforms facing similar allegations. As Reuters puts it, the industry is undergoing "a reckoning after a slump in crypto prices led to the collapse of several companies."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a public statement, U.S. Attorney Damian Williams made his stance clear:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Whether it's old-school fraud or some new-school crypto scheme, it doesn't matter one bit. It's all fraud to us."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Accusations and Counterarguments</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Celsius Network, founded by Mashinsky in 2017, promised easy loan access and high interest rates to depositors, with the company lending out tokens to institutional investors with the intention of profiting from the difference. But the company filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection in July 2022 after a wave of customer withdrawal requests during a downturn in crypto prices. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC's lawsuit against Mashinsky and Celsius alleges that the firm misled investors about the company's financial health, even as it pursued increasingly risky strategies to deliver high promised returns. Despite the significant loss of funds as customers rushed to withdraw, Mashinsky and Celsius continued to assert that the company was financially stable and had sufficient funds to meet withdrawals, the SEC claimed.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Awaiting What's Next</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Despite the mounting allegations and legal challenges, Mashinsky and his legal team remain defiant. His attorneys, Benjamin Alee and Jonathan Ohring, have signaled their intent to challenge the charges, stating that Mashinsky "looks forward to vigorously defending himself in court against these baseless charges."</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">As the case proceeds, the world will watch closely, considering the potential implications not just for Mashinsky and Celsius, but also for the broader crypto industry.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Synthetix Founder Launches Infinex Perpetuals Exchange $SNX]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/synthetix-founder-launches-infinex-perpetuals-exchange-snx</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/synthetix-perpetuals-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/synthetix-perpetuals-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/synthetix-perpetuals-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/synthetix-founder-launches-infinex-perpetuals-exchange-snx</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kain Warwick, founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The venture sets its sights on challenging the dominance of centralized exchanges such as Binance by prioritizing user experience, marking a notable shift in the DeFi status quo.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex: Reinventing DeFi User Experience</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The inception of Infinex reflects a crucial shift among blockchain developers. Increasingly, these innovators recognize that improving user experience is key to onboarding new users and expanding the DeFi sector. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a significant departure from typical DeFi user interfaces, Infinex eliminates the need to use a crypto wallet to sign transactions. Instead, it adopts a common approach: users create a username and password. Their private keys, still essential for signing transactions, are stored in their browsers. However, according to Warwick, these keys will not be able to withdraw deposited funds, prioritizing user security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Centralized Exchanges in Infinex&rsquo;s Sights</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Warwick has a clear vision for Infinex: directly compete with centralized exchanges like Binance. To achieve this, the exchange needs to balance several factors. It must ensure a user experience on par with centralized counterparts, maintain a genuinely decentralized framework, and address potential security concerhns of storing private keys in the browser.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex also recognizes the importance of regulatory compliance. The exchange is defsigned to minimize proprietary components, emphasizing its decentralized foundations and reshaping the traditional concept of liability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex Governance and Operational Design</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to details on the project shared via Mirror.xyz, Infinex won't issue its own token for governance purposes. Instead, it will use Synthetix's SNX token to manage its governance. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex's initial target market comprises existing crypto traders. To kickstart their trading on Infinex, users will need to deposit either USDT or USDC, both dollar-pegged stablecoins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The exchange is expected to generate revenue from several sources, including trading fees, integration fees from a rewards program, and fees from staking SNX.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the unveiling of Infinex, Warwick brings a fresh perspective to the DeFi sector, placing a premium on user experience. This approach underscores a shift in priorities within the industry and sets a new standard for decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By focusing on existing crypto traders, Infinex makes a calculated move to attract a significant segment of the market that currently operates on centralized exchanges. The success of this approach will undoubtedly be observed closely by other players in the DeFi sector.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Kain Warwick, founder of the Synthetix derivatives protocol, has introduced Infinex, a new decentralized perpetuals exchange.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The venture sets its sights on challenging the dominance of centralized exchanges such as Binance by prioritizing user experience, marking a notable shift in the DeFi status quo.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex: Reinventing DeFi User Experience</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The inception of Infinex reflects a crucial shift among blockchain developers. Increasingly, these innovators recognize that improving user experience is key to onboarding new users and expanding the DeFi sector. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a significant departure from typical DeFi user interfaces, Infinex eliminates the need to use a crypto wallet to sign transactions. Instead, it adopts a common approach: users create a username and password. Their private keys, still essential for signing transactions, are stored in their browsers. However, according to Warwick, these keys will not be able to withdraw deposited funds, prioritizing user security.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Centralized Exchanges in Infinex&rsquo;s Sights</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Warwick has a clear vision for Infinex: directly compete with centralized exchanges like Binance. To achieve this, the exchange needs to balance several factors. It must ensure a user experience on par with centralized counterparts, maintain a genuinely decentralized framework, and address potential security concerhns of storing private keys in the browser.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex also recognizes the importance of regulatory compliance. The exchange is defsigned to minimize proprietary components, emphasizing its decentralized foundations and reshaping the traditional concept of liability.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex Governance and Operational Design</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to details on the project shared via Mirror.xyz, Infinex won't issue its own token for governance purposes. Instead, it will use Synthetix's SNX token to manage its governance. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Infinex's initial target market comprises existing crypto traders. To kickstart their trading on Infinex, users will need to deposit either USDT or USDC, both dollar-pegged stablecoins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The exchange is expected to generate revenue from several sources, including trading fees, integration fees from a rewards program, and fees from staking SNX.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">With the unveiling of Infinex, Warwick brings a fresh perspective to the DeFi sector, placing a premium on user experience. This approach underscores a shift in priorities within the industry and sets a new standard for decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By focusing on existing crypto traders, Infinex makes a calculated move to attract a significant segment of the market that currently operates on centralized exchanges. The success of this approach will undoubtedly be observed closely by other players in the DeFi sector.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Mining Firm Hive Rebrands, Pivots To AI and Web3 $HIVE]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-mining-firm-hive-rebrands-pivots-to-ai-and-web3</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hive-digital-technologies-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hive-digital-technologies-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/hive-digital-technologies-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-mining-firm-hive-rebrands-pivots-to-ai-and-web3</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Crypto mining company Hive Blockchain Technologies has unveiled its new brand identity, Hive Digital Technologies, representing a strategic shift towards artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Canadian firm aims to leverage its vast Nvidia graphics processing unit (GPU) fleet to tap into burgeoning opportunities in AI and cloud computing.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">An Evolved Focus</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a statement issued on July 12, Hive Digital revealed that the updated brand better represents the company's current focus. In the burgeoning era of GPU cloud technology, Hive is poised to expand its Nvidia GPU-oriented revenue channels while also contributing to AI advancements that propel the new Web3 ecosystem.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We're excited to announce that today we officially changed our name to   . The name better reflects our evolving focus on cloud compute technology, AI and the Web3 ecosystem.Read the press release: https://t.co/yczuLivGq6 pic.twitter.com/5jijZFqdeI</p>
&mdash; HIVE Digital Technologies (@HIVEDigitalTech) July 12, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to Hive's CEO Aydin Kilic, the company plans to grow its cloud hosting business using its extensive GPU fleet, recognising the growing demand driven by AI and machine learning applications. In addition to crypto mining, Hive will offer rental services of GPU server clusters and introduce a new service, HIVE Cloud. The service targets small and medium-sized businesses, offering them an efficient and cost-effective alternative to major cloud service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">From Crypto Mining to AI Cloud Services</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Established in 2017, Hive has been a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining sector. Despite maintaining a strong presence in Bitcoin mining, the company sees tremendous potential in leveraging its 38,000 Nvidia GPU fleet for large-scale computational tasks.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Hive has been using these high-performance GPUs to mine Ether (ETH), the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum network. However, since Ethereum transitioned to a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism in September 2022, reducing the profitability of mining, the company has been exploring other revenue streams for its GPUs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Hive's rebranding comes as several mining companies pivot from their original blockchain-focused models. Earlier this year, Riot Blockchain, a Bitcoin mining firm, rebranded to Riot Platforms to reflect its diversified business operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Projected Market Impact</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an official press release, Hive's Executive Chairman, Frank Holmes, expressed optimism for the AI sector's potential, highlighting large language models (LLMs) like ChatGPT as a driving factor. According to Holmes, the high-margin business opportunity with their Nvidia GPU cards could generate over $100,000,000 in annual revenues.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Crypto mining company Hive Blockchain Technologies has unveiled its new brand identity, Hive Digital Technologies, representing a strategic shift towards artificial intelligence (AI).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Canadian firm aims to leverage its vast Nvidia graphics processing unit (GPU) fleet to tap into burgeoning opportunities in AI and cloud computing.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">An Evolved Focus</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a statement issued on July 12, Hive Digital revealed that the updated brand better represents the company's current focus. In the burgeoning era of GPU cloud technology, Hive is poised to expand its Nvidia GPU-oriented revenue channels while also contributing to AI advancements that propel the new Web3 ecosystem.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">We're excited to announce that today we officially changed our name to   . The name better reflects our evolving focus on cloud compute technology, AI and the Web3 ecosystem.Read the press release: https://t.co/yczuLivGq6 pic.twitter.com/5jijZFqdeI</p>
&mdash; HIVE Digital Technologies (@HIVEDigitalTech) July 12, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p">According to Hive's CEO Aydin Kilic, the company plans to grow its cloud hosting business using its extensive GPU fleet, recognising the growing demand driven by AI and machine learning applications. In addition to crypto mining, Hive will offer rental services of GPU server clusters and introduce a new service, HIVE Cloud. The service targets small and medium-sized businesses, offering them an efficient and cost-effective alternative to major cloud service providers.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">From Crypto Mining to AI Cloud Services</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Established in 2017, Hive has been a pioneer in the cryptocurrency mining sector. Despite maintaining a strong presence in Bitcoin mining, the company sees tremendous potential in leveraging its 38,000 Nvidia GPU fleet for large-scale computational tasks.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Hive has been using these high-performance GPUs to mine Ether (ETH), the native cryptocurrency of the Ethereum network. However, since Ethereum transitioned to a proof-of-stake consensus mechanism in September 2022, reducing the profitability of mining, the company has been exploring other revenue streams for its GPUs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Hive's rebranding comes as several mining companies pivot from their original blockchain-focused models. Earlier this year, Riot Blockchain, a Bitcoin mining firm, rebranded to Riot Platforms to reflect its diversified business operations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Projected Market Impact</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In an official press release, Hive's Executive Chairman, Frank Holmes, expressed optimism for the AI sector's potential, highlighting large language models (LLMs) like ChatGPT as a driving factor. According to Holmes, the high-margin business opportunity with their Nvidia GPU cards could generate over $100,000,000 in annual revenues.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
