<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>3 Most Serious Claims in the SEC Lawsuit V. Binance</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253936</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Binance_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here are the allegations prompting the SEC to try and shut down Binance’s entire business. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On Monday, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) pressed a slew of charges against Binance, marking one of the agency’s most significant enforcement actions against the crypto industry in history. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Let’s have a look at the regulator’s most stunning allegations against the exchange, alongside Binance’s response to its claims. </span></p>
<h2>What Did Binance Do?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The </span><a href="https://www.docdroid.net/I02zzqT/sec-v-binance-4-pdf#page=2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">136-page filing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> accused Binance and Binance US of partaking in “unregistered offers and sales” of crypto asset securities, while serving the function of an “exchange, broker-dealer, and clearing agency” without prior registration. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Among its illegal securities offerings were its yield-generation schemes “BNB Vault” and “Simple Earn,” alongside the platform’s native token BNB, and its stablecoin BUSD. BNB is currently the 4th largest cryptocurrency by market cap, and Binance holds a significant portion of its total supply. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Without the oversight typical of registered exchanges and broker-dealers, the SEC said Binance also moved and commingled customer assets in ways that regulated firms wouldn’t have been able to.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">For example, the agency said Binance and Binance US commingled billions of dollars in users assets from both platforms within an entity called “Merit Peaked Limited”, which is controlled by both Binance and its CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Those assets were then transferred to third parties – similar to what former FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried had done at his now-collapsed exchange. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In general, the lawsuit claims that Binance and CZ exercised control over Binance US and the assets on its platform, despite the pretense of independence from the American entity. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">It also accused Binance of secretly continuing to service its most valuable US clients at the international exchange, as alleged by the Commodities and Futures Trading Commission in March. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Finally, the SEC alleged a Zhao-controlled entity called “Sigma Chain” engaged in wash trading at Binance US to inflate the trading volume and valuation of certain assets on the platform. This was possible since the entity did not implement the “surveillance or manipulative trading controls” that the firm’s management promised investors. </span></p>
<h2>Binance’s Punishment and Response</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As punishment for its violations, the SEC seeks to ban Binance from the securities and crypto trading businesses altogether and to pay disgorgement penalties for any of its ill-gotten gains that resulted from its actions, plus pre-judgment interest. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a public response </span><a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/sec-complaint-aims-to-unilaterally-define-crypto-market-structure-8707489117122437402" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">letter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Binance accused the SEC of not prioritizing investors, but instead attempting to gain “jurisdictional ground” in overseeing crypto against other regulators.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“All user assets on Binance and Binance affiliate platforms, including Binance.US, are safe and secure, and we will vigorously defend against any allegations to the contrary,” wrote the company. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Binance </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-responds-to-reuters-claims-about-mixing-user-funds/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">denied</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> claims made by Reuters last month that it had mixed user funds with corporate funds, saying any “mixing” that occurred was simply to convert users’ dollar deposits into BUSD. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3-most-serious-claims-in-the-sec-lawsuit-v-binance/" rel="nofollow">3 Most Serious Claims in the SEC Lawsuit V. Binance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Metropolitan Museum of Art to Return FTX&#8217;s $550K Donations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-metropolitan-museum-of-art-to-return-ftxs-550k-donations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253832</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Metropolitan_FTX.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Metropolitan_FTX.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Met is the latest FTX beneficiary to return donations to the bankrupt company.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Metropolitan Museum of Art (the Met) has agreed to return the $550,000 donations it received from bankrupt crypto exchange FTX last year.</p>
<p>The donations were made by West Realm Shires Services, an affiliated entity of FTX responsible for overseeing the operations of FTX.US, the American division of the company.</p>
<p>The firm donated around $300,000 to the museum in March 2022 and another $250,000 in May before FTX encountered a liquidity crisis in November, leading to its devastating collapse.</p>
<h2>Agreement in Good Faith</h2>
<p>According to a recent <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.deb.188450/gov.uscourts.deb.188450.1562.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">court filing</a> at the United States Bankruptcy Court in Delaware on June 2, 2023, the New York-based museum, which harbors more than 1.5 million paintings, is set to return the funds as part of a settlement aimed at repaying creditors.</p>
<p>The court document showed that both parties engaged in transparent negotiations, striving to achieve a mutually acceptable resolution, noting that the agreement came from the back of good faith.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Met wishes to return the Donations to the FTX Debtors, and the FTX Debtors and the Met have engaged in good faith, arm&#8217;s length negotiations concerning the return of the Donations,&#8221; reads the court document.</p></blockquote>
<p>The museum said in its filing that repayments would be finalized within a month once the court approves the settlement.</p>
<h2>FTX Seeks to Claw Back Donated Funds</h2>
<p>FTX was one of the leading global crypto exchanges in the industry before its demise. Under the leadership of its founder and former CEO, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the firm was known for advocating the concept of impactful benevolence, utilizing funds raised by the exchange to support various commendable causes, including political campaigns.</p>
<p>Since its demise, the company has been trying to reclaim the donations to aid its restructuring plan. In February, it issued a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-requests-return-of-donations-from-sbfs-political-beneficiaries/" data-wpel-link="internal">press release</a>, demanding politicians and charity organizations who received political contributions from FTX and its executives to return the funds or face legal consequences.</p>
<p>Court documents showed that the exchange donated approximately $93 million to 180 politicians in the United States between March 2020 and November 2022.</p>
<p>SBF ranked second in contributions to the Democratic party during the last election cycle, following George Soros, who claimed the top spot with a remarkable donation of over $128 million.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, some politicians who benefited from the company&#8217;s benevolence last year have already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/democratic-pac-to-return-3-million-of-ftxs-political-donations/" data-wpel-link="internal">returned</a> their funds, distancing themselves from the exchange.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-metropolitan-museum-of-art-to-return-ftxs-550k-donations/" rel="nofollow">US Metropolitan Museum of Art to Return FTX&#8217;s $550K Donations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Transaction Fees Drop by 80% as PEPE Enters a Slumber</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-transaction-fees-drop-by-80-as-pepe-enters-a-slumber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253810</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ethereum_shadow_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/ethereum_shadow_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's memecoin frenzy via Ordinals has also simmered down. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum gas fees spiked to their highest level since 2022 following May&#8217;s memecoin comeback championed by the emergence of &#8220;Pepe the frog&#8221; themed altcoin, PEPE. This trend, however, appears to have slowed down amidst a waning interest in PEPE despite transforming several investors into overnight millionaires.</p>
<p>According to new data by on-chain analytic firm IntoTheBlock, the total Ethereum transaction fees declined by more than 16% this week alone.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Total Ethereum transaction fees dropped by 16.5% this week! May&#8217;s meme token mania that fueled the recent fee spike seems to be receding into crypto history. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ethereum?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Ethereum</a> <a href="https://t.co/QuKgve8wNM" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/QuKgve8wNM</a></p>
<p>— IntoTheBlock (@intotheblock) <a href="https://twitter.com/intotheblock/status/1664587764137082890?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 2, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>On zooming out, the transaction fee <a href="https://etherscan.io/chart/avg-txfee-usd" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">dropped</a> by 80% over one month from $27.62 on May 5th to $5.50 as of June 4th. The figure is currently hovering near a level last seen during mid-April.</li>
<li>The latest development comes as a major respite for the blockchain, whose critics have forever deemed the exorbitant gas fee as its &#8220;fatal flaw.&#8221;</li>
<li>Apart from mainnet, Ethereum layer 2 scaling solutions were also hit by surging transaction fees during the memecoin renaissance last month.</li>
<li>Notable spikes were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/someone-just-lost-120k-in-a-costly-mistake-with-eth-fees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">seen</a> particularly on chains built using zero-knowledge proofs such as Polygon zkEVM and zkSync Era. In fact, the cost of a single transaction on these rollups ranged between $2 to $11, temporarily rising as high as $30.</li>
<li>Pepe&#8217;s market cap, on the other hand, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-meme-coins-to-watch-as-pepe-coin-mania-winds-down/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">witnessed</a> a significant drawdown from $1.15 billion to $450 million over the past month.</li>
<li>Its price was down by over 60% during the same period despite listing support by prominent crypto exchanges, including Binance.</li>
<li>Besides Ethereum, the Bitcoin network&#8217;s memecoin frenzy led by Ordinals&#8217; inscriptions has also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">faded</a> considerably in recent weeks. As a result, the transaction fee on the network was back in mid-April level.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-transaction-fees-drop-by-80-as-pepe-enters-a-slumber/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Transaction Fees Drop by 80% as PEPE Enters a Slumber</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wall Street Memes Raises $4 Million: Which Crypto Presales to Watch this Week?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-memes-raises-4-million-which-crypto-presales-to-watch-this-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253863</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CryptoPotato-1200x780-2.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/CryptoPotato-1200x780-2.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Identifying potential investment opportunities in the fast-paced cryptocurrency market can often be challenging – especially given the sheer volume of new coins and tokens launched each week. However, this also means that the crypto market has a constant influx of innovative projects with exponential growth potential. In this article, we delve into three promising cryptocurrencies [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Identifying potential investment opportunities in the fast-paced cryptocurrency market can often be challenging – especially given the sheer volume of new coins and tokens launched each week.</p>
<p>However, this also means that the crypto market has a constant influx of innovative projects with exponential growth potential.</p>
<p>In this article, we delve into three promising cryptocurrencies – Wall Street Memes, yPredict, and Ecoterra – each offering scope for potential gains in the coming weeks and months.</p>
<h2>Wall Street Memes Harnesses Power of Community &amp; Raises Over $4 Million in Under Two Weeks</h2>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Memes</a> (WSM) has been one of the most talked-about cryptocurrency projects over the past week. This dynamic meme coin only launched its presale phase on May 26, yet has already raised an incredible $4 million from early investors.</p>
<p>The project draws inspiration from the subculture formed around the WallStreetBets subreddit, which gained fame following the GameStop and AMC short squeezes in 2021.</p>
<p>However, the project’s developers have already tasted success of their own – launching an NFT collection called <a href="https://opensea.io/collection/wall-street-bulls" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Wall Street Bulls</a>, which sold out in 32 minutes and generated $2.5 million in revenue.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253871" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-3.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="297" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-3-300x148.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-3-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The team is now focusing on the cryptocurrency market, launching the WSM token. This community-focused token is designed to empower holders to benefit from the continued evolution of the Wall Street Memes community, which comprises over 1.1 million people.</p>
<p>The community has reacted positively to the launch of WSM, with the official Telegram channel seeing a wave of new members in the past 14 days.</p>
<p>Moreover, several prominent crypto influencers have also expressed their support for WSM.</p>
<p>My Financial Friend, a well-known crypto YouTuber with over 236,000 subscribers, released a video recently where he speculated that WSM could be the next 10x meme coin.</p>
<p>The backing from big names like My Financial Friend has created even more buzz around Wall Street Memes – contributing to the project&#8217;s substantial early fundraising.</p>
<p>Currently, investors can buy WSM tokens through the project’s presale for $0.0271 – a 24% discount on the final stage price.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_54c27399.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Wall Street Memes Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Polygon-Based yPredict Seeks to Revolutionize Crypto Analytics After Raising Over $2m</h2>
<p>Another crypto recently making headlines is yPredict (YPRED) – the trailblazing crypto analytics platform built on the Polygon blockchain.</p>
<p>Like Wall Street Memes, yPredict has hit the ground running, raising over $2 million through its active presale.</p>
<p>Not only that, but yPredict already has over 20,000 users on its waiting list ahead of the platform’s launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-5.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253872" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-5.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-5.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-5-300x199.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-5-50x33.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>The buzz around yPredict is palpable, with the crypto community showing immense interest due to the platform’s unique predictive analytics tools.</p>
<p>As outlined in yPredict’s whitepaper, users can access real-time trading signals, sentiment analysis, AI-powered technical analysis, automated chart pattern recognition, and more.</p>
<p>yPredict will also have a prediction marketplace, where top artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) experts can sell their advanced predictive models, and users can subscribe to them using YPRED – yPredict&#8217;s native token.</p>
<p>Holders of YPRED have the added benefit of staking their tokens to generate a steady yield. This yield is derived from the fees collected from predictive model subscription services, a portion of which is allocated to the rewards pool.</p>
<p>All in all, yPredict is standing out as a pioneering entity in the crypto analytics space – and with early investors able to buy YPRED for just $0.09 through the ongoing presale, it’s clear why the project is drawing so much attention.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<h2>Sustainability-Focused Ecoterra Raises $4.7 Million for Building Recylce2Earn App</h2>
<p>Lastly, the sustainability-focused project Ecoterra (ECOTERRA) is also making waves throughout the crypto community.</p>
<p>Ecoterra has surpassed the $4.7 million funding milestone in its ongoing presale, which is now in its second-last stage – meaning prospective investors only have a narrow window to secure ECOTERRA tokens at a discount.</p>
<p>The success of Ecoterra’s presale can be attributed to its groundbreaking approach to environmental conservation, which leverages the power of blockchain technology to create a transparent and accountable platform.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253873" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-3.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="264" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-3.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-3-300x132.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-3-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Per Ecoterra’s whitepaper, users can earn <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ECOTERRA tokens</a> for recycling used materials like glass, cardboard, and plastic. Moreover, users can then spend these tokens in the carbon offset marketplace to counterbalance their carbon footprint.</p>
<p>Ecoterra’s ecosystem will also boast a recycled materials marketplace, where businesses can seamlessly purchase used resources, and a public “Impact Profile” for each user.</p>
<p>Adding more hype to the project&#8217;s appeal is that the development team boasts extensive experience in the European recycling industry – meaning they&#8217;re well-equipped to drive Ecoterra towards a successful future.</p>
<p>With Ecoterra’s official <a href="https://twitter.com/ecoterraio" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter account</a> swelling to over 15,700 followers, it&#8217;s clear that the project is quickly gaining momentum, paving the way for an impactful second half of 2023.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit the Ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wall-street-memes-raises-4-million-which-crypto-presales-to-watch-this-week/" rel="nofollow">Wall Street Memes Raises $4 Million: Which Crypto Presales to Watch this Week?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Joins $1 Billion Bitcoin Mining Initiative in El Salvador</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-joins-1-billion-bitcoin-mining-initiative-in-el-salvador/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 20:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253915</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/El_Salvador_Volcano_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/El_Salvador_Volcano_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Tether is expanding into El Salvador-based Bitcoin mining powered by the region’s volcanoes. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">An El Salvador-based Bitcoin firm has begun the first phase of a planned $1 billion investment into sustainably powered digital asset mining in the country.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The firm behind the project, “Volcano Energy,” said in a </span><a href="https://volcano-energy.tiiny.co/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">press release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that its chief goal is to “position El Salvador as a prominent global player in the Bitcoin mining industry.”</span></p>
<h2>A Special Anniversary Announcement</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Volcano Energy’s </span><a href="https://volcano-energy.tiiny.co/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">announcement</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> comes exactly two years after El Salvador President Nayib Bukele revealed that Bitcoin would be deemed legal tender across his country in June 2021. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">So far, the firm has raised $250 million for the project, bootstrapped by “key Bitcoin industry leaders,” and “top manufacturers” of Bitcoin industry tech. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Right now, the company is developing a 241 MW capacity power generation facility powered solely by wind and solar, starting with a computational capacity of 1.3 EH/s. This will pave the way for geothermal-powered mining down the line. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-bull-max-keiser-has-high-hopes-for-el-salvadors-btc-volcano-bonds/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Max Keiser</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – a member of El Salvador’s national <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-launches-a-national-bitcoin-office-onbtc/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin Office</a> – is now the Chairman of Volcano Energy.  “The goal is economic liberty, self-determination &amp; sovereign wealth accumulation for generations to come,” he said in a tweet regarding the raise.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">El Salvador&#8217;s government will be involved with planning and executing the initiative and will earn 23% of the Bitcoin revenue it generates. Another 27% of revenues will go to investors, while the final 50% is reinvested into developing mining infrastructure.</span></p>
<p>El Salvador is occupied by more than a dozen volcanoes that its national government has already <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-president-shares-images-of-what-seems-to-be-its-volcano-powered-bitcoin-mining-facility/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">demonstrated</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> being used to mine BTC. </span></p>
<h2>Tether’s Involvement</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The investment includes backing from Tether – the world’s largest stablecoin provider – which revealed last month that it was breaking into mining in Uruguay. Given Tether’s domination of the stablecoin space, the company </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-generated-1-5b-in-profits-in-q1-2023-holds-2-bitcoin-in-total-reserves/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">reported</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> a net profit of $1.5 billion in Q1 2023. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether CTO Paolo Ardoino </span><a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1665734136617656321" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">clarified</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Monday that its investment is “well within its own excess reserves,” and that all USDT tokens remain fully backed.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The potential of El Salvador as the global energy and bitcoin hub is immense, and at Tether we&#8217;re grateful to be part of this opportunity,” he said.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Tether <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-to-launch-sustainable-bitcoin-mining-operations-in-uruguay/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> last month that it is investing in sustainable Bitcoin mining in Uruguay, where it plans to leave a “minimal ecological footprint.&#8221;</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-joins-1-billion-bitcoin-mining-initiative-in-el-salvador/" rel="nofollow">Tether Joins $1 Billion Bitcoin Mining Initiative in El Salvador</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>As the Ripple v. SEC June 13th Deadline Approaches, Commission Deletes Hinman&#8217;s Bio</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-ripple-v-sec-june-13th-deadline-approaches-commission-deletes-hinmans-bio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253900</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ripple_sec_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/03/ripple_sec_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC must hand over unredacted emails of Hinman’s internal communications by next week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has mysteriously removed former commissioner William Hinman’s biography from its website.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This occurs only 8 days before the court requires the SEC to provide unredacted copies of all of Hinman’s emails – widely viewed as paramount to the agency’s lawsuit with crypto industry giant Ripple. </span></p>
<h2>Are Hinman’s Emails the Smoking Gun?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On the SEC’s site, Hinman’s biography now only includes his name, photo, and his previous role as the “Director of the Division of Corporation Finance” from May 2017 to Dec. 2020. His former bio stated that in his role, Hinman provided “interpretive assistance to companies with respect to SEC rules, and makes recommendations to the Commission regarding new and existing rules.”</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">The <a href="https://twitter.com/SECGov?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@SECGov</a> has now removed Bill Hinman&#39;s biography from its website. Getting ready to throw him under the bus. <a href="https://t.co/O7HCUGWSgt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/O7HCUGWSgt</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Mr. Huber<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f985.png" alt="🦅" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f525.png" alt="🔥" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Leerzeit) <a href="https://twitter.com/Leerzeit/status/1665662937376145408?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The month of Hinman’s departure was the same month that the SEC filed its suit against Ripple Labs for its unregistered sale of the cryptocurrency XRP, which collapsed in value that day by 45% and has fallen far away from its former position as a top 3 crypto by market cap. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hinman is known for having delivered a </span><a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/speech/speech-hinman-061418" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">speech</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in 2018 saying that he did not view current transactions and sales of Ether as securities transactions. Given that XRP was distributed in a similar way to ETH, Ripple and other SEC critics have long sought internal transcripts and discussions on the speech to determine if ETH was getting preferential treatment over XRP. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400">The End is Near<br />
</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The Ripple V. SEC case has loomed large over the U.S. crypto industry, which seeks clarity and legal precedent on which cryptocurrencies will be delegated as securities in the United States. Both the SEC and Ripple filed for summary judgment in December 2022, bringing hope that its conclusion might be on the horizon. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ripple’s victory in </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-obtains-hinman-documents-optimistic-about-sec-case/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">securing</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> Hinman’s speech documents in October 2022 was also considered a major victory, but they remained confidential at the time. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Prominent voices in crypto such as </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-vs-sec-lawsuit-to-wrap-up-as-soon-as-june-charles-hoskinson/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Charles Hoskinson</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> believe the SEC lawsuit will likely conclude this month. Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse said early last month that he was expecting a summary judgment on the case to be submitted within “3 to 6 weeks.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ripple has already spent $200 million in court to defend its case that XRP is not a security, as it does not satisfy all requirements of the SEC’s oft-cited Howey Test. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-ripple-v-sec-june-13th-deadline-approaches-commission-deletes-hinmans-bio/" rel="nofollow">As the Ripple v. SEC June 13th Deadline Approaches, Commission Deletes Hinman&#8217;s Bio</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Plummets After SEC Sues Binance for Securities Violations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253881</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/cz_binance_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The agency alleged that Binance’s native tokens, including BUSD and BNB, are unregistered securities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed a lawsuit against Binance – the world’s largest crypto exchange – on Monday, alongside its CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) and partner firm, Binance US.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Allegations include securities law violations such as self-dealing market manipulation, and the sale/offer of multiple unregistered securities. </span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">According to a </span><a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2023-101" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">press release</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the SEC on Monday, the agency alleged that both Binance and Binance US operated “unregistered national securities exchanges, broker-dealers, and clearing agencies.”</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Some of Binance’s unregistered products include its staking program, certain crypto lending products, and its native exchange tokens BUSD and BNB. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">The SEC also echoed </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-addresses-the-cftc-in-house-trading-allegations/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">allegations</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the Commodities and Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) in March, such as market manipulation and illegal service to U.S. clients from its international platform. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">“Through thirteen charges, we allege that Zhao and Binance entities engaged in an extensive web of deception, conflicts of interest, lack of disclosure, and calculated evasion of the law,” said SEC Chair Gary Gensler in a prepared statement. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin immediately tanked on the news, dropping from $26,800 before the release to just $26,297 at press time. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">In response, CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1665742100845961217" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">tweeted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> “4” – a sign to followers to ignore negative press and “fake news” about the exchange designed to spread fear, uncertainty, and doubt. “We will issue a response once we see the complaint,” he added.  </span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Plummets After SEC Sues Binance for Securities Violations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Whales Selling at Huge Losses as Meme Coins Continue Bleeding</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-whales-selling-at-huge-losses-as-meme-coins-continue-bleeding/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:45:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253850</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sad_pepe_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/sad_pepe_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Meme coins have seen better days. Some PEPE coin whales are calling it quits and are selling at considerable losses.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PEPE coin whales have seen better days as the cryptocurrency loses another 9% in the past 24 hours. Some of the larger investors are calling it quits and are selling at a considerable loss.</p>
<ul>
<li>Data from the popular on-chain analytics resource <em>Lookonchain </em>revealed that at least two whales are realizing considerable losses.</li>
<li>One of them is an address ending at 0x4614, which sold a total of 375.8 billion PEPE at a loss of $142,000 (worth some 76 ETH) today.</li>
<li>Another whale sold around 257 billion PEPE (worth $306K) at a loss of about $35,000.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Whales/SmartMoneys are selling <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a>.</p>
<p>A whale deposited 649B <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a>($761K) 1 hr ago.</p>
<p>0x4614 who made 1,182 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a>($2.2M) on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a> sold 375.8B <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a>($306K) at a loss of 76 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$ETH</a>($142K) 1 hr ago.</p>
<p>0x6544 who made $352K on <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a> sold 257.9B <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PEPE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$PEPE</a>($306K) at a loss of $35K 4 hrs ago. <a href="https://t.co/w8crgva6S0" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/w8crgva6S0</a></p>
<p>— Lookonchain (@lookonchain) <a href="https://twitter.com/lookonchain/status/1665689366855925762?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 5, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>The broader market for meme coins continues bleeding out.</li>
<li>Data from CoinMarketCap shows that almost all of the larger meme coins are trading at considerable losses.</li>
<li>For the past seven days, DOGE is down 2.5%, SHIB &#8211; 4.2%, PEPE &#8211; 20%, FLOKI &#8211; 7.83%, BONE &#8211; 13.3%, ELON &#8211; 4.2%, and so forth.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepe-whales-selling-at-huge-losses-as-meme-coins-continue-bleeding/" rel="nofollow">PEPE Whales Selling at Huge Losses as Meme Coins Continue Bleeding</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Prepare for the Next Bitcoin Bull Market: 10 Tips You Must Know</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/how-to-prepare-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market-10-tips-you-must-know/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 13:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253845</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_bull_market_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/btc_bull_market_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin bull markets are typically categorized by tremendous price swings, and even though the direction is up, corrections also take place. During the last Bitcoin bull market that took place in 2021, the BTC price reached an all-time high just shy of $70K. It started the year trading at around $20K, exploded above $60K on [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin bull markets are typically categorized by tremendous price swings, and even though the direction is up, corrections also take place.</p>
<p>During the last Bitcoin bull market that took place in 2021, the BTC price reached an all-time high just shy of $70K. It started the year trading at around $20K, exploded above $60K on a couple of different occasions, retraced by almost 50% toward the middle of the year, and shot up once again to almost touch $70K in November.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253846" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253846" style="width: 624px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253846" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-2.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="624" height="423" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-2.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-2-300x203.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-2-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253846" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>The previous bull market was back in 2017 and the beginning of 2018. Bitcoin had reached a high of around $20,000, but its chart looked a lot differently:</p>
<figure id="attachment_253847" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253847" style="width: 624px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253847" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-4.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="624" height="485" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-4.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-4-300x233.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-4-50x39.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253847" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoinGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>As you can see, each cycle has its own intricacies, and playing it correctly could make or break your bankroll. Riding an uptrend can be a lot more challenging than just holding on to your assets. There’s knowledge involved as to when is the right moment to sell or reposition yourself to bets preserve your gains.</p>
<p>The last thing you want is to be left holding a bag of an altcoin that’s down 99% since its all-time high and pray that it will go there once again.</p>
<p>With this in mind, we’ve prepared 10 tips that everyone should know, and they should help you to better navigate the next Bitcoin bull market.</p>
<h2>10 Tips For the Next Bitcoin Bull Market</h2>
<h3>Educate Yourself</h3>
<p>Regardless of what you invest in, gaining sound knowledge of its underlying merits is step number one in any investor’s playbook. You absolutely must know what you invest in, and the same goes for Bitcoin (or any altcoin, for that matter).</p>
<p>Familiarize yourself with Bitcoin’s fundamentals, such as its total limited supply, utility, and adoption rates.</p>
<p>You can also analyze historical price patterns, market cycles, and factors that tend to influence Bitcoin’s price. This knowledge will definitely help you make more informed decisions.</p>
<p>A great place to start learning more about the BTC fundamentals is our section called <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-for-beginners/" data-wpel-link="internal">Bitcoin for Beginners</a>. It contains a lot of helpful information, such as who created Bitcoin, who is eligible to create an account, how to store Bitcoin, is it safe, and much more.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-234217" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls.jpg" alt="Bitcoin_Bulls" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin_Bulls-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h3>Research and Analyze</h3>
<p>Once you have the fundamentals down, it’s important to stay informed about both Bitcoin and the broader cryptocurrency market. Think about it this way &#8211; if you’re investing in land, you will undoubtedly analyze the factors that could impact it. These include the condition of the land, what you can grow on it, but also &#8211; who your neighbors are, the general area where it’s located, and so forth.</p>
<p>The same goes for investing in Bitcoin. You should stay informed about what’s going on in the market. You can read books, follow reputable news sources, join online communities, and in general &#8211; do a ton of other things that will help you learn about the technology.</p>
<p>In turn, this will help you anticipate market trends and potential catalysts, which can maximize the return on your investment in Bitcoin.</p>
<h3>Define Your Investment Goals</h3>
<p>What are your plans for the money invested in Bitcoin? When do you want to cash out? Can you afford to lose it?</p>
<p>Determining your investment objectives is paramount because it will also impact other important decisions, such as how much risk you’re willing to tolerate and the time horizon.</p>
<p>Despite being the largest and, supposedly, most secure cryptocurrency, it’s still considered very risky relative to investments in traditional finance. Please refer to the charts above &#8211; the BTC price went on to gain 300% and then lost 50% of it in a matter of less than six months. This tumultuous performance can be hard to stomach, so being aware of it in advance and being able to tolerate it is something you should consider.</p>
<h3>Develop an Investment Strategy</h3>
<p>Once you have the above all clear, you should be more or less ready to develop an overall investment strategy.</p>
<p>There are multiple ways to invest in Bitcoin. One of the more popular strategies is the so-called Dollar Cost Average (DCA).</p>
<p>We have a dedicated guide and a video explainer of DCA that you can <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/should-i-buy-bitcoin-now-is-it-now-a-good-price-for-btc/" data-wpel-link="internal">find here</a>. In general, though, it represents a way to buy Bitcoin in similar increments over a similar period of time. For example &#8211; you can buy $100 in BTC every month. The benefits of it are that over a long-enough time period, you get the best average price.</p>
<p>There are also other strategies to invest in Bitcoin. For instance, the so-called value averaging suggests adjusting your investment amounts based on market performance. E.g., you can buy more Bitcoin when there’s a bigger dip.</p>
<p>In all cases, you must set guidelines for when to buy, hold, or sell BTC based on your own risk appetite and analysis.</p>
<h3>Set a Budget</h3>
<p>Now that you know how you will invest in Bitcoin, the next step is to set your budget &#8211; how much do you want to spend?</p>
<p>This is incredibly personal and depends entirely on your current and projected financial situation. Setting up a budget and sticking to it will help you better track your investment and also manage your risk tolerance.</p>
<p>The most important takeaway here, however, that is specific to investing in Bitcoin for the next bull market is to understand that BTC is a risky purchase. That said, you should never invest more than what you can afford to lose without significantly impacting your overall financial stability.</p>
<h3>Secure Your Investments</h3>
<p>Crypto scams and hacks happen regularly. Not only that &#8211; what were generally considered reliable firms (such as FTX and Celsius) have failed and left investors empty-handed and in search of reparations.</p>
<p>Here is a breakdown of the industry’s <a href="https://youtu.be/CLT88qsRngI" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">most shocking events</a>. You’ll surely notice that some of them are related to platforms being hacked or having failed.</p>
<p>Make sure to use reputable cryptocurrency exchanges or platforms to buy Bitcoin. Once you’ve bought, make sure to move your stash off-chain and keep it in a hardware wallet.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/9-must-tips-securing-crypto-wallet/" data-wpel-link="internal">9 Tips for Securing Your Bitcoin and Crypto Wallets You Must Follow</a></p>
<h3>Diversify Your Portfolio</h3>
<p>As you might have probably noticed, Bitcoin bull runs also result in a massive expansion of the broader market capitalization. For reference, it reached over $3 trillion in 2021.</p>
<p>This means that other cryptocurrencies are also benefitting from the Bitcoin price increase.</p>
<p>It’s worth considering having your investment diversified by including other promising cryptocurrencies or even blockchain-related assets. Keep in mind, though, that if Bitcoin is volatile and risky, other cryptocurrencies are even more volatile and risky.</p>
<p>However, a properly diversified portfolio can spread your risk and even capture additional opportunities.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-97655" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover.jpg" alt="altcoins_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/altcoins_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h3>Practice Risk Management</h3>
<p>The crux of this guide is to help you practice better risk management. The cryptocurrency market is one that’s characterized by volatility, and it is very easy to get caught up in traders posting tremendous ROI screenshots. Approach these with tremendous caution.</p>
<p>There will always be missed opportunities, no matter how much time and effort you spend or how well-educated you are. However, there will also be new opportunities. Do not FOMO, do not panic sell, and do not let your emotions get the better of you.</p>
<p>Employ a risk-management strategy and stick to it. Determine your exit strategies, use stop-loss orders (if it’s a shorter-term leveraged investment) to limit your potential losses, and make sure you follow your rules.</p>
<h3>Stay Disciplined</h3>
<p>Staying disciplined is just as important as making the decision to invest in Bitcoin. It’s important to remain committed to your strategy and not be swayed by any type of short-term market hype or the fear of missing out (FOMO).</p>
<p>Remember that emotional decisions probably result in impulsive actions and most commonly lead to potential losses.</p>
<h3>Stay Informed and Adapt</h3>
<p>Remain involved in the industry, at least to some extent. Keep up with the latest news, market trends, and regulatory developments in the broader cryptocurrency space.</p>
<p>Make sure to adapt your strategy, if it’s necessary, based on new information or changes in the broader market landscape.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Investing in Bitcoin should be regarded as investing in multiple other asset classes, but it has its intricacies and specifics. The sheer volatility of the BTC price makes it a lot tougher to stomach overnight swings in your portfolio, but if you have your sight set on the bigger picture, these become easier to go through.</p>
<p>One sign that you’re overinvested is that you’re constantly on your phone, checking the prices every hour.</p>
<p>If done correctly, investing in Bitcoin can be stress-free, and all of the above tips are aimed at exactly that.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/how-to-prepare-for-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market-10-tips-you-must-know/" rel="nofollow">How to Prepare for the Next Bitcoin Bull Market: 10 Tips You Must Know</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Over $35 Million Reportely Stolen From Atomic Wallet Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/over-35-million-reportely-stolen-from-atomic-wallet-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253797</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Atomic_Wallet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Atomic_Wallet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Atomic Wallet has not yet released the specifics of the attack. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The week started on a grim note following the large-scale theft of digital assets from Atomic Wallet users resulting in a six-figure loss across different chains.</p>
<p>Distraught users have taken to Twitter to challenge some of the Atomic Wallet&#8217;s claims after the company assured them that it is working with &#8220;leading security companies&#8221; and has reached out to organizations that can help trace the stolen funds.</p>
<h2>Largest Victim Lost ~$8M</h2>
<p>According to pseudonymous on-chain sleuth ZachXBT, the largest amount lost by a user in the Atomic Wallet hack was $7.95 million in Tether (USDT) on the Tron blockchain. Further investigation <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1665267820836319233" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that the five biggest losses account for a whopping $17 million.</p>
<p>In the latest update, ZachXBT, who had previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacked-largest-victim-reportedly-lost-2-8m-usdt/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> receiving numerous messages from the wallet users regarding their lost funds, estimated that the total funds stolen may have surpassed $35 million.</p>
<p>Atomic Wallet, in a <a href="https://twitter.com/AtomicWallet/status/1665550651735023616" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">statement</a> on June 5th, said that less than 1% of its monthly active users were affected by the exploit. The team behind the wallet service also added that the last drained transaction was confirmed over 40 hours ago, a <a href="https://twitter.com/2LeilaLeila/status/1665582278448148480" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">claim</a> that has been <a href="https://twitter.com/vzlaxfree/status/1665572760221896705" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">challenged</a> by several community members.</p>
<p>So far, no compensation plans have been announced. Atomic Wallet has not been able to determine the root cause. While some users reported that their digital assets were stolen following a recent software update, others revealed being affected despite not updating to the latest version.</p>
<h2>Previous Red Flags</h2>
<p>Following the episode, a security disclosure from February 2022 resurfaced, which raised several security vulnerabilities in Atomic Wallet.</p>
<p>Least Authority&#8217;s security research team conducted a thorough security audit in March 2021 and claimed to have discovered vulnerabilities in the wallet&#8217;s system design, putting users at significant risk.</p>
<p>The report was delivered to Atomic in April. The Berlin-based security consulting firm concluded Atomic sent them a response noting their updates and improvements seven months later but had a &#8220;significant number of issues and suggestions remain unresolved.&#8221;</p>
<p>It had issued a <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20220210153123/https://leastauthority.com/blog/disclosure-of-security-vulnerabilities-in-atomic-wallet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">warning</a> &#8220;strongly recommending&#8221; that the Atomic Wallet team immediately notify users of the existing security vulnerabilities. Least Authority further added,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In addition, until the issues and suggestions outlined in the report have been sufficiently remediated and the Atomic Wallet has undergone subsequent security audits, we strongly recommend against the Atomic Wallet’s deployment and use.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-35-million-reportely-stolen-from-atomic-wallet-users/" rel="nofollow">Over $35 Million Reportely Stolen From Atomic Wallet Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
