<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance Labs Leads Funding Round For Web3 Security Startup</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-leads-funding-round-for-web3-security-startup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227912</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/binance_labs_goplus_security_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/binance_labs_goplus_security_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Despite the crypto carnage that was exacerbated by FTX's fall, Web3's appeal to investors remains unfazed.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Aligning with ambitious investment plans in the ongoing bear market, Binance Labs &#8211; the venture capital arm of the world&#8217;s largest crypto exchange &#8211; announced leading a private round II for GoPlus Security. The value of the investment has not been disclosed.</p>
<p>The fresh capital infusion will be deployed to develop security data further, build a security service marketplace, and conduct new hiring for the Web3 security infrastructure provider.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the official blog <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/blog/ecosystem/binance-labs-leads-private-round-ii-for-goplus-security-to-build-open-permissionless-userdriven-security-services-2729295307357186183" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a>, Go Plus Security also intends to use the funds to launch a security service marketplace at the end of 2022.</li>
<li>So far, the startup provides security data to 13 chains.</li>
<li>Following the development, Yi He, Co-Founder of Binance and Head of Binance Labs, commented,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Security is foundational to the ever-growing Web3 ecosystem and community. By supporting consumer-facing solutions like Goplus Security, we hope to see how security services to end users can evolve and prosper.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The move comes days after Binance CEO, Changpeng Zhao (CZ), confirmed plans to use an astonishing reserve of $1 billion on acquisitions and investments.</li>
<li>According to recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-could-surpass-1-billion-in-investment-spending-by-years-end/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">estimates</a>, Binance has already committed more than $325 million to over 67 projects this year alone. In contrast, the crypto exchange spent around $140 million across 73 projects for the entire year of 2021 amidst a far more bullish crypto market.</li>
<li>Binance Labs launched a $500 million fund to support promising Web 3 projects and start-up firms with great potential earlier this year.</li>
<li>Traditional e-commerce and gaming companies will remain on Binance&#8217;s radar for potential investment opportunities.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-labs-leads-funding-round-for-web3-security-startup/" rel="nofollow">Binance Labs Leads Funding Round For Web3 Security Startup</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waves Breaks Silence Over DAXA Investigation, USDN Stablecoin Fails to Repeg</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/waves-break-silence-over-daxa-investigation-usdn-stablecoin-fails-to-repeg/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 18:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Waves]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228057</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Waves.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Waves.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[WAVES is currently trading around $2 after falling 12% over the past week as speculation mounts over the sustainability of USDN.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It has been a tough year for algorithmic stablecoins. Historically, these pegged tokens have failed to maintain a grip on $1, especially under extreme selling pressure. But the Terra collapse has been disastrous, and the ripple effects have had a decisive impact on the rest of the market.</p>
<p>Seven months later, another algorithmic stablecoin is having trouble maintaining its dollar peg. In fact, this is the fifth time that Waves-backed Neutrino Dollar (USDN), currently trading at $0.84, de-pegged from the dollar. South Korean exchanges have issued a warning that this has impacted the Waves token, which has come under the scanner for apparent fluctuation in its value.</p>
<h2>Waves Address FUD</h2>
<p>In the latest <a href="https://blog.waves.tech/en/waves-statement-on-daxa-investigation-into-waves-token" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">post</a>, Waves maintained that USDN is a separate project that uses WAVES as collateral and is not &#8220;intrinsically&#8221; linked to the native token.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;USDN is a separate project built on Waves blockchain that uses WAVES as collateral; it is not intrinsically linked to WAVES token. There is only one way in which USDN can directly affect WAVES price &#8211; through redeeming WAVES from the contract and selling WAVES on the market.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>It all started when the Digital Asset Exchange Association (DAXA), which consists of the five major crypto exchanges (Upbit, Bithumb, Coinone, Korbit, and Gopax) in South Korea, cautioned users against investing in WAVES citing high volatility caused by USDN de-pegging.</p>
<p>One DAXA platform &#8211; Upbit &#8211; announced that the platform is looking to suspend the WAVES/KRW and WAVES/BTC pairs and added that it will monitor the token over a period of the next two weeks to determine its next course of action.</p>
<p>Waves revealed cooperating with the investigation to alleviate &#8220;serious and obviously damaging misunderstandings&#8221; of the relationship between WAVES and USDN. The team behind the open-source platform also said that is extremely confident in reaching a resolution within the two-week investigation period.</p>
<h2>DAXA Targets Another Token</h2>
<p>The Terra collapse and the subsequent fall of FTX have left South Korean regulators to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/south-korea-to-establish-guidelines-for-crypto-exchanges-as-watchdogs-probe-terra-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">tread</a> with caution. Aligning with the sentiment, the Seoul Central District Court <a href="https://www.koreaherald.com/view.php?ud=20221208000589" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">ruled</a> to justify DAXA&#8217;s decision to delist Wemade&#8217;s Wemix (WEMIX) tokens from major crypto exchanges in the country.</p>
<p>As per court <a href="https://koreajoongangdaily.joins.com/2022/12/08/business/tech/Korea-Wemade-Wemix/20221208183614019.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">documents</a>, DAXA accused Wemede, which is backed by tech giant Microsoft, of failing to disclose the number of outstanding tokens. The game developer dismissed the allegations and said that it will continue the legal battle against the crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/waves-break-silence-over-daxa-investigation-usdn-stablecoin-fails-to-repeg/" rel="nofollow">Waves Breaks Silence Over DAXA Investigation, USDN Stablecoin Fails to Repeg</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Initiate Next Rally If this Level Gets Broken</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-initiate-next-rally-if-this-level-gets-broken/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228264</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is fighting to get over two crucial resistance levels. A successful breakout above these vital barriers could potentially result in a bullish surge in the near future. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart After touching the lower trendline of the descending wedge pattern, the price of bitcoin initiated a mini-rally followed by extremely [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin is fighting to get over two crucial resistance levels. A successful breakout above these vital barriers could potentially result in a bullish surge in the near future.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>After touching the lower trendline of the descending wedge pattern, the price of bitcoin initiated a mini-rally followed by extremely low momentum and trading volume. The price now faces two substantial resistance levels: the 50-day moving average at $17.9K and the 100-day moving average at $18.7K.</p>
<p>A successful breakout above the abovementioned barriers should push the price toward the upper boundary of the wedge, roughly around $20.5K.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the price fails to break above these critical resistance levels, a retest of lower levels toward the $15K region and another attempt at the lower trendline would become much more likely.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228267" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>The Fibonacci retracement is a valuable indicator for witnessing consolidation phases and price targets. Typically, the 0.5 and 0.618 Fib levels are considered significant resistance levels during bearish expansion moves.</p>
<p>The following chart shows that the price forms a low-momentum bullish trend inside an ascending price channel.</p>
<p>However, there is a static resistance region between the 0.5 and the 0.618 Fibonacci levels, between $18.5K and $19.1K, which is the main barrier in Bitcoin’s path toward higher price levels.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228266" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTC-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<h2>On-chain Analysis</h2>
<p>The following Spent Output Value Bands (%) demonstrate the distribution of all spent outputs according to their value. Each colored band illustrates the ratio of the total value of spent outputs that have a value within the indicated range.</p>
<p>Bitcoin whales continue to allocate their assets. According to on-chain data, large bitcoin holders (also known as “Whales”) haven’t started yet to accumulate coins. The UTXO Value Bands Metric (1K-10K BTC) indicates that an upward trend in bitcoin’s price is often linked to whales’ accumulation.</p>
<p>However, since June 2022, whales have decreased their holdings by 367K BTC. The market should observe a heavy accumulation by this significant cohort to sustain a price increase.</p>
<p>In terms of spending, the ongoing high level of whale distribution is contradictory with a sign that could lead to a market cycle change. On the other hand, a significant portion of the BTC being spent since June 2022 (up to 80% of the total) came from whales.</p>
<p>To see a change in the market cycle, the market should also witness a much lower whale distribution.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228265" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Spent-Output-Value-Bands--50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-analysis-btc-could-initiate-next-rally-if-this-level-gets-broken/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Analysis: BTC Could Initiate Next Rally If this Level Gets Broken</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pillar, Non-Custodial Crypto Wallet, Released An Updated Version</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pillar-non-custodial-crypto-wallet-released-an-updated-version/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228271</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pillar-pr.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/pillar-pr.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PR &#8211; London, United Kingdom, 10th December, 2022, Chainwire] Pillar’s latest release for its non-custodial cryptocurrency wallet ships with a sophisticated recovery mechanism that protects user funds without compromising security. Other game-changing updates include in-app cross-chain swaps and meta-transactions, which allow users to pay for gas fees on any chain with stablecoins housed on any [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PR &#8211; London, United Kingdom, 10th December, 2022, Chainwire]</strong></p>
<p><a href="http://bit.ly/3Pi8kJS" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Pillar’s</a> latest release for its non-custodial cryptocurrency wallet ships with a sophisticated recovery mechanism that protects user funds without compromising security. Other game-changing updates include in-app cross-chain swaps and meta-transactions, which allow users to pay for gas fees on any chain with stablecoins housed on any other chain.</p>
<p>The security that is a major benefit of non-custodial wallets is also a user’s main risk. Should they lose their private or public key, there is no other way to regain access to the wallet. People often lose access to their funds because their private key was written on a scrap of paper and got lost.</p>
<p>Pillar Wallet solves this single point of failure without compromising security through a sophisticated and fully decentralized mechanism. The private keys to a Pillar Wallet are secured by a smart contract, meaning that if the owner loses access to it, they can still recover their funds. At the same time, Pillar never retains knowledge of the private key.</p>
<p>A community-run, multichain DeFi wallet, Pillar supports Ethereum, Polygon, Gnosis Chain, BNB Chain, and Optimism with more coming. Pillar Wallet is powered by Etherspot SDK. While private key wallets are usually free, smart wallets come with a small cost, as a smart contract must be deployed on the blockchain. However, Pillar Wallet offers to deploy Polygon and Gnosis wallets for free, covering all deployment fees.</p>
<p>Users of Pillar Wallet can:</p>
<ul>
<li>Store, buy, send, trade, and swap assets with low-to-no gas fees on numerous EVM-compatible chains within the app</li>
<li>Buy crypto directly on Ethereum or Polygon with card or bank transfer via implemented on-ramps</li>
<li>Move funds seamlessly between different EVM chains without the need for external bridging apps</li>
<li>Perform cross-chain swaps without gas tokens on the destination chain. Users can cover gas fees with any stablecoin they have in their wallet on any chain (Meta-transactions)</li>
<li>Use Wallet Connect to interact with a wide range of supported DeFi applications directly within the in-app browser</li>
</ul>
<p>Pillar is a fully decentralized, open-source, non-custodial, and community-run wallet. Users are free to join the Pillar DAO, help manage the project’s treasury, make proposals to the DAO and shape future developments.</p>
<h2>About Pillar Wallet</h2>
<p>Pillar Wallet is a next-generation crypto wallet that stores your cryptocurrencies securely and provides you with the same level of comfort as any custodial wallet. Its advanced smart contract design supports account recovery without exposing the private key to any third party including Pillar.</p>
<p>Learn more: <a href="https://www.pillar.fi/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://www.pillar.fi/</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pillar-non-custodial-crypto-wallet-released-an-updated-version/" rel="nofollow">Pillar, Non-Custodial Crypto Wallet, Released An Updated Version</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Starbucks Introduces Coffee-Themed NFTs on Polygon to Beta Testers</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/starbucks-introduces-coffee-themed-nfts-on-polygon-to-beta-testers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 14:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228081</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/starbucks_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/starbucks_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Starbucks' NFTs offer US beta testers a chance to learn interesting facts about coffee and get involved in various activities.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The American multinational chain of coffeehouses &#8211; Starbucks &#8211; launched its blockchain-based loyalty program, called Starbucks Odyssey, to its first group of US beta testers.</p>
<p>The effort is an extension of the company&#8217;s existing project &#8211; Starbucks Rewards &#8211; and includes coffee-themed NFTs that relate to real-world experiences.</p>
<ul>
<li>The entity <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/starbucks-is-building-a-web-3-experience-alongside-polygon/" data-wpel-link="internal">displayed</a> its intentions to hop on the NFT and Web3 bandwagon earlier this year by introducing the Starbucks Odyssey program.</li>
<li>The initiative, which is now live, <a href="https://waitlist.starbucks.com/#/learnmore" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">offers</a> customers a chance to engage in activities called &#8220;Journeys,&#8221; which allow members to earn NFTs. Starbucks Odyssey is based on Polygon and is currently available only to US beta testers.</li>
<li>The &#8220;Journeys&#8221; advertise the Starbucks brand and educate clients about coffee and the firm&#8217;s history. They include various activities like playing puzzles, watching videos, or taking quizzes.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Starbucks Odyssey members can earn and purchase digital collectible Stamps (NFTs), accumulating Odyssey Points that unlock access to exclusive offers, experiential rewards, and one-of-a-kind Starbucks artwork that can&#8217;t be found anywhere else,&#8221; the multinational chain of coffeehouses stated.</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Starbucks is not new to the world of crypto. The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bakkt-has-launched-its-bitcoin-app-and-announced-starbucks-partnership/" data-wpel-link="internal">teamed up</a> with Bakkt to enable its customers to use BTC as a payment method. Outlining the app&#8217;s merits was Bakkt&#8217;s CEO, Gavin Michael, who said:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The average consumer holds a wealth of digital assets – from gift cards to loyalty points to bitcoin – but lacks the tools to adequately track and utilize their value. We&#8217;re thrilled to bring the Bakkt App to the public as a step along our journey to expand digital asset access to all.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/starbucks-introduces-coffee-themed-nfts-on-polygon-to-beta-testers/" rel="nofollow">Starbucks Introduces Coffee-Themed NFTs on Polygon to Beta Testers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Japan Has Until March 2023 to Cease All Operations (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-has-until-march-2023-to-cease-all-operations-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 11:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Japan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228108</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_japan_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ftx_japan_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Kanto Local Finance Bureau will supposedly halt FTX Japan's activities on March 9, 2023.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Japanese authorities reportedly extended the business suspension order to FTX Japan until March 9, 2023.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Initially, the company had to cease all services on December 9.</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://jp.reuters.com/article/ftx-japan-idJPKBN2ST0F5" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the Kanto Local Finance Bureau will grant FTX Japan three more months before halting all its activities.</span></li>
<li>The final date has moved from December 9, 2022, to March 9, 2023, because the company still struggles to return assets to customers.</li>
<li>The authorities further claimed that FTX Japan&#8217;s trading system continues to be out of order.</li>
<li>The Japanese subsidiary of the bankrupt exchange <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-before-the-end-of-2022-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to resume customer withdrawals by the end of 2022 by developing new infrastructure.</span></li>
<li>It <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/japanese-customers-cash-and-crypto-not-part-of-ftx-japans-estate-will-resume-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">reiterated</a> its intentions at the beginning of December, assuring that cash and cryptocurrencies stored on the platform are not part of the company&#8217;s estate.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Based on this, we will promote the above return plan and plan to resume withdrawal and retrieval services as part of normal operations as soon as preparations are complete,&#8221; FTX Japan stated at the time.</span></p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Logically, the collapse of FTX has caused tremendous issues for the Japanese affiliate. The latter reportedly <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/22/collapsed-crypto-exchange-ftx-has-about-1point24-billion-of-cash-in-total-but-still-owes-at-least-3point1-billion-.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">has</a> over $170 million in cash on its books, making it the third-biggest source of money for the former crypto giant.</span></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-japan-has-until-march-2023-to-cease-all-operations-report/" rel="nofollow">FTX Japan Has Until March 2023 to Cease All Operations (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Remains Calm in Anticipation of Tuseday&#8217;s CPI Release (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-remains-calm-in-anticipation-of-tusedays-cpi-release-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 09:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228253</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BitcoinCalm.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price remains stable above $17K as the market is bracing for Tuesday's CPI release. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market has remained calm over the past 24 hours with unimpressive volumes, which is rather typical for the weekend. It&#8217;s also worth noting that market participants might be cautious before the release of November&#8217;s CPI numbers.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Stable at $17K</h2>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has failed to produce any significant movements in the past 24 hours and has maintained above $17K for a total of 0.2% gains on the day, according to CoinGecko.</p>
<p>As seen in the chart below, there were no major fluctuations, and the price dipped to a low of slightly below $17,100.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228254" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228254" style="width: 1913px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228254" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_111201" width="1913" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201.jpg 1913w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201-300x135.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201-1024x461.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201-768x346.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201-1536x691.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/btc_price_chart_111201-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1913px) 100vw, 1913px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228254" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Binance via TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>It&#8217;s entirely possible for market participants to be careful because there&#8217;s an important announcement coming from the US Bureau of Labor Statistics on Tuesday. They will release the numbers for November&#8217;s Consumer Price Index, which is largely used as a metric to gauge the inflation rate in the country. It has so far always had a considerable impact on Bitcoin&#8217;s price, usually resulting in immediate and massive volatility.</p>
<h2>Altcoins in Green but Gains Insignificant</h2>
<p>The altcoin market is largely in green throughout the past 24 hours, although the increases are not so significant, as seen in the heatmap below.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228255" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228255" style="width: 1858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228255" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201.jpg" alt="cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201" width="1858" height="782" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201.jpg 1858w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201-300x126.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201-1024x431.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201-768x323.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201-1536x646.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/cryptocurrency_heatmap_111201-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1858px) 100vw, 1858px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228255" class="wp-caption-text">Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>OSMO seems to be the best performer for the day, gaining a total of 11.5%, followed by the native cryptocurrency of the decentralized derivatives trading platform GMX, which is up almost 7%.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Axie Infinity&#8217;s AXS seems to be taking a breather and is down some 4.8% in the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance remains at 37%, showcasing that the market is in somewhat of an equilibrium where altcoins are currently unable to chip away at any of BTC&#8217;s share.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-remains-calm-in-anticipation-of-tusedays-cpi-release-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Remains Calm in Anticipation of Tuseday&#8217;s CPI Release (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Three Things That Went Wrong for FTX According to Ripple CTO</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/the-three-things-that-went-wrong-for-ftx-according-to-ripple-cto/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228101</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GCCM6JEOHJD5VJAVV44QECLTQQ.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/GCCM6JEOHJD5VJAVV44QECLTQQ.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple CTO believes FTX's collapse was due to "incompetence" and "fraud."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>But blockchain firm Ripple&#8217;s Chief Technology Officer, David Schwartz, weighed in on Sam Bankman-Fried&#8217;s sympathizers but also went on to detail what went wrong with the company.</p>
<h2>Ripple CTO&#8217;s Take on FTX Collapse</h2>
<p>The exec <a href="https://twitter.com/JoelKatz/status/1601004815256981505" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">listed</a> out three things that went &#8220;horribly wrong.&#8221;</p>
<ul>
<li>FTX customer fiat assets were left in Alameda accounts and used by Alameda.</li>
<li>Customer deposits FTX was just supposed to hold were commingled with assets used in riskier ways.</li>
<li>Alameda was supposed to be executing risk-managed, nearly delta-neutral strategies. Somehow, positions weren&#8217;t tracked, risks weren&#8217;t managed at all, and strategies were not at all delta-neutral.</li>
</ul>
<p>While the exec does not want to believe that corruption may have taken place in FTX, he added that even &#8220;willful blindness&#8221; on the leadership of the bankrupt firm&#8217;s part is equally appalling. Schwartz contemplated that &#8220;bad luck&#8221; during a long bear market may cause a lot of crypto companies to shut shop. But that is not the case with FTX and its sister trading firm Alameda.</p>
<h2>Shark Tank Star&#8217;s Puzzling Take on SBF</h2>
<p>But there are industry experts who do not share the same belief that Bankman-Fried may have committed a crime. One such is Shark Tank star and investor Kevin O&#8217;Leary, who confessed to losing $15 million that FTX paid him to be its official spokesperson.</p>
<p>At a time when a major chunk of the crypto community has turned against Bankman-Fried, the television personality&#8217;s comments naturally attracted a significant backlash. The investor had recently stated that SBF should be treated as innocent until proven guilty. In yet another interview, O&#8217;Leary <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftx-bankruptcy-kevin-oleary-would-still-invest-in-sbf/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">asserted</a> that he would invest in the disgraced founder should he come up with a new venture.</p>
<p>But Ripple CTO David Schwartz is having a tough time cracking Mr. Wonderful&#8217;s take on the whole fiasco, especially after the latter reinstated faith in the Bankman-Fried&#8217;s trading prowess. Schwartz <a href="https://twitter.com/JoelKatz/status/1600980143354179585" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">tweeted</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Maybe his thinking is &#8220;Hey, lots of people lost a lot of money, but Sam made sure I made out okay so I&#8217;d do business with him again&#8221;. But if there&#8217;s any other possible explanation, I&#8217;d prefer to believe that. The thing is, I&#8217;m not sure there is any other possible explanation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-three-things-that-went-wrong-for-ftx-according-to-ripple-cto/" rel="nofollow">The Three Things That Went Wrong for FTX According to Ripple CTO</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kazakhstan Lawmakers Pass New Bitcoin Mining Bills</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-lawmakers-pass-new-bitcoin-mining-bills/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 15:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kazakhstan]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227749</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Kazakhstan.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Kazakhstan.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Kazakhstan may no longer be the bitcoin sanctuary it once was, thanks to the new regulation on crypto mining.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers in the country have passed the &#8220;On Digital Assets of the Republic of Kazakhstan&#8221; crypto assets bill and other laws that focus on crypto mining. The Mäjilis, or the lower hours of the Parliament of Kazakhstan, approved the four bills.</p>
<p>Following the Chinese miner exodus, Kazakhstan emerged as one of the preferred destinations due to cheap electricity. However, as crypto mining boomed, lawmakers have come up with hostile measures against the industry.</p>
<h2>Stringent Rules</h2>
<p>The details of the five bills that introduce a new scheme of electricity purchasing for mining equipment, as well as updated licensing and taxation schemes, were shared by Didar Bekbauov, co-founder of Xive, a crypto mining solutions platform.</p>
<p>Miners will now be required to purchase only surplus electricity from the public grid. Exclusive purchase of electricity through the Kazakhstan Electricity and Power Market Operator [KOREM] exchange can also be carried out by the miners. However, not everyone will be able to make this purchase as electricity would sell in an auction form &#8211; meaning the highest bids win.</p>
<p>The mining license procedure is categorized into two. The first one will involve the digital miners who own the appropriate infrastructure &#8211; data processing centers with the appropriate requirements for equipment, location, and security.</p>
<p>The second category is for digital miners &#8211; equipment owners who rent cells in data processing centers and do not claim an energy quota.</p>
<p>Commenting on the bill, a member of the Mäjilis’ Committee on Economic Reform and Regional Development, Ekaterina Smyshlyaeva, <a href="https://twitter.com/didar_bekbau/status/1600442939959693313" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said:</a></p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The bill, in addition to mandatory accreditation, introduces separate requirements for mining pools in terms of the location of their server capacities in Kazakhstan and compliance with information security rules.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Crypto Clampdown Inevitable?</h2>
<p>New crypto taxes have also been presented that include provisions for miners, mining pool commission, value-added tax, and tax on crypto exchanges as business entities.</p>
<p>With the new rules approved, both single miners and mining pools will be imposed corporate income tax based on the value of the crypto-asset as well as the commission rates for the pools. In addition to that, the Majilis is also looking to enforce a blanket ban on advertising crypto transactions and design regulations specifically for &#8220;cryptocurrency securities.&#8221;</p>
<p>Moreover, individuals conducting crypto transactions will also be levied value-added tax along with corporate income tax on crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>The latest development comes over a month after the Mäjilis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-wants-more-regulations-for-crypto-miners-with-new-bill-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">greenlighted</a> bills that sought to establish appropriate rules in the domestic crypto sector. As such, crypto miners and mining pools will come under the purview of the Ministry of Digital Development, Innovation, and Aerospace Industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/kazakhstan-lawmakers-pass-new-bitcoin-mining-bills/" rel="nofollow">Kazakhstan Lawmakers Pass New Bitcoin Mining Bills</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bear Market, Luna Crash, FTX Meltdown: How it Impacted Crypto&#8217;s Public Perception (Survey)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bear-market-luna-crash-ftx-meltdown-how-it-impacted-cryptos-public-perception-survey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 13:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Survey]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=227843</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinAdoption.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/BitcoinAdoption.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[43% of the US participants in the survey currently have a negative view of digital currencies, while just 8% are supportive of them.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A recent study conducted by CNBC estimated that only 8% of American participants currently have a favorable view of cryptocurrencies.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Those who supported the asset class in March 2022 were 19%. The market has been through a lot since then &#8211; the prices plummeted, the Terra ecosystem crashed, and FTX filed for bankruptcy.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Change of Trends</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">43% of the US participants in CNBC&#8217;s &#8220;All-America Economic Survey&#8221; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fm.cnbc.com/applications/cnbc.com/resources/editorialfiles/2022/12/07/allamericafourthquarter.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> they have a negative view of digital currencies, while this figure was 25% nine months ago. The proponents of the asset class have shrunk to 8%, down from 19%, and 18% feel neutral. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the results, 24% of the respondents admitted having invested, traded, or used crypto in the past (up 6% from the March results).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">17% of those who have allocated some of their wealth in bitcoin or altcoins have a &#8220;very negative&#8221; stance, while 47% of the non-investors showed such an attitude.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The increased criticism could be a result of the numerous adverse events that the world of crypto endured throughout the ongoing year, with Terra&#8217;s collapse and the crash of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> being some of them. Former giants like </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Three Arrows Capital, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-files-for-bankruptcy-following-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BlockFi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and many others filed for bankruptcy, while the global crypto market capitalization has slipped below $1 trillion.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The rise of negativity toward cryptocurrencies coincides with record-low confidence in stocks. Only 26% of the participants believe now is the right moment to invest in equities which is the most pessimistic level in the 15-year history of the research. 51% think they should stay away.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Young Americans are More Supportive</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A survey carried out by Bank of America <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/75-of-young-us-investors-want-to-diversify-portfolios-with-crypto-boa-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">estimated</a> that 75% of American respondents aged 21-42 believe it is impossible to achieve above-average returns relying only on traditional finance. They think crypto should be one of the instruments to diversify with.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">32% of the older individuals share the same stance but prefer to invest their funds in equities. Just 5% of those above 42 years old have hopped on the cryptocurrency bandwagon.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The research further informed that 68% of the polled parents have already had an educational discussion with their children on how to transfer the family wealth to them. Generation X and Millennials are expected to inherit around $84 trillion by 2045.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Those two demographic groups have been among the most active on the crypto scene. A research conducted in 2021 <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/rich-millennials-have-a-large-chunk-of-their-wealth-in-crypto-cnbc-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">showed</a> that 47% of Millennial millionaires have invested at least a quarter of their total funds in bitcoin or alternative coins. 36% <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/half-of-millennials-and-generation-z-prefer-to-get-parts-of-their-salaries-in-bitcoin-survey/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> they would like to receive some of their salaries in digital currencies instead of fiat. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bear-market-luna-crash-ftx-meltdown-how-it-impacted-cryptos-public-perception-survey/" rel="nofollow">Bear Market, Luna Crash, FTX Meltdown: How it Impacted Crypto&#8217;s Public Perception (Survey)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
