<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:25:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>PayPal Ventures Leads $52M Funding Round for Web3 Firm Magic</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-ventures-leads-52m-funding-round-for-web3-firm-magic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 22:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253226</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Funding.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Crypto_Funding.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The new round brings the total raised to more than $80 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>San Francisco-based wallet-as-a-service (WaaS) provider Magic has raised $52 million in a strategic funding round led by PayPal Ventures bringing the firm&#8217;s valuation to just under $500 million.</p>
<p>Other participants of the fund round include Cherubic, Synchrony, KX, Northzone, and Volt Capital.</p>
<ul>
<li>The latest capital infusion will be deployed to expand Magic&#8217;s functionality and enable growing use cases. The focus will also be on making a deeper integration within the European Union (EU) and Asia-Pacific region (APAC).</li>
<li>Commenting on the latest development, Alan Du, Partner at PayPal Ventures, stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Mass adoption of web3 is a hot topic, and Magic is facilitating this with a safe and simple solution. We&#8217;re proud to be investing in Magic and believe the company will help drive the growing number of web3 use-cases amongst global brands.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Sean Li, Magic&#8217;s co-founder and CEO, highlighted that global brands have realized the potential of blockchain beyond crypto and are utilizing it to engage with their customers and monetize the experience in new ways.</li>
<li>The exec further revealed that Magic is working with Fortune 500 companies to bring their Web3 use cases to daily users.</li>
<li>According to the <a href="https://newsroom.paypal-corp.com/2023-05-31-PayPal-Ventures-leads-52M-Funding-Round-for-Magic" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">stats</a>, the WaaS provider has churned more than 20 million unique wallets, and its SDK is used by over 130,000 developers. Magic&#8217;s scalability produces over 2,000 wallets per second (wps) versus the fastest alternatives at 80-100 wps.</li>
<li>Besides Magic, several other companies in the Web3 space are betting on the wallet-as-a-service model that enables users to plug crypto tools into their operations. Coinbase recently announced starting a WaaS service that will let companies customize blockchain wallets for their customers.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-ventures-leads-52m-funding-round-for-web3-firm-magic/" rel="nofollow">PayPal Ventures Leads $52M Funding Round for Web3 Firm Magic</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traders are Backing This AI Crypto Coin to Boom After Hitting $2M in Presale</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-this-ai-crypto-coin-to-boom-after-hitting-2m-in-presale/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 22:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253745</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture1-1.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The yPredict presale has raced past the $2 million milestone as buyers rush to invest in the AI-powered trading and analytics platform. YPRED tokens, which power the project through a tiered subscription model, are currently on sale for $0.09 but will still increase in price by a further 33.3% when the project reaches its final [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The yPredict presale has raced past the $2 million milestone as buyers rush to invest in the AI-powered trading and analytics platform.</p>
<p>YPRED tokens, which power the project through a tiered subscription model, are currently on sale for $0.09 but will still increase in price by a further 33.3% when the project reaches its final presale stage.</p>
<p>The platform supplies AI-powered trading insights, predictive models, and trading tools and has been developed by a group of professional traders, quants, AI experts, and software developers.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> has also just launched a new product that will see the platform expand beyond just crypto analytics and trading tools.</p>
<h2>AI-Powered Trading Gives Users an Edge</h2>
<p>Crypto and stock market trading have become increasingly powered by algorithms and machines in recent years.</p>
<p>yPredict will allow its users to access the very best predictive models that have been developed by artificial intelligence experts, with the platform also using AI to provide a wide range of data, insights, and metrics.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-3.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253750" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-3.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="624" height="343" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-3.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-3-300x165.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture2-3-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The platform will allow its users to make smarter decisions when trading and maximize their earning potential.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict</a> will be able to auto-detect 100+ chart patterns, provide an overview of sentiment in the market having scanned social media and automatically test hundred of technical indicators.</p>
<p>It will also analyze transactions and tick data for assets and develop metrics to provide data-driven insights.</p>
<p>Furthermore, financial scientists can also offer their predictive models and signals to other users, with yPredict acting as a marketplace for retail traders to purchase products offered by developers.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253751" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-2.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="624" height="423" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-2.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-2-300x203.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture3-2-50x34.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>More than 20,000 people have already put their names on the waiting list.</p>
<p>The platform will be free and open to all, although there will be two paid tiers where premium members get access to enhanced features by staking YPRED.</p>
<p>yPredict, which is built on the super-fast and efficient layer-2 network Polygon, also has a robust staking mechanism and incorporates play-to-earn and learn-to-earn elements to keep its community engages.</p>
<p>Users can wager on token prices and also complete learning modules to earn YPRED as a reward.</p>
<h2>yPredict Launches New AI Content Editor</h2>
<p>The platform has just announced it is launched a self-hosted content solution product designed for medium to large content teams.</p>
<p>It will compete with the likes of SurferSEO and wants to help streamline content creation and enhance productivity.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4.gif" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253752" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture4.gif" alt="Picture4" width="624" height="351" /></a></p>
<p>The content editor will allow administrators to easily add or remove new users and editors to assign tasks.</p>
<p>It also utilizes AI in the content editor that offers suggestions to include the quality and structure of the work, based on things such as word length, list, and images, as well as providing analysis on top-ranking keywords to help users optimize for search engine visibility.</p>
<p>The yPredict content editor also incorporates a built-in scoring system to evaluate the quality of the work that also includes a ChatGPT detection feature to ensure integrity.</p>
<p>Raj Sharma, CEO of <a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">yPredict.ai</a> said:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are thrilled to introduce our expanded product lineup, which goes beyond the scope of crypto analytics and caters to a broader range of industries.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our content solution addresses the needs of content teams by simplifying their workflow, harnessing the power of AI, and delivering valuable insights for creating engaging and optimized content.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Does the YPRED Presale Have Big Potential?</h2>
<p>Crypto analysts, such as Jacob Crypto Bury, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Apwv0qrlFHQ" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">believe</a> the token has huge potential, given its wide utility and robust tokenomics.</p>
<p>The project has a max supply of 100 million tokens, with 80% of those available to purchase through eight presale rounds.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-253753" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-1.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="624" height="329" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-1.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-1-300x158.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-1-50x26.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>Now in stage 6, tokens are priced at $0.09, but after the presale ends will list for $0.12 &#8211; a price increase of 33.3%</p>
<p>The project has a hard cap of around $6.5 million, with the remaining tokens split between exchange liquidity (10%), development (5%), and the project’s treasury (5%).</p>
<p>yPredict has already secured a listing with leading exchange Bitmart, with others expected to follow in the near future.</p>
<p>For the latest news, follow yPredict on <a href="https://twitter.com/yPredict_ai" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter</a> or <a href="https://t.me/ypredict" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_72a7e4de.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit yPredict Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/traders-are-backing-this-ai-crypto-coin-to-boom-after-hitting-2m-in-presale/" rel="nofollow">Traders are Backing This AI Crypto Coin to Boom After Hitting $2M in Presale</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ONFO Coin Co-Founder and Crypto Advocate Found Dead in Arkansas: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/onfo-coin-co-founder-and-crypto-advocate-found-dead-in-arkansas-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 19:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253358</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/death.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although investigations into John’s mysterious death are still ongoing, the police said there are no signs of foul play so far. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>John Forsyth, a Missouri emergency room doctor, crypto advocate, and co-founder of crypto project Onfo (ONFO), was recently found dead in northwest Arkansas after being reported missing for over a week.</p>
<p>The 49-year-old man was last heard from on May 21 through text messages with his fiancée. Authorities told the deceased’s brother Richard Forsyth that John’s corpse was found on Tuesday.</p>
<h2>ONFO Coin Co-Creator Mysteriously Found Dead</h2>
<p>The Forsyth brothers created the ONFO coin in 2020, allowing users to earn tokens while referring others to the platform through a strategy called “network mining.” Forbes <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/lukefitzpatrick/2020/04/27/bitcoin-halving-a-new-class-of-bitcoin-millionaires-may-emerge/?sh=7177246a61fc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tagged</a> John a “Bitcoin millionaire” in the same year, shortly before the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-2020-bitcoin-halving-is-finally-here-as-block-number-630000-mined/" data-wpel-link="internal">third Bitcoin halving event</a>, while he was a mathematics undergraduate.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://apnews.com/article/missouri-doctor-missing-ozarks-f7f68205ec6db1f866e99ec4707443af" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> from The Associated Press, Richard told the police that John was missing after he failed to show up for work on May 21 at the Mercy Hospital in Cassville, which was unlike him. The doctor had worked at the hospital for about 15 years, and his brother described him as a doting father and family physician.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We had dinner Wednesday before he disappeared, and we sat and talked for three hours. I told him this is the happiest I’d seen him in a long time. His divorce was final on May 11, and I think that gave him energy for the future. He really cared about his patients, and he loved his kids,” Richard said.</p></blockquote>
<h2>No Signs of Foul Play: Police</h2>
<p>On May 30, the Missouri State Highway Patrol and law enforcement agencies searching for John found his black Infiniti car unlocked and parked in a remote area close to an aquatic park in Cassville with his wallet, two phones, a laptop, and other items inside.</p>
<p>After searching within a nine-mile radius around the park with dogs and drones, the officers got a call about a body in a water bank across from the Lost Bridge South area. John’s body was eventually found with an apparent gunshot wound.</p>
<blockquote><p>“It doesn’t seem like a person who left with a plan. Right now, we really don’t have any breaks in the case. I’m confused, and I’m worried. And I don’t like this one bit,” Richard said.</p></blockquote>
<p>While an investigation into John’s mysterious death is ongoing, the police said there are no signs of foul play so far.</p>
<p>John’s demise comes less than two months after Cash App co-founder Bob Lee was fatally <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cashapp-founder-bob-lee-stabbed-to-death-in-san-francisco-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">stabbed</a> to death in San Francisco. Other crypto executives, including Amber Group’s co-founder, have also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-recent-wave-of-mysterious-deaths-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">mysteriously died</a> over the past six months.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/onfo-coin-co-founder-and-crypto-advocate-found-dead-in-arkansas-report/" rel="nofollow">ONFO Coin Co-Founder and Crypto Advocate Found Dead in Arkansas: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Rug Pull Losses Outpaced DeFi Exploits in May: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-rug-pull-losses-outpaced-defi-exploits-in-may-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 16:13:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253537</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/rugpulls_cryptopotato_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/rugpulls_cryptopotato_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The largest exit scam in May was executed by Fintoch, which absconded with users' funds worth $31.6 million.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new report by blockchain security company Beosin revealed that the total amount of crypto assets lost to exit scams and rug pulls was higher than the amount stolen from decentralized finance (DeFi) projects through exploits and attacks last month.</p>
<p>Beosin also <a href="https://medium.com/@Beosin_com/blockchain-security-monthly-recap-of-may-19-69m-lost-in-total-979a1dd57b" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">discovered</a> that losses from the exploits in May were down 79% compared to April, signaling a continued decline for two consecutive months.</p>
<h2>Losses From Rug Pulls Surpass DeFi Exploits</h2>
<p>Over $45 million was lost to crypto rug pulls in May across six incidents. The largest exit scam was that of DeFi lending protocol Fintoch – suspected of being a Ponzi scheme – which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-lending-protocol-fintoch-reportedly-rug-pulls-investors-for-31-6m/" data-wpel-link="internal">vanished</a> with 31.6 million USDT ($31.6 million) in users funds on May 24.</p>
<p>The second-largest rug pull was the theft of roughly $5.9 million by Inferno Drainer, a multi-chain scam service provider, which affected about 5,000 victims. Another notable rug pull was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/swaprum-dex-drained-in-3m-crypto-rugpull/" data-wpel-link="internal">executed</a> by the developers of decentralized exchange (DEX) Swaprum on May 19. The team drained $3 million in Ether (ETH) tokens from the protocol&#8217;s liquidity pools.</p>
<p>On the other hand, DeFi exploits amounted to $19.6 million worth of stolen crypto assets. The largest exploit was the attack on Arbitrum-based liquidity protocol Jimbos, which <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hacked-liquidity-protocol-jimbos-offers-deadline-to-exploiters-before-onboarding-law-enforcement/" data-wpel-link="internal">compromised</a> over 4,000 ETH worth about $7.5 million. The Ethereum-based crypto mixer Tornado Cash was also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tornado-cash-attacker-submits-proposal-to-revert-governance-control-torn-down-40-in-2-days/" data-wpel-link="internal">hacked</a> for roughly $2 million.</p>
<p>DeFi protocol Deus Finance, which has fallen victim to many attacks, was hacked again on May 5 through a public burn vulnerability on its stablecoin DEI (DEI). The attacker exploited the DEI token contracts on the BNB Smart Chain (BSC) and Arbitrum network and made away with more than $6 million.</p>
<h2>Raising Anti-Fraud Awareness</h2>
<p>The blockchain security firm also noted that hardware wallet-related security incidents increased in May. Beosin warned against a new type of coin theft using shared or public charging devices to implant malicious programs that could steal private keys.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The amount involved in Rug Pulls exceeded that in attacks this month, and new ways of stealing coins such as using shared rechargeables to steal private keys also emerged. Hackers and scammers are gradually shifting the target of their attacks from various project parties to ordinary users,&#8221; Beosin said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The firm urged users to raise anti-fraud awareness, learn several methods for safeguarding their assets, and conduct due diligence on projects before investing in them. The largest exit scam in May was executed by Fintoch, which absconded with users&#8217; funds worth $31.6 million.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-rug-pull-losses-outpaced-defi-exploits-in-may-report/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Rug Pull Losses Outpaced DeFi Exploits in May: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Explodes 11% Weekly But Bulls Must Now Focus on This Resistance (XRP Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-explodes-11-weekly-but-bulls-must-now-focus-on-this-resistance-xrp-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253748</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In recent weeks, Ripple&#8217;s price has displayed an upward trend, recovering from a notable support level. However, there is still a crucial resistance level that must fall for the market to enter a bullish phase in the coming months. Technical Analysis By: Edris XRP/USDT Daily Chart: The XRP price has consistently increased after bouncing back [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In recent weeks, Ripple&#8217;s price has displayed an upward trend, recovering from a notable support level. However, there is still a crucial resistance level that must fall for the market to enter a bullish phase in the coming months.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></strong></p>
<h3>XRP/USDT Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>The XRP price has consistently increased after bouncing back from the $0.43 support. This level has also been reinforced by the 200-day moving average, while the price has surpassed the 50-day moving average at around $0.47.</p>
<p>Ripple is currently approaching the $0.6 resistance level, and a successful breakthrough could trigger a potential rally toward $0.9 in the coming months. However, it&#8217;s worth noting that the RSI has entered the overbought zone, indicating a potential correction in the near future.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253757" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253757" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253757 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0406231" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPUSDT-Daily-June-4-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253757" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>XRP/BTC Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the BTC paired chart, there is a notable upward trend after the price successfully broke out of the significant descending channel. The 0.000017 SAT and 0.000019 SAT levels, representing the 50-day and 200-day moving averages, respectively, have both been surpassed, indicating positive momentum.</p>
<p>Currently, the Ripple price is approaching the psychological resistance level at 0.00002 SAT. However, it is important to note that the RSI indicator is signaling overbought conditions, implying a potential correction in the near term prior to any further upward movement.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253756" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253756" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253756 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0406232" width="2560" height="1441" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-2048x1153.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/XRPBTC-Daily-June-4-2023-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253756" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-explodes-11-weekly-but-bulls-must-now-focus-on-this-resistance-xrp-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Ripple Explodes 11% Weekly But Bulls Must Now Focus on This Resistance (XRP Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calm Before the Storm? BTC Attempts to Push Above $27K (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-btc-attempts-to-push-above-27k-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253695</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price is currently going through a phase of consolidation and has reached the 100-day moving average of $26,922. However, two significant support areas ahead on its path could potentially halt the ongoing decline and trigger the next bullish rally. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart During the consolidation correction stage, BTC dipped slightly [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is currently going through a phase of consolidation and has reached the 100-day moving average of $26,922. However, two significant support areas ahead on its path could potentially halt the ongoing decline and trigger the next bullish rally.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>During the consolidation correction stage, BTC dipped slightly below the middle trendline of the ascending channel and tested it as a pullback. However, the Bitcoin price continued the downtrend by printing small consecutive red candles and temporarily stalled at the 100-day moving average of $26.9K.</p>
<p>If it falls below the 100-day moving average, the lower threshold of the channel of around $24K and the 200-day moving average of $23K could be potential price targets.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if Bitcoin finds support at the 100-day moving average, an attempt to surpass the significant resistance level at $30K will be the most likely scenario.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253700" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253700" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253700 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0406231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253700" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Analyzing the 4-hour timeframe, a flag pattern has been developed during the recent correction phase of the market. Bitcoin&#8217;s price is currently consolidating within this flag, forming lower highs and lower lows.</p>
<p>However, there is a substantial support area between the 61.8% ($23,923) and 50% ($25,274) levels of the Fibonacci retracement. These two well-known Fibonacci levels indicate potential targets for correction stages. Given the market situation, it is likely that the price will continue the correction leg until it reaches this critical support zone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253699" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253699" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253699 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0406231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTC-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253699" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">On-chain Analysis</span></p>
<p>The following chart demonstrates the SOPR ratio metric alongside Bitcoin’s price since the 2015 bear market. The SOPR ratio is measured by dividing the values of long-term holders’ SOPR values by short-term holders. It has consistently signaled long-term investment opportunities, as in the previous two bearish cycles in 2015 and 2019.</p>
<p>This ratio reached its lowest point since 2019 &#8211; around 0.53 &#8211; in December 2022, indicating the onset of a bullish stage in the market. Currently, it is experiencing an uptrend, surpassing 1, which has historically coincided with successful bull runs in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p>Although it is uncertain whether the bull market has concluded, as long as the SOPR Ratio remains above one, the buyers are expected to continue dominating.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253698" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253698" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-253698 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_sopr_ratio_0406231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Bitcoin-SOPR-Ratio-LTH-SOPR_STH-SOPR-SMA-30-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253698" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-btc-attempts-to-push-above-27k-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Calm Before the Storm? BTC Attempts to Push Above $27K (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>4 Meme Coins to Watch as PEPE Coin Mania Winds Down</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/4-meme-coins-to-watch-as-pepe-coin-mania-winds-down/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elon Musk]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Floki Inu (FLOKI)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meme coins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253721</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/meme_coins_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/meme_coins_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[PEPE coin's price is winding down and the hype seems to have disappeared for the time being. Here are four othere meme coins to watch. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coins have had a long-lasting impact on the cryptocurrency market as they&#8217;ve been cemented into the crypto culture and become an inseparable part of the industry.</p>
<p>It all seemingly started with the pioneer Dogecoin (DOGE) back in 2013 when Jackson Palmer and Billy Marcus launched the protocol, giving birth to a subsection of crypto that would be amongst the most explosive ones.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-pepe/" data-wpel-link="internal">PEPE coin</a> seems to be the latest considerable iteration of the meme coin trend, and it also took the market by storm. The cryptocurrency went from virtually zero to obtaining close to a $2 billion market cap in less than a few weeks, printing numerous millionaires. But now, the mania seems to be winding down.</p>
<p>The meme coin is down 70% from its all-time high achieved 30 days ago, and has also lost some 26% in the past week alone.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253725" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253725" style="width: 841px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253725" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin.jpg" alt="img1_pepe_coin" width="841" height="467" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin.jpg 841w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin-300x167.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin-768x426.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/img1_pepe_coin-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 841px) 100vw, 841px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253725" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CoingeGecko</figcaption></figure>
<p>By all means, it appears that the euphoria that spread across the market like wildfire a few weeks back is now gone.</p>
<p>But this doesn&#8217;t mean that meme coins are dead. Here are four meme coins to watch as the PEPE coin mania winds down.</p>
<h2>Four Meme Coins to Watch</h2>
<p>The following meme coins are amongst the largest by means of total market capitalization and have established liquidity across both centralized and decentralized exchanges.</p>
<h3>Dogecoin (DOGE)</h3>
<p>DOGE needs little introduction as it&#8217;s the dominant king of the meme coin market. It&#8217;s the largest meme coin by means of total market capitalization and the one with the most established market. It&#8217;s traded across all major cryptocurrency exchanges and has more than sufficient liquidity.</p>
<p>DOGE&#8217;s price has been dormant over the past week but if there&#8217;s a meme coin to follow, it surely must be included in the conversation.</p>
<p>Dogecoin was created as a joke in 2013, but it went on to become a driving force in the cryptocurrency market, attracting support from the likes of Elon Musk and many other celebrities. It&#8217;s the godfather of meme coins and deserves a spot on everyone&#8217;s meme coin watchlist.</p>
<p>Here are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-dogecoin-doge-5-facts-about-the-crypto-that-started-as-a-joke/" data-wpel-link="internal">5 interesting facts</a> about Dogecoin that you might not know.</p>
<h3>Shiba Inu (SHIB)</h3>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-shiba-inu-shib/" data-wpel-link="internal">Shiba Inu (SHIB)</a> is perhaps the second best-known meme coin, and it&#8217;s also the second-largest in terms of total market capitalization.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-145038" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight.jpg" alt="ShibaInuSpotlight" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/ShibaInuSpotlight-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p>It gained popularity back in 2021 when it reached a market cap of upwards of $70 billion. Down 90% since then, the cryptocurrency has demonstrated on multiple occasions that it&#8217;s not one to underestimate. SHIB has exploded in price many times, often catching investors off guard.</p>
<p>The team behind it has developed an entire ecosystem, tapping into the realm of the metaverse and even issuing two other tokens, both of which also performing relatively well since inception.</p>
<p>SHIB is currently trading flat on the week but is down by about 12% in the past month. Monitoring the performance of this meme coin is important because, as we mentioned above, it oftentimes leaves investors sidelined with an expansive move.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, over the past couple of weeks, the community was met with a considerable number of delays on upcoming iterations of the protocol, which has seemingly suppressed SHIB&#8217;s momentum. This could also be interpreted that once the developers deliver on their promises, the volatility could pick up.</p>
<h3>Floki Inu (FLOKI)</h3>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-floki-inu/" data-wpel-link="internal">Floki Inu (FLOKI)</a> is another one of the dog-inspired meme coins, but it has a different inception story. The team behind it decided to go with it once Elon Musk revealed his decision to name his dog Floki. As you will commonly encounter in the world of meme coins, Elon Musk plays a vital role in a lot of the projects. FLOKI is not an exception.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-148959" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover.jpg" alt="flokiinu_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/flokiinu_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p>Another thing that separated Floki Inu from the rest of the meme coins was the widespread ad campaign that the team took back in 2022.</p>
<p>At one point, London buses were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-floki-inu-ad-campaign-begins-on-london-buses-despite-warnings/" data-wpel-link="internal">painted</a> and decorated with the project&#8217;s brand in what seemed to be the first advertisement meme coin campaign of this kind.</p>
<p>Riding on the back of meme coin hype, FLOKI is oftentimes influenced by the movements of its peers &#8211; the likes of SHIB and DOGE. Therefore, when the market is calm, it&#8217;s usually a precursor to a considerable move.</p>
<h3>Dogelon Mars (ELON)</h3>
<p>Dogelon Mars (ELON) is a space-themed meme coin that obviously takes away from the name of Elon Musk and his quest to populate Mars.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency is themed around a Shiba Inu dog that&#8217;s called Dogelon Mars and who wants to explore the mysteries of the universe.</p>
<p>That said, ELON has managed to acquire a market cap of more than $110 million at the time of this writing, effectively putting it in the top 5 of the largest meme coins by this metric.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s down around 17% in the past month, but its price is commonly impacted by tweets of Elon Musk (to no one&#8217;s surprise), so monitoring it might be a good idea.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>All in all, the PEPE coin price madness seems to have calmed down for the time being, and the cryptocurrency is winding down in terms of momentum. Buyers are absent.</p>
<p>This could be a precursor to a move in other parts of the meme coins market, and monitoring some of the best-established names in the field might be a good idea.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-meme-coins-to-watch-as-pepe-coin-mania-winds-down/" rel="nofollow">4 Meme Coins to Watch as PEPE Coin Mania Winds Down</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atomic Wallet Hacked: Largest Victim Reportedly Lost 2.8M USDT</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacked-largest-victim-reportedly-lost-2-8m-usdt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 10:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253733</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/hacker_steal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Some users blamed the wallet provider that they had funds stolen from their accounts in the past as well.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The non-custodial decentralized crypto wallet Atomic Wallet &#8211; with a reported user base of over five million customers &#8211; said some of its users complained about having their digital assets drained.</p>
<p>Later reports suggested that numerous users had six figures worth of crypto wiped out, while the largest victim lost nearly $3 million worth of Tether (USDT).</p>
<ul>
<li>The team behind the wallet took it to Twitter yesterday to <a href="https://twitter.com/atomicwallet/status/1664946301815910400?s=46" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">inform</a> that some users complained about having their accounts compromised. Atomic said the team will go into further investigations, but there have been no official updates as of writing these lines.</li>
<li>The waves of complaints under the Atomic Twitter post continue, with some <a href="https://twitter.com/JimWear/status/1664996030482378752" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claiming</a> that they had their funds stolen in the past and that the wallet provider did nothing to help them at the time.</li>
<li>Popular crypto sleuth &#8211; ZachXBT &#8211; said he received numerous messages from Atomic users regarding their lost funds.</li>
<li>According to the on-chain investigator, the largest single victim lost 2.8 million worth of Tether (USDT). ZachXBT added that they observed &#8220;multiple other losses&#8221; worth six figures in digital assets across different chains.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Some things to note about this hack.</p>
<p>Largest single victim I have observed is for 2.8M USDT. Multiple other losses for 6 figures across different chains.</p>
<p>Thanks to all of the victims who have messaged me their transaction hash. The root cause is still tbd. <a href="https://t.co/4sybXUrXBo" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/4sybXUrXBo</a> <a href="https://t.co/or2b3eMvIs" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/or2b3eMvIs</a></p>
<p>— ZachXBT (@zachxbt) <a href="https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1665080799253733377?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 3, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<ul>
<li>Although some reports claim that DeFi hacks are on the decline in contrast to rug pulls, there have been several larger ones in the past few weeks.</li>
<li>The latest example was the liquidity protocol Jimbos, which had $7.5 million worth of crypto <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/hacked-liquidity-protocol-jimbos-offers-deadline-to-exploiters-before-onboarding-law-enforcement/" data-wpel-link="internal">drained</a> last weekend.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacked-largest-victim-reportedly-lost-2-8m-usdt/" rel="nofollow">Atomic Wallet Hacked: Largest Victim Reportedly Lost 2.8M USDT</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido DAO (LDO) Soars 17% Weekly, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $27K (Weekend Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lido-dao-ldo-soars-17-weekly-bitcoin-btc-maintains-27k-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 08:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253726</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin_Lido_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/Bitcoin_Lido_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Aside from LDO, INJ and QNT are the two other massive gainers in the past week.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin has remained stuck during the weekend amid the lower trading volumes but still stands above $27,000.</p>
<p>The altcoins are also quiet on a daily scale, but several &#8211; such as LDO, INJ, and QNT, have produced massive weekly gains.</p>
<h2>BTC Flat at $27K</h2>
<p>It was less than a week ago, on Monday when the primary cryptocurrency initiated a massive leg-up that resulted in tapping a three-week high at $28,500. This came after the initial deal reached by the US government in regard to the nation&#8217;s debt ceiling.</p>
<p>However, the asset failed to continue upwards and returned to $28,000 by Tuesday. A significant $1,000 price drop occurred on Wednesday, which was mimicked by a similar one a day later. Ultimately, BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-ldo-and-aptos-apt-soar-by-7-btc-remains-shaky-at-27k-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">dropped</a> to a weekly low on Friday morning at under $26,600.</p>
<p>The bulls managed to intercept the move and helped bitcoin recover some of the losses by the time the weekend arrived. The past two days have been rather <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tron-explodes-10-daily-bitcoin-stable-at-27k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">uneventful</a>, as the cryptocurrency remains stuck at just above $27,000 amid the typically low weekend trading volumes.</p>
<p>Consequently, BTC&#8217;s total capitalization is still at $525 billion, and its dominance over the alts is at the same place as yesterday &#8211; 45.9%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253727" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253727" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253727" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="875" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3-300x143.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3-1024x489.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3-768x366.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3-1536x733.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/BTCUSD-3-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253727" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LDO, INJ, QNT Record Weekly Gains</h2>
<p>The larger-cap altcoins have mimicked BTC&#8217;s performance during the weekend, meaning there are little-to-no volatile movements. Despite a minor daily setback, ETH still stands at precisely $1,900 after going below and over that level during the week.</p>
<p>Binance Coin, Ripple, Dogecoin, Polygon, Litecoin, Shiba Inu, and Avalanche have all added less than 1% in the past 24 hours. ADA, SOL, and DOT are up by somewhere between 1-2%.</p>
<p>Yesterday&#8217;s top performer &#8211; TRON &#8211; has dumped hard today by almost 5%. Looking at the charts on a weekly scale provides a different picture for several alts. Lido DAO, Injective, and Quant have all soared by over 15% within the past seven days.</p>
<p>In total, though, the crypto market cap has remained relatively sluggish in the past two days and sits close to $1.150 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_253728" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-253728" style="width: 1879px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-253728" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1879" height="849" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2.jpg 1879w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2-300x136.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2-1024x463.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2-768x347.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2-1536x694.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Allcoins-2-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1879px) 100vw, 1879px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-253728" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-dao-ldo-soars-17-weekly-bitcoin-btc-maintains-27k-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Lido DAO (LDO) Soars 17% Weekly, Bitcoin (BTC) Maintains $27K (Weekend Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>OvalPixel Launches Groundbreaking Play-to-Earn OPAIG AI Game Token</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ovalpixel-launches-groundbreaking-play-to-earn-opaig-ai-game-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 06:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=253641</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/OvalPixel_AI_Play2Earn_game_1685715297dX6UyMp4Ct.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/OvalPixel_AI_Play2Earn_game_1685715297dX6UyMp4Ct.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Los Angeles, USA, June 2nd, 2023] OvalPixel announced the launch of its groundbreaking blockchain-powered artificial intelligence (AI) trivia game that pays players in crypto tokens. The OvalPixel AI game token with the symbol $OPAIG allows players of all ages and experience levels, from gamers to grandmas, to earn OPAIG utility tokens by [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Los Angeles, USA, June 2nd, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://ovalpixel.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">OvalPixel </a>announced the launch of its groundbreaking blockchain-powered artificial intelligence (AI) trivia game that pays players in crypto tokens.</p>
<p>The OvalPixel AI game token with the symbol $OPAIG allows players of all ages and experience levels, from gamers to grandmas, to earn OPAIG utility tokens by correctly answering trivia/quiz questions generated in real-time by OvalPixel’s innovative AI system.</p>
<p>We live in an age of constant connectivity and information at our fingertips. But one thing has been missing—until now. OPAIG is the first play-to-earn game that harnesses the power of AI, blockchain technology, and crypto to revolutionize how people play and interact.</p>
<p>Players can then exchange their OPAIG tokens for real money through the Banana Crystal Payments platform or use them in-game to buy exciting 3D NFT trophies from the <a href="https://www.flatpyramid.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">FlatPyramid 3D Model Marketplace</a>.</p>
<p>To enable mainstream audience access, OvalPixel has partnered with <a href="https://www.bananacrystal.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Banana Crystal Payments</a>. This allows anyone to play OPAIG and earn tokens which they can simply convert to USDT digital dollars. No complex crypto knowledge is needed.</p>
<p>OvalPixel will institute a continuous buyback and burn mechanism to increase the value of OPAIG tokens over time. In addition to buying back and burning OPAIG tokens, OvalPixel will also buy back redeemed tokens and reintroduce them into the rewards pool. Thus, preventing the need to mint additional tokens and inflating the supply, and helping with the preservation of OPAIG’s value.</p>
<p>This means that early adopters stand to gain the most as supply decreases and demand rises. The company will also airdrop free OPAIG tokens to early adopters and players.</p>
<blockquote><p>“We believe OPAIG represents the future of gaming, AI and blockchain technology,” said OvalPixel CEO George Egbuonu. “For the first time, we have created a seamless experience that fuses these revolutionary technologies in an accessible way for the masses. Players of all backgrounds can now enjoy the benefits of crypto and be rewarded for expanding their knowledge.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The OPAIG game is available now for play on the OvalPixel website. OvalPixel aims to onboard millions of active players in the first year and demonstrate how blockchain and AI can go mainstream. The revolution starts today at OvalPixel with the fusion of AI, blockchain technology and crypto. Users can play to earn and get paid in crypto.</p>
<p>OPAIG token is now trading on the Uniswap Polygon chain (Trading Pair: $OPAIG &#8211; $MATIC). Users can take part in the revolution and play to earn real crypto rewards.</p>
<p><img src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/OPAIG_Token_Life_on_Uniswap_1685703122Br9cLNaVV0.jpg" /></p>
<h2>About OvalPixel</h2>
<p>OvalPixel provides a Play to Earn Blockchain-Powered AI Trivia &amp; Quiz Game. The AI game generates new trivia multiple-choice questions and answers on any topic on-demand, so players are always challenged and expanding their knowledge. Players can play with ease and win OPAIG utility tokens and redeem them for digital dollars through the Banana Crystal payment platform.</p>
<p>Visit: https://ovalpixel.com/</p>
<p><div class="embed"><iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/a4B14_DbQLE?showinfo=0"></iframe></div></p>
<h2>About Banana Crystal Payments</h2>
<p>Banana Crystal is the leading peer-to-peer payment provider enabling user-friendly web3 payment technology. It provides onramp and offramp crypto-fiat and vice versa solutions as the official payment network for AI and Gaming Applications. It is the only payment network that works anywhere and everywhere in the world and its users are able to send and receive payments for FREE.</p>
<p>Visit: https://www.bananacrystal.com/</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ovalpixel-launches-groundbreaking-play-to-earn-opaig-ai-game-token/" rel="nofollow">OvalPixel Launches Groundbreaking Play-to-Earn OPAIG AI Game Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
