<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:40:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This Canadian Man Lost his Life Savings in a Crypto Scam on YouTube</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-canadian-man-lost-his-life-savings-in-a-crypto-scam-on-youtube/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 21:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234799</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Scam_Alert.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Stephen Carr lost almost half a million dollars and put his home for sale after becoming a victim of a cryptocurrency scam.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stephen Carr &#8211; a resident of Meaford, Ontario &#8211; said he lost his entire life savings of nearly $500,000 after being conned into a cryptocurrency scheme on YouTube.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Scammers have used the video-sharing website multiple times to lure victims. Some have even uploaded fake recordings of famous people, including Elon Musk, Steve Wozniak, Bill Gates, and Kanye West, who appear to promote dubious cryptocurrency investments.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;I&#8217;m Devastated&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://toronto.ctvnews.ca/ontario-man-devastated-after-losing-his-home-and-nearly-500k-to-crypto-scam-1.6244788" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Carr said he got involved in the crypto scam through a video he watched on YouTube. The wrongdoers promised viewers they could make significant profits if they invested in their project. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Initially, the Canadian found nothing suspicious and contacted the people. He started with a $250 investment and contributed another $2,500 shortly after.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">After a while, Carr requested a $1,000 withdrawal, and the entity honored it immediately. This gave him more confidence that everything was legitimate, and between October 2022 to January 2023, he invested almost $500,000 (his entire life savings). </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Canadian had his first doubts when he saw his funds growing to $1.3 million and asked to cash out part of it. However, the bad actors insisted he pays a $150,000 liquidation fee to complete the withdrawal. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I got conned, and in hindsight, I put a ridiculous amount of money in this and a ridiculous amount of trust in these people,&#8221; Carr regretted. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The devastated individual admitted the fraud had forced him to put his house for sale so he could reorganize his life. &#8220;I&#8217;ve got maybe two or three months of useable cash left, and that&#8217;s it,&#8221; he added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Carr said he wanted to share his story so others could stay cautious and not repeat his mistake.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jason Tschetter &#8211; an Alberta resident who also got conned in a similar scheme last year &#8211; recently launched Fraud Hunters Canada (an organization that supports victims and helps them recover funds).</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He outlined that criminals have turned cryptocurrency scams into an &#8220;actual business,&#8221; while the police lack the necessary time and ability to research and catch the culprits.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Unfortunately, a lot of people are going to go through the anger, the depression, the denial. They will even try to bargain with the criminal, but it just won&#8217;t work. I&#8217;ve spoken to several recovery firms, but a lot of them are in the same boat and are fraudulent themselves,&#8221; Tschetter stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Crypto Scams on YouTube</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Steve Wozniak &#8211; one of Apple&#8217;s Co-Founders &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/apple-co-founder-steve-wozniak-sues-youtube-over-fake-bitcoin-giveaways/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a lawsuit against YouTube in the summer of 2020, alleging it allowed fraudsters to use his face to lure people into fake bitcoin giveaways. The American inventor and computer programmer </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/apples-co-founder-steve-wozniak-loses-bitcoin-scam-case-against-youtube/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the case in 2021 after the court determined his arguments were not strong enough. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Wozniak is not the only famous figure involved in such scams. Criminals have also impersonated Elon Musk, Bill Gates, and others over the years.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-canadian-man-lost-his-life-savings-in-a-crypto-scam-on-youtube/" rel="nofollow">This Canadian Man Lost his Life Savings in a Crypto Scam on YouTube</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>8 Years in Prison for a Doctor Paying $60K in BTC to Dark Web Hitmen</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/8-years-in-prison-for-a-doctor-paying-60k-in-btc-to-dark-web-hitmen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234991</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ArrestJail.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/ArrestJail.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Doctor Ilg will stay behind bars for 96 months for transferring over $60,000 in BTC to hitmen to injure victims.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Senior United States District Judge William Fremming Nielsen sentenced the 56-year-old American Ronald Craig Ilg to eight years in federal prison.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The latter hired hitmen on the Dark Web to kidnap his wife and beat his former colleague, and paid them over $60,000 worth of bitcoin.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Maximum Penalty for the Doctor</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US Department of Justice (DOJ) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-edwa/pr/former-spokane-doctor-sentenced-eight-years-federal-prison-after-paying-dark-web" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that Ronald Ilg will serve 96 months in federal prison and will be supervised for three years after his release. He will also pay $25,000 in restitution and a $100,000 fine. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The former neonatologist from Spokane, Washington, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/a-doctor-paid-60k-worth-of-btc-to-hitmen-to-kidnap-his-wife/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">hired</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> hitmen on the Dark Web in 2021 who were supposed to injure a former professional colleague of his. Ilg particularly requested the criminals to break the hands of the victim, paying more than $2,000 worth of bitcoin for the misdeed. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The next victim was his estranged wife. Ilg instructed the wrongdoers to kidnap and inject her with heroin so she could drop divorce proceedings. He paid them approximately $60,000 worth of bitcoin and promised a bonus upon completing the mission. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The FBI intercepted Ilg&#8217;s messages on the Dark Web and started an investigation. At first, the doctor falsely claimed he paid the hitmen to kill him and not hurt other people. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He later sent a letter to a key case witness, begging her to marry him so he could control her testimony in court. The American even promised to pay tuition for her children to attend St. Aloysius Catholic School and Gonzaga Preparatory School.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Judge Nielsen, who ruled the maximum sentence, described Ilg&#8217;s crime as &#8220;really egregious, and even evil.&#8221; He further stated:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;A doctor&#8217;s goal in life is to protect people, keeping people alive &#8211; not taking overt steps to do the opposite.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Vanessa Waldref &#8211; US Attorney for the Eastern District of Washington &#8211; said this case demonstrates how violent individuals could exploit cyberspace and cryptocurrencies to finance their gruesome intentions. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Assistant US Attorney Richard Barker added that Ilg tried to profit from his crimes by selling the story to the media. He congratulated the victims for their &#8220;incredible courage&#8221; and shed more light on the doctor&#8217;s plans:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Even before Mr. Ilg sent his terrifying messages through the dark Web and paid more than $60,000 to multiple purported hitmen, Mr. Ilg sought to manipulate and maintain control his victims – sending them harassing text messages, placing GPS trackers on their cars, and even subjecting them to domestic abuse.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Jessica Sledge&#8217;s Case</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American authorities have some experience with such cases as last summer they </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/mississippi-woman-jailed-for-10-years-after-paying-for-murder-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">sentenced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Jessica Sledge &#8211; resident of Pelahatchie, Mississippi &#8211; to ten years in jail. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">She paid $10,000 in bitcoin to a Dark Web hitman who had to kill her husband, but the FBI detected the plot. Apart from the prison time, she paid a $1,000 fine, and law enforcement agents will monitor her actions three years after her release.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/8-years-in-prison-for-a-doctor-paying-60k-in-btc-to-dark-web-hitmen/" rel="nofollow">8 Years in Prison for a Doctor Paying $60K in BTC to Dark Web Hitmen</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Argo Blockchain Slapped With Lawsuit Over Misleading Statements</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/argo-blockchain-slapped-with-lawsuit-over-misleading-statements/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 15:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235175</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Argo_Lawsuit.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Argo_Lawsuit.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The lawsuit claimed that Argo's "wrongful acts and omissions" caused a "precipitous decline" in ADS's market value leading to significant investor losses and damages. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Argo Blockchain has been accused of federal securities law violation during the initial public offering (IPO) of its American depositary shares (ADS) in 2021, according to a filing in the United States District Court for the Eastern District of New York.</p>
<p>The latest development is yet another blow to Argo, which was struggling to stay afloat amidst a brutal crypto winter. The complaint alleged that the company negligently prepared its IPO documents which hid crucial details that would affect its business profitability.</p>
<h2>Lawsuit Against Argo</h2>
<p>In the class action <a href="https://assets.law360news.com/1569000/1569805/https-ecf-nyed-uscourts-gov-doc1-123119695867.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">lawsuit</a>, investors of Argo Blockchain have accused the firm of making untrue statements and omitting key information, thereby failing to disclose its capital constraints, electricity, and other costs, in addition to network difficulties. The filing said the constraints hampered its ability to mine Bitcoin and operate its Helios facility in Texas.</p>
<p>The argument was centered around Argo&#8217;s business being less sustainable than investors were led to believe. They also alleged that the firm&#8217;s business and financial prospects were overstated. As a result of &#8220;wrongful acts and omissions&#8221; by Argo, investors were at the receiving end of significant losses.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Offering Documents were negligently prepared and, as a result, contained untrue statements of material fact or omitted to state other facts necessary to make the statements made not misleading and were not prepared in accordance with the rules and regulations governing their preparation.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>During its IPO, the London-based miner issued about 7.5 million ADS shares at an offering price of $15, resulting in proceeds of roughly $105 million to the mining firm. The share price, though, has plunged massively since then.</p>
<h2>Crypto Winter Proved Rocky for Argo</h2>
<p>Alongside several miners, Argo Blockchain was forced to sell more than it mined in a month last summer as prices went south. As its shares took a beating, the formerly announced plan to raise $27 million was called off. By the end of 2022, it suspended trading of its shares on Nasdaq.</p>
<p>Argo even sold its Helios mining facility in Texas to Galaxy Digital for $65 million. The deal also required Galaxy will also provide the mining company with a $35 million loan to avoid bankruptcy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/argo-blockchain-slapped-with-lawsuit-over-misleading-statements/" rel="nofollow">Argo Blockchain Slapped With Lawsuit Over Misleading Statements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Tried to Influence a Former FTX Employee&#8217;s Testimony, US Prosecutors Claim</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-tried-to-influence-a-former-ftx-employees-testimony-us-prosecutors-claim/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235358</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sam_Bankman-Fried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Sam_Bankman-Fried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The prosecutors are trying to change SBF's bail rules.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The disgraced founder and former CEO of FTX tried to contact and potentially influence the witness testimony of another exchange employee, according to the US Department of Justice.</p>
<p>As such, the prosecutors want to introduce two new rules for SBF&#8217;s bail.</p>
<ul>
<li>Sam Bankman-Fried was released on a $250 million bond in December last year, and he is confined to his parent&#8217;s house. However, he seems to have tried to contact FTX US General Counsel Ryne Miller on the encrypted messaging app Signal.</li>
<li>Recall that this is not SBF&#8217;s first reported case of using Signal for controversial goals. He wanted to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-battles-for-control-of-450m-robinhood-shares-in-us-bankruptcy-court/" data-wpel-link="internal">sell</a> the highly disputed Robinhood shares through the app in 2022.</li>
<li>The <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940/gov.uscourts.nysd.590940.50.0.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">letter</a> to Judge Kaplan outlined the message SBF sent to Miller:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>“I would really love to reconnect and see if there’s a way for us to have a constructive relationship, use each other as resources when possible, or at least vet things with each other.”</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The DOJ believes Bankman-Fried also tried contacting other FTX and Alameda employees, which the prosecutor said suggests &#8220;an effort to influence&#8221; at least one of the witnesses&#8217; future testimony.</li>
<li>As such, the DOJ wants the Judge to amend SBF&#8217;s bail rules and include two more. The first is to prohibit him from contacting any current or former employees or related parties of FTX, Alameda, or any of their affiliated companies, except for family members.</li>
<li>The second read that SBF should be constrained from using encrypted messaging applications such as Signal.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-tried-to-influence-a-former-ftx-employees-testimony-us-prosecutors-claim/" rel="nofollow">SBF Tried to Influence a Former FTX Employee&#8217;s Testimony, US Prosecutors Claim</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weekend Watch: Litecoin Soars 7.5% to 8-Month High, Bitcoin Stands Above $23K</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-litecoin-soars-7-5-to-8-month-high-bitcoin-stands-above-23k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 09:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235348</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Litecoin_Bitcoin_MW.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[LTC is among the few altcoins with an impressive price surge over the past 24 hours. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite failing to overcome $23,500 once again in the past 24 hours, BTC is still slightly in the green today and stands above $23,000.</p>
<p>The altcoins are quite calm today, as only Litecoin stands out as a notable gainer.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Firm Above $23K</h2>
<p>The start of last weekend saw bitcoin&#8217;s price surge from $21,000 to and beyond $23,000. Somewhat expectedly, reaching the latter meant tapping a multi-month high since BTC was stuck around $17,000 for months.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency spent most of the week in a range between $22,000 and $23,000, aside from a couple of brief price pumps. The most notable one took the asset to $23,800, which became the new highest price point since September.</p>
<p>However, each attempt was intercepted quickly by the bears, and they didn&#8217;t allow new local peaks. Then came the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stable-at-23k-as-q4-2022-us-gdp-beats-expectations/" data-wpel-link="internal">US GDP data</a> and the PCE numbers, but they didn&#8217;t bring any substantial volatility.</p>
<p>As such, BTC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/avalanche-skyrockets-14-bitcoin-calm-at-23k-weekend-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">entered</a> the weekend at just under $23,000. It shot up to $23,300 (on Bitstamp), and even though it has retraced slightly since then, it still trades north of $23,000 as of now.</p>
<p>Its market cap has jumped to just over $445 billion, while its dominance over the alts sits at 42.3%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235349" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235349" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235349" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-29-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235349" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>LTC 7.5% Up</h2>
<p>Litecoin stands out as the most impressive performer from the larger-cap altcoins today. It is up by over 7% and trades close to $100, which is its highest price point since May 6.</p>
<p>LEO and APT are the other larger caps well in the green today. Both are up by around 3% and trade at $3.7 and $18, respectively.</p>
<p>Ethereum, Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Polygon, and OKB are quite calmer today, with gains of up to 1%.</p>
<p>With the rest of the market trading with little-to-no volatility now, it&#8217;s somewhat normal that the cumulative market cap of all crypto assets is quiet at just over $1.050 trillion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_235350" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-235350" style="width: 1858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-235350" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1858" height="733" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19.jpg 1858w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19-300x118.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19-1024x404.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19-768x303.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19-1536x606.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-19-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1858px) 100vw, 1858px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-235350" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/weekend-watch-litecoin-soars-7-5-to-8-month-high-bitcoin-stands-above-23k/" rel="nofollow">Weekend Watch: Litecoin Soars 7.5% to 8-Month High, Bitcoin Stands Above $23K</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Loud North Carolina Crypto Miner Forces Residents to Relocate (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/loud-north-carolina-crypto-miner-forces-residents-to-relocate-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234689</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_mining_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin_mining_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Resident Lugiewicz said the crypto miner could be as loud as the Niagara Falls.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Residents of Murphy, North Carolina, complained that a cryptocurrency miner located in the area causes &#8220;insane&#8221; noise and negatively impacts the electric grid. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As such, some people have decided to leave the town and settle in another place.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;It Sounds Like You Are Behind a Jet&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The crypto miner installed by the San Francisco-based company PrimeBlock seems to be a huge problem for some of the 1,600 inhabitants of Murphy, North Carolina. In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.foxnews.com/media/north-carolina-crypto-mine-drives-residents-away-insane-noise-electric-grid-concerns" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, resident Mike Lugiewicz said he will relocate because of the unbearable noise coming from the facility.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;This morning it&#8217;s running at about 85 decibels. It sounds and feels like you&#8217;re behind a jet sitting on the tarmac, and that jet never leaves, or imagine being inside of Niagara Falls and not being able to get rid of the noise ever like your house is dead center of Niagara Falls,&#8221; he said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from that, the miner has harmed the domestic power grid. Lugiewicz said the community was left without electricity over the Christmas holidays when temperatures dropped to three degrees Celsius. Despite the blackout across the town, the facility was still working:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;While we&#8217;re sitting in the dark, I can look out my window, and I could see the crypto mine had power, and I think that that&#8217;s kind of hurtful right there for the power companies to shut down our power, but leave the crypto mines up and running.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While Lugiewicz has already decided to move somewhere else, many locals are elderly people who do not have that ability. He raised hopes that the authorities take necessary measures to stop the &#8220;insane&#8221; noise and restore the well-being of the Murphy inhabitants:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;My fight is more for my friends and neighbors. We had one neighbor up on top of the mountain, and her house feels like it&#8217;s going to vibrate apart. It&#8217;s so loud up there.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto Mining Could Have Benefits, too</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Despite the numerous claims that cryptocurrency mining harms the environment and consumes a lot of energy, the process could have a positive impact if employed properly. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One such example is the Canadian town of North Vancouver, where the Lonsdale Energy Corporation (LEC) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-mining-to-provide-heat-in-vancouver-canada/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">partnered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with the bitcoin miner – MintGreen &#8211; to recycle released energy and use it for heating residential and commercial buildings.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The innovative heating solution provides the locals with a constant source of electricity since the mining company operates at full capacity 365 days a year.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/loud-north-carolina-crypto-miner-forces-residents-to-relocate-report/" rel="nofollow">Loud North Carolina Crypto Miner Forces Residents to Relocate (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>El Salvador&#8217;s Bitcoin City Wins an International Design Award (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-city-wins-an-international-design-award-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 23:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[El Salvador]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235174</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Bitcoin_City.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Bitcoin_City.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The LOOP Design Awards honored the innovative Bitcoin City for its architecture and interior design.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The LOOP Design Awards reportedly recognized the Bitcoin City of El Salvador&#8217;s government as one of the most outstanding projects in interior design and architecture. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">When completed, the metropolis will use the energy released from the Conchagua volcano to power itself and BTC as its currency. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bukele&#8217;s Dream City Gets an Award</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.noticiasdebariloche.com.ar/la-bitcoin-city-de-el-salvador-gana-premio-de-diseno-arquitectonico/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, El Salvador&#8217;s urban project stood out among 700 proposals. The jury outlined its innovative interior style, while the beautiful surrounding nature and the nearby volcanoes also attributed to the success. They also highlighted the work of the Mexican architect Fernando Romero who designed it.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Bitcoin City will be built in the southeast of the Latin American country, close to two of the nation&#8217;s biggest volcanoes &#8211; Conchagua and Tecapa. Romero&#8217;s team said the future metropolis will be &#8220;efficient and sustainable&#8221; and will use geothermal energy from the volcanoes to power itself. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It will use bitcoin as its currency which could provide certain monetary benefits to the residents. &#8220;The new public space will be the culmination of decades of research into what humans need to live well in an anti-inflationary economy,&#8221; the architect outlined.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Romero designed the urban area in the shape of a circle so it could represent the logo of bitcoin when looked at from above. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The President of El Salvador &#8211; Nayib Bukele &#8211; was the first to present the project in 2021. The local government planned to raise a $1 billion bitcoin-backed bond to finance the construction, which was supposed to mature in 2032. However, the authorities </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-1b-bitcoin-bond-offering-delayed-will-wait-for-favorable-market-conditions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">postponed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it in March 2022, citing unfavorable market conditions.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bukele shed more light on the design in May last year, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/president-bukele-shows-plans-of-proposed-ambitious-bitcoin-city/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showing </span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">how the city will look when observed from the air, its modern airport, and its volcano watchtower.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">So Many More Bitcoin Initiatives</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Apart from becoming the first nation to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/three-months-later-bitcoin-now-officially-a-legal-tender-in-el-salvador/" data-wpel-link="internal">embrace</a> the primary cryptocurrency as a legal tender, El Salvador&#8217;s government has also introduced several projects related to it in the past few years.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-fueled-vet-hospital-opens-this-week/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">built</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a massive vet hospital named Chivo Pets, where treatments are paid in BTC, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-education-centre-opens-in-el-salvador/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">opened</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an education center that provides &#8220;free and accessible learning opportunities&#8221; surrounding the asset for Salvadorans.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The authorities have also started accumulating bitcoin on a macroeconomic level, holding approximately $54 million of it (as of now). The amount, though, could be higher since Bukele </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvador-to-start-buying-1-bitcoin-per-day-says-bukele/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">announced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in November that the government will purchase one BTC per day. It remains unknown whether the buying spree goes as promised.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/el-salvadors-bitcoin-city-wins-an-international-design-award-report/" rel="nofollow">El Salvador&#8217;s Bitcoin City Wins an International Design Award (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>2022 Was Crypto’s Dot Com Bust: Let’s Recap Tech Stocks After 2000 (Opinion)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/2022-was-cryptos-dot-com-bust-lets-recap-tech-stocks-after-2000-opinion/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 20:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Opinions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234196</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[2022 saw a myriad of major market participants crash and burn, but that's not the end of cryptocurrency. In fact, it's just getting started. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The last year saw the fall of the Terra-Luna ecosystem, BlockFi, Celsius, Voyager Digital, 3AC, and Alameda-FTX. But it&#8217;s not the end of cryptocurrency. Like the Internet after the Dot Com bust, crypto is still just getting started.</p>
<p>Sure, it&#8217;s true that several crypto firms went down in 2022. But it seems worse in the headlines than it is in reality. Cryptocurrency&#8217;s critics in news journalism and the traditional finance industry are treating the failure stories as representative of the entire industry.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency community likes to use the term &#8220;FUD&#8221; to describe the proliferation of negative crypto news. In some ways, that&#8217;s natural and understandable in terms of vigilance, transparency, and threat detection.</p>
<p>Fud is an acronym to describe crypto news articles or social media posts that add to perceptions and feelings of fear, uncertainty, and doubt. While the FUD may start arguments on Twitter or YouTube and boost engagement, it rarely informs about recent threats and weaknesses.</p>
<p>Instead, it usually over-discusses them and creates a bias for participants in these discussions to overweigh them in their view of the industry and markets. Besides, all the FUD doesn&#8217;t tell anyone about the great products the crypto industry is building.</p>
<h2>Crypto Critics Continue to Inspire Doubt</h2>
<p>At this point, crypto&#8217;s inevitability is hard to hold in doubt for anyone who is apprised of the facts about cryptocurrencies and the latest techniques and products of the global financial market.</p>
<p>Take, for example, <a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2023/01/19/scaramucci-crypto-davos-sbf-00078631" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">this recent story</a> in The Politico about the attitude toward crypto at Davos. It says:</p>
<blockquote><p>Scaramucci is one of a slew of crypto junkies — executives and staffers from high-profile exchanges, intermediaries and tech companies — who are here in this Swiss ski resort town to try to convince investors and potential backers that, despite the nearly complete collapse of the industry this fall, everything is just fine.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>There is simply no sense of these words, &#8220;nearly complete collapse,&#8221; that is accurate. The crypto industry did not come near completely collapsing last fall. Another company in the cryptocurrency industry, a new venture startup company in an innovative tech space at that, went out of business.</p>
<h2>The Internet Never Stopped Growing After the Dot Com Crash</h2>
<p>More crypto businesses and altcoins will fail in the crypto industry in the future. That doesn&#8217;t make blockchain different than any other sector of the economy. Additionally, the Bitcoin price and altcoins were all <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-bitcoin-price-winter-continue-in-2023-8-key-considerations/" data-wpel-link="internal">in deep correction</a> in 2022. But the context is that was after an equally steep bull run through November 2021.</p>
<p>But the production of crypto networks throughout the crypto winter of 2022 did not come near total collapse. They did not fail. They did not even falter. Bitcoin hashrate and difficulty <a href="https://btc.com/stats/diff" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">continued to climb</a> through the crypto winter. The network&#8217;s miners continue to find a new block on average every ten minutes and fulfill transaction orders for addresses.</p>
<p>Activity on the Bitcoin network remained robust. Daily new active BTC addresses <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/bitcoin-activeaddresses.html#3y" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">were the picture of</a> healthy globally-scaled digital platform usage. The most popular altcoin, Ethereum (ETH), saw the same robust growth in staking and network usage.</p>
<p>So it is simply misleading to say the cryptocurrency industry nearly completely collapsed in 2022. It may be that many people with only a superficial understanding of crypto think that is what really happened.</p>
<p>But crypto didn&#8217;t almost disappear last year, and neither is it a &#8220;pet rock,&#8221; as JP Morgan&#8217;s Jamie Dimon <a href="https://fortune.com/2023/01/19/jpmorgan-ceo-jamie-dimon-bitcoin-hyped-up-fraud-cryptocurrencies-waste-of-time-but-blockchain-deployable-technology/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recently taunted</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-234490" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover.jpg" alt="bubble_burst_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/bubble_burst_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Drawing a Comparison</h2>
<p>Crypto&#8217;s future fortunes look today like the Internet&#8217;s did in 2000. Even after several dot com stocks crashed and burned in a widely discussed media spectacle. The parallels are almost eerie.</p>
<p>Back in 1999, the Internet had the same sort of criticism in the media that crypto has today. They said it was a passing fad. They complained it was too clunky and difficult to use. The public, at first, regarded the Internet as a neat toy for computer nerds.</p>
<p>But they did not see its potential to connect the entire world. Neither do they today see the expected future value of organizing that global connection to be more fair and secure.</p>
<p>Most people did not invest in &#8220;tech stocks&#8221; even after everybody and every business started keeping the Internet within arm&#8217;s reach 24/7 within about a decade after the dot com crash.</p>
<p>Back in 2000, the fud pieces were flying about the Internet. They said it was a place for scams, wire fraud, and over-hyped businesses that didn&#8217;t really produce anything. Not that what they were talking about was entirely untrue.</p>
<p>They were reporting facts, but not really to efficiently sort through them and put them in their greater context to leave their audiences better informed.</p>
<h2>From Failure to Shaping the World</h2>
<p>The newspapers started a small panic in the public over the Y2K bug as if it were going to be the end of the Internet.</p>
<p>Today they use the Internet for their circulation. But the same organizations used to mock the Internet on giant, folded pieces of paper delivered to people&#8217;s houses by a truck.</p>
<p>Many investments made in a late-90s economy, flush with capital and low-interest financing, at the height of dot com mania, were ill-advisable. They burned up when the stock market corrected.</p>
<p>But it was not really hard to notice some of the Internet companies that would go on to win the next couple of decades. Some dot coms had customers and revenues. Others had a dot com website, with some pictures and their email address on it, but not customers or sales.</p>
<p>Amazon, for example, was a well-publicized Internet success story when the Internet was new. It has a sharp business model and founder. This dot com made more books available to its customers than any other bookstore in the world ever had. Then they shipped your order right to your door and took great care of their customers.</p>
<p>Just $1,000 worth of AMZN, bought at $18 a share at its IPO in 1997, had a market value of <a href="https://m.timesofindia.com/business/international-business/what-if-you-had-invested-in-1000-amazons-ipo-in-may-1997/amp_articleshow/84173075.cms" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">over $2 million</a> in 2021. That was just a little over two decades later.</p>
<p>Many cryptocurrencies have already scaled like that in far less time than Amazon stock did.</p>
<h2>A Ton of Developer Interest in the 2020s Is In Crypto</h2>
<p>Young developers in 1999 all wanted to build dot com websites and video games. By the late 2000s, they all wanted to build mobile apps and video games.</p>
<p>By the late 2010s, they all wanted to build cryptocurrencies and DeFi apps (and video games).</p>
<p>Really talented computer science students, creative entrepreneurs, and smart venture capitalists are excited <a href="https://fortune.com/2022/06/29/web3-students-graduates-blockchain-development-crypto-market/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">about cryptocurrency today</a> the way those same kinds of business people were about the Internet twenty years ago.</p>
<p>The emergence of the digital network itself created a global connection revolution. That was characterized by the ability to make digital copies of so many things. Moreover, digital computer copies were super instant, super fast to send around the world, and all of it was super affordable.</p>
<p>There was a flood of digital abundance.</p>
<p>Cryptocurrency is the next step in that connection revolution. Blockchain is an industry that supports the global computer network by reliably producing digital scarcity and securing it to its owners.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/2022-was-cryptos-dot-com-bust-lets-recap-tech-stocks-after-2000-opinion/" rel="nofollow">2022 Was Crypto’s Dot Com Bust: Let’s Recap Tech Stocks After 2000 (Opinion)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fannie Redux? Home Loan Banks Are Bailing Out Crypto Banks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fannie-redux-home-loan-banks-are-bailing-out-crypto-banks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=234561</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/corporate_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/corporate_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[An interesting dynamic is taking shape, despite the fact that the crypto market has largely priced in last year's bankruptcies.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto market seems to have priced in last year&#8217;s string of crypto company bankruptcies. But the crypto firms that survived will still be paying off bank loans to cover their positions for some time.</p>
<p>Crypto prices continue to edge upward while the market bears and bulls regroup.</p>
<p>Even the recent <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" data-wpel-link="internal">bankruptcy of Genesis</a> hasn&#8217;t dampened crypto investors&#8217; enthusiasm.</p>
<h2>Regulators Worry</h2>
<p>Meanwhile, at least two banks with a high-profile roster of cryptocurrency companies for customers are staying afloat with money from home loan banks.</p>
<p>That may be a bullish signal for cryptocurrency in the big-picture view. It could signal traditional finance appetite for crypto exposure despite the risks. It is also, however, a source of consternation for economic planners and regulators.</p>
<p>They are concerned that the growing connections between the crypto sector and traditional finance pose &#8220;contagion&#8221; or &#8220;spillover&#8221; risks that could endanger the entire economy.</p>
<p>It was this kind of over-sophistication of financial markets that led to the financial crisis in 2008. Ironically, that happened as a result of the housing market crash that started in 2007.</p>
<p>A web of connections and fixed-income derivatives (just a kind of smart contract without the blockchain) left the entire economy vulnerable when home prices cratered.</p>
<h2>US Home Loan System Bails Out Two Crypto Banks</h2>
<p>According to a <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-banks-borrow-billions-from-home-loan-banks-to-plug-shortfalls-11674263424" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">recent report</a> in the Wall Street Journal, crypto banks have taken billions in loans out from home loan banks to cover their shortfalls.</p>
<p>The United States Federal Home Loan Banks System (FLHB) has loaned out billions of dollars to two major crypto banks. The organization was originally founded amid the Great Depression to support home lending.</p>
<p>Signature Bank is one of them. Silvergate is another. Both are tradfi companies that made the pivot to do business with crypto but still qualify for home loans.</p>
<p>Even though they technically qualify, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/silvergate-capital-announced-a-1-billion-net-loss-for-q4-2022/" data-wpel-link="internal">their losses</a> over the past year came from crypto, not housing. The loans they&#8217;ve taken out from FLHB may be correct on paper, but they almost certainly support its high-risk, high-reward activities in crypto.</p>
<p>This is the sort of creative banking that causes the spillover risks that worry financial regulators. They are concerned this kind of multiple-role financial business models create technicalities that destabilize the financial system.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fannie-redux-home-loan-banks-are-bailing-out-crypto-banks/" rel="nofollow">Fannie Redux? Home Loan Banks Are Bailing Out Crypto Banks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Despite Recent Market Revival, These Crypto Companies Dismissed More Employees</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/despite-recent-market-revival-these-crypto-companies-dismissed-more-employees/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=235005</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Empty_Office.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Empty_Office.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase, Kraken, Crypto.com, and Gemini are some of the well-known cryptocurrency firms to fire staff after the FTX catastrophe.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The prolonged bear market reduced the interest in cryptocurrencies and hampered the operations of numerous industry players. Some leading exchanges, including Coinbase, Crypto.com, Bybit, and Kraken, laid off a chunk of their workforce to cope with the challenging times. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trend seems to be similar at the start of the new year despite the recent revival of the market, with Gemini, Blockchain.com, Coinbase, and many others announcing a new wave of layoffs.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Dismissal Spree Goes on</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Thousands of people have lost their jobs because of the unfavorable macroeconomic conditions, while <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">the FTX crash</a> and its consecutive domino effect appear to have triggered additional layoffs. Here is a list of crypto firms that trimmed the size of their teams between early November and now.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Argentinean exchange Lemon Cash <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-lemon-cash-reduces-its-team-by-38/" data-wpel-link="internal">cut</a> </span><span data-preserver-spaces="true">around 38% of its personnel, which equals around 100 people. CEO Cavazzoli assured the amendments are not related to the collapse of FTX, admitting that the company had a &#8220;tiny&#8221; exposure to Alameda Research.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Mexican crypto platform Bitso </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberglinea.com/english/mexican-crypto-unicorn-bitso-cuts-25-of-staff-after-ftx-crash/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">dismissed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> around 25% of its staff at the end of November. This was the entity&#8217;s second round of layoffs which previously fired 80 individuals.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The San Francisco-based Kraken also added its name to the list, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/kraken-slashes-30-of-workforce-amid-bear-market-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reducing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its headcount by a third.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8220;Unfortunately, negative influences on the financial markets have continued, and we have exhausted preferable options for bringing costs in line with demand,&#8221; it said.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Bybit </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-to-lay-off-30-of-workforce-amid-colder-crypto-winter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">joined</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the bandwagon in early December, cutting 30% of its headcount, while the Australian exchange Swyftx </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/aussie-crypto-exchange-dismisses-almost-half-of-its-staff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">followed suit</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> with a nearly 50% layoff.</span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://medium.com/@CryptoSavingExpert/crypto-exchange-gate-io-reportedly-lays-off-40-50-of-its-workforce-e124d08661ac" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gate.io</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8211; a trading venue based in the Cayman Islands, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/trons-justin-sun-confirms-20-layoff-at-huobi/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Huobi</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> did not have the best start to the new year, dismissing nearly 50% and 20%, respectively.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the biggest crypto exchanges &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-dismisses-950-people-citing-current-economic-climate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> &#8211; laid off staff for the second time on January 10, while Blockchain.com (28%) and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-respite-from-layoffs-crypto-com-cuts-20-workforce/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Crypto.com</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (20%) did so in the following days.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The other trading platforms that recently reduced the size of their teams are </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.moneycontrol.com/news/business/startup/coindcx-starts-restructuring-business-units-lays-off-employees-9848661.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CoinDCX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Amber Group, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/gemini-lays-of-10-of-employees-due-to-crypto-industrys-bad-actors/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gemini</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (10%), and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-subsidiary-luno-lays-off-35-of-employees-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Luno</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> (35%).</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Industry Players</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The line-up does not include only digital asset exchanges but also companies that offer different types of services. One such example is the cryptocurrency-focused investment firm &#8211; Paradigm. It </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/tradeparadigm/status/1603111504869752832?s=20&amp;t=O6SqEOwrZ_8TwGiE7L3hKw" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reduced</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> salaries instead of dismissing people.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The multichain network supporting Web3 applications &#8211; Octopus Network &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-crypto-company-dismisses-40-of-its-employees-to-survive-the-bear-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">laid off</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 40% of its team members towards the end of 2022. The NFT marketplace &#8211; SuperRare &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/01/06/nft-marketplace-superrare-cuts-30-of-staff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">slashed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 30% at the beginning of 2023, while the blockchain software technology company &#8211; ConsenSys &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/consensys-and-amber-group-join-list-of-companies-dismissing-employees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">took</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the &#8220;extremely difficult decision&#8221; to let go 96 of its employees.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Silvergate Capital &#8211; a crypto-focused bank headquartered in California &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-focused-bank-silvergate-slashes-40-workforce-abandons-several-projects/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">trimmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 40% (around 200 people) and abandoned several projects due to unsatisfying revenue in the previous quarters.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Digital Currency Group &#8211; a venture capital company run by Barry Silbert &#8211; recently dismissed 30% and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcg-wealth-management-division-shuts-down-hours-after-genesis-announced-layoffs-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">closed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its wealth management division. The move came shortly after its subsidiary Genesis announced workforce reduction. Moreover, the platform also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/dcgs-subsidiary-genesis-global-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">filed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Chapter 11 bankruptcy protection.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some Layoffs Until FTX&#8217;s Meltdown</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The first wave of dismissals started at the beginning of Q2 last year (coinciding with Terra&#8217;s fallout and the consecutive market decline). BitMEX </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.scmp.com/business/banking-finance/article/3173139/bitmex-lays-quarter-staff-cryptocurrency-exchanges-revamp" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">fired</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 25% at the time and another 30% months later. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Argentinean platform Buenbit </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/fedeogue/status/1528769450912129026?cxt=HHwWhICxkejto7cqAAAA" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">slashed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> 45% in May in an attempt to reshape its business strategy during the global monetary crisis. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">June also saw a lot of companies shrinking their teams, with Coinbase, Crypto.com, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/winklevoss-gemini-will-lay-off-10-of-its-staff-amid-crypto-winter/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gemini</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/aussie-crypto-operator-lays-off-40-of-staff-citing-crypto-winter-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Banxa</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Vauld, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberglinea.com/english/brazils-crypto-unicorn-2tm-is-cutting-12-of-its-staff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">2TM</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/markets/rates-bonds/middle-east-focused-crypto-firm-bitoasis-cuts-jobs-amid-sector-turmoil-2022-06-19/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BitOasis</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> being some examples. </span></p>
<p><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/opensea-lays-off-20-of-staff-due-to-bear-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">OpenSea</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, CoinFLEX, Core Scientific, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.outlookindia.com/business/wazirx-fires-40-of-its-staff-what-ails-the-crypto-exchange--news-227344" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">WazirX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/crypto-broker-nydig-lays-off-one-third-of-staff-in-effort-to-narrow-focus-11665707545" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">NYDIG</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/nft-giant-dapper-labs-lays-off-22-of-staff-citing-macroeconomic-environment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Dapper Labs</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and more fired employees until the FTX crash, too. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance is Hiring</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Contrary to the countless job cuts, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Binance &#8211; has expansion plans. CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-expanding-hirings-amid-falling-crypto-market/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">assured</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in June last year that the firm has a &#8220;healthy war chest,&#8221; arguing the bear market is an excellent period to hire more personnel.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He doubled down this month, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-aims-for-binance-to-expand-headcount-by-up-to-30-in-2023/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">revealing</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> Binance&#8217;s intentions to increase its team by up to 30%. The Chinese-Canadian executive said the team grew to 8,000 in 2022 (from around 3,000 at the start of the year). </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-recent-market-revival-these-crypto-companies-dismissed-more-employees/" rel="nofollow">Despite Recent Market Revival, These Crypto Companies Dismissed More Employees</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
