<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Italy Introduces Capital Tax on Cryptocurrency Gains - Will Other Countries Follow Suit?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/italy-introduces-capital-tax-on-cryptocurrency-gains-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</link><description>Italy’s parliament has approved a proposal for a 26% tax on crypto gains above 2,000 euros ($2,110). &lt;br /&gt;
In addition to bringing a hefty tax on crypto gains, the new law also introduces incentives for taxpayers to report their crypto. Under the law, crypto owners are entitled to an amnesty for unreported gains achieved in previous years by paying a “substitute tax” of 3.5%, plus a 0.5% fine for each additional year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/italy-introduces-capital-tax-on-cryptocurrency-gains-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm"&gt;Read More: Italy Introduces Capital Tax on Cryptocurrency Gains - Will Other Countries Follow Suit?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Italy</category><category>Portugal</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/italy-introduces-capital-tax-on-cryptocurrency-gains-will-other-countries-follow-suit.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99942/247523/italian-crypto-tax.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2742306"/></item><item><title>Is it Too Late to Buy OKB as Price Pumps Up 25% in 7 Days? Traders Give Their OKB Price Predictions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-okb-as-price-pumps-up-25-7-days-traders-give-their-okb-price-predictions.htm</link><description>In light of its recent run to the upside that has seen the OKB token gain over 23% in the last week and nearly 35% in the last month, despite a broadly stagnant broader cryptocurrency market, investors are asking whether it might now be too late to buy the cryptocurrency. Have the easy gains also been printed? Can the rally be sustained? For the most part, price predictions remain bullish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-okb-as-price-pumps-up-25-7-days-traders-give-their-okb-price-predictions.htm"&gt;Read More: Is it Too Late to Buy OKB as Price Pumps Up 25% in 7 Days? Traders Give Their OKB Price Predictions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>OKB</category><category>OKX Exchange</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-okb-as-price-pumps-up-25-7-days-traders-give-their-okb-price-predictions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99922/247522/20230103-160940-0000.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="531476"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Ukrainian Pharmacy Partners with Binance to Offer Crypto Payments, Sushi Shutting Down Two Products</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ukrainian-pharmacy-partners-with-binance-to-offer-crypto-payments-sushi-shutting-down-two-products.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ukrainian-pharmacy-partners-with-binance-to-offer-crypto-payments-sushi-shutting-down-two-products.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Ukrainian Pharmacy Partners with Binance to Offer Crypto Payments, Sushi Shutting Down Two Products&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Legal</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Bithumb</category><category>FTX</category><category>Bahamas</category><category>Regulation</category><category>DeFi</category><category>SushiSwap</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Aptos</category><category>Bitstamp</category><category>Career</category><category>Ukraine</category><category>Binance</category><category>Payments</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ukrainian-pharmacy-partners-with-binance-to-offer-crypto-payments-sushi-shutting-down-two-products.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99860/247410/adobestock-michaela-jilkova-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="38562"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Today 3 January – FGHT, SOL, D2T, LDO, CCHG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-3-january-fght-sol-d2t-ldo-cchg.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has opened the new year continuing to trade sideways, falling 0.5% over the past 24 hours and trading at around $16.66K currently, close to the daily 20-day Exponential Moving Average resistance. The leading crypto is struggling to maintain a positive bias from the past couple of days with a steady increase in volume....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-3-january-fght-sol-d2t-ldo-cchg.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Today 3 January – FGHT, SOL, D2T, LDO, CCHG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>FGHT</category><category>FightOut</category><category>C-Charge</category><category>CCHG</category><category>SOL</category><category>Solana</category><category>Lido Dao</category><category>LDO</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-today-3-january-fght-sol-d2t-ldo-cchg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99908/247443/best-crypto-3-jan.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="295748"/></item><item><title>New Report: Sam Bankman Fried’s Empire Began to Crumble Long Before the Crypto Crash – Here’s What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-sam-bankman-frieds-empire-began-crumble-long-before-crypto-crash-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>The crypto empire controlled by disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried was fragile for years, with cracks starting to show up already in 2022, a new report has suggested. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the report, published by the Wall Street Journal on New Year’s Eve, Bankman-Fried’s crypto trading firm Alameda Research “never was particularly good at investing.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-sam-bankman-frieds-empire-began-crumble-long-before-crypto-crash-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: New Report: Sam Bankman Fried’s Empire Began to Crumble Long Before the Crypto Crash – Here’s What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Alameda Research</category><category>Sam Bankman-Fried</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/new-report-sam-bankman-frieds-empire-began-crumble-long-before-crypto-crash-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99895/247428/sbf.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="470592"/></item><item><title>Brad Kam, Co-Founder of Unstoppable Domains, on Web3 Domains and Owning Your Data | Ep. 192</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/brad-kam-co-founder-of-unstoppable-domains-on-web3-domains-and-owning-your-data-ep-192.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Brad Kam, Co-Founder of Unstoppable Domains, talks about owning your data on the internet, Web3 domains, and building in a bear market. &lt;br /&gt;
Brad Kam is the Co-Founder of Unstoppable Domains, a Web3 domain name provider working to onboard the world onto Web3. Prior to Unstoppable Domains, he co-founded Talkable, a marketing tech company backed by Y Combinator. Brad holds a B.A. in Political Science from Emory University....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/brad-kam-co-founder-of-unstoppable-domains-on-web3-domains-and-owning-your-data-ep-192.htm"&gt;Read More: Brad Kam, Co-Founder of Unstoppable Domains, on Web3 Domains and Owning Your Data | Ep. 192&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/brad-kam-co-founder-of-unstoppable-domains-on-web3-domains-and-owning-your-data-ep-192.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99894/247424/brad-kam-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="57621"/></item><item><title>Crypto Experts Believe These Altcoins Will Soar in 2023 – Find Out Why</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-experts-believe-these-altcoins-will-soar-2023-find-out-why.htm</link><description>In 2022, the cryptocurrency market experienced an earth-shaking shift as giants such as FTX and Luna crashed. With fintech and DeFi advancing at a rapid pace, analysts are starting to doubt whether current regulations can protect investors from fraud or market manipulation. Governments appear to be stuck in the past and are still failing to keep up with modern innovation, and as cryptocurrencies become more popular it is essential for stakeholders to better comprehend these issues....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-experts-believe-these-altcoins-will-soar-2023-find-out-why.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Experts Believe These Altcoins Will Soar in 2023 – Find Out Why&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>FGHT</category><category>FightOut</category><category>C-Charge</category><category>Calvaria</category><category>RIA</category><category>Taro</category><category>RobotEra</category><category>Altcoins To Buy</category><category>Cryptos Ot Buy</category><category>2023</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-experts-believe-these-altcoins-will-soar-2023-find-out-why.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99866/247400/crypto-experts.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="466003"/></item><item><title>Russian Finance Ministry Says ‘Why Not?’ to Crypto in International Payments</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-finance-ministry-says-why-not-crypto-international-payments.htm</link><description>The Russian Finance Minister has confirmed that his department wants to green-light the use of crypto as a payment tool in international trade. And he says that countries that “want to do business” with Moscow should be allowed to pay in crypto if it is “convenient” for them. &lt;br /&gt;
The comments, which were reported by Tass, came from the ministry chief Anton Siluanov. The minister was speaking to the TV channel Rossiya-24 ahead of the New Year....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-finance-ministry-says-why-not-crypto-international-payments.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Finance Ministry Says ‘Why Not?’ to Crypto in International Payments&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Russia</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-finance-ministry-says-why-not-crypto-international-payments.htm</guid></item><item><title>Grayscale Ethereum Trust Discount Reaches Record 60%, GBTC at 45%</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-ethereum-trust-discount-reaches-record-60-gbtc-at-45.htm</link><description>The Grayscale Ethereum Trust (ETHE) is currently trading at a steep discount to its assets under management (AUM) amid dwindling institutional interest in the fund.  &lt;br /&gt;
As of now, the fund’s discount to net asset value (NAV) has plunged to a record 60%, the lowest premium rate since the inception of the ETHE. ETHE’s premium rate started to collapse significantly by the end of October after a gradual improvement in September amid the excitement around the Merge upgrade. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-ethereum-trust-discount-reaches-record-60-gbtc-at-45.htm"&gt;Read More: Grayscale Ethereum Trust Discount Reaches Record 60%, GBTC at 45%&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Grayscale Investments</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>GBTC</category><category>ETHE</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/grayscale-ethereum-trust-discount-reaches-record-60-gbtc-at-45.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99854/247338/dc8c26531f-media-library-original-900-600.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="59087"/></item><item><title>BitDAO Price Prediction as BIT Rallies 13% – How High Can BIT Go?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitdao-price-prediction-as-bit-rallies-13-how-high-can-bit-go.htm</link><description>The BitDAO price is among the few crypto assets starting the New Year with gains towering above the cryptocurrency space. The decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) token is eyeing a breakout to $0.80 following a massive rebound from support at $0.26. &lt;br /&gt;
BitDAO recently completed a voting process on the BIT Purchase Program, a proposal designed to support the development of the DAO....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitdao-price-prediction-as-bit-rallies-13-how-high-can-bit-go.htm"&gt;Read More: BitDAO Price Prediction as BIT Rallies 13% – How High Can BIT Go?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitdao-price-prediction-as-bit-rallies-13-how-high-can-bit-go.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99846/247320/bitusd-2023-01-03-13-46-45.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="335627"/></item><item><title>Lido DAO Price Prediction as LDO Rockets Up 13% in 24 Hours – LDO to the Moon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-dao-price-prediction-as-ldo-rockets-up-13-24-hours-ldo-moon.htm</link><description>The Lido DAO price has risen by as much as 13% since lows yesterday, with its current price of $1.23 representing a 7.5% gain in 24 hours, and an 18% rise in a week. It's also up by 30% in two weeks, with organic growth in the use of Lido DAO largely responsible for its improving fortunes....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-dao-price-prediction-as-ldo-rockets-up-13-24-hours-ldo-moon.htm"&gt;Read More: Lido DAO Price Prediction as LDO Rockets Up 13% in 24 Hours – LDO to the Moon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/lido-dao-price-prediction-as-ldo-rockets-up-13-24-hours-ldo-moon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99832/247313/lido-dao-price-prediction-as-ldo-rockets-up-13-in-24-hours-ldo-to-the-moon.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1444864"/></item><item><title>Australia Now Home to More Crypto ATMs Than El Salvador – How Does This Impact Adoption?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/australia-now-home-more-crypto-atms-than-el-salvador-how-does-impact-adoption.htm</link><description>The number of crypto ATM machines in Australia has hit new highs over the past four months, surpassing El Salvador, the country where Bitcoin (BTC) is legal tender. What's more, two other countries overtook El Salvador: Spain and Poland.  &lt;br /&gt;
Per Coinatmradar.com, the top 3 countries by the number of installed crypto ATMs are the US, Canada, and Spain, with 33,950, 2,649, and 273 locations, respectively. The difference in the numbers between these countries is vast. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/australia-now-home-more-crypto-atms-than-el-salvador-how-does-impact-adoption.htm"&gt;Read More: Australia Now Home to More Crypto ATMs Than El Salvador – How Does This Impact Adoption?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ATM</category><category>El Salvador</category><category>Australia</category><category>Spain</category><category>Poland</category><category>USA</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Canada</category><category>Latin America</category><category>Africa</category><category>Asia</category><category>Adoption</category><category>Europe</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/australia-now-home-more-crypto-atms-than-el-salvador-how-does-impact-adoption.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99813/247306/adobestock-l-martinez-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="165158"/></item><item><title>Major Game Publisher Square Enix Continues to Invest in Blockchain Games Despite Bear Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-game-publisher-square-enix-continues-invest-blockchain-games-despite-bear-market.htm</link><description>Prominent Japanese video game developer and publisher Square Enix has revealed that it will continue to invest in blockchain games despite the recent turbulence in the crypto market. &lt;br /&gt;
In a Sunday letter, Yosuke Matsuda, the president of the company, said the game publisher will double down on Web3 gaming in the upcoming year. He detailed that Square Enix is “most focused” on blockchain-powered gaming amid its new business development efforts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/major-game-publisher-square-enix-continues-invest-blockchain-games-despite-bear-market.htm"&gt;Read More: Major Game Publisher Square Enix Continues to Invest in Blockchain Games Despite Bear Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Square Enix</category><category>NFT</category><category>NFT games</category><category>Adoption</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/major-game-publisher-square-enix-continues-invest-blockchain-games-despite-bear-market.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99835/247300/ogp-square-enix.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="52117"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Blasts Up 5.6% – Are Whales Buying?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-blasts-up-56-are-whales-buying.htm</link><description>The Terra Luna Classic price has jumped by over 5% in the past 24 hours, reaching $0.00016077 as the cryptocurrency market as a whole remains static over the same timeframe. Its current level marks a 0.5% drop in a week but a 23% gain in a fortnight, with the altcoin down by 7% in a month....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-blasts-up-56-are-whales-buying.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction as LUNC Blasts Up 5.6% – Are Whales Buying?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-blasts-up-56-are-whales-buying.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99817/247294/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-as-lunc-blasts-up-5-6-are-whales-buying-image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1648243"/></item><item><title>Binance Reportedly Close to Sealing Deal for South Korean Exchange Gopax</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-reportedly-close-sealing-deal-for-south-korean-exchange-gopax.htm</link><description>Binance is allegedly close to sealing a deal to buy a majority stake in the South Korean crypto exchange Gopax – per multiple domestic media reports. Outlets are claiming that the deal has been agreed in principle. But they note that a few final remaining legal and procedural hurdles still need to be cleared before the deal can be made official....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-reportedly-close-sealing-deal-for-south-korean-exchange-gopax.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Reportedly Close to Sealing Deal for South Korean Exchange Gopax&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Binance</category><category>South Korea</category><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-reportedly-close-sealing-deal-for-south-korean-exchange-gopax.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99818/247280/adobestock-553210104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="6435073"/></item><item><title>World Economic Forum Says Crypto and Blockchain Technologies Will Continue to be an "Integral" Part of Modern Economy</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/world-economic-forum-says-crypto-blockchain-technologies-will-continue-an-integral-part-of-modern-economy.htm</link><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) believes the technology underpinning cryptocurrencies and digital assets will continue to be an "integral" part of the modern economy.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Monday blog post, the international organization talked about what the future holds for the crypto industry. The WEF particularly highlighted the widespread applications of cryptography and blockchain technologies, adding that their use in the financial services sector is already notable. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/world-economic-forum-says-crypto-blockchain-technologies-will-continue-an-integral-part-of-modern-economy.htm"&gt;Read More: World Economic Forum Says Crypto and Blockchain Technologies Will Continue to be an "Integral" Part of Modern Economy&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>World Economic Forum</category><category>Cryptography</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/world-economic-forum-says-crypto-blockchain-technologies-will-continue-an-integral-part-of-modern-economy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/99764/247171/world-economic-forum-logo-svg.jpg" type="image/png" length="76535"/></item></channel></rss>
