<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</link><description>South Korea’s Justice Ministry has hit out at claims that Minister Han Dong-hoon “refused to disclose information” about whether or not he owns crypto. &lt;br /&gt;
Per the media outlet Newsis, the ministry claimed that “the cryptoasset holding status of public officials who work with cryptoasset [regulation]” is “checked regularly.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: South Korean Justice Ministry Hits Out at Claims it ‘Refused to Say’ if Minister Owns Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Politics</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/south-korean-justice-ministry-hits-out-at-claims-it-refused-say-if-minister-owns-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114373/276294/adobestock-555291710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="304195"/></item><item><title>Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</link><description>Democratic presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. made campaign promises on Friday advocating for bitcoin users, adding that he plans to accept campaign donations in bitcoin. &lt;br /&gt;
“As president, I will make sure that your right to hold and use bitcoin is inviolable,” Kennedy said at the Bitcoin 2023 Conference in Miami. &lt;br /&gt;
Kennedy, who is the nephew of former President John F. Kennedy and the son of Robert F. Kennedy, announced his run for US president last month. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm"&gt;Read More: Democratic Presidential Candidate Kennedy Lays Out Campaign Promises for Bitcoin&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Presidential campaign</category><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/democratic-presidential-candidate-kennedy-lays-out-campaign-promises-for-bitcoin.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114436/276402/screen-shot-2023-05-03-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="570501"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</link><description>The battle between Bitcoin and the $27,000 mark continues, with the cryptocurrency struggling to make headway in the face of mounting economic challenges. &lt;br /&gt;
However, a ray of hope is beginning to break through the macroeconomic clouds as Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell suggests a possible abatement in rate increases.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the face of mounting cryptocurrency market uncertainty, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 May – Bitget Token, Render, Injective&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>AI</category><category>BGB</category><category>$COPIUM</category><category>RNDR</category><category>Ecoterra</category><category>INJ</category><category>YPRED</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>Bitget</category><category>Render Token</category><category>Injective</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>NFT</category><category>Recycle To Earn</category><category>Meme To Earn</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 22:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-19-may-bitget-token-render-injective.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114440/276407/19-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="338633"/></item><item><title>Pseudonymous Creator Ben.eth Rakes in $7 Million in Suspicious Meme Coin Presale – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Pseudonymous NFT collector turned celebrity meme coin creator Ben.eth has raked in a huge more than $7 million in ETH sales in the past seven days via a presale of his next memecoin called $PSYOP. &lt;br /&gt;
Investors were eager to get in on Ben.eth’s latest meme coin project in wake of the success of his first meme coin launch called $BEN....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Pseudonymous Creator Ben.eth Rakes in $7 Million in Suspicious Meme Coin Presale – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ben.eth</category><category>PSYOP</category><category>Presale</category><category>ETH</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pseudonymous-creator-beneth-rakes-7-million-suspicious-meme-coin-presale-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114438/276403/ben-eth.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="355940"/></item><item><title>Bankrupt Crypto Firm Celsius May Receive Second Chance from Wall Street</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm</link><description>The now-bankrupt crypto lender Celsius Network may get a second chance with the help of Wall Street investment giants. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Wall Street Journal article from Thursday, two groups of investment heavyweights are currently engaged in a bidding war for what remains of Celsius, close to a year after the lender filed for bankruptcy in New York....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankrupt Crypto Firm Celsius May Receive Second Chance from Wall Street&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-crypto-firm-celsius-may-receive-second-chance-from-wall-street.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114395/276330/celsius-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="124729"/></item><item><title>Global Payments Giant Visa Experiments with Ethereum's Goerli Testnet – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Global payments giant Visa has used Ethereum's Goerli testnet to try out transaction-free payments with the help of account abstraction.  &lt;br /&gt;
On-chain data shows that Visa used a smart contract called Paymaster, allowing the company to take advantage of account abstraction to perform complex tasks on behalf of accounts and manage transaction costs....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Global Payments Giant Visa Experiments with Ethereum's Goerli Testnet – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Visa</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Smart Contract</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/global-payments-giant-visa-experiments-with-ethereums-goerli-testnet-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114377/276302/19ec1be016-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="56740"/></item><item><title>US Lawmakers Introduce ‘First Bipartisan Bill’ Blocking a CBDC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm</link><description>US lawmakers from both sides of the aisle introduced a bill this week to block the Federal Reserve from issuing a central bank digital currency.  &lt;br /&gt;
Republican Rep. French Hill of Arkansas and Democratic Rep. Jake Auchincloss of Massachusetts introduced the bill this week, dubbed the Power of the Mint Act.  &lt;br /&gt;
Hill said it was the first bipartisan bill in Congress to block the central bank from issuing a CBDC, on the House floor this week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm"&gt;Read More: US Lawmakers Introduce ‘First Bipartisan Bill’ Blocking a CBDC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Legislation</category><category>French Hill</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-lawmakers-introduce-first-bipartisan-bill-blocking-a-cbdc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114430/276384/us-capitol-g6d9c63c16-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="104371"/></item><item><title>US CFTC Chair Rostin Behnam Says DeFi Crypto Exchanges Can Be Regulated – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm</link><description>Decentralized exchanges (DEXs) and other aspects of the decentralized finance (DeFi) world can be regulated in the US, even though it is “just code,” according to Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) chair Rostin Behnam....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: US CFTC Chair Rostin Behnam Says DeFi Crypto Exchanges Can Be Regulated – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>CFTC</category><category>SEC</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 17:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-cftc-chair-rostin-behnam-says-defi-crypto-exchanges-can-regulated-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114429/276383/rostin-behnam.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1187381"/></item><item><title>President Biden’s Crypto Mining Tax “Isn’t Going To Happen,” Sen. Lummis Says</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm</link><description>US Sen. Cynthia Lummis is not a fan of President Biden’s proposed 30 percent tax on cryptocurrency miners.  &lt;br /&gt;
“That isn't going to happen,” the Wyoming Republican and crypto enthusiast, said on Friday at Bitcoin 2023 Conference in Miami.  &lt;br /&gt;
There are environmental benefits including “not venting gases into the atmosphere as well as stabilizing grids,” Lummis said. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm"&gt;Read More: President Biden’s Crypto Mining Tax “Isn’t Going To Happen,” Sen. Lummis Says&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Cynthia Lummis</category><category>President Joe Biden</category><category>Mining</category><category>Taxes</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/president-bidens-crypto-mining-tax-isnt-going-happen-sen-lummis-says.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114423/276382/cl-official-portrait-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="720776"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction Following Fed Chair Powell's Speech – Is the Bear Market Over?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm</link><description>Fed Chair Powell's recent speech has sparked significant interest and speculation within the financial community.  &lt;br /&gt;
As one of the most influential figures in the global economy, Powell's remarks carry substantial weight and have the potential to impact various sectors, including the cryptocurrency market.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors are analyzing his statements for insights into the future direction of monetary policy and its potential effects on Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction Following Fed Chair Powell's Speech – Is the Bear Market Over?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-following-fed-chair-powell-speech-is-bear-market-over.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114419/276378/19-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481296"/></item><item><title>Ripple Launches Platform To Help Governments Issue CBDCs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-launches-platform-help-governments-issue-cbdcs.htm</link><description>Ripple launched a platform on Thursday that would help central banks, governments and financial institutions around the world issue their own central bank digital currency. &lt;br /&gt;
The Ripple CBDC Platform would offer customers ledger technology and enable issuers to manage CBDCs from start to finish, according to a press release.  &lt;br /&gt;
The platform would encompass both wholesale and retail CBDCs — respectively CBDCs used in interbank settlements or CBDCs used by everyday people....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-launches-platform-help-governments-issue-cbdcs.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple Launches Platform To Help Governments Issue CBDCs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-launches-platform-help-governments-issue-cbdcs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114318/276215/earth-g610e18582-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="461183"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Officially Debuts Coinbase One Subscription in US, UK, Germany, and Ireland – What Does it Do?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-officially-debuts-coinbase-one-subscription-us-uk-germany-ireland-what-does-it-do.htm</link><description>Amid the rigid regulatory atmosphere in the US crypto market, San Francisco-based crypto exchange Coinbase is expanding its offering to other regions.  &lt;br /&gt;
A recent blog post shows the cryptocurrency exchange has updated its Coinbase One trading platform while extending its product access in the US, UK, Germany, and Ireland....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-officially-debuts-coinbase-one-subscription-us-uk-germany-ireland-what-does-it-do.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Officially Debuts Coinbase One Subscription in US, UK, Germany, and Ireland – What Does it Do?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-officially-debuts-coinbase-one-subscription-us-uk-germany-ireland-what-does-it-do.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114416/276375/coinbase-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="178800"/></item><item><title>Adidas Web3 Lead Says Bored Ape Yacht Club Deal Was a Big Risk but Paid Off in the End</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/adidas-web3-lead-says-bored-ape-yacht-club-deal-was-big-risk-but-paid-off-end.htm</link><description>The new wave of popularity in tokenized digital assets saw many brands entering the Web3 space, generating billions in NFT sales.  &lt;br /&gt;
Among these brands, Adidas' Web3 move performed remarkably well after taking a huge leap of faith in the BAYC NFT deal.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent podcast discussion, former global VP of marketing for Adidas Originals and now VP and GM of Adidas Three Stripes Studios, Erika Wykes-Sneyd, weighed in. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/adidas-web3-lead-says-bored-ape-yacht-club-deal-was-big-risk-but-paid-off-end.htm"&gt;Read More: Adidas Web3 Lead Says Bored Ape Yacht Club Deal Was a Big Risk but Paid Off in the End&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/adidas-web3-lead-says-bored-ape-yacht-club-deal-was-big-risk-but-paid-off-end.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114413/276367/pexels-pixabay-355669.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="126188"/></item><item><title>Texas Lawmakers Pass Proof-of-Reserves Cryptocurrency Bill</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-pass-proof-of-reserves-cryptocurrency-bill.htm</link><description>The Texas legislature passed a bill this week requiring cryptocurrency exchanges to provide a “proof of reserves,” the latest move by the lone star state.  &lt;br /&gt;
HB-1666, co-sponsored by state Republicans Rep. Giovanni Capriglione and Sen. Tan Parker, applies to digital asset service providers that serve more than 500 customers or has $10 million in customer funds, and requires them to maintain reserves in an “amount sufficient to fulfill all  obligations to digital asset customers.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-pass-proof-of-reserves-cryptocurrency-bill.htm"&gt;Read More: Texas Lawmakers Pass Proof-of-Reserves Cryptocurrency Bill&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Texas</category><category>Mining</category><category>Crypto Exchanges</category><category>Legislation</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-pass-proof-of-reserves-cryptocurrency-bill.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114414/276368/pexels-lesli-whitecotton-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="65976"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Shibarium Beta Transactions Approach 10 Million – SHIB Adoption on the Rise?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shibarium-beta-transactions-approach-10-million-shib-adoption-rise.htm</link><description>Shiba Inu (SHIB), the world’s second most popular and largest crypto meme token by market capitalization that lives as an ERC-20 token on Ethereum, has been range bound in the $0.00000850-0.0000090 area over the last few days. &lt;br /&gt;
The bears have been catching their breath after sending the cryptocurrency cascading lower earlier this month. &lt;br /&gt;
But near-term price predictions remain bearish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shibarium-beta-transactions-approach-10-million-shib-adoption-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as Shibarium Beta Transactions Approach 10 Million – SHIB Adoption on the Rise?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shiba inu</category><category>SHIB</category><category>Shibarium</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shibarium-beta-transactions-approach-10-million-shib-adoption-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114410/276359/shib-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="721872"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Bank of England to Reject Revolut's Banking Licence Application, ASX Abandons Blockchain, HashKey to Raise Funds at $1BN Valuation, Ledger Co-founder Calls Recover Service Launch a 'Horrible Mess'</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-england-to-reject-revoluts-banking-licence-application-asx-abandons-blockchain-hashkey-to-raise-funds-at-1bn-valuation-ledger-co-founder-calls-recover-service-launch-a-horrible-mess.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-england-to-reject-revoluts-banking-licence-application-asx-abandons-blockchain-hashkey-to-raise-funds-at-1bn-valuation-ledger-co-founder-calls-recover-service-launch-a-horrible-mess.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Bank of England to Reject Revolut's Banking Licence Application, ASX Abandons Blockchain, HashKey to Raise Funds at $1BN Valuation, Ledger Co-founder Calls Recover Service Launch a 'Horrible Mess'&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bank of England</category><category>UK</category><category>Treasury</category><category>Revolut</category><category>Banking</category><category>Australia</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Investment</category><category>HashKey Group</category><category>Hong Kong</category><category>Grayscale</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>ETF</category><category>Ledger</category><category>Wallet</category><category>Mining</category><category>Iceland</category><category>Tax</category><category>CBDC</category><category>USA</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>Ethereum</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-bank-of-england-to-reject-revoluts-banking-licence-application-asx-abandons-blockchain-hashkey-to-raise-funds-at-1bn-valuation-ledger-co-founder-calls-recover-service-launch-a-horrible-mess.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114388/276352/adobestock-formatoriginal-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125202"/></item><item><title>Is Pepe Coin Price Dead? $COPIUM and AiDoge Might Be The Best Crypto to Buy Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-dead-copium-aidoge-might-best-crypto-buy-today.htm</link><description>The Pepe Coin (PEPE) price continues to cool and some are claiming that the cryptocurrency might now be dead. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE/USD was last changing hands around $0.0000015, according to DEX Tools. &lt;br /&gt;
That’s a more than 60% pullback from the cryptocurrency’s recent highs near $0.0000040. &lt;br /&gt;
Technicians note that Pepe is in the process of forming a pennant structure that could either signal the start of a new parabolic run higher, or a fresh tumble....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-dead-copium-aidoge-might-best-crypto-buy-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Is Pepe Coin Price Dead? $COPIUM and AiDoge Might Be The Best Crypto to Buy Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Pepe</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>AI</category><category>$COPIUM</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-dead-copium-aidoge-might-best-crypto-buy-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114404/276354/pepe-pic.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="167955"/></item><item><title>Michael Sanders, Co-Founder of Horizon Blockchain Games, on Web3 gaming, Blockchain, and Ayahuasca | Ep. 231</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/michael-sanders-co-founder-of-horizon-blockchain-games-on-web3-gaming-blockchain-and-ayahuasca-ep-231.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Michael Sanders, Co-Founder &amp; Storyteller of Horizon Blockchain Games, talks about the benefits of blockchain technology for gaming, the potential for web3 to shape the future of the gaming industry, and the challenges and opportunities of developing web3 games....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/michael-sanders-co-founder-of-horizon-blockchain-games-on-web3-gaming-blockchain-and-ayahuasca-ep-231.htm"&gt;Read More: Michael Sanders, Co-Founder of Horizon Blockchain Games, on Web3 gaming, Blockchain, and Ayahuasca | Ep. 231&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/michael-sanders-co-founder-of-horizon-blockchain-games-on-web3-gaming-blockchain-and-ayahuasca-ep-231.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114396/276333/michael-sanders-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="154033"/></item><item><title>Bankrupt FTX Sues to Retrieve Over $240 Million from Trading Platform Embed</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-ftx-sues-retrieve-over-240-million-from-trading-platform-embed.htm</link><description>The bankrupt crypto exchange FTX is taking legal action in an attempt to retrieve more than $240 million it paid for the stock trading platform Embed. &lt;br /&gt;
Embed was acquired by FTX’s American branch FTX.US in mid-2022, but representatives for FTX’s bankruptcy estate now say former company executives, including CEO Sam Bankman-Fried, did no investigation before buying the stock trading platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-ftx-sues-retrieve-over-240-million-from-trading-platform-embed.htm"&gt;Read More: Bankrupt FTX Sues to Retrieve Over $240 Million from Trading Platform Embed&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bankrupt-ftx-sues-retrieve-over-240-million-from-trading-platform-embed.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114387/276324/ftx-logo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="40924"/></item><item><title>NY Attorney General Secures $4.3 Million Refund for Coin Cafe Customers Misled by Hidden Fees</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-secures-43-million-refund-for-coin-cafe-customers-misled-by-hidden-fees.htm</link><description>The New York Attorney General’s office has ordered crypto trading platform Coin Cafe to repay $4.3 million to users for charging hidden fees.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday announcement, Attorney General Letitia James revealed that it has secured $4.3 million for Coin Cafe users after the company charged “exorbitant and undisclosed fees" for storing crypto on its platform....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-secures-43-million-refund-for-coin-cafe-customers-misled-by-hidden-fees.htm"&gt;Read More: NY Attorney General Secures $4.3 Million Refund for Coin Cafe Customers Misled by Hidden Fees&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>New York</category><category>New York Attorney General</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ny-attorney-general-secures-43-million-refund-for-coin-cafe-customers-misled-by-hidden-fees.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/114369/276286/jamelitte.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="21974"/></item></channel></rss>
