<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 18:26:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sam Bankman-Fried to Binance CEO: You Won, Stop Lying</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-binance-ceo-you-won-stop-lying/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228155</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Binance and FTX’s bosses have two different accounts of their exchange’s business dealings prior to the latter firm’s collapse. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Binance CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ) and ex-FTX boss Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) traded barbs over Twitter on Friday as each contested the true nature of their private business dealings.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">During the exchange, Bankman-Fried asked CZ why he would “lie” about their situation, given he had already “won,” post bankruptcy.</span></p>
<h2>CZ’s Story</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1601140809491185664" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">began</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with reference to Kevin O’Leary’s latest comments on FTX’s fallout. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In his interview with CNBC, the Shark Tank star suggested that FTX spent much of its cash attempting to buy back its equity from Binance due to the latter’s “opque” ownership. He also refrained from accusing Bankman-Fried of fraud, as he has done </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/despite-ftx-bankruptcy-kevin-oleary-would-still-invest-in-sbf/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">multiple times</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> since FTX’s bankrupcy.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">O’Leary was </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-how-much-kevin-oleary-got-paid-to-promote-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">paid</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> $15 million to promote FTX’s brand in August 2021, and was an early investor in the company. CZ believes this has something to do with why he would seemingly run defense for FTX and SBF – even after the exchange’s collapse. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“Unlike Kevin O’Leary, we continue to do due diligence even after we make an investment,” said CZ. “As an early investor in FTX, we became increasingly uncomfortable with Alameda/SBF and initiated the exit process more than 1.5 years ago.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">According to CZ, Binance began to leave behind its equity position in July 2021 due to worries about SBF and Alameda’s practices. This, per the Binance CEO, set off Bankman-Fried on multiple “unhinged” tirades against Binance team members, wherein the former billionaire threatened to “go to extraordinary lengths” to punish Binance. “We still have those text messages,” said CZ. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">This apparently sparked FTX to launch a mass investment campaign among “friends in high places,” including media, politicans, and celebrities like Kevin O’Leary to steer public opinion in favor of FTX, and against its opponents. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In early November, CZ </span><a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1589374530413215744" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">implied</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that FTX was lobbying against other player in the crypto industry in congress. Later that month, congressman Tom Emmer said he’d received reports of SBF </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-conspired-with-sec-for-special-treatment-us-congressman/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">conspiring</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> with the SEC to forge a regulatory monopoly for FTX in the exchange business. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“You don&#8217;t have to be a genius to know something don&#8217;t smell right at FTX,” continued CZ. “They were 1/10th our size, yet outspent us 100/1 on marketing &amp; &#8220;partnerships&#8221;, fancy parties in the Bahamas, trips across the globe, and mansions for all of their senior staff.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-is-expanding-hirings-amid-falling-crypto-market/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400;">boasted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in June that his company was especially frugal during the 2021 crypto bull market, and had developed a large “war chest” relative to other more profligate competitors. </span></p>
<h2>SBF’s Story</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Unlike CZ, Bankman-Fried </span><a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX/status/1601191234034274304" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400;">alleged</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> that his company was the one that initiated talks about buying out Binance’s stake in FTX, echoing his word to Kevin O’Leary on the matter. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">He also claimed that Binance never had the right to pull out as an investor unless FTX voluntarily opted for a buyout. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400;">“But again, none of this is necessary. You won. Why are you lying about this now?” he asked. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">CZ contested SBF’s framing of their dealings as a “competition” or “fight,” asserting that “no one won,” as an outcome. </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1601204678184013826</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-to-binance-ceo-you-won-stop-lying/" rel="nofollow">Sam Bankman-Fried to Binance CEO: You Won, Stop Lying</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SBF Willing to Testify Before US House Committee of Financial Services Next Week</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-willing-to-testify-before-us-house-committee-of-financial-services-next-week/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228115</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried promised to testify before the US House Committee on Financial Services on December 13.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The former CEO of FTX &#8211; Sam Bankman-Fried &#8211; said he is &#8220;willing&#8221; to testify before the relevant US authorities on December 13.</p>
<p>He vowed to shed more light on the reasons behind his exchange&#8217;s collapse and his own failures as a leader.</p>
<ul>
<li>The US House Committee on Financial Services <a href="https://twitter.com/RepMaxineWaters/status/1599858166359068676" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">claimed</a> earlier this week that the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX crisis</a> caused colossal investor losses and urged Bankman-Fried to testify on the matter on December 13.</li>
<li>SBF took it to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/SBF_FTX/status/1601186246990401537?t=UzKt6Rq-UcE9W9K2fZ2Vug&amp;s=35" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announce</a> he is ready to satisfy the Committee&#8217;s request.</li>
<li>However, he said he doesn&#8217;t have access to much of his data (personal or professional), hence the limit on what he will be able to reveal.</li>
<li>SBF pledged to be &#8220;helpful&#8221; during the hearing and bring more clarity to significant problems, including FTX US&#8217; solvency and what American and international users should do to obtain their lost assets.</li>
<li>He will also explain the main reasons that triggered the crash and what he could have done better to prevent it.</li>
<li>Subsequently, he blamed himself for changing from a &#8220;model CEO&#8221; to &#8220;lazy or disconnected.&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-willing-to-testify-before-us-house-committee-of-financial-services-next-week/" rel="nofollow">SBF Willing to Testify Before US House Committee of Financial Services Next Week</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CZ Binance Spats With SBF, Crypto Markets Go Back and Forth, More Proof of Reserves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-spats-with-sbf-crypto-markets-go-back-and-forth-more-proof-of-reserves-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 17:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228042</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/CZ_SBF.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[SBF and CZ go head to head, CryptoCom publishes its proof-of-reserves, while the cryptocurrency market ends up where it was last week. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With certain slight exceptions, the cryptocurrency market is found more or less where it was during the same time last week. The total capitalization sits at around $890 billion, according to data from CoinGecko and Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance is at 37%.</p>
<p>Speaking of Bitcoin, the primary cryptocurrency went back and forth (just like the rest of the market, dipping below $17K on a few occasions throughout the week. However, the bulls were successful in reclaiming this important level, and the price is now found above it for an increase of 1% throughout the past seven days.</p>
<p>Most of the major cryptocurrencies are trading roughly at similar prices compared to last week, with certain exceptions. For example, DOGE is down 5%, and XRP is down 3%. On the other hand, Uniswap&#8217;s UNI and Avalanche&#8217;s AVAX are up by 6.4% and 4.9% respectively. In any case, the BTC dominance remained at 37%, which shows that there&#8217;s no serious imbalance in the market between the primary cryptocurrency and altcoins.</p>
<p>Perhaps more interestingly, the FTX drama rages on. Earlier on Friday, 3AC&#8217;s co-founder &#8211; Zhu Su, took a stab at SBF (the exchange&#8217;s former CEO) for allegedly exercising pressure over media. The latter denied categorically.</p>
<p>A few hours later, the CEO of Binance, Changpeng Zhao, had another go at SBF and people who used to represent FTX. More precisely, CZ was talking about Kevin O&#8217;Leary and the way he looks at the whole fiasco. SBF responded, acknowledging again that CZ &#8220;won,&#8221; causing many to believe that he treats the entire ordeal as some sort of a game. Binance&#8217;s CEO said no one is a winner in this case.</p>
<p>Elsewhere, CryptoCom also published its Proof of Reserves report and allowed users to verify their holdings. The company handling the PoR was Mazars Group but it&#8217;s worth noting that they didn&#8217;t carry a financial report but rather carried out agreed-upon procedures (AUPs) requested by CryptoCom in advance.</p>
<p>All in all, it&#8217;s shaping up to be quite exciting in the cryptocurrency market, especially given that the US Bureau of Labor Statistics is going to announce the November CPI numbers on December 13th.</p>
<h2>Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $892B | 24H Vol: 48B | BTC Dominance: 37%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>BTC:</strong> $17,162 (+1%) | <strong>ETH:</strong> $1,275 (-0.1%) | <strong>BNB</strong>: $289 (-0.9%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228144" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg" alt="09.12" width="1000" height="500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12.jpg 1000w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-300x150.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-768x384.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/09.12-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Federal Judge Dismisses Kim Kardashian&#8217;s Crypto Promotion Lawsuit. </strong>A US federal judge has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/federal-judge-dismisses-kim-kardashians-crypto-promotion-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">dismissed</a> the lawsuit against Kim Kardashian, Floyd Mayweather, and other top celebrities. It was for promoting a cryptocurrency project called EthereumMax (EMAX).</p>
<p><strong>SBF Could Have Reportedly Been Involved in Terra&#8217;s Collapse, Do Kwon Chips In. </strong>A new report <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sbf-could-have-reportedly-been-involved-in-terras-collapse-do-kwon-chips-in/" data-wpel-link="internal">suggested</a> that Sam Bankman-Fried may have been involved in the crash of the Terra-Luna ecosystem. Do Kwon also chipped in with some questions to the former CEO of the bankrupt FTX exchange.</p>
<p><strong>Senator Lummis Now Believes Ether is a Security. </strong>Senator Cynthia Lummis <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senator-lummis-now-believes-ether-is-a-security/" data-wpel-link="internal">thinks</a> that Bitcoin is the only cryptocurrency that could be considered a security. The main reason for her changing her mind on Ether is the inability to de-stake, which makes it &#8220;susceptible to being a security.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>3AC Co-Founders Su Zhu, Kyle Davies Subpoenaed in Bankruptcy Case. </strong>A federal judge has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founders-su-zhu-kyle-davies-subpoenaed-in-bankruptcy-case/" data-wpel-link="internal">approved</a> the issuance of subpoenas to the founders of Three Arrows Capital (the hedge fund that collapsed earlier in 2022). The document was published on Tuesday by the Southern District Court of New York.</p>
<p><strong>5 Failing Crypto Narratives of Late, According to CZ Binance. </strong>The CEO of the world&#8217;s leading exchange came out on Twitter with five failing cryptocurrency narratives. He openly <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/5-failing-crypto-narratives-of-late-according-to-cz-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">called</a> Sam Bankman-Fried &#8220;one of the greatest fraudsters in history.&#8221;</p>
<p><strong>Goldman Sachs to Invest Millions in Crypto Businesses Following FTX Meltdown. </strong>The multinational investment giant Goldman Sachs sees opportunities in the cryptocurrency market following the crash of FTX. The company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/goldman-sachs-to-invest-millions-in-crypto-businesses-following-ftx-meltdown/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> that some valuations are now much more reasonable and plans to invest millions in the industry.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Litecoin – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-9-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-ltc/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-binance-spats-with-sbf-crypto-markets-go-back-and-forth-more-proof-of-reserves-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">CZ Binance Spats With SBF, Crypto Markets Go Back and Forth, More Proof of Reserves: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Approaches Critical Resistance but Bearish On-Chain Signal Flashes (Ethereum Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-approaches-critical-resistance-but-bearish-on-chain-signal-flashes-ethereum-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228126</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum’s price is currently facing crucial resistance, and the current focus is to surpass it. A successful breakout from this level could potentially result in bullish momentum in the near term. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Ethereum’s price has been forming a descending flag price pattern over the last few months. After recently [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum’s price is currently facing crucial resistance, and the current focus is to surpass it. A successful breakout from this level could potentially result in bullish momentum in the near term.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Ethereum’s price has been forming a descending flag price pattern over the last few months. After recently touching the lower trendline, it has initiated a small rally with extremely low momentum.</p>
<p>The price is now consolidating around the middle threshold, which closely aligns near the two intense resistance levels, the 100-day and 50-day moving average lines (standing roughly at $1,350).</p>
<p class="p1">The positive momentum will be fully confirmed if bears push the price above the aforementioned barriers.</p>
<p class="p1">On the other hand, if the middle boundary rejects the price, market participants should be prepared for another plummet toward the lower trendline, around $1K, which has served as significant support over the past few months.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228128" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228128" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228128 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_091201" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-Daily-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228128" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Each explosive price move is followed by continuation consolidation phases. The Fibonacci retracement is a valuable indicator to detect these stages and the potential targets. Typically, the 0.5 and 0.618 Fib levels are considered significant resistance in bearish expansion targets.</p>
<p>As the chart demonstrates, an evident imbalance aligns with the 0.5 level of the Fib retracement (standing at $1380) for the recent impulsive bearish price move.  That makes this particular static level a powerful resistance. If the price successfully surpasses this decisive level, bullish momentum will likely return to the market.</p>
<p>Yet, considering the market situation, a rejection from the above-mentioned level followed by a plummet toward the $1K mark might be a more likely outcome.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228127" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228127" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228127 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_091201" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETH-4H-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228127" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>The following chart reveals the exchange depositing transactions for Ethereum. The metric demonstrates the total number of deposits counted to the exchanges, with higher values indicating an increased possibility of selling on the spot markets.</p>
<p>The metric marked an explosive jump in Aug 2022, resulting in a significant decline in Ethereum’s price. This was the result of panic selling and asset distribution from market participants.</p>
<p>However, the metric has recently printed two small surges. This increases the possibility of a new cascade in the upcoming days.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228129" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228129" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228129 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_exchange_deposits_091201" width="2560" height="1600" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-300x188.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-1024x640.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-768x480.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-1536x960.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-2048x1280.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Ethereum-Onchain-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228129" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-approaches-critical-resistance-but-bearish-on-chain-signal-flashes-ethereum-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">ETH Approaches Critical Resistance but Bearish On-Chain Signal Flashes (Ethereum Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price Bounces Off $16.8K in Anticipation of Next Week&#8217;s CPI Numbers (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-bounces-off-16-8k-in-anticipation-of-next-weeks-cpi-numbers-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228120</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price is approaching a key resistance area as the markets are patiently waiting for the CPI release next week. Both the chart and the high probability of another decline showing in the inflation readings are suggesting that a turning point for Bitcoin may be near. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart On the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price is approaching a key resistance area as the markets are patiently waiting for the CPI release next week. Both the chart and the high probability of another decline showing in the inflation readings are suggesting that a turning point for Bitcoin may be near.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://cryptoquant.com/profile/u/Edris?tab=quicktake" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price is still trapped in a large descending channel and has yet to break it to either side. This pattern is typically an early sign of the exhaustion of the bearish trend and points to a probable bullish reversal if a breakout to the upside occurs.</p>
<p>However, before the price even reaches the higher boundary of the channel, the $18K resistance level and the 50-day moving average, located around the same price, should be surpassed.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the price fails to break above this resistance level, a drop toward the $15K area and a retest of the lower trendline of the pattern would become a lot more likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228122" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228122" style="width: 1598px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228122 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_091201" width="1598" height="807" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022.jpg 1598w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022-1024x517.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022-768x388.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022-1536x776.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-Daily-Dec-9-2022-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1598px) 100vw, 1598px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228122" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour chart, market participants appear to have been bracing themselves for Tuesday&#8217;s CPI release, as neither could exert visible dominance over the other. This led to a range-bound price action between the $16,800 and $17,400 levels.</p>
<p>However, the bulls may be starting to gain some momentum, as suggested by the last few candles and a strong rebound from the $16,800 support level.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator has also been on the rise, pointing to the relative strength of the bulls over the bears and a higher probability for a bullish breakout and rally toward the $18K resistance zone.</p>
<p>Yet, the RSI is approaching the overbought area (above 70%), which could be an early caution sign for a potential pullback or bearish reversal when the price finally reaches the $18K level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228121" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228121" style="width: 1598px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228121 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_091202" width="1598" height="807" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022.jpg 1598w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022-300x152.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022-1024x517.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022-768x388.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022-1536x776.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSDT-4H-Dec-9-2022-50x25.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1598px) 100vw, 1598px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228121" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2 class="p1">Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<h3 class="p3">Bitcoin Funding Rates</h3>
<p class="p6">Bitcoin has been in a gruesome downtrend for nearly the entirety of 2022 as the new year approaches swiftly. However, some promising signs are developing, which could suggest that the bear market bottom is closer than many might think.</p>
<p class="p6">The futures market has been the most crucial factor in determining the short-term price action of Bitcoin over the last couple of years, with liquidations initiating significant surges and plunges.</p>
<p class="p6">One of the most useful metrics for futures market sentiment evaluation is the funding rates, which demonstrates whether the bulls or bears are more aggressively longing or shorting, with negative values for the former and positive values for the latter.</p>
<p class="p6">During the recent crash caused by FTX&#8217;s bankruptcy, the funding rates dropped deeper in the negative region, showing values previously observed during the Covid-19 crash.</p>
<p class="p6">Highly negative funding rates are one of the common features of the Bitcoin price bottoms, especially when this situation carries on for a while.</p>
<p class="p6">This highly bearish sentiment usually leads to short liquidation cascades, which could set the stage for at least a short-term recovery.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228123" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228123" style="width: 2159px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-228123 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022.jpg" alt="btc_funding_rates_091201" width="2159" height="1362" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022.jpg 2159w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-1024x646.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-1536x969.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-2048x1292.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitcoin-Funding-Rates-Dec-9-2022-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2159px) 100vw, 2159px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228123" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-bounces-off-16-8k-in-anticipation-of-next-weeks-cpi-numbers-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price Bounces Off $16.8K in Anticipation of Next Week&#8217;s CPI Numbers (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amber Group Slows Down Expansion Plans on Bear Market Worries (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/amber-group-slows-down-expansion-plans-on-bear-market-worries-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228059</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/bears_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/bears_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Amber Group supposedly secured only $50 million of its planned $100 million funding round.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group reportedly raised just half of its $100 million funding round and halted its global expansion efforts due to the ongoing bear market.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company recently laid off a portion of its staff after previously admitting it has been an &#8220;active trading participant&#8221; on the bankrupt crypto exchange FTX.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Change of Plans</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group raised hopes at the beginning of 2022 that it will manage to boost its valuation nearly three times, reaching $10 billion. The shaken condition of the cryptocurrency market, though, foiled those intentions.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a Financial Times </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.ft.com/content/5dca5327-124a-4a44-8af3-116e9634a2dd" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">coverage</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Amber Group &#8211; which is backed by Singapore&#8217;s investment company Temasek &#8211; secured a $50 million fundraiser, which is half of the initially planned amount. Despite the reduced funds, Annabelle Huang &#8211; Managing Partner at the firm &#8211; did not classify the effort as &#8220;unsuccessful.&#8221; </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We are not under pressure to raise capital,&#8221; she added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Amber Group&#8217;s issues seem to have escalated after the collapse of </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. The company dismissed the rumors that it had some exposure to the bankrupt entity or Alameda Research. However, it has been an &#8220;active trading participant&#8221; on FTX.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The organization </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/downturn-effects-amber-groups-workforce-to-see-5-10-reduction-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">trimmed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the size of its team by 5-10% in September, citing current &#8220;market conditions,&#8221; and</span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-12-07/crypto-firm-amber-cuts-staff-pauses-fundraising-in-ftx-fallout?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=social&amp;utm_campaign=socialflow-organic&amp;utm_content=crypto#xj4y7vzkg&amp;leadSource=uverify%20wall" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> laid off</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> more employees earlier this month.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Death of the Co-Founder</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A curious and yet tragic event was the unexpected death of Tiantian Kullander – Co-Founder of Amber Group. The 30-year-old man<a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-recent-wave-of-mysterious-deaths-in-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal"> passed away</a> in his sleep at the end of November, while sources failed to provide information on whether he suffered from any illness.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Lost a dear friend who has changed my life, among many others, in ways he didn&#8217;t realize,&#8221; Huang stated.</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/amber-group-slows-down-expansion-plans-on-bear-market-worries-report/" rel="nofollow">Amber Group Slows Down Expansion Plans on Bear Market Worries (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Calls Bitcoin and Ether Bottoms, Predicts Recovery After Q1 2023</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-calls-bitcoin-and-ether-bottoms-predicts-recovery-after-q1-2023/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228030</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Huobi_Australia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Huobi_Australia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin and ether could sink to $15,000 and $1,000, respectively, before starting a price rally after Q1 next year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Huobi Research, an affiliate of Huobi Global, estimated in its <em>Global Crypto Annual 2022-2023 Report</em> that the prices of bitcoin and ether will start surging after the first quarter of 2023. Until then, they might find a bottom at $15,000 and $1,000, respectively.</p>
<p>The company touched upon the FTX&#8217;s meltdown, describing it as &#8220;one of the catastrophes in the financial world.&#8221; Other incidents in the world of crypto so far this year include Terra&#8217;s collapse and the bankruptcy of Three Arrows Capital. Huobi believes those adverse events will prompt global regulators to impose pertinent rules on the sector.</p>
<p>The report also determined that Vietnam has the highest crypto adoption rate (with around 20 million users) and is the second most mature cryptocurrency market after the USA.</p>
<h2>Huobi&#8217;s Price Forecast</h2>
<p>According to the <a href="https://research.huobi.com/#/ArticleDetails?id=356" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">research</a>, the bear market for bitcoin and ether may last a few more months, where the USD valuation of the primary cryptocurrency could shrink by an additional 13%, while ETH could go down by over 20%. The downturn should consolidate in the first quarter of next year, after which Huobi expects a &#8220;decent rebound&#8221; to occur.</p>
<p>The Federal Reserve is supposed to slow interest rate hikes at the beginning of 2023, which could be among the main factors in boosting crypto&#8217;s prices, the exchange stated.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;In other words, the pace of hikes is slowing, the toughest part in this cycle has passed, and the bottom of monetary policy has nearly been shaped.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Huobi believes the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX&#8217;s decay</a> was the &#8220;last bullet&#8221; of the current crypto winter. Negative events that have sent shockwaves through the entire industry also include the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-valuable-lessons-from-terras-collapse-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">crash</a> of Terra&#8217;s algorithmic stablecoin &#8211; UST &#8211; and its native token &#8211; LUNA &#8211; as well as the bankruptcy of Three Arrows Capital (3AC). According to Huobi, global watchdogs will speed up enforcing rules in the space to prevent future disruption.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Consequences have been seen on the market, the effects will gradually be digested by the market, and a bottom will be formed during the fluctuations, which is expected to last until the first quarter of 2023.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Vietnam Leads the Way</h2>
<p>Huobi&#8217;s report evaluated the most active nations in the blockchain sector, labeling Vietnam the world&#8217;s global leader in crypto adoption. The South-East Asian country has around 20 million users and is the second most-mature cryptocurrency market after the USA.</p>
<p>The local government has recently presented a cashless policy and has set a relatively flexible crypto tax legislation to further encourage the usage of digital currencies.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;At the same time, traditional financial system in the region is still primitive, turning users away to the more efficient alternative: cryptocurrency.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>A recent Chainalysis research also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vietnam-reaffirms-global-leadership-in-crypto-adoption-chainalysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">placed</a> Vietnam at the top of that list. According to the results, 21% of Vietnamese consumers have used or owned bitcoin or alternative coins at one point during their lives.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-calls-bitcoin-and-ether-bottoms-predicts-recovery-after-q1-2023/" rel="nofollow">Huobi Calls Bitcoin and Ether Bottoms, Predicts Recovery After Q1 2023</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>MetaClash: The Unreal-Engine Powered Web3 Vehicular Combat Game</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/metaclash-the-unreal-engine-powered-web3-vehicular-combat-game/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Danish Yasin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228091</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In the past few years, several  Metaverse gaming projects have become well-known brands in the crypto space. Numerous play-to-earn games attempted to bridge the worlds of cryptocurrency and traditional gaming. However, we have yet to see a P2E game launch into the mainstream with definitive and continuous success: оnly a few have proven to be [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past few years, several  Metaverse gaming projects have become well-known brands in the crypto space.</p>
<p>Numerous <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-play-to-earn/" data-wpel-link="internal">play-to-earn games</a> attempted to bridge the worlds of cryptocurrency and traditional gaming. However, we have yet to see a P2E game launch into the mainstream with definitive and continuous success: оnly a few have proven to be capable of surviving the ongoing crypto-winter.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.metaclash.online/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">MetaClash: Digital Avatars of Destruction</a> is attempting to alter the industry by applying all of the lessons learned to bring blockchain-based gaming to the next level. It’s a free-to-play sci-fi vehicular combat Web3 game where players can use their PFP avatars and customize their vehicles to battle in multiple game modes.</p>
<p>Players fight in PvP (Player vs. Player) matches, earn rewards and choose one of the three factions to dictate game development, build communities, and battle for dominance in an exciting post-apocalyptic scenario.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228093" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover.jpg" alt="metalclash_cover" width="1280" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover.jpg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/metalclash_cover-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></a></p>
<h2>A Revolutionary Concept</h2>
<p>This project is committed to achieving a game&#8217;s ultimate goal: to entertain. Metaclash aims to live up to the high standards of gaming with a unique setting, a complex story, and compelling gameplay. The project&#8217;s progression shows impressive shape after achieving major milestones in less than a year of development.</p>
<p>Metaclash: Digital Avatars of Destruction was able to showcase a playable Alpha version to the Philippine Web3 Festival 2022. Those who attended had the opportunity to experience the thrill of driving these vehicles and try out what the project has developed thus far.</p>
<p>With a playable Alpha version of the game completed, and a Beta build on the horizon, Metaclash: Digital Avatars of Destruction started its<a href="https://www.metaclash.online/whitelist" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"> Whitelisting process</a>. Now, the efforts are focused on reaching the next major milestone: the NFT Genesis collection.</p>
<p>These NFTs will feature unique vehicle parts and perks. Those who own them will become the core of the Metaclash community, enjoying all the well-known benefits of being an OG in a Play-to-Earn crypto gaming project.</p>
<h2>The In-Game Experience</h2>
<p>The game features Free-to-Play and Play-to-Earn models to offer an experience tailored to a wide range of players.  Firstly, it will include two game modes -Team Deathmatch and Escort the Cargo- and a mixed reward system that takes into account both casual players and NFTs holders.</p>
<p>Metaclash&#8217;s concept goes beyond the boundaries of traditional gaming. It includes a full-fleshed worldbuilding consisting of a vast sci-fi universe. Players will be immersed in the storyline of a dystopian futuristic Earth where vehicles, factions, and pilots are the protagonists, and drama is everywhere.</p>
<p>The visual section stands out by its own merit. It is an original artwork made with advanced illustration techniques in 2D and 3D. The result is a dark post-apocalyptic world full of excitement and creativity.</p>
<p>Storytelling developments include treatments, plots, articles, short stories, and graphic novels. Also, gamers will experience an interactive narrative, having the opportunity to shape the storylines in the way of classic role-playing games.</p>
<p>Token holders will vote on motions that govern how the factions grow. Each voter&#8217;s voting power is determined by the number of tokens staked; the largest stakers will form a cabinet to manage the factions.</p>
<p>Finally, MetaClash has an ongoing <a href="https://bit.ly/WL-SignUp1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">whitelist campaign</a> for their upcoming NFT sale: the Digital Avatars of Destruction Genesis NFT Collection. Each NFT will have several perks, including a Premium Battle Pass, MetaClash Garage Access Pass, VIP privileges, NFT staking, priority access to the Beta version of the game, side products related to the lore, and a Genesis limited edition skin. Also, it will serve as a ‘booster pack,’ providing the owner with all the parts required to play the game.</p>
<p>Players can be part of the community of this project and be updated with the latest news by visiting the website and following on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/metaclash-the-unreal-engine-powered-web3-vehicular-combat-game/" rel="nofollow">MetaClash: The Unreal-Engine Powered Web3 Vehicular Combat Game</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis Dec-9: ETH, XRP, ADA, BNB and LTC</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-9-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-ltc/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:05:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BNBUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228003</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Litecoin. Ethereum (ETH) In the past week, Ethereum consolidated its price above the key support at $1,240 by moving sideways, which did not allow it to diverge much compared to seven days ago. However, this price action made a higher low [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Binance Coin, and Litecoin.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-228085" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201.jpg" alt="friday_charts_091201" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/friday_charts_091201-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>In the past week, Ethereum consolidated its price above the key support at $1,240 by moving sideways, which did not allow it to diverge much compared to seven days ago. However, this price action made a higher low which could be interpreted as bullish.</p>
<p>If buyers return to ETH, the next key resistance is found at $1,365, where it is likely to face a more significant pushback. While there are signs to be optimistic, the indicators show a lack of conviction which is also reflected in the current price.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, Ethereum could try to break the key resistance in the coming weekend. To do that, buyers will need to return in force since, right now, the volume has dropped to October levels when the price action was also flat. The longer this consolidation lasts, the more volatile the breakout will likely be from the current range.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228007" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228007" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228007" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39.png" alt="ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ETHUSD_2022-12-09_08-32-39-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228007" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>XRP has a similar price action to Ethereum after moving sideways since late November. For this reason, its price is very similar to seven days ago, albeit with a small loss of 1.8%. With good support at $0.37, XRP seems more likely to attempt a breakout above the $0.44 key resistance in the coming weeks.</p>
<p>The volume remains low, but so long as this cryptocurrency manages to stay above the key support, then the bias leans to the bull side. This is because sellers lack the conviction to push the price lower, and so far, XRP has made higher lows like ETH.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, market participants could be in for a test of the critical resistance. This could be the trigger this cryptocurrency needs to bring back the much-needed volume. A sharp rejection at $0.44 would be considered extremely bearish, while a breakout would open the path for XRP to reach $0.50 again.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228009" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228009" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228009" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/XRPUSDT_2022-12-09_08-36-29-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228009" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>Compared to ETH and XRP, Cardano looks weaker, and this can also be measured by the distance of the current price from the all-time low this year. Bulls were very shy in the past few weeks, which did not allow ADA to move much beyond its key support at $0.30. This also means its price is pretty much identical to seven days ago.</p>
<p>The current price action places ADA in a consolidation period, and the key resistance is found at $0.34, which is still some distance away. While some cryptocurrencies (like ETH and XRP) suggest this flat trend could end with a breakout, the chart for Cardano shows a lot of uncertainty.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, ADA may attempt to test the key resistance, but equally, the price can also break below its current support if the overall market turns bearish again. Such a bearish turn could quickly see ADA&#8217;s price fall to the next key support at $0.28.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228005" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228005" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228005" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/ADAUSDT_2022-12-09_08-32-53-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228005" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Binance Coin (BNB)</h2>
<p>BNB is in a much better position compared to the other coins on this week&#8217;s list. Since the low it made in June, the price continued to make higher lows and higher highs. This uptrend has stopped somewhat in the past few months as the price ranged under $300 most of the time.</p>
<p>Due to this flat price action, the price of BNB is pretty similar to seven days ago, and the expectation is that it will continue to range between $300 and $260. The catalyst for a major breakout is still to come, and the overall market appears to be waiting for this.</p>
<p>As the token of the largest crypto exchange in the world, BNB continues to show strength. The additional demand created by Binance users has allowed it to never revisit the lows from June, while many other cryptocurrencies have made lower lows since then. This means that BNB may have already bottomed during this bear market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228006" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228006" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228006" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52.png" alt="BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BNBUSDT_2022-12-09_08-34-52-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228006" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Litecoin (LTC)</h2>
<p>As one of the best performers in the past few weeks, Litecoin continues to look strong. The price is currently consolidating above the key support at $74, which so far has held well. While momentum has faded a bit, with only a 0.9% increase in the past seven days, there are reasons to be optimistic.</p>
<p>The failure of sellers to push LTC under $74 after multiple attempts is a bullish sign. For this reason, this cryptocurrency seems more likely to move to $95 next as bulls appear to have the upper hand.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, LTC could continue to outperform the overall market. However, its biggest challenge will be to break into a three digits valuation as sellers may be waiting for that moment to strike. More so, buyers may also turn into sellers once LTC approaches $100 to secure profits. This is why a break above $100 appears difficult now.</p>
<figure id="attachment_228008" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228008" style="width: 2852px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-228008" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21.png" alt="LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21" width="2852" height="1420" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21.png 2852w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-300x149.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-1024x510.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-768x382.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-1536x765.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-2048x1020.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/LTCUSDT_2022-12-09_08-35-21-50x25.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2852px) 100vw, 2852px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-228008" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-dec-9-eth-xrp-ada-bnb-and-ltc/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis Dec-9: ETH, XRP, ADA, BNB and LTC</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeFiChain’s Much Anticipated ‘Grand Central’ Hard Fork Goes Live</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defichains-much-anticipated-grand-central-hard-fork-goes-live/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=228071</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/defichain-pr3.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/defichain-pr3.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PR &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, 8th December, 2022, Chainwire] DeFiChain, the world’s leading blockchain on the Bitcoin network dedicated to bringing decentralized financial applications to everyone, has officially activated the much-anticipated Grand Central hard fork on its network at 01 AM EST on Thursday, December 8th on Block Height 2,479,000. The Grand Central hard fork is [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PR &#8211; Singapore, Singapore, 8th December, 2022, Chainwire]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://defichain.com/" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">DeFiChain</a>, the world’s leading blockchain on the Bitcoin network dedicated to bringing decentralized financial applications to everyone, has officially activated the much-anticipated Grand Central hard fork on its network at 01 AM EST on Thursday, December 8th on Block Height 2,479,000.</p>
<p>The Grand Central hard fork is one of the biggest and most monumental updates for DeFiChain in 2022. It marks the rollout of four main features:</p>
<ul>
<li>On-chain governance</li>
<li>Token consortium framework</li>
<li>Support for masternode parameter updates (owner, operator, reward address)</li>
<li>Pool commission and reward fixes</li>
</ul>
<p>This hard fork addresses some of the long-awaited product debt and prepares the DeFiChain community for an accelerated growth in 2023.</p>
<blockquote><p>U-Zyn Chua, Co-Founder of DeFiChain, said, “Grand Central marks a major step in DeFiChain’s governance structure since it is implementing on-chain governance. This makes the voting processes perfectly transparent, easier and strengthens the governance structure of DeFiChain. A major step for the whole ecosystem.”</p></blockquote>
<h2>On-chain governance</h2>
<p>To make changes in the DeFiChain ecosystem, community members can submit three types of proposals to be voted on by masternode owners:</p>
<ol>
<li>Community development fund request proposal (also known as Community Fund Proposal; CFP)</li>
<li>Vote of confidence (also known as DeFiChain Improvement Proposal; DFIP)</li>
<li>Block reward reallocation proposal</li>
</ol>
<p>Currently, the process of creating a proposal and voting is largely done off-chain. With On-Chain Governance (OCG), any proposal which requires voting by community can be conducted directly on the blockchain. It will strengthen DeFiChain’s governance structure and ensure that there is complete transparency in the entire voting process for the DeFiChain community.</p>
<p>The voting results will now be available real-time on a dashboard on defiscan.live, which makes tracking the results much easier. For masternode owners, they will be able to generate a script to vote for each proposal via the dashboard, reducing the effort required for voting. Overall, this would result in higher levels of participation in the voting of proposals.</p>
<h2>DeFiChain Consortium</h2>
<p>In DeFiChain, tokenized digital assets are meant to be backed 1:1 by the actual asset in its respective ecosystem (e.g. one dBTC being backed by one BTC). However, this backing is currently not enforceable via the blockchain. The DeFiChain Consortium will give a proper structure to the backing of dAssets to ensure that all digital assets are backed.</p>
<p>Members of the Consortium (e.g Cake DeFi) will have their own dedicated key for the minting and burning of tokenized digital assets. Each member is required to back any digital assets they mint, regardless of whether they are minting for themselves or on behalf of users of their platform.</p>
<p>The Consortium members will also be required to pledge two days worth of collateral, in DFI or DUSD, that will be locked up in a smart contract. It is required on top of the backing of the tokenized digital assets. This collateral will determine how many digital assets a member can mint each day.</p>
<p>This additional collateral is meant to deter members from engaging in activities that are contrary to the interests of the community, and to pay for damages in the event where a member overmints digital assets or is unable to provide backing for tokenized digital assets.</p>
<p>The formation of the Consortium will enhance the governance structure and transparency in the DeFiChain community. It also provides a mechanism for the community to monitor the backing of tokenized digital assets, which deters overminting.</p>
<h2>About DeFiChain</h2>
<p>DeFiChain is a decentralized Proof-of-Stake blockchain created as a hard fork of the Bitcoin network to enable advanced DeFi applications. It is dedicated to enabling fast, intelligent, and transparent decentralized financial services. DeFiChain offers liquidity mining, staking, decentralized assets, and decentralized loans. The DeFiChain Foundation&#8217;s mission is to bring DeFi to the Bitcoin ecosystem.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defichains-much-anticipated-grand-central-hard-fork-goes-live/" rel="nofollow">DeFiChain’s Much Anticipated ‘Grand Central’ Hard Fork Goes Live</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
