<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:20:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Senators Lummis and Gillibrand to Unveil Updated Bill Classifying Crypto Assets as Commodities</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/senators-lummis-and-gillibrand-to-unveil-updated-bill-classifying-crypto-assets-as-commodities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 06:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260039</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/Cynthia_lummis_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Pro-crypto U.S. Senators Lummis and Gillibrand are poised to unveil proposed legislation to determine how crypto assets should be regulated.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On July 12, an amended crypto bill by Senators Cynthia Lummis and Kirsten Gillibrand will be submitted.</p>
<p>The revamped “Responsible Financial Innovation Act” aims to classify most crypto assets as commodities, similar to gold.</p>
<p>This would bring them under the umbrella of the Commodities Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) rather than the Securities and Exchange Commission, which is “stifling innovation in financial technologies,” according to the Senators.</p>
<h2>Crypto Bill Redux</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-calls-out-sec-for-approving-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-while-denying-spot/" data-wpel-link="internal">SEC</a> wants to apply 90-year-old legislation to regulate and treat crypto companies the same as banks and stock exchanges.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The domestic industries really are trying to comply, for the most part, and they’re just getting the cold shoulder,” said Lummis who added, “That’s not how we regulate in this country,” <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/congress-wants-to-take-back-power-over-crypto/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">according</a> to Wired.</p></blockquote>
<p>The newly proposed legislation aims to protect investors and prevent the major collapses that crippled the industry in 2022. However, it does not advocate enforcement action, lawsuits, or the demand for exchange asset freezes to hurt investors (which is what the SEC has been doing).</p>
<p>The report, citing a person with knowledge of the act, explained that the new bill, if passed, would require crypto exchanges to store customer funds in third-party trusts. It would also prevent internal trading by exchanges using their own funds or tokens.</p>
<p>Furthermore, the CFTC would also have the power to supervise exchange affiliates for potential misdemeanors.</p>
<p>The act also prohibits “rehypothecation,” which is a practice of financing digital assets already locked up in other loans.</p>
<p>The legislation has already been passed to the CFTC and SEC for their purview, but <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cynthia-lummis-says-bidens-30-miner-tax-isnt-going-to-happen/" data-wpel-link="internal">Lummis</a> is concerned that it will get stonewalled.</p>
<blockquote><p>“After all of our efforts to reach out to them and work with them, I do not want them to come in at the last minute to put their kibosh on this.”</p></blockquote>
<p>America is already way behind the rest of the world with regard to crypto regulations. As a result, an exodus of talent, innovation, and capital is already underway.</p>
<h2>Crypto Market Outlook</h2>
<p>While crypto markets would be buoyed by progressive legislations in the U.S., sentiment and volumes are currently flat.</p>
<p>Total capitalization remains flat on the day at $1.23 trillion, with very little movement from the high-cap coins over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/senators-lummis-and-gillibrand-to-unveil-updated-bill-classifying-crypto-assets-as-commodities/" rel="nofollow">Senators Lummis and Gillibrand to Unveil Updated Bill Classifying Crypto Assets as Commodities</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boxwind Allies With Exinity Group to Streamline Access to Digital Asset Markets</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/boxwind-allies-with-exinity-group-to-streamline-access-to-digital-asset-markets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 05:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259907</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tokenization_2_1689064807qhh50ICb3S.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Tokenization_2_1689064807qhh50ICb3S.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, UK, July 11th, 2023] Exinity Group, the global fintech business dedicated to providing investors with the freedom to succeed in digital markets, announced its entering into a strategic, long-term partnership with Boxwind, the digital exchange platform for cryptocurrency traders. Together, Boxwind and Exinity Group will transform the digital asset trading landscape, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; London, UK, July 11th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://group.exinity.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Exinity Group</a>, the global fintech business dedicated to providing investors with the freedom to succeed in digital markets, announced its entering into a strategic, long-term partnership with <a href="https://boxwind.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Boxwind</a>, the digital exchange platform for cryptocurrency traders.</p>
<p>Together, Boxwind and Exinity Group will transform the digital asset trading landscape, empowering ambitious individuals to participate in investing opportunities and explore new asset classes across markets. By combining Boxwind’s innovative asset trading technology with Exinity’s world-class investing products, the partners will enable a new generation of investors to discover financial freedom and grow their wealth.</p>
<p>Boxwind is the creator of a digital asset trading platform, providing hassle-free onboarding, instant spot trading and secure asset storage. It promises to redefine the way users can trade, buy, hold and invest digital assets. With its user-friendly interface and advanced features, Boxwind paves the way for individuals to secure their financial future.</p>
<p>With its innovative trading and investing products, Exinity Group has emerged as a pivotal player that’s revolutionizing access to economic opportunities in developing nations across Asia, the Middle East and Africa. It merges its proprietary trading platforms with original concepts to attract users seeking alternative financial solutions beyond traditional finance.</p>
<p>A global wealth engine backed by decades of experience in trading and investment, Exinity is the home of successful retail businesses, including Alpari International and ForexTime (FTXM). Its birth can be traced back to the beginnings of the Forex trading industry and the founding of Alpari Group back in 1998. Through its pioneering MetaTrader platform, Alpari rapidly expanded to hold a significant presence in the world’s financial markets, joined by its sister brand FXTM in 2011. Together, Exinity’s brands have become a force to be reckoned with in the online trading space, trusted by more than two million clients in 180 countries.</p>
<p>The integration of Exinity&#8217;s proprietary technology with Boxwind’s novel digital asset trading platform is designed to appeal to a new generation of customers seeking to explore alternative financial solutions beyond traditional products.</p>
<h2>About Boxwind</h2>
<p><a href="https://boxwind.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Boxwind</a> is a digital exchange platform that plans to revolutionize the way users trade, buy and hold cryptocurrency. We provide easy access to digital assets that can empower everyone on their journey to financial freedom.</p>
<h2>About Exinity Group</h2>
<p><a href="https://group.exinity.com" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Exinity Group</a> is a global fintech business dedicated to providing a new generation with the freedom to succeed. From our roots in FX brokerage, we’re creating and developing a unique range of innovative trading and investing products, using proprietary platforms and original concepts to attract new customers who want the freedom financial independence can bring &#8211; but for whom traditional products don’t appeal.</p>
<p>Exinity focuses on the developing economies of Asia, the Middle East and Africa, huge markets served by a highly motivated, customer-focused and creative workforce operating out of four strategic centers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/boxwind-allies-with-exinity-group-to-streamline-access-to-digital-asset-markets/" rel="nofollow">Boxwind Allies With Exinity Group to Streamline Access to Digital Asset Markets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Singapore&#8217;s Investment Giant Temasek Pauses Crypto Efforts, Cites Regulatory Uncertainty</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-investment-giant-temasek-pauses-crypto-efforts-cites-regulatory-uncertainty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Singapore]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259898</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Singapore-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Singapore-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The entity might change its stance should watchdogs implement "the right regulatory framework," CEO Sipahimalani said.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Rohit Sipahimalani &#8211; Chief Executive Officer of the Singaporean state-owned conglomerate Temasek &#8211; said the entity is currently not interested in cryptocurrency investments due to the lack of regulatory clarity. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The company had a bad experience with the digital asset sector, losing $275 million when FTX collapsed.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A Possible Re-Entry With Appropriate Rules</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CEO Sipahimalani </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/07/11/temasek-says-its-not-looking-to-invest-in-crypto-firms-right-now.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in a recent interview that there is &#8220;a lot of regulatory uncertainty&#8221; in the cryptocurrency sector, which makes it &#8220;very difficult&#8221; for Temasek to join the ecosystem with another investment. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">On the other hand, he assured that the company will re-think its position should regulators impose a comprehensive regulatory framework on the industry:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;If you have the right regulatory framework, and we are comfortable with it, and you have the right investment opportunity, there&#8217;s no reason for us not to look at it.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_259954" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259954" style="width: 400px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259954" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani.jpg" alt="Rohit Sipahimalani" width="400" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani.jpg 500w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Rohit-Sipahimalani-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259954" class="wp-caption-text">Rohit Sipahimalani, Source: The Org</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth mentioning that the Monetary Authority of Singapore has taken some steps to ensure maximum protection for local crypto participants. The watchdog <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapore-requires-crypto-companies-to-hold-customer-funds-in-a-trust-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">plans</a> to ban digital asset organizations from offering lending and staking services to retail investors. It might also insist that such firms hold customers’ assets in a designated trust by the end of 2023.</span></p>
<p>Temasek was among the numerous entities that parted with a considerable amount of money due to its interaction with the once-prominent crypto exchange FTX. The company, which has almost $500 billion of assets under management, invested $275 million in FTX and <a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-temasek-says-ftx-investment-now-worth-nothing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">lost</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> everything due to the latter&#8217;s demise in November last year. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Sipahimalani explained that the FTX investment was part of Temasek&#8217;s early-stage strategy, where it distributed funds in &#8220;new disruptive technologies to see what&#8217;s around the corner.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The CEO also revealed that the company conducted proper due diligence when considering the move and went ahead since the marketplace &#8220;had good technology, was gaining market share, and showed a willingness to engage with regulators and be licensed.&#8221;</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Taking Responsibility</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The unsuccessful interaction in FTX has harmed the reputation of the Singaporean state-owned conglomerate. As such, the team and senior manager who approved the investment have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/temasek-slashes-pay-for-executives-who-recommended-investing-in-ftx-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">taken</a> full responsibility and had their annual compensations cut down:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The investment team and senior management, who are ultimately responsible for investment decisions made, took collective accountability and had their compensation reduced.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Temasek did not reveal the exact deducted amount or whether other employees&#8217; bonuses or salaries have been decreased. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lengthy list of companies that suffered losses due to investing in FTX also includes the world&#8217;s largest asset manager &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-worlds-largest-asset-manager-was-also-exposed-to-ftx/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BlackRock</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, the venture capital firm &#8211; Sequoia Capital, the crypto technology investment company &#8211; Paradigm, the Japanese Softbank, and many more.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/singapores-investment-giant-temasek-pauses-crypto-efforts-cites-regulatory-uncertainty/" rel="nofollow">Singapore&#8217;s Investment Giant Temasek Pauses Crypto Efforts, Cites Regulatory Uncertainty</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Arkham May Have Inadvertently Doxxed Many of its Users</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/arkham-may-have-inadvertently-doxxed-many-of-its-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259813</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Arkham_Dox.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Arkham_Dox.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Arkham recently announced a tool that deanonymizes blockchain users on one hand and was exposed for poor data protection on the other.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Arkham Intelligence, a blockchain sleuthing company in the vein of Chainalysis and others, recently announced the release of a platform to deanonymize and trade information pertaining to blockchain users, as well as the release of a new ARKM token to go with it.</p>
<h2>Snitching as a Service</h2>
<p>Touted as “the world’s first on-chain intelligence exchange,” Arkham Intelligence will allow users of the service to <a href="https://www.arkhamintelligence.com/announcements/arkham-intel-exchange" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">post bounties</a> for any information on blockchain users.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Our vision for the Intel Exchange is a decentralized intel-to-earn economy powered by smart contracts, in which any sleuth can earn based on their skills &amp; experience. As such, all transactions on the Arkham Marketplace will take place through smart contracts audited by our partner Quantstamp.”</p></blockquote>
<p>There are no limitations on what kind of information can be requested, although the company did promise to ban spammers and those submitting low-quality information.</p>
<p>Once the information requested has been uncovered, the person who posted the bounty will have a 90-day exclusivity period to use the newly gleaned information as they see fit. After this period, the info will become a part of Arkham’s public database.</p>
<p>Naturally, the announcement of a tool that could strip away one of the main things that attract some users to blockchain technology left the crypto community divided, with some <a href="https://twitter.com/hudsonjameson/status/1678384583576891393" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">accusing</a> Arkham of trying to become the arbiter of good and evil.</p>
<p>More cynical users also chimed in, reminding others that this platform could very easily be employed to uncover the identities of whales, who could be targeted online or in real life – much like what happened following the Ledger Wallet <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ledger-admits-users-data-leaked-amid-the-shopify-incident-in-april-june-2020/" data-wpel-link="internal">leak</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Announcing The World’s First On-Chain Intelligence Exchange</p>
<p>Buy and sell information on the owner of any blockchain wallet address—anonymously, via smart contract. <a href="https://t.co/4xr7dLvOjp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/4xr7dLvOjp</a></p>
<p>— Arkham (@ArkhamIntel) <a href="https://twitter.com/ArkhamIntel/status/1678339355314900992?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Meanwhile, Arkham seems to have gotten a head start in the game of deanonymizing the blockchain – starting with its own fans.</p>
<h2>Doxxing Their Own Userbase</h2>
<p>Shortly after announcing the launch of its new service, Arkham came under fire for doxing its own users via the referral links for the platform’s waiting list.</p>
<p>The referral, which was thought to contain a random string of numbers, actually encoded the email address of the user using BASE64 – an encryption algorithm that is trivially easy to <a href="https://www.base64decode.org/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">decode</a>.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">ABSOLUTE LMAO. ALL <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ARKHAM?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#ARKHAM</a> REFERRAL LINKS SHARED ON TWITTER IS DOXXING EVERYONE BECAUSE THE EMAIL IS IN THE REFERRAL URL. <a href="https://twitter.com/inversebrah?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">@inversebrah</a><a href="https://t.co/HM6veJOmNp" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/HM6veJOmNp</a> -&gt; bkatmis012@gmail.com <a href="https://t.co/1INvtXLEva" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/1INvtXLEva</a> <a href="https://t.co/m38VnNMS8k" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/m38VnNMS8k</a></p>
<p>— m4gicpotato ⟁ (@m4gicpotato) <a href="https://twitter.com/m4gicpotato/status/1678462447005618176?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Some users even accused Arkham of doing it on purpose, as a company centered around sleuthing would be unlikely to commit such a huge mistake accidentally.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/arkham-may-have-inadvertently-doxxed-many-of-its-users/" rel="nofollow">Arkham May Have Inadvertently Doxxed Many of its Users</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paradigm Criticizes SEC&#8217;s Actions Against Bittrex in New Amicus Brief Filing</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paradigm-criticizes-secs-actions-against-bittrex-in-new-amicus-brief-filing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:37:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paradigm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259794</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The_SEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/The_SEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ Paradigm's amicus brief claims that the SEC has overstepped its jurisdiction.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto investment company Paradigm has filed an amicus brief in the US Securities and Exchange Commission&#8217;s (SEC) case against Bittrex, claiming that the regulator is &#8220;wrongfully attempting to lay claim over crypto secondary markets.&#8221;</p>
<p>The brief filed on July 7th stated that the case against the US-based crypto exchange should be dismissed. It argued that the SEC cannot support extending the Howey test to determine that secondary market sales are investment contract transactions relies upon an unreasonable use of that test to make its claims.</p>
<h2>Paradigm&#8217;s Amicus Brief</h2>
<p>The SEC <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-receives-wells-notice-from-sec-for-violating-investor-protection-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">charged</a> Bittrex in April for allegedly operating an unregistered securities exchange, broker, and clearing agency just weeks after the crypto exchange <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bittrex-to-close-operations-in-the-us-due-to-regulatory-hurdles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> the termination of its US operations. Two other crypto weights &#8211; Coinbase and Binance &#8211; are also facing similar charges by the SEC.</p>
<p>Paradigm noted that the claims made by the financial regulator against Bittrex and the other crypto exchanges are &#8220;fundamentally different&#8221; from its many prior cases against token sellers. The previous ones witnessed the SEC exercising its authority to regulate fundraising schemes under the Howey test.</p>
<p>This, however, changed in the recent cases targeting crypto exchanges. Paradigm argued that the SEC is attempting to expand its authority past the initial fundraising transactions to incorporate &#8220;downstream&#8221; sales of crypto assets.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The SEC lacks the authority to regulate secondary markets for crypto assets because they do not involve &#8216;investment contracts&#8217; and are therefore not securities transactions under the agency&#8217;s remit.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The investment firm&#8217;s <a href="https://policy.paradigm.xyz/assets/writing/bittrex-41-1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">amicus brief</a> claims that even if a crypto asset was first sold in a fundraising transaction, the financial regulator has &#8220;no legal basis&#8221; to argue that the asset itself &#8220;embodies an investment contract, or that secondary market transactions in that asset are investment contract transactions.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Amicus Brief for Coinbase</h2>
<p>Paradigm, led by Coinbase co-founder Fred Ehrsam, <a href="https://policy.paradigm.xyz/assets/writing/Coinbase-Amicus-File-Marked.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">petitioned</a> to file an amicus brief in support of Coinbase in May, a month after the San Francisco-based crypto exchange received a Wells notice from the SEC.</p>
<p>The investment firm backed the exchange&#8217;s legal action against the agency, claiming that it had &#8220;a strong interest&#8221; in ensuring the financial regulator is held accountable for its delays in the company&#8217;s petitions.</p>
<p>The filing also criticized the SEC&#8217;s failure to provide clear rules or guidance for digital asset firms in the country.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paradigm-criticizes-secs-actions-against-bittrex-in-new-amicus-brief-filing/" rel="nofollow">Paradigm Criticizes SEC&#8217;s Actions Against Bittrex in New Amicus Brief Filing</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazilian CBDC Could Reportedly Allow Government to Freeze or Manipulate Accounts</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/brazilian-cbdc-could-reportedly-allow-government-to-freeze-or-manipulate-accounts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brazil]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259875</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Brazil_Flag.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Brazil_Flag.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The source code for the Brazilian CBDC in testing was analyzed by blockchain dev Pedro Magalhães.
]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Brazil has been developing a CBDC for some time now. If all goes according to plan, the digital Real will be launched sometime in 2024.</p>
<p>Once launched, it would support retail payments for anyone inclined to use it, backing up the payment with funds in the users’ bank accounts.</p>
<h2>Planning Ahead</h2>
<p>The Brazilian CBDC would not, however, interfere with other payment methods common in Brazil, such as Pix.</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazil-begins-cbdc-pilot-with-public-use-scheduled-for-2024-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">spokesman</a> for the Brazilian government, the decision to push on with the CBDC project was taken in order to open up new avenues for technological improvement. The digital Real could also potentially reduce the cost of credit and other customer-facing financial products, allowing the banks to reach a wider customer base.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This could reduce the cost of credit, the cost of improving the return on investments. There is a great potential for new service providers, fintech, democratizing access to the market and offering new services.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Unfortunately, the current iteration of the Brazilian CBDC contains some interesting code that could allow the government to directly interfere with users’ wallets.</p>
<h2>Possible Attack on Privacy</h2>
<p>Although there is no shortage of CBDC advocates, many in the tech sphere have long been suspicious of government-backed digital currencies. According to critics, a CBDC removes the beneficial aspects of decentralization and anonymity from cryptocurrencies, essentially transforming them into the same abstract figure shown in your bank balance.</p>
<p>Digital currencies would therefore subject to fractional lending and similar practices, with no real incentive for consumers to use them.</p>
<p>An overreaching government, however, would probably be very interested in technology that would keep a permanent and immutable list of financial transactions.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">5/ In addition to operations such as “minting” Real Digital tokens and enabling/disabling target accounts, explained in the documentation, a developer found other functions by applying reverse engineering techniques to the material made available by the Central Bank.</p>
<p>— Vini Barbosa (@vinibarbosabr) <a href="https://twitter.com/vinibarbosabr/status/1678511787610603523?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>After reviewing the <a href="https://github.com/bacen/pilotord-kit-onboarding" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">source code</a> for the digital Real, full-stack developer Pedro Magalhães submitted his <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pemagalhaes_github-ioralabsrealdigitalsmartcontracts-activity-7082009809549484032-Beqi/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=member_desktop" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">findings</a> on LinkedIn.</p>
<p>According to Magalhães, the source code contains some interesting functions that would allow the government to directly freeze and unfreeze accounts, move, create, and burn CBDC tokens in someone else’s account, and transfer assets on the user&#8217;s behalf.</p>
<p>Although these functions might only be used in order to help banks offer loans and other financial products to customers or to track down financial crime, there are also much more sinister possibilities.</p>
<p>For the moment, no comment on the matter has been made by any representative of the Brazilian government.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brazilian-cbdc-could-reportedly-allow-government-to-freeze-or-manipulate-accounts/" rel="nofollow">Brazilian CBDC Could Reportedly Allow Government to Freeze or Manipulate Accounts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grayscale Calls Out SEC For Approving Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF While Denying Spot</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-calls-out-sec-for-approving-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-while-denying-spot/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grayscale]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=260003</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/GrayscaleSEC.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/GrayscaleSEC.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC can only end its “unequal” treatment of Bitcoin ETPs by approving Grayscale’s spot ETF, said the company.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grayscale, the owner of the world’s largest Bitcoin fund, has grown even more frustrated with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) after the regulator approved a leveraged Bitcoin futures ETF last month.</p>
<p>The firm has taken its complaint to the court, arguing that the approval strengthens its case that the SEC’s denial of its Bitcoin spot ETF application is “discriminatory.”</p>
<h2>2X Futures VS Spot: What’s Riskier?</h2>
<p>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/Grayscale/status/1678431528156794880/photo/1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">letter</a> to the Court of Appeals for the DC Circuit on Monday, Grayscale explained the risks involved with the Volatility Shares’ 2x Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITX), which the SEC allowed to begin trading on June 27.</p>
<p>The leverage product, which raised eyebrows in the crypto industry weeks ago, seeks to double the performance of the S&amp;P 500 CME Bitcoin Futures Daily Roll Index each day.</p>
<p>“As a result, it exposes investors to an even riskier investment product than traditional Bitcoin futures exchange-traded products, which encompass risks related to both the futures and spot bitcoin markets,” Grayscale wrote.</p>
<p>Since October 2021, the SEC has approved an array of Bitcoin Futures ETFs for public trading, including a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-ceo-the-launch-of-short-bitcoin-etf-is-positive-for-crypto/" data-wpel-link="internal">short-linked</a> ETF last year. At the time, Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnhenshein saw the approval optimistically, believing the SEC was growing more comfortable with Bitcoin-related products across the board.</p>
<p>Days later, however, the agency denied Grayscale’s filing to convert the Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (OTCMKTS: GBTC) into a spot ETF, arguing that the underlying Bitcoin spot market contains risks of market manipulation that could harm investors.</p>
<p>Yet according to Grayscale, the recently approved BITX is much riskier: the fund’s registration statement itself states that it “may only be suitable for knowledgable investors,” and that such investors could “potentially lose the full value of their investment within a single day.”</p>
<h2>The Case Against The SEC</h2>
<p>The registration statement noted that the ETF invests in CME Bitcoin futures contracts, whose value “depends on, or is derived from, the underlying reference asset” – ie. “bitcoin.”</p>
<p>One of Grayscale’s core legal arguments against the SEC is that CME Bitcoin Futures – the market with which it intends to form a surveillance-sharing agreement (SSA) for its spot Bitcoin ETF – are directly linked to the Bitcoin spot market.</p>
<p>While the SEC has argued otherwise, judges overseeing the case appeared more sympathetic to Grayscale’s arguments during <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judges-scrutinize-sec-during-oral-arguments-in-grayscale-lawsuit/" data-wpel-link="internal">oral arguments</a> in March.</p>
<p>“The only way to eliminate the SEC’s unequal treatment of bitcoin-based ETPs is to allow proposed spot Bitcoin ETPs like Grayscale’s to begin trading,” concluded the company.</p>
<p>Bitcoin surged last month after asset management giant BlackRock filed for a Bitcoin spot ETF, stoking optimism that it might be the first to please the SEC. Unlike Grayscale, the company has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-stock-surges-12-as-blackrock-names-it-as-surveillance-partner/" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that it will form a SSA with the spot Bitcoin exchange Coinbase.</p>
<p>Uncertainty around BlackRock’s filing still looms, however: commercial litigator Joe Carlasare <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/will-the-sec-approve-a-bitcoin-spot-etf-in-2023-lawyer-breaks-down-the-odds/" data-wpel-link="internal">told</a> CryptoPotato this month that Coinbase may not be considered adequate by the SEC for detecting market manipulation, since it only comprises ~2% of global Bitcoin trading volume.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/grayscale-calls-out-sec-for-approving-leveraged-bitcoin-futures-etf-while-denying-spot/" rel="nofollow">Grayscale Calls Out SEC For Approving Leveraged Bitcoin Futures ETF While Denying Spot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Algorand&#8217;s Largest DeFi Protocol Shutting Down Operations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/algorands-largest-defi-protocol-shutting-down-operations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259887</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/algofi_shut_down_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/algofi_shut_down_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Algofi will remain active only on Discord and will shut down all the other social media channels. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Algorand-based decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol, Algofi, has announced winding down its operations.</p>
<p>In a statement, Algofi cited a &#8220;confluence of events&#8221; as the reason behind its decision that has rendered it no longer viable to continue building and maintaining the platform to the &#8220;highest standards.&#8221; As a result, the platform will soon transition to withdrawal-only mode.</p>
<ul>
<li>The DeFi platform <a href="https://blog.algofi.org/algofi-community-update-3cc989962d57" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that closing down all the social media platforms associated with the platform except Discord in a bid to ensure &#8220;seamless, unified communication.&#8221;</li>
<li>The process of winding down the protocol is estimated to take several months.</li>
<li>In the meantime, the team will work on reducing the collateral factors of the digital asset markets on its platform, enabling liquidity to migrate to other protocols.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This is obviously not the outcome any of us on the team or in the community hoped for at the outset of this project. We can’t thank the Algorand community enough for their support throughout this journey and can’t wait to see what comes next for Algorand.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Algofi is the largest DeFi hub in Algorand boasting a TVL of $32.36 million and accounting for nearly 55% of the layer 1 ecosystem&#8217;s value.</li>
<li>According to the latest data compiled by DeFiLlama, TVL hit an all-time high of $134 million earlier in February this year, since then, the figures have gone downhill.</li>
<li>Zooming out, Algorithm&#8217;s TVL has also <a href="https://defillama.com/chain/Algorand" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">plummetted</a> by over 73% since its peak of $218 million last November to $58.35 million at the time of writing.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/algorands-largest-defi-protocol-shutting-down-operations/" rel="nofollow">Algorand&#8217;s Largest DeFi Protocol Shutting Down Operations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mr. Hankey Coin Set for $500k Presale Launch This Week with New Meme Coin Expected to Go Viral</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mr-hankey-coin-set-for-500k-presale-launch-this-week-with-new-meme-coin-expected-to-go-viral/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259982</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mr_hankey_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/mr_hankey_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[FOMO and hype are already building around a brand new meme project, Mr. Hankey Coin, which is set for an ICO launch on July 13. Momentum is gathering around the shitcoin based on the beloved South Park Christmas deity, who first appeared in season one of the sitcom back in 1997 and has since become [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FOMO and hype are already building around a brand new meme project, Mr. Hankey Coin, which is set for an ICO launch on July 13.</p>
<p>Momentum is gathering around the shitcoin based on the beloved South Park Christmas deity, who first appeared in season one of the sitcom back in 1997 and has since become one of its most beloved characters.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=mr-hankey-coin-set-for-500k-presale-launch-this-week-with-new-meme-coin-expected-to-go-viral" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$HANKEY presale</a> could be as soon as 6pm UTC on July 13, with the project to reveal full details and the exact timing of the launch on their social media channels.</p>
<p>The secretive launch and experience of the team &#8211; rumored to have been behind previously viral meme coins like $SPONGE &#8211; has only increased excitement for the token.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259985" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8.png" alt="Picture8" width="936" height="304" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8.png 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-300x97.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-768x249.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture8-50x16.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<h2>$HANKEY Tokenomics &#8211; Low Hard Cap and Large Liquidity</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=mr-hankey-coin-set-for-500k-presale-launch-this-week-with-new-meme-coin-expected-to-go-viral" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$HANKEY ICO</a> will not only have a secret drop but is also launching with an extremely limited supply that is intended to get investors scrambling for tokens.</p>
<p>Only 400 million tokens have been made available, with a hard cap of just $500,000, which the team expects to be bought up by the time the weekend starts.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259984" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="936" height="754" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2-300x242.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2-768x619.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture7-2-50x40.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>That presale allocation is 40% of the max supply of just 1 billion tokens, with another 40% available for the liquidity pool when it launches on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>This combination of a small hard cap, huge FOMO, and high liquidity is positioning the token for a potential increase soon after its DEX launch as orders fly in and the wider market apes into a position.</p>
<p>With liquidity expected to be locked at launch, there is also no chance of a rug pull.</p>
<p>Crypto analysts are already expecting big things of $HANKEY because of its fair launch, short ICO, the hype already building around it, and the name recognition of one of South Park’s favorite creations.</p>
<p>With similarly themed shitcoins exploding every week, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7aRT6sH4zBw" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">one analyst has already predicted the project to quickly 10x</a> due to the growing anticipation over the launch.</p>
<h2>Large Marketing Budget and Experienced Team</h2>
<p>The remaining supply has been allocated to its marketing budget (10%), team and development (5%) and centralized exchange liquidity (5%).</p>
<p>As mentioned above, there are growing rumors that the team has previously been involved with the likes of $SPONG, a token that exploded over 100x in price during the meme coin frenzy earlier this year.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-259983" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="936" height="506" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1.jpg 936w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1-768x415.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Picture6-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 936px) 100vw, 936px" /></a></p>
<p>They have allocated a large marketing budget to the project and their contacts in Web3 have already seen results as the project becomes a name on the lips of serious investors across the space.</p>
<p>It is already being featured in numerous crypto news websites and even heavily visited data aggregators such as DEXTools and CoinGecko.</p>
<p>The team is also set to use its contacts to have $HANKEY listed on as many centralized exchanges as possible in as quick a time as possible &#8211; the expected volume from the launch will help in that task.</p>
<h2>Growing Community and First Access to ICO Drop</h2>
<p>The Mr Hankey Coin community is rapidly growing as FOMO builds and potential investors get excited by the new coin. While the presale is not yet live, investors can join now to get notified of the drop date and secure their place.</p>
<p>Its social media following will also be the first place to reveal crucial details on the launch time, with investors needing to follow its <a href="https://twitter.com/MrHankeythecoin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Twitter page</a> and <a href="https://t.me/MrHankeyOfficial" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram channel</a> to receive the news and act quickly.</p>
<p>The project has also put together a <a href="https://mrhankey.vip/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Brownpaper.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">whitepaper &#8211; or brownpaper</a> &#8211; so potential investors can dig a bit deeper into the project ahead of the anticipated July 13 launch.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.care/b_misterhankey_34322?referrer=mr-hankey-coin-set-for-500k-presale-launch-this-week-with-new-meme-coin-expected-to-go-viral" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit Mr Hankey Coin Website</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mr-hankey-coin-set-for-500k-presale-launch-this-week-with-new-meme-coin-expected-to-go-viral/" rel="nofollow">Mr. Hankey Coin Set for $500k Presale Launch This Week with New Meme Coin Expected to Go Viral</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New ATH: Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Peaks Amid Institutional Interest (Bitfinex Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-ath-bitcoins-unmoved-supply-peaks-amid-institutional-interest-bitfinex-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 13:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=259805</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-6.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/bitcoin_cover-6.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[According to the report, the unmoved BTC has led to a decrease in liquidity for bitcoin traders.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leading crypto exchange Bitfinex released its latest Bitfinex Alpha report, a weekly publication that offers on-chain data and insights into the dynamic crypto market. This week&#8217;s document found that the amount of unmoved bitcoin has reached its highest point.</p>
<p>The report further highlights an intriguing development in liquidity trends. Bitcoin liquidity has experienced a decrease, while that of Tether USDT has witnessed a noteworthy increase.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Hits ATH</h2>
<p><a href="https://blog.bitfinex.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/Bitfinex-Alpha-62.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Bitfinex Alpha</a> attributes the surge in unmoved bitcoin to the growing interest of institutional investors in the digital asset.</p>
<p>Citing data from Ark Invest, an investment firm headed by the renowned <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cathie-wood-reiterates-her-1-million-bitcoin-bet/" data-wpel-link="internal">Cathie Wood</a>, the paper stated that about 70% of BTC&#8217;s circulating supply has been unmoved for at least a year, the highest ever recorded.</p>
<p>The increasing involvement of these big players indicates strong bullish sentiment and unwavering confidence in bitcoin&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<p>According to the report, the BTC balance held on over-the-counter (OTC) desks, which serves as a reliable indicator of institutional activity, reached a one-year high in June. The balance surged by an impressive 60% by the end of the third quarter. This growth suggests that institutions and large investors are actively embracing the cryptocurrency as an attractive investment option.</p>
<p>The researchers also found that the bitcoin holdings of crypto-related hedge funds, investment firms, and private funds have significantly increased as institutional investors accumulate BTC at the current price level.</p>
<h2>Derivatives Traders Dominating the Market</h2>
<p>However, per the report, there has been a notable surge in Bitcoin Open Interest, exceeding a substantial 38% increase since the initial spot Bitcoin ETF <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/not-just-blackrock-these-companies-have-also-filed-for-spot-bitcoin-etf-in-the-us/" data-wpel-link="internal">filing</a> by the world&#8217;s largest asset manager BlackRock.</p>
<p>This rise indicates a potential shift in market dynamics, with derivatives traders potentially exerting greater influence on the current momentum, dethroning spot traders.</p>
<p>Bitfinex researchers caution that increased positions in futures contracts typically indicate short-term downward pressure on BTC&#8217;s price. As such, traders should monitor the trend closely, as it could impact market performance in the short run.</p>
<h2>A Decreased Bitcoin Liquidity</h2>
<p>The report also found that there has been a decline in bitcoin&#8217;s liquidity, contrasted with a substantial increase in the liquidity of Tether USDT, the largest stablecoin in the market. The decreased BTC liquidity aligns with the trend of long-term bitcoin holdings, as outlined in the publication.</p>
<blockquote><p>The researchers shed light on the development, stating, &#8220;As more investors hold onto their Bitcoin, less of it is available for trading, leading to decreased liquidity. This trend of &#8216;HODLing&#8217; is often perceived as a testament to the confidence placed in Bitcoin&#8217;s long-term value, despite temporary market fluctuations.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>However, it is worth noting that insufficient liquidity can give rise to increased price volatility. When less BTC is available for trading, price changes can become more drastic, which may pose risks for traders.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-ath-bitcoins-unmoved-supply-peaks-amid-institutional-interest-bitfinex-report/" rel="nofollow">New ATH: Bitcoin&#8217;s Unmoved Supply Peaks Amid Institutional Interest (Bitfinex Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
