<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Pepe Coin Price Prediction as $500 Million Trading Volume Comes In – On-Chain Data Shows Whales are Accumulating</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-500-million-trading-volume-comes-in-on-chain-data-shows-whales-are-accumulating.htm</link><description>The Pepe Coin price has fallen by 24% in the past 24 hours, with its drop to $0.00000123 coming amid a 3% fall for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. &lt;br /&gt;
PEPE's current price means it has dropped by 36% in the last seven days, although it remains up by a very impressive 330% in the last 30. &lt;br /&gt;
Its 24-hour trading volume has also seen a recovery towards $600 million after dipping earlier in the week, raising the possibility of further price rises to come....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-500-million-trading-volume-comes-in-on-chain-data-shows-whales-are-accumulating.htm"&gt;Read More: Pepe Coin Price Prediction as $500 Million Trading Volume Comes In – On-Chain Data Shows Whales are Accumulating&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pepe-coin-price-prediction-as-500-million-trading-volume-comes-in-on-chain-data-shows-whales-are-accumulating.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113728/275166/pepe-coin-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1428579"/></item><item><title>IRS Trains Ukraine to Track Russian Cryptocurrency Activity – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-trains-ukraine-track-russian-cryptocurrency-activity-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) is offering virtual and in-person training sessions on tracing blockchain transactions for Ukrainian officials.  &lt;br /&gt;
The criminal investigation division of the agency has joined hands with blockchain analysis firm Chainalysis and Ukrainian investigators to trace Russian individuals suspected of using cryptocurrency to conceal their assets following Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, Bloomberg reported Thursday. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-trains-ukraine-track-russian-cryptocurrency-activity-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: IRS Trains Ukraine to Track Russian Cryptocurrency Activity – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>IRS</category><category>Russia</category><category>Ukraine</category><category>Ukraine war</category><category>Sanctions</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/irs-trains-ukraine-track-russian-cryptocurrency-activity-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113731/275157/adobestock-aevan-1-1-medi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="172894"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Slides 10%: Is $25,000 the Key Price Level to Watch?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-slides-10-25000-key-price-level-watch.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, has experienced a significant decline of 10% in its price.  &lt;br /&gt;
This downward movement raises the question of whether the key support level at $25,000 will hold. Investors and traders are closely monitoring the market to determine if Bitcoin's price will find stability and bounce back from this crucial level. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-slides-10-25000-key-price-level-watch.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Slides 10%: Is $25,000 the Key Price Level to Watch?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-slides-10-25000-key-price-level-watch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113726/275154/12-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="528052"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 May – Pepe Coin, Bitget Token, Cosmos</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-may-pepe-coin-bitget-token-cosmos.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has dipped below the $27,500 mark, effectively neutralizing the gains previously sparked by U.S. inflation data. &lt;br /&gt;
This trend has been developing over the last month, ever since Bitcoin peaked above $30,600 in mid-April. &lt;br /&gt;
Given the ongoing bearish market trend, what are the best cryptos to buy now? &lt;br /&gt;
Data collated by Santiment suggests a decrease in social media discussions around top crypto assets, including Bitcoin, which saw an 18% drop....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-may-pepe-coin-bitget-token-cosmos.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 11 May – Pepe Coin, Bitget Token, Cosmos&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe Coin</category><category>Bitget token</category><category>Cosmos</category><category>AiDoge</category><category>DeeLance</category><category>yPredict</category><category>Sponge</category><category>AI</category><category>DLANCE</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>Freelancing</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Remote Work</category><category>Web3</category><category>Non-fungible tokens</category><category>NFT</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto</category><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-11-may-pepe-coin-bitget-token-cosmos.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113716/275124/best-crypto-11-may.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="305488"/></item><item><title>US House Financial Services Committee Chair Rep. McHenry Accuses SEC Chair of Avoiding Answering Questions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-chair-rep-mchenry-accuses-sec-chair-of-avoiding-answering-questions.htm</link><description>House Financial Services Committee Chair Patrick T. McHenry accused US Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler of avoiding requests for information about cryptocurrency-related matters, going so far as to threaten a hearing if they don’t hear back soon....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-chair-rep-mchenry-accuses-sec-chair-of-avoiding-answering-questions.htm"&gt;Read More: US House Financial Services Committee Chair Rep. McHenry Accuses SEC Chair of Avoiding Answering Questions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Securities and Exchange Commission</category><category>Gary Gensler</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-house-financial-services-committee-chair-rep-mchenry-accuses-sec-chair-of-avoiding-answering-questions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113714/275123/screen-shot-2023-05-11-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="381673"/></item><item><title>Binance Criticizes US Crypto Regulations, Eyes UK for Better Oversight</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-criticizes-us-crypto-regulations-eyes-uk-for-better-oversight.htm</link><description>Major crypto exchange Binance has criticized crypto regulations in the US, calling on the country to follow in Europe’s footsteps and provide clearer rules. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking at the Financial Times’ Crypto and Digital Assets Summit in London on Wednesday this week, Binance’s Chief Strategy Officer Patrick Hillman took aim at US regulators, saying enforcement of crypto regulations in the US have “been very confusing over the past six months.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-criticizes-us-crypto-regulations-eyes-uk-for-better-oversight.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Criticizes US Crypto Regulations, Eyes UK for Better Oversight&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>UK</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-criticizes-us-crypto-regulations-eyes-uk-for-better-oversight.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113713/275122/united-kingdom.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="119837"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Keep BTC Above $27,000 Support – What is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-keep-btc-above-27000-support-what-next-btc-target-1.htm</link><description>Bitcoin's price has been a topic of great interest and speculation as bulls manage to maintain its value above the crucial $27,000 support level.  &lt;br /&gt;
This resilience has sparked curiosity about the next target for BTC and what lies ahead in terms of its price movement.  &lt;br /&gt;
Traders and investors alike are closely watching the market dynamics, searching for clues to forecast the future trajectory of Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-keep-btc-above-27000-support-what-next-btc-target-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bulls Keep BTC Above $27,000 Support – What is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bulls-keep-btc-above-27000-support-what-next-btc-target-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113712/275121/11-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="479890"/></item><item><title>S&amp;P Global Finds Ties Between Crypto and Macroeconomic Changes in Latest Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sp-global-finds-ties-between-crypto-macroeconomic-changes-latest-report.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency is still tied to the effects of macroeconomic changes despite drivers such as technology and market sentiment, according to S&amp;P Global’s latest report. &lt;br /&gt;
The authors of that US-focused report looked into how monetary policy affects crypto, whether a perception of a possible recession matters for crypto and whether financial stress spills into those markets among other related topics in a report released this month. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sp-global-finds-ties-between-crypto-macroeconomic-changes-latest-report.htm"&gt;Read More: S&amp;P Global Finds Ties Between Crypto and Macroeconomic Changes in Latest Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category/><category>Economy</category><category>Macroeconomics</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sp-global-finds-ties-between-crypto-macroeconomic-changes-latest-report.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113711/275117/pexels-rdne-stock-project.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="164271"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Will Probably Retest $25K But Bears Beware, On-chain Indicators Suggest BTC Price in Early-Stage Bull Market</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-will-probably-retest-25k-but-bears-beware-on-chain-indicators-suggest-btc-price-in-early-stage-bull-market.htm</link><description>Bitcoin (BTC)’s short-term technical outlook is not looking good. &lt;br /&gt;
The world’s first and largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization has now pulled more than 13% lower versus the yearly highs it printed back in April to the north of the $31,000 level. &lt;br /&gt;
In doing so, it has fallen convincingly to the south of its 21 and 50-Day Moving Averages (both in the mid-$28,000s) and was last changing hands just under the $27,000....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-will-probably-retest-25k-but-bears-beware-on-chain-indicators-suggest-btc-price-in-early-stage-bull-market.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Will Probably Retest $25K But Bears Beware, On-chain Indicators Suggest BTC Price in Early-Stage Bull Market&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>On-Chain</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-will-probably-retest-25k-but-bears-beware-on-chain-indicators-suggest-btc-price-in-early-stage-bull-market.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113710/275118/btc-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="160058"/></item><item><title>Tether Announces Q1 Profit of $1.48 Billion and Discloses Bitcoin, Gold Reserves</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-announces-q1-profit-of-148-billion-discloses-bitcoin-gold-reserves.htm</link><description>Stablecoin issuer Tether has announced a profit of $1.48 billion for the first quarter of this year, after rising interest rates helped the company earn higher returns on its massive reserves. &lt;br /&gt;
In addition to announcing the massive billion-dollar profit, Tether revealed in a press release on Wednesday that it now holds both physical gold and Bitcoin (BTC) – by some considered digital gold – as part of its reserves....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-announces-q1-profit-of-148-billion-discloses-bitcoin-gold-reserves.htm"&gt;Read More: Tether Announces Q1 Profit of $1.48 Billion and Discloses Bitcoin, Gold Reserves&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Tether</category><category>USDT</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tether-announces-q1-profit-of-148-billion-discloses-bitcoin-gold-reserves.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113688/275057/tether.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4211511"/></item><item><title>Launchpad XYZ Presale Picks Up Pace as All-in-One Web3 Hub Hits $300K Mark</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-presale-picks-up-pace-as-all-one-web3-hub-hits-300k-mark.htm</link><description>Revolutionary all-in-one web3 hub Launchpad XYZ’s crypto presale is gaining momentum. &lt;br /&gt;
The start-up, which only launched its presale a few weeks ago, has already raised over $300,000 via the sale of the platform’s native $LPX crypto token. &lt;br /&gt;
Launchpad XYZ is building a revolutionary, all-encompassing web3 platform that, according to the project’s Whitepaper, aims to make the highly “fractured and intimidating” web3 space more easily accessible....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-presale-picks-up-pace-as-all-one-web3-hub-hits-300k-mark.htm"&gt;Read More: Launchpad XYZ Presale Picks Up Pace as All-in-One Web3 Hub Hits $300K Mark&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Launchpad Xyz</category><category>LPX</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/launchpad-xyz-presale-picks-up-pace-as-all-one-web3-hub-hits-300k-mark.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113704/275102/launchpax-xyz.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1217355"/></item><item><title>yPredict Presale on Fire, $750K Milestone Hit as Investors Scoop Up Tokens Ahead of 28.5% Price Rise</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-fire-750k-milestone-hit-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm</link><description>Revolutionary AI-powered trading and intelligence platform yPredict’s presale is on fire. &lt;br /&gt;
And there’s no time to lose to invest in the project, whose institutional-grade AI-powered crypto price prediction system is being touted as a game-changer for the trading industry. &lt;br /&gt;
The web3 start-up has now nearly raised a whopping $900,000 via the presale of its $YPRED crypto token as investors rush to secure tokens ahead of an impending 28.5% price rise....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-fire-750k-milestone-hit-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm"&gt;Read More: yPredict Presale on Fire, $750K Milestone Hit as Investors Scoop Up Tokens Ahead of 28.5% Price Rise&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>yPredict</category><category>YPRED</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ypredict-presale-fire-750k-milestone-hit-as-investors-scoop-up-tokens-ahead-of-285-price-rise.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113703/275098/ypred.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="56765"/></item><item><title>Smart Contracts Have Arrived on the Bitcoin Blockchain – Will BTC Become a DeFi Powerhouse?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/smart-contracts-arrived-bitcoin-blockchain-will-btc-become-defi-powerhouse.htm</link><description>A new era has begun for the Bitcoin blockchain. &lt;br /&gt;
Last week, a group of developers deployed a suite of Uniswap smart contracts directly onto the Bitcoin blockchain. &lt;br /&gt;
Uniswap is a decentralized cryptocurrency exchange (DEX) that operates on multiple smart contract-enabled blockchains like Ethereum and Polygon and operates based on automated market maker (AMM) smart contracts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/smart-contracts-arrived-bitcoin-blockchain-will-btc-become-defi-powerhouse.htm"&gt;Read More: Smart Contracts Have Arrived on the Bitcoin Blockchain – Will BTC Become a DeFi Powerhouse?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Smart Contract</category><category>DeFi</category><category>DEX</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/smart-contracts-arrived-bitcoin-blockchain-will-btc-become-defi-powerhouse.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113701/275092/btc-5.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="69477"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Legal Officer Responds to PEPE Uproar Following Newsletter Calling the Memecoin a “Hate Symbol”</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-legal-officer-responds-pepe-uproar-following-newsletter-calling-memecoin-hate-symbol.htm</link><description>Twitter got a bit heated on Thursday after memecoin PEPE enthusiasts jumped on the social media site with the hashtag #DeleteCoinbase trending after a newsletter was posted by the exchange calling the coin a “hate symbol.” &lt;br /&gt;
Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal has since responded Thursday afternoon to the uproar....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-legal-officer-responds-pepe-uproar-following-newsletter-calling-memecoin-hate-symbol.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Legal Officer Responds to PEPE Uproar Following Newsletter Calling the Memecoin a “Hate Symbol”&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Pepe</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Twitter</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-legal-officer-responds-pepe-uproar-following-newsletter-calling-memecoin-hate-symbol.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113699/275093/screen-shot-2023-05-11-at.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="349608"/></item><item><title>Bittrex Processed $425 Million in Withdrawals Since April 1, Claims Attorney Amid Bankruptcy Proceedings</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bittrex-processed-425-million-withdrawals-since-april-1-claims-attorney-amid-bankruptcy-proceedings.htm</link><description>The US and Maltese arms of crypto exchange Bittrex have processed $425 million in withdrawals since the platform announced plans to wind down US operations.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Wednesday, Bittrex attorney Susheel Kirpalani reportedly told a Delaware bankruptcy court that the firm had not engaged in any negative behaviors that have been alleged against other entities in the crypto space. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bittrex-processed-425-million-withdrawals-since-april-1-claims-attorney-amid-bankruptcy-proceedings.htm"&gt;Read More: Bittrex Processed $425 Million in Withdrawals Since April 1, Claims Attorney Amid Bankruptcy Proceedings&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bittrex</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bittrex-processed-425-million-withdrawals-since-april-1-claims-attorney-amid-bankruptcy-proceedings.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113687/275058/172454329-m-normal-none.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="145947"/></item><item><title>Texas Lawmakers Vote To Cement Digital Currencies in Lone State’s Bill of Rights</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-vote-cement-digital-currencies-lone-states-bill-of-rights.htm</link><description>Texas lawmakers voted almost unanimously to change the state’s bill of rights to include the right of its residents to own, hold and use digital currency. &lt;br /&gt;
The joint resolution was passed through a 139-2 vote on Wednesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-vote-cement-digital-currencies-lone-states-bill-of-rights.htm"&gt;Read More: Texas Lawmakers Vote To Cement Digital Currencies in Lone State’s Bill of Rights&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Texas</category><category>Legislation</category><category>Digital Currency</category><category>CBDC</category><category>Ted Cruz</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/texas-lawmakers-vote-cement-digital-currencies-lone-states-bill-of-rights.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113695/275065/pexels-lesli-whitecotton-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="98180"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Forecast: Hydra Scaling Solution Gains Attention Amid Ethereum Gas Fee Surge – Is It Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-hydra-scaling-solution-gains-attention-amid-ethereum-gas-fee-surge-it-time-buy.htm</link><description>Cardano (ADA) continues to hold above its 200-Day Moving Average just above $0.3500, but sell pressure appears to be building. &lt;br /&gt;
Nonetheless, price forecasts are becoming more downbeat....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-hydra-scaling-solution-gains-attention-amid-ethereum-gas-fee-surge-it-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Forecast: Hydra Scaling Solution Gains Attention Amid Ethereum Gas Fee Surge – Is It Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Cardano</category><category>ADA</category><category>Hydra</category><category>Layer-2 scaling solution</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-forecast-hydra-scaling-solution-gains-attention-amid-ethereum-gas-fee-surge-it-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113691/275061/adausd.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="694346"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: NY Proposes Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds, Franklin Templeton Plans Second Blockchain Fund, Circle Won't Hold Treasurys Past June, Bittrex Allowed to Borrow $7M</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ny-proposes-bill-to-allow-stablecoin-payments-for-bail-bonds-franklin-templeton-plans-second-blockchain-fund-circle-wont-hold-treasurys-past-june-bittrex-allowed-to-borrow-7m.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ny-proposes-bill-to-allow-stablecoin-payments-for-bail-bonds-franklin-templeton-plans-second-blockchain-fund-circle-wont-hold-treasurys-past-june-bittrex-allowed-to-borrow-7m.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: NY Proposes Bill to Allow Stablecoin Payments for Bail Bonds, Franklin Templeton Plans Second Blockchain Fund, Circle Won't Hold Treasurys Past June, Bittrex Allowed to Borrow $7M&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Regulation</category><category>USA</category><category>Investment</category><category>SEC</category><category>Circle</category><category>Politics</category><category>Bittrex</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>OKX</category><category>advertising</category><category>Legal</category><category>Mining</category><category>Marathon</category><category>CleanSpark</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-ny-proposes-bill-to-allow-stablecoin-payments-for-bail-bonds-franklin-templeton-plans-second-blockchain-fund-circle-wont-hold-treasurys-past-june-bittrex-allowed-to-borrow-7m.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113626/274968/adobestock-iqoncept-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="219146"/></item><item><title>Su Zhu of Three Arrows Capital Gets Restraining Order Against Billionaire Arthur Hayes Amid Dispute</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/su-zhu-of-three-arrows-capital-gets-restraining-order-against-billionaire-arthur-hayes-amid-dispute.htm</link><description>A Singapore court has granted the restraining order request by Three Arrows Capital (3AC) co-founder Su Zhu against BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes.  &lt;br /&gt;
The order stated that the Judge's ruling could be sent to Hayes through his Twitter account.  &lt;br /&gt;
Hayes has been bombarding Zhu and his partner Davies with tweets after the crash of the hedge fund 3AC, demanding the return of the $6 million the fund owed him. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/su-zhu-of-three-arrows-capital-gets-restraining-order-against-billionaire-arthur-hayes-amid-dispute.htm"&gt;Read More: Su Zhu of Three Arrows Capital Gets Restraining Order Against Billionaire Arthur Hayes Amid Dispute&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/su-zhu-of-three-arrows-capital-gets-restraining-order-against-billionaire-arthur-hayes-amid-dispute.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113685/275084/screenshot-2023-03-09-at-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2564934"/></item><item><title>Half of North Korea's Missile Funding Comes from Cybercrimes and Cryptocurrency Theft, Says White House</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/half-of-north-koreas-missile-funding-comes-from-cybercrimes-cryptocurrency-theft-says-white-house.htm</link><description>As North Korean military activities continue to capture the attention of decision-makers and analysts across the world, around 50% of the country’s secretive missile program could be financed by cyberattacks and cryptocurrency theft, according to Anne Neuberger, the U.S. deputy national security adviser for cyber and emerging technology....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/half-of-north-koreas-missile-funding-comes-from-cybercrimes-cryptocurrency-theft-says-white-house.htm"&gt;Read More: Half of North Korea's Missile Funding Comes from Cybercrimes and Cryptocurrency Theft, Says White House&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hackers</category><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/half-of-north-koreas-missile-funding-comes-from-cybercrimes-cryptocurrency-theft-says-white-house.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/113680/275048/adobestock-459050824-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="197398"/></item></channel></rss>
