<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Binance Sale of USDC for BTC and ETH Raises Fresh Concerns In Latest Proof-of-Reserves Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-sale-of-usdc-for-btc-and-eth-raises-fresh-concerns-in-latest-proof-of-reserves-report.htm</link><description>Binance's latest proof-of-reserves (PoR) report has come under scrutiny following its depleting USDC reserves after the collapse of Silvergate Bank. &lt;br /&gt;
The report released on Aug 1 to show transparency in the exchange’s dealings with user assets has sparked arguments across social media spaces heightened by Brian Armstrong’s witty comment at the company’s latest earning call....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-sale-of-usdc-for-btc-and-eth-raises-fresh-concerns-in-latest-proof-of-reserves-report.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Sale of USDC for BTC and ETH Raises Fresh Concerns In Latest Proof-of-Reserves Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>USDC</category><category>btc</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-sale-of-usdc-for-btc-and-eth-raises-fresh-concerns-in-latest-proof-of-reserves-report.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121865/322667/adobestock-286536398-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="303155"/></item><item><title>Glassnode Data Reveals Bitcoin HODLers Reach New Record: Long-Term Holders Now Control More BTC Than Ever</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/glassnode-data-reveals-bitcoin-hodlers-reach-new-record-long-term-holders-now-control-more-btc-than-ever.htm</link><description>The staunchest Bitcoiners, known in industry terms as long-term holders, now control more Bitcoin (BTC) than ever before, new data from blockchain analytics firm Glassnode has revealed. &lt;br /&gt;
According to the data, the so-called long-term holder supply now stands at 14.599 million BTC, representing 75% of the circulating BTC supply. &lt;br /&gt;
14.599 million BTC held by long-term holders is the highest reading ever recorded for this metric, Glassnode said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/glassnode-data-reveals-bitcoin-hodlers-reach-new-record-long-term-holders-now-control-more-btc-than-ever.htm"&gt;Read More: Glassnode Data Reveals Bitcoin HODLers Reach New Record: Long-Term Holders Now Control More BTC Than Ever&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Glassnode</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/glassnode-data-reveals-bitcoin-hodlers-reach-new-record-long-term-holders-now-control-more-btc-than-ever.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121866/322660/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="125125"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Prediction as Blockchain Transactions Surge Up Nearly 50% in 3 Months – Are Whales Moving to Cardano?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transactions-surge-up-nearly-50-3-months-are-whales-moving-cardano.htm</link><description>The price of Cardano (ADA) has dropped by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, with its slide to $0.290402 also representing a 5% loss in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
This weekly fall comes amid a difficult period for the wider cryptocurrency market, which has recently been undermined by negativity surrounding the downgrading of US government debt, as well as by the development of Coinbase's legal battle with the SEC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transactions-surge-up-nearly-50-3-months-are-whales-moving-cardano.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Prediction as Blockchain Transactions Surge Up Nearly 50% in 3 Months – Are Whales Moving to Cardano?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-blockchain-transactions-surge-up-nearly-50-3-months-are-whales-moving-cardano.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121847/322636/cardano-price-prediction-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1146974"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Bitstamp to Expand Operations with New Fundraising Plan</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-expand-operations-with-new-fundraising-plan.htm</link><description>Bitstamp, an early crypto exchange founded in 2011, is reportedly planning fresh fundraising “through strategic investors” to gear up the exchange’s growth and operations. &lt;br /&gt;
Speaking to Bloomberg, Jean-Baptiste Graftieaux, CEO of Bitstamp said that the exchange is “not for sale.” He said that the company started the fundraising process in June under the guidance of Galaxy Digital Holdings....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-expand-operations-with-new-fundraising-plan.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Bitstamp to Expand Operations with New Fundraising Plan&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-bitstamp-expand-operations-with-new-fundraising-plan.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121852/322621/bitstamp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="63400"/></item><item><title>Ripple is Going to Zero as XRP Price Plummets 12% While This New XRP Coin Raises $1.1 Million – 1,000x Potential Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-going-zero-as-xrp-price-plummets-12-while-new-xrp-coin-raises-11-million-1000x-potential-soon.htm</link><description>While the landmark ruling in the Ripple vs SEC case has sent waves through the crypto market, XRP price action has faced a disappointing bleed-out. &lt;br /&gt;
High expectations of XRP breaking $1 seem to be crushed, as XRP's downside slide enters its 21st day. &lt;br /&gt;
The downward momentum has left XRP trading relatively low, at a current price of $0.61 (a 24-hour change of -1.09%)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-going-zero-as-xrp-price-plummets-12-while-new-xrp-coin-raises-11-million-1000x-potential-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Ripple is Going to Zero as XRP Price Plummets 12% While This New XRP Coin Raises $1.1 Million – 1,000x Potential Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ripple-going-zero-as-xrp-price-plummets-12-while-new-xrp-coin-raises-11-million-1000x-potential-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121851/322632/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="596713"/></item><item><title>Cypher Protocol Loses $1 Million in Blockchain Exploit – Here's What Happened</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cypher-protocol-loses-1-million-blockchain-exploit-heres-what-happened.htm</link><description>Solana-based decentralized exchange Cypher Protocol halted its smart contract following an exploit that saw an estimated $1 million stolen. &lt;br /&gt;
On the evening of August 7 (UTC), Cypher confirmed that there had been a security incident, saying that the team was investigating it, but without providing specific information.  &lt;br /&gt;
The event resulted in the smart contract getting frozen, it said....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cypher-protocol-loses-1-million-blockchain-exploit-heres-what-happened.htm"&gt;Read More: Cypher Protocol Loses $1 Million in Blockchain Exploit – Here's What Happened&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Hack</category><category>Security</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Solana</category><category>SOL</category><category>USDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cypher-protocol-loses-1-million-blockchain-exploit-heres-what-happened.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121833/322620/adobestock-maksim-kabakou.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3445008"/></item><item><title>Binance Labs Maintains Dominance in Crypto Funding Despite Regulatory Challenges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-maintains-dominance-crypto-funding-despite-regulatory-challenges.htm</link><description>Binance Labs, the venture capital arm of the largest cryptocurrency exchange, Binance, remains an active investor in the crypto space despite its parent company facing regulatory challenges and potential fraud charges.  &lt;br /&gt;
Last week, Binance Labs announced four investments through its Most Valuable Builder (MVB) incubator program. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-maintains-dominance-crypto-funding-despite-regulatory-challenges.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Labs Maintains Dominance in Crypto Funding Despite Regulatory Challenges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Binance Labs</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-labs-maintains-dominance-crypto-funding-despite-regulatory-challenges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121853/322622/adobestock-286536398-edit.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="302949"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as $1.2 Billion Trading Volume Sends XRP into the Green – Big Move Coming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-12-billion-trading-volume-sends-xrp-into-green-big-move-coming.htm</link><description>The XRP price has risen by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, with its move to $0.618192 coming as the cryptocurrency market as a whole barely budges today. &lt;br /&gt;
XRP is now down by 10% in the last seven days, but remains up by 31% in the past month and by 81% since the beginning of the year, following the largely positive outcome Ripple welcomed in July in its case with the SEC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-12-billion-trading-volume-sends-xrp-into-green-big-move-coming.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as $1.2 Billion Trading Volume Sends XRP into the Green – Big Move Coming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-12-billion-trading-volume-sends-xrp-into-green-big-move-coming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121839/322601/xrp-price-prediction-as-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1270865"/></item><item><title>TBOT Token is Up 10,000% in 24 Hours But Blockchain Experts Say It Has a Hidden 100% Tax Function – Here's What They're Stacking Instead</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/tbot-token-up-10000-24-hours-but-blockchain-experts-say-it-hidden-100-tax-function-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm</link><description>As the hype around Telegram trading bots such as Unibot continues to grow, Turbobot token (TBOT) has been the latest straight-to-DEX product launch to undertake a sensational skyrocket price move. &lt;br /&gt;
Launched on August 7, Turbobot token gained explosive growth after igniting a flood of volume which drove price up +34,200%....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/tbot-token-up-10000-24-hours-but-blockchain-experts-say-it-hidden-100-tax-function-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm"&gt;Read More: TBOT Token is Up 10,000% in 24 Hours But Blockchain Experts Say It Has a Hidden 100% Tax Function – Here's What They're Stacking Instead&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/tbot-token-up-10000-24-hours-but-blockchain-experts-say-it-hidden-100-tax-function-heres-what-theyre-stacking-instead.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121838/322594/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="431824"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Becomes Top Performing Coin of the Week as Shibarium Launch Approaches – Can SHIB 1,000x From Here?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-becomes-top-performing-coin-of-week-as-shibarium-launch-approaches-can-shib-1000x-from-here.htm</link><description>The price of Shiba Inu (SHIB) remains up by 7.5% in the past week, despite the meme token's 1.5% drop today, to $0.00000897. &lt;br /&gt;
SHIB is also up by 18% in the last 30 days, as the market becomes increasingly optimistic about the approaching launch of Shibarium, Shiba Inu's very own layer-two network....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-becomes-top-performing-coin-of-week-as-shibarium-launch-approaches-can-shib-1000x-from-here.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Becomes Top Performing Coin of the Week as Shibarium Launch Approaches – Can SHIB 1,000x From Here?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-becomes-top-performing-coin-of-week-as-shibarium-launch-approaches-can-shib-1000x-from-here.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121832/322580/shiba-inu-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1381005"/></item><item><title>Monetary Authority of Singapore Grants Payment License to Crypto Exchange Blockchain.com</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/monetary-authority-of-singapore-grants-payment-license-crypto-exchange-blockchaincom.htm</link><description>Crypto exchange Blockchain.com announced on Monday that it had received a major payment institution (MPI) license from the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) on August 1. &lt;br /&gt;
The announcement follows Blockchain.com receiving its in-principle approval from Singapore’s central bank in October last year. With the MPI license, the exchange can continue to extend its Digital Payment Token (DPT) services to institutional customers and investors in Singapore....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/monetary-authority-of-singapore-grants-payment-license-crypto-exchange-blockchaincom.htm"&gt;Read More: Monetary Authority of Singapore Grants Payment License to Crypto Exchange Blockchain.com&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/monetary-authority-of-singapore-grants-payment-license-crypto-exchange-blockchaincom.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121835/322569/asia-1782429-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="226510"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Pull BTC Down to $29,000 Level – Where is BTC Heading Next?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has recently held above $29,000, signaling potential positivity, but hasn't reached $30,000 yet. It's been trading between roughly $28,900 and $29,280, reflecting uncertainty. &lt;br /&gt;
Notably, significant Bitcoin holders are selling less, possibly indicating their confidence in its future value increase. &lt;br /&gt;
The recent increase in the value of Bitcoin may be connected to PayPal's announcement of their new digital currency, PayPal USD (PYUSD)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Bears Pull BTC Down to $29,000 Level – Where is BTC Heading Next?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-bears-pull-btc-down-29000-level-where-btc-heading-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121817/322560/8-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="533139"/></item><item><title>Russian Banks Say Citizens Are ‘Wary’ of CBDC Plans – Digital Ruble Faces Roadblock?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm</link><description>Russia’s biggest banking association has demanded clarification on Moscow’s CBDC plans, and says citizens are “wary” of the digital ruble. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Komersant and BFM, the Association of Russian Banks (ARB) sent a letter to the Central Bank with “a request to clarify certain issues pertaining to the digital ruble.” &lt;br /&gt;
The Central Bank is currently working with over a dozen commercial banks on a “real-world” pilot. &lt;br /&gt;
But, the ARB wrote:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Banks Say Citizens Are ‘Wary’ of CBDC Plans – Digital Ruble Faces Roadblock?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-banks-say-citizens-are-wary-of-cbdc-plans-digital-ruble-faces-roadblock.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121774/322442/adobestock-619979221.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="473630"/></item><item><title>Belarus Prepares to Launch ‘Cross-Border’ CBDC – Russia’s Digital Ruble an Inspiration?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm</link><description>Belarus is set to follow suit with Russia’s CBDC development plans – and plans to launch a digital version of the Belarusian ruble for use in “cross-border” payments. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Minsk-Novosti and Interfax, the National Bank of the Republic of Belarus (NBRB) has earmarked the launch of CBDC as one of its most “significant” projects of recent years. &lt;br /&gt;
Dmitry Kalechits, the NRBR’s Board’s Deputy Chairman, said:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm"&gt;Read More: Belarus Prepares to Launch ‘Cross-Border’ CBDC – Russia’s Digital Ruble an Inspiration?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Belarus</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/belarus-prepares-to-launch-cross-border-cbdc-russias-digital-ruble-an-inspiration.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121700/322310/adobestock-615575824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="685848"/></item><item><title>Investors Have Stopped Shorting Bitcoin for First Time in 3 Months: CoinShares Report</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm</link><description>According to the latest Coinshares Fund Report, outflows into short Bitcoin (BTC) products have ceased for the first time in fourteen weeks.  &lt;br /&gt;
This notable shift in the market suggests that significant digital asset funds are now adopting a different strategy towards the leading cryptocurrency, seeking alternative opportunities for returns....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Investors Have Stopped Shorting Bitcoin for First Time in 3 Months: CoinShares Report&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>CoinShares</category><category>Report</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Volatility</category><category>Shorting</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/investors-stopped-shorting-bitcoin-for-first-time-3-months-coinshares-report-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121801/322511/getpaidstock-com-64d17106.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="203916"/></item><item><title>Web3 Utility Coin LPX Raises $1.2 Million in Funding for AI Trading Analytics Platform – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Web3 represents the new age of internet technology where everything is decentralized. Unlike traditional internet services where a few companies control data, Web3 allows people to own and control their data. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Web3 Utility Coin LPX Raises $1.2 Million in Funding for AI Trading Analytics Platform – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>Central Crypto Hub</category><category>Crypto Presale</category><category>Utility Coin</category><category>Best crypto to buy</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/web3-utility-coin-lpx-raises-12-million-funding-for-ai-trading-analytics-platform-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121793/322502/f2n0-kuxcaiw1f4.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="111620"/></item><item><title>Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Algorand</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm</link><description>PayPal, the global payments giant, continued its journey into the cryptocurrency space with the launch of its own stablecoin today, PayPal USD (PYUSD). &lt;br /&gt;
This development marks a significant stride since PayPal's initial foray into the cryptocurrency industry in late 2020. &lt;br /&gt;
Given this development, what are the best cryptos to buy now?...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm"&gt;Read More: Best Crypto to Buy Now 7 August – XDC Network, Kaspa, Algorand&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><category>XDC Network</category><category>Wall Street Memes</category><category>Kaspa</category><category>Xrp20</category><category>Algorand</category><category>XDC</category><category>XDC price</category><category>Kas</category><category>KAS price</category><category>ALGO</category><category>ALGO PRICE</category><category>Price Prediction</category><category>Technical Analysis</category><category>Fundamental Analysis</category><category>Cryptocurrencies</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>CRYPTO</category><category>Cryptos</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Now</category><category>Best Crypto To Buy Today</category><category>Best Crypto</category><category>Meme Coins</category><category>Meme coin</category><category>WSM</category><category>Memecoin</category><category>Memecoins</category><category>Staking</category><category>Passive income</category><category>Crypto Projects 2023</category><category>Crypto Presales 2023</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/best-crypto-buy-now-7-august-xdc-network-kaspa-algorand.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121798/322503/bctbt-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260398"/></item><item><title>Mega Dice Telegram Casino App: World’s First Crypto Casino Offering Licensed Gambling Through TG</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm</link><description>In a breakthrough for crypto casino adoption, Mega Dice is leading the way by opening the world’s first licensed crypto casino accessible via the Telegram app.  &lt;br /&gt;
The crypto casino sector is a big business and growing in popularity because it leverages blockchain's unique transparency and trust features to create a new standard for fairness in the industry....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm"&gt;Read More: Mega Dice Telegram Casino App: World’s First Crypto Casino Offering Licensed Gambling Through TG&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>News</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/mega-dice-telegram-casino-app-worlds-first-crypto-casino-offering-licensed-gambling-through-tg.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121797/322496/mega-dice-homepage.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1988120"/></item><item><title>Crypto Hedge Funds Grapple with Shutdowns and Lackluster Returns in 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm</link><description>Crypto hedge funds have on average underperformed Bitcoin (BTC) by a significant margin in the first half of 2023, while about 13% of funds have shut down so far this year. &lt;br /&gt;
On average, crypto hedge funds generated a 15.2% return in the first six months of this year, well below the 83.3% that an investor would earn by simply holding spot BTC over the same period, Bloomberg reported this weekend. &lt;br /&gt;
The report cited data from Switzerland-based investment adviser 21e6 Capital AG....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Hedge Funds Grapple with Shutdowns and Lackluster Returns in 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Altcoins</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-hedge-funds-grapple-with-shutdowns-lackluster-returns-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121789/322477/lackluster-returns.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="258327"/></item><item><title>Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: August 7, 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm</link><description>Here is our weekly collection of digital asset listing and delisting, trading pair-related announcements by crypto exchanges that we found last week and today. &lt;br /&gt;
Have we missed something? Do you have information about new listings and/or delistings? Let us know here. &lt;br /&gt;
_________________________________________ &lt;br /&gt;
AscendEXListings:Knights of Degen (DGEN) &lt;br /&gt;
BitForexListings: Novem Gold (NVM)...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Exchange Listing and Delisting Announcements: August 7, 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Altcoins</category><category>Exhange</category><category>Trading</category><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-exchange-listing-delisting-announcements-august-7-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/121775/322439/listings-and-delisting.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="293198"/></item></channel></rss>
