<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 22:53:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy Buys Another 420 BTC For $14.4 Million</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-another-420-btc-for-14-4-million/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263768</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/MicroStrategy_Bitcoin.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has published its Q2 earnings report, which includes far less brutal figures surrounding its Bitcoin holdings than last year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin (BTC) whale MicroStrategy announced on Tuesday that it has gobbled up another 420 BTC since its last announcement in June.</p>
<p>This brings the company’s total holdings up to 152,800 BTC worth $4.46 billion.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to MicroStrategy’s <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/en/investor-relations/press/microstrategy-announces-second-quarter-2023-financial-results_08-01-2023" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Q2 earnings report</a>, the firm’s 12,800 BTC acquired since Q1 was acquired for $28,233 per coin – below the asset’s current market price of $29,195.<br />
However, the company’s average purchase price for its total BTC holdings remains at $29,672, slightly above the market price.</li>
<li>
<blockquote><p>“We efficiently raised capital through our at-the-market equity program and used cash from operations to continue to increase bitcoins on our balance sheet,” stated Andrew Kang, CFO of MicroStrategy.</p></blockquote>
</li>
<li>The CFO added that Bitcoin has a promising backdrop of “increasing institutional interest, progress on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylors-wish-for-bitcoin-accounting-changes-has-arrived/" data-wpel-link="internal">accounting transparency</a>, and ongoing regulatory clarity.”</li>
<li>In late June, MicroStrategy <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-12333-btc-for-350-million-at-28k-per-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> that it had purchased 12,333 BTC since April through money raised by the company selling shares.</li>
<li>MicroStrategy executive chairman Michael Saylor remains the firm’s largest shareholder and primary <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-saylor-thinks-the-sec-crackdown-could-boost-bitcoins-dominance-to-80/" data-wpel-link="internal">advocate</a> for BTC. He personally owns tens of thousands of coins.</li>
<li>As a software business, MicroStrategy reported $120.4 million in revenue in Q2 2023, down 1.4% from the same period last year.</li>
<li>Operating expenses, however, were down a whopping 88.2% compared to last year. That’s largely due to only suffering a $24.1 million impairment loss on its BTC holdings this quarter, versus a $917.8 million loss in Q2 2022.</li>
<li>During an earnings presentation on Tuesday, the company asserted that its core business “is insulated from near-term Bitcoin price volatility.”</li>
<li>While stacking BTC, the company also increased its cash holdings since Q4 2022 from $43.8 million to $66 million.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-buys-another-420-btc-for-14-4-million/" rel="nofollow">MicroStrategy Buys Another 420 BTC For $14.4 Million</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>FTX Didn&#8217;t Speak Up About Exchange Reboot Plans, Say Creditors</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-didnt-speak-up-about-exchange-reboot-plans-say-creditors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263765</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTX_Restart.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/FTX_Restart.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Creditors say FTX’s proposed restructuring plans are mere “ideas,” and were not formally negotiated. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Lawyers representing FTX’s creditors said they weren’t filled in on a recently proposed plan to revive the company’s international exchange, according to a Monday night filing. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Creditors claimed that the proposed restructuring plan is a mere “idea” with no formal talks having taken place to actually put it into action. </span></p>
<h2>No Contact With Creditors?</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The claimants’ </span><a href="https://restructuring.ra.kroll.com/FTX/Home-DocketInfo" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">statement</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> accused FTX’s lawyers of breaking their promise to provide a public roadmap for the bankruptcy proceedings and to work with creditors on a successful reorganization plan. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Instead, debtors ignored creditors&#8217; suggestions for restructuring, which were not formally negotiated. Though the plan has been released in line with a pre-established deadline, creditors claim that what has been proposed only presents an “illusion” of progress. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Unfortunately, what was supposed to be a watershed moment for these bankruptcy cases—the filing of a plan of reorganization preceded by robust, good faith negotiation and collaboration—is anything but,” read the filing. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">FTX’s </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-reboot-proposal-presented-as-part-of-reorganization-efforts-ftt-jumped-10-overnight/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">plan</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – put forth earlier that day – was to divide the exchange’s creditors into distinct classes based on whether they worked with FTX US, or the much larger international exchange. Members of each class would receive a “pro rata share” of each exchange’s asset pool. </span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">Both FTX CEO John Ray III and the company’s former boss, Sam Bankman-Fried, have claimed that FTX US funds were kept separate from FTX and Alameda’s, with the latter claiming that the US branch is 100% solvent. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The plan’s release was coupled with a 10% rise in the price of FTT – which collapsed as FTX filed for bankruptcy in November. Yet according to creditors, this is no “plan,” but merely the debtors’ “ideas for a plan.”</span></p>
<h2>Specific Problems With The Plan</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Specifically, the plan did not address how creditors would select qualified parties to manage FTX, post-restructuring. Creditors also want a say on how the exchange could launch a “regulatory-compliant recovery token,” and how to most fairly compensate those “most injured by the fraud that occurred.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Finally, creditors showed dismay at the massive </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-influencers-in-trouble-while-advisors-pocket-103m-in-q1/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">legal fees</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that debtors have incurred throughout the entire bankruptcy process, despite initially providing them with a blueprint to stay frugal. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The cases are now on track to be “among the most expensive in history,” having burned an average of $50 million per month on professional fees since the exchange went down. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“The Committee is extremely disappointed that the Debtors have not engaged with the Committee on these issues nor yet discussed them with its members to appreciate their import,” creditors added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Many have expressed skepticism that FTX could pull off an effective reboot, with investors like Anthony Scaramucci </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-did-not-put-ftx-out-of-business-anthony-scaramucci-consensus-2023-live/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">suggesting</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that the exchange would require a total rebranding at a minimum. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ftx-didnt-speak-up-about-exchange-reboot-plans-say-creditors/" rel="nofollow">FTX Didn&#8217;t Speak Up About Exchange Reboot Plans, Say Creditors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>CZ Sheds Light on Binance&#8217;s Plans About Launching its Own Stablecoin</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/cz-sheds-light-on-binances-plans-about-launching-its-own-stablecoin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stablecoins]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263592</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/Changpeng_Zhao.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Zhao said that there is another partnership between Binance and a stablecoin issuer on the horizon.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Chief Executive Officer of Binance &#8211; Changpeng Zhao (CZ) &#8211; said one reason why his company recently introduced the stablecoin FDUSD is the terminated partnership with Paxos. While the two entities teamed up in 2019 to launch the USD-denominated BUSD, the New York state regulators told Paxos to stop minting new tokens earlier this year.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CZ said that, as of the moment, Binance has no intention to list its own stablecoin but rather collaborate with other companies focusing on that product.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Given That Everything is a Risk, Let&#8217;s Diversify&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Zhao </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1685976178006351873?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">shared</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> some of Binance&#8217;s plans regarding stablecoins during a Twitter space from this week. The crypto exchange recently added its support to FDUSD &#8211; a stablecoin issued by a Hong Kong custodian called First Digital Trust. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">CZ said many other deals could follow this partnership since the marketplace has been cooperating with stablecoin projects from different regions. One of those should see the light of day in the near future, the CEO stated:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We also have another partnership based on stablecoins that is coming up. I wouldn&#8217;t quite announce it just yet, but there is another one coming up.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_259698" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-259698" style="width: 400px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-259698" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp" alt="Changpeng Zhao" width="400" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ.webp 1200w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-300x300.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-1024x1024.webp 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-100x100.webp 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-768x768.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-239x239.webp 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-50x50.webp 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/CZ-45x45.webp 45w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-259698" class="wp-caption-text">Changpeng Zhao, Source: The Guardian</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He explained that the increased efforts in that field come as a result of the suspended collaboration with Paxos. The New York Department of Financial Services </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-regulator-reportedly-stops-paxos-from-issuing-busd-but-is-it-just-fud/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ordered</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the latter earlier this year to stop issuing the Binance USD (BUSD) stablecoin. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Prior to that, the US SEC alleged Paxos of selling unregistered securities when minting the token. Nonetheless, the stablecoin issuer </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-when-paxos-will-stop-minting-binance-usd-busd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">vowed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to continue supporting BUSD until February 2024 so customers could have enough time to convert their holdings into Pax Dollar (USDP) or cash them out in American dollars.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some crypto participants have doubted over the past few years whether Tether (the company behind the largest stablecoin USDT) has enough funds to back the substantial market capitalization of the asset. CZ acknowledged the expansion of the token but said he had never seen any audits related to it:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;We have seen many different issues with stablecoins. First of all, USDT has a very large market cap, but I personally have not seen any audits of USDT; most people I have spoken to have not seen either. So it&#8217;s kind of a black box because we don&#8217;t know, and there is a certain level of risk nature to that.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He maintained that Binance partnered with Paxos to offer a &#8220;regulated stablecoin&#8221; where &#8220;everything is audited.&#8221;</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;But guess what? It was regulated in New York, and the regulators shut it down, so the regulated stablecoins had that risk we didn&#8217;t foresee,&#8221; he regretted.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Subsequently, Zhao revealed that Binance is interested in digital assets tied to the valuation of the euro and has a team working on algorithmic stablecoins. However, he warned that the latter also hide their risks since they are pegged to the valuation of another token that is usually highly volatile.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His Crypto Prediction</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Besides talking about stablecoins and Binance&#8217;s plans in that field, Zhao gave his two cents on the overall cryptocurrency industry.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He said he is not a &#8220;good predictor&#8221; but outlined blockchain technology and Artificial Intelligence as niches that could transform the future financial network, with AI having a more direct impact. Still, Zhao said he goes &#8220;with the flow&#8221; and relies on his team to guide some of his decisions.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I support different types of developers in each sector of the crypto industry, and we&#8217;ll see which ones will grow big.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cz-sheds-light-on-binances-plans-about-launching-its-own-stablecoin/" rel="nofollow">CZ Sheds Light on Binance&#8217;s Plans About Launching its Own Stablecoin</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>IRS Rules Crypto Staking Rewards as Taxable Income</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/irs-rules-crypto-staking-rewards-as-taxable-income/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 21:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IRS]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263591</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/IRS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/IRS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The IRS said taxpayers must include the fair market value of their staking rewards in their gross income as soon as they gain control of the crypto assets.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) has ruled that U.S. cryptocurrency investors must include staking rewards in their gross income since crypto assets are treated as property for federal income tax purposes.</p>
<p>According to an official <a href="https://www.irs.gov/pub/irs-drop/rr-23-14.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">document</a>, taxpayers must include the fair market value of their staking rewards in their gross income as soon as they gain control of the crypto assets.</p>
<h2>IRS Declares Crypto Staking Rewards Taxable</h2>
<p>In the Proof-of-Stake consensus mechanism, crypto staking refers to the pledging of cryptocurrencies toward validating transactions on the blockchain and getting rewards.</p>
<p>As per the IRS, since general tax principles applied to property transactions are applicable to crypto transactions, rewards gained from validation activities must be recorded as gross income alongside rent, royalties, and compensation for goods and services.</p>
<p>The agency explained that the fair market value of staking rewards is determined on the date and time the crypto investor gains control of the assets. The same applies to investors who receive rewards by staking their assets through crypto exchanges.</p>
<p>Likewise, taxpayers who receive cryptocurrencies as payment for goods and services, including crypto miners, must include the fair market value of their assets in their gross income for the taxable year.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;If a cash-method taxpayer stakes cryptocurrency native to a proof-of-stake blockchain and receives additional units of cryptocurrency as rewards when validation occurs, the fair market value of the validation rewards received is included in the taxpayer&#8217;s gross income in the taxable year in which the taxpayer gains dominion and control over the validation rewards,&#8221; the IRS stated.</p></blockquote>
<h2>Staking Issues in the U.S.</h2>
<p>The latest update comes as authorities in the U.S. crackdown on crypto staking activities, a move that has led some exchanges to shut down their staking offerings.</p>
<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), in particular, has tackled crypto staking activities since the beginning of this year. In February, the Commission charged crypto exchange Kraken with offering its staking services as unregistered securities. The firm later <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-eth-plunge-4-following-sec-termination-of-kraken-staking/" data-wpel-link="internal">agreed</a> to terminate the service and pay $30 million in disgorgement and civil penalties.</p>
<p>It is worth mentioning that a U.S. judge <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/judge-orders-kraken-to-turn-over-user-information-to-the-irs/" data-wpel-link="internal">ordered</a> Kraken to submit sensitive user information to the IRS in June so the agency could determine if crypto investors were cheating on their tax reports.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, the SEC has also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" data-wpel-link="internal">gone</a> after Coinbase with a lawsuit alleging, among other things, that its staking-as-a-service product is an unregistered security offering. The case is still in court.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/irs-rules-crypto-staking-rewards-as-taxable-income/" rel="nofollow">IRS Rules Crypto Staking Rewards as Taxable Income</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tether Freezes $20 Million Linked To Phishing Scammer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-freezes-20-million-linked-to-phishing-scammer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263757</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/hacker2-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/hacker2-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[On-chain sleuth ZachXBT was relieved but surprised by Tether’s immediate response to the scam.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A phishing scammer recently nabbed $20 million in USDT from an unsuspecting victim using a zero transfer phishing attack, reported blockchain security firm PeckShield on Tuesday.</p>
<p>The stolen funds were frozen in short order by Tether – the issuer behind USDT – raising questions about who the victim was given the speed of their response.</p>
<h2>The Zero Transfer Phishing Attack</h2>
<p>According to PeckShield, the <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0x407e4b78c16d22b21b5ddcd0b0f7ad9cb07b9cbc#tokentxns" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">victim address</a> intended to send funds to <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xa7B4BAC8f0f9692e56750aEFB5f6cB5516E90570" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">one wallet</a>, but was fooled into sending the USDT to a <a href="https://etherscan.io/address/0xa7Bf48749D2E4aA29e3209879956b9bAa9E90570" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">phishing address</a> that began and ended with the same set of characters.</p>
<p>Days earlier, the victim had received 10 million USDT from Binance, and had sent those funds to the desired alternative address. However, at the time of that transfer, the scammer <a href="https://etherscan.io/tx/0x1d1577cfd4a45c5bfbc98991acdbc93e2c53be511968fc4908a9284da92125cf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">conducted</a> a zero-value token transfer from the victim’s address to their phishing address.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PeckShieldAlert?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#PeckShieldAlert</a> A <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/ZeroTransfer?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#ZeroTransfer</a> scammer grabbed 20M <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$USDT</a> from 0x4071&#8230;9Cbc.<br />Intended Address: 0xa7B4BAC8f0f9692e56750aEFB5f6cB5516E90570<br />Phishing Address: 0xa7Bf48749D2E4aA29e3209879956b9bAa9E90570<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tether?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#Tether</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24USDT&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">$USDT</a> has already added the scammer&#39;s address 0xa7bf&#8230;0570 to the… <a href="https://t.co/Y0APPTxIrT" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/Y0APPTxIrT</a></p>
<p>&mdash; PeckShieldAlert (@PeckShieldAlert) <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1686278380306731008?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">August 1, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>As <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/zero-transfer-phishing-part-1-attack-analysis" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">explained</a> by Coinbase in a February blog post, scammers started developing smart contracts in November 2022 designed to create spoofed zero-value transactions from a victim’s address to a scammer’s, the latter of which is designed to look much like one of the victim’s actual addresses.</p>
<p>Since the transfers have zero value, they do not require the approval of the victim’s private key to execute. Though this transfer itself cannot steal funds, it can fool victims into later sending real funds to the spoof address – especially if the user often relies on their transaction history to verify addresses that they can send funds to.</p>
<p>Users often don’t check every character of the address they send coins to, instead only checking the first and last characters, making them more vulnerable to such a scam.</p>
<h2>Tether’s Freeze</h2>
<p>Moments after the transfer, Tether <a href="https://twitter.com/PeckShieldAlert/status/1686278380306731008" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">froze</a> the USDT held at the scammer’s address by adding the address to its blacklist.</p>
<p>On-chain sleuth ZachXBT, who has investigated and <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/canadian-phishing-scammer-exposed-for-stealing-over-1-million-in-crypto-and-nfts/" data-wpel-link="internal">exposed</a> numerous phishing scams in the past, found the speed of the company’s response unusual. “Curious who this would be if it was blacklisted within ~1hr,” he tweeted on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Twitter user 0xG00gly also expressed confusion, saying they “couldn&#8217;t remember a single precedent like this where Tether would have acted so quickly.” ZachXBT suggested the transfer might be related to an OTC transaction.</p>
<p>Rival stablecoin issuer Circle has previously frozen transactions connected to the Ethereum privacy mixer Tornado Cash, at the request of the U.S. Treasury Department. Tether did not <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-hasnt-sanctioned-tornado-cash-transfers-unlike-usdc/" data-wpel-link="internal">follow through</a> on a similar freeze.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-freezes-20-million-linked-to-phishing-scammer/" rel="nofollow">Tether Freezes $20 Million Linked To Phishing Scammer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Slow Recovery for DeFi Tokens on Positive Crypto Industry Developments: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/slow-recovery-for-defi-tokens-on-positive-crypto-industry-developments-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263545</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/defi.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Decentralized finance tokens have been steadily recovering amid more positive developments for the wider crypto industry.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It may not seem like it today, with crypto markets tanking, but DeFi assets have been steadily recovering over the past month, according to Glassnode.</p>
<p>On July 31, on-chain analytics platform Glassnode published a report on the state of DeFi tokens amid this year’s regulatory issues.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Regulatory conditions in 2023 have been a tug-of-war between positive and negative news, with altcoins and DeFi tokens being the most heavily impacted,” it stated.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Regulatory conditions in 2023 have been a tug-of-war between positive and negative news, with altcoins and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DeFi?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#DeFi</a> tokens being the most heavily impacted.</p>
<p>With <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/MKR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#MKR</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/COMP?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#COMP</a> experiencing significant out-performance in recent weeks, we explore how we can extract information from… <a href="https://t.co/zkIzfdYbRl" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/zkIzfdYbRl</a></p>
<p>— glassnode (@glassnode) <a href="https://twitter.com/glassnode/status/1686026151481761792?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">July 31, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>DeFi Token Recovery?</h2>
<p>The report noted that several <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/stuttering-sec-chair-gary-gensler-disappointed-at-ripple-victory/" data-wpel-link="internal">positive</a> developments in the crypto asset industry have been beneficial to the DeFi sector.</p>
<blockquote><p>“The uptick in DeFi token interest has sparked the interest of market makers, who have increased liquidity in the respective pools, indicating a positive outlook for trading and price activities around these tokens.”</p></blockquote>
<p>The firm referenced its “DeFi index price,” which it claims has rallied 56% since the low set in mid-June.</p>
<p>Glassnode’s DeFi index consists of the top 8 such tokens by market cap. Furthermore, it has established an almost two-month-long uptrend relative to Ethereum, it added.</p>
<p>CoinGecko’s DeFi token <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/categories/decentralized-finance-defi" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">category</a>, which contains hundreds of DeFi tokens, has also seen an increase of 22% since mid-June.</p>
<p>It should be noted, however, that most DeFi tokens remain painfully down from their peaks, many by over 90%.</p>
<p>Glassnode said that two tokens stand out, and these are MakerDAO (MKR) and Compound Finance (COMP). Their performance “may well be closely related to new project fundamentals, rather than wider market developments,” it noted.</p>
<p>There has also been a slight upshift in DEX trading volumes for DeFi tokens, but it still remains in bear market lows, the report added.</p>
<h2>No Love for Crypto Today</h2>
<p>Crypto markets are currently in sharp free fall, with total cap dropping around $20 billion over the past couple of hours during Tuesday morning Asian trading.</p>
<p>As usual, altcoins and DeFi tokens have been hit harder than BTC and ETH.</p>
<p>DeFi tokens are all in the red at the time of writing. The largest losses are from <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/aave-stablecoin-gho-launches-to-mainnet-on-ethereum/" data-wpel-link="internal">Aave</a> (12%), Synthetix SNX (8%), <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/curve-finance-hacker-returns-5-4-million-but-crv-dumps-15/" data-wpel-link="internal">recently exploited</a> Curve DAO CRV (17%), Compound COMP (18%), and Frax Share FXS dumping 13% on the day.</p>
<p>Around $1 billion has left DeFi tokens over the past 24 hours, keeping most of them at multi-year lows. Therefore, that recovery might be slower than Glassnode has envisaged.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/slow-recovery-for-defi-tokens-on-positive-crypto-industry-developments-report/" rel="nofollow">Slow Recovery for DeFi Tokens on Positive Crypto Industry Developments: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Margot Robbie Says Bitcoin Has &#8220;Ken Energy&#8221; as Quip Appears Canonical to Barbie Film</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/margot-robbie-says-bitcoin-has-ken-energy-as-quip-appears-canonical-to-barbie-film/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Wesley Messamore]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 18:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263523</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/margot-robbie-barbie-event-seoul-070323-1-21a1fad7406b4901bb5b7628beb0c551.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/margot-robbie-barbie-event-seoul-070323-1-21a1fad7406b4901bb5b7628beb0c551.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Barbie film star Margot Robbie's nod to Bitcoin got a rise out of crypto Twitter over the weekend. But it might be more than a random mention.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ken&#8217;s job in the Barbie movie might literally be Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Influencers across the crypto sphere went wild for Robbie&#8217;s remarks last week. During a recent interview, the Australian actress (Wolf of Wall Street, Suicide Squad) said Bitcoin talk is &#8220;Big Ken Energy.&#8221;</p>
<p>Ken, of course, is Barbie&#8217;s boyfriend. The Ken doll first debuted in 1961, and Ken accompanies Barbie on her adventures in this year&#8217;s high-grossing comedic fantasy movie.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s had many jobs over the years, but some context from the 2023 Barbie film may shed light on Margot Robbie mentioning cryptocurrency in connection with Ken.</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s what Robbie told an interviewer in a celebrity panel discussion with America Ferrera next to her.</p>
<h2>Margot Robbie: Bitcoin = &#8216;Big Ken Energy&#8217;</h2>
<p>Robbie said when she would overhear her husband Tom Ackerley and producer David Heyman talking about Bitcoin, it reminded her of Ken&#8217;s character from the movie:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;When David and Tom would start talking about like Bitcoin or something like Greta and I would be like, &#8216;They&#8217;re being such Kens.&#8217; They&#8217;d talk about golf. We&#8217;re like, &#8216;Stop being Kens.'&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Barbie actress went as far as to associate Bitcoin with the acme of masculinity and attractiveness, mentioning that:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;There can also be Big Ken Energy and that&#8217;s a good thing.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That energy may refer to the type of confidence men have who are holding a pretty bag of Bitcoin or some other quality, hash-secured, store-of-value cryptocurrency. Margot Robbie may have just given the Chad meme a name update where crypto influencers gather.</p>
<p>But there might be more to the story than this recent interview. She may have been dropping another hint that Bitcoin is actually Ken&#8217;s job in the Barbie movie.</p>
<h2>Ken&#8217;s Job is &#8216;Beach,&#8217; <em>not</em> Surfer or Lifeguard</h2>
<p>While the women of Barbieland work as politicians, doctors, and lawyers in the movie, the men spend all day at the beach. What do they do there all day? &#8220;Shredding waves&#8221; is what Ken says in the film.</p>
<p>He also boasts it&#8217;s more dangerous than people think:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Shredding waves is much more dangerous than people realize.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>When Barbie answers, &#8220;You&#8217;re very brave, Ken,&#8221; the character played by Ryan Gosling replies:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Thank you, Barbie. You know, surfer is not even my job. And it is <em>not</em> life guard, which is a common misconception. Actually my job is just beach.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>That involves standing in the sand, watching the waters, and &#8220;shredding waves.&#8221; If his job isn&#8217;t literal, like surfer or lifeguard, then Ken&#8217;s job might be a metaphor. Most movies are metaphorical, after all.</p>
<p>The sand could be computers because of silicon microchips; the waters could be market capital liquidity; and shredding waves might be watching charts for trading signals.</p>
<p>Ken has had many jobs over the years, including astronaut (1963) and banker (1996). it wouldn&#8217;t be out of this world for Ken to work in Bitcoin in 2023. <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mattel-is-launching-a-hot-wheels-nft-collection-in-its-brand-new-marketplace/" data-wpel-link="internal">Mattel is</a> not shy in its support of cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>Best of all, Ryan Gosling also got to land on the moon when he portrayed Neil Armstrong in &#8220;First Man&#8221; (2018).</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/margot-robbie-says-bitcoin-has-ken-energy-as-quip-appears-canonical-to-barbie-film/" rel="nofollow">Margot Robbie Says Bitcoin Has &#8220;Ken Energy&#8221; as Quip Appears Canonical to Barbie Film</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Cryptocurrency to Watch: XRP20 Presale Goes Live &#8211; Will it Pump Like the XRP Price?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-cryptocurrency-to-watch-xrp20-presale-goes-live-will-it-pump-like-the-xrp-price/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263724</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/xrp20_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Although the world of cryptocurrency is undoubtedly exciting, opportunities to be part of game-changing innovations are fleeting. However, XRP20 ($XRP20), a new ERC-20 token, has emerged as a beacon of hope for those seeking to experience the returns produced during Ripple&#8217;s ($XRP) early days. Offering cutting-edge features like deflationary burning and on-chain staking, XRP20’s recently [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Although the world of cryptocurrency is undoubtedly exciting, opportunities to be part of game-changing innovations are fleeting.</p>
<p>However, <a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-cryptocurrency-to-watch-xrp20-presale-goes-live-will-it-pump-like-the-xrp-price" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20 ($XRP20)</a>, a new ERC-20 token, has emerged as a beacon of hope for those seeking to experience the returns produced during Ripple&#8217;s ($XRP) early days.</p>
<p>Offering cutting-edge features like deflationary burning and on-chain staking, XRP20’s recently launched presale could mark the beginning of an exciting venture.</p>
<h2>XRP20’s Presale Offers Second Chance to Reignite $XRP Bull Run</h2>
<p>The launch of XRP20 marks a deliberate and exciting step toward offering a unique opportunity in the low-cap crypto space.</p>
<p>Boasting the ERC-20 standard, XRP20 taps into the legacy of the original $XRP, aiming to provide a second chance for those who missed out on the token’s meteoric rise.</p>
<p>Although it bears the same name, XRP20 is a project in its own right, unaffiliated with $XRP or Ripple Labs.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263732" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-1.jpg" alt="Picture1" width="602" height="264" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-1-300x132.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture1-1-50x22.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This brand-new token takes advantage of Ethereum’s functionalities, ensuring accessibility and ease of use for potential buyers.</p>
<p>However, what truly sets XRP20 apart is its vision to reignite the passion that surrounded $XRP’s rise through the launch of an appealing presale phase.</p>
<p>This presale, now live, allows early investors to purchase $XRP20 tokens for just $0.000092, 30 times cheaper than $XRP’s all-time low.</p>
<p>Early investors can use $ETH or $USDT to purchase tokens; although with the soft cap set at just $1.85 million, there’s a high chance the presale concludes in record time.</p>
<h2>XRP20’s Unique Tokenomics Boost Scarcity &amp; Stability</h2>
<p>Importantly, <a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-cryptocurrency-to-watch-xrp20-presale-goes-live-will-it-pump-like-the-xrp-price" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20</a> isn’t just a copycat of its predecessor; it has its own unique features that set the stage for prosperous growth.</p>
<p>With a total supply of 100 billion tokens, $XRP20’s distribution is carefully crafted to foster longevity and reward participation.</p>
<p>The ongoing presale will receive 40% of the total supply, underscoring the importance of early investment, while another 40% is dedicated to the project’s staking pool.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263731" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-1.jpg" alt="Picture2" width="602" height="219" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-1-300x109.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture2-1-50x18.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>This staking utility is crucial since it allows holders to earn passive income by locking up their tokens.</p>
<p>Furthermore, $XRP20 will feature a deflationary structure that includes a 0.1% burning rate applied to all buying and selling transactions.</p>
<p>With a compelling tokenomics design, XRP20 offers a prime opportunity for investors looking to tap into a project with tangible long-term prospects.</p>
<h2>Project Roadmap Presents Plans to Drive $XRP20 Price Growth</h2>
<p><a href="https://xrp20coin.com/en#roadmap" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20’s roadmap</a> lays out future plans that seek to promote value growth and community engagement.</p>
<p>Following the presale, XRP20’s team plans to conduct pre-launch marketing and burn activation, with the latter designed to enhance the token’s scarcity before its open market debut.</p>
<p>$XRP20 will then be launched on a decentralized exchange (DEX), democratizing access to the token and boosting its market presence.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-263730" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-1.jpg" alt="Picture3" width="602" height="236" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-1.jpg 602w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-1-300x118.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Picture3-1-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 602px) 100vw, 602px" /></a></p>
<p>Subsequently, XRP20&#8217;s team will commence post-launch community staking to further reward and engage the project&#8217;s community.</p>
<p>This compelling roadmap has already caught the interest of many crypto investors, with the <a href="https://t.me/XRP20_coin" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">XRP20 Telegram channel</a> seeing impressive early growth.</p>
<p>Overall, with the presale phase offering an attractive entry point, coupled with XRP20’s vision for the future, the token is already positioning itself as an excellent investment opportunity for those looking to explore new projects.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_b791c467.cryptopotato.care/?referrer=new-cryptocurrency-to-watch-xrp20-presale-goes-live-will-it-pump-like-the-xrp-price" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit XRP20 Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, it’s written by a third party. CryptoPotato doesn’t endorse or assume responsibility for the content, advertising, products, quality, accuracy, or other materials on this page. Nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully before engaging with any company mentioned and do their own research. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above-sponsored content.</em></p>
<p>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-cryptocurrency-to-watch-xrp20-presale-goes-live-will-it-pump-like-the-xrp-price/" rel="nofollow">New Cryptocurrency to Watch: XRP20 Presale Goes Live &#8211; Will it Pump Like the XRP Price?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Will Trigger Crypto’s Mass Adoption Next Years: Animoca Brands’ Yat Siu</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/this-will-trigger-cryptos-mass-adoption-next-years-anomicas-yat-siu/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 17:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Editorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interviews]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web 3]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=262870</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[What will cause crypto's next big boom? Are NFTs and blockchain gaming dead? A close-up with Animoca Brand's co-founder Yat Siu.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency industry is rapidly changing. There&#8217;s no doubt about it. From a field reserved only for cypherpunks and heavily tech-oriented people to a global phenomenon that&#8217;s now ventured into the mainstream, blockchain is no longer a topic that&#8217;s raising as many eyebrows as it used to, and Web3 became mainstream in talks.</p>
<p>Those who&#8217;ve been following the latest gaming and NFT developments have surely heard of Animoca Brands: one of the most prominent gaming studios and VC, boasting a tremendous investment portfolio, including names like The Sandbox, Axie Infinity, Atari, Alien Worlds, Aurory, and many more.</p>
<p>Animoca Brands has been one of the driving forces of the blockchain gaming niche &#8211; a use case touted by many as the most prolific and powerful when it comes to implementing the technology.</p>
<p>During EthCC 2023, <em>CryptoPotato </em>sat down with Yat Siu &#8211; Animoca Brands&#8217; co-founder and executive chairman. In an eye-opening interview, he shared his thoughts on the latest rise in popularity of crypto in Asian countries, or even a China 2.0 wave (“they see an opportunity to break away from the US”), why he is sure that there will be a second wave of NFTs and why Ripple’s win over the SEC is a breakthrough for the industry, where the next big trend will come from and when.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-262888" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu.jpg" alt="animoca_brands_yat_siu" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/animoca_brands_yat_siu-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<p><strong>What made you believe in the emerging blockchain industry, and when did you first hear about Bitcoin?</strong></p>
<p>I heard about Bitcoin over 10 years ago, but my interest in it wasn&#8217;t really that big. I experimented. It was more intellectual interest.</p>
<p>What really got me into crypto was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-nft/" data-wpel-link="internal">non-fungible tokens (NFTs),</a> which are basically CryptoKitties in 2017. One of our subsidiaries was based in Vancouver, and it was involved in building CryptoKitties. And the co-founder of that business ended up becoming a co-founder of Dapper Labs, and we became investors in that business.</p>
<p>Since you&#8217;re talking about Bitcoin, I find that the conversation that happened with CryptoKitties back in 2017 is very similar to NFTs, with the ERC-721 standard being very similar to what we&#8217;re seeing today with Ordinals and Inscriptions.</p>
<blockquote><p>It almost feels like history repeating itself.</p></blockquote>
<p>What really excited us wasn&#8217;t so much about the financial aspect of it; although that&#8217;s a key component, it&#8217;s the cultural aspect. The fact that we can now actually own, basically, stores of digital culture through NFTs. Because we had a gaming background, it meant a lot to us because, as a gamer, you wanted to keep your virtual identities, you wanted to keep your weapons or your assets or things, and things that evolved you as a character in the game.</p>
<p>We embarked on this vision. And in the last five years, we have made over 450 investments in anything related to NFTs and Web3.</p>
<p><strong>You&#8217;re based in Hong Kong. China has had a love-hate relationship with crypto. How do you view the recent developments in Hong Kong&#8217;s opening to crypto? In your EthCC 6 speech, you mentioned that Asian countries are pushing Web3 because they see an opportunity to break away from the US. Do you believe there are other reasons?</strong></p>
<p>China&#8217;s always had a love relationship with blockchain, to be precise. It is a love-hate relationship with crypto for a couple of reasons. First of all, there&#8217;s obviously a whole currency matter, but I think the bigger issue that China had with crypto, and particularly with Bitcoin, was mining.</p>
<blockquote><p>Because when you think about what&#8217;s important for China, it&#8217;s about energy safety. And it wasn&#8217;t very helpful that people were basically mining Bitcoin, right?</p></blockquote>
<p>That was perhaps the bigger reason why there was a crackdown on mining in China. But separately speaking, blockchain technology, they&#8217;re very excited about. And when you think about the role of Hong Kong, Hong Kong has always been the financial intermediary of China. It&#8217;s always been the way in which money flows in and out of China, for foreign direct investment, for investments outside, and so forth.</p>
<p>I think when it comes to digital assets, as in crypto, it&#8217;s exactly the same. As I was talking in my ETHCC speech, it&#8217;s not a coincidence, I think, that Hong Kong was opening up to Web3 and crypto and blockchain, and then China was talking about it and releasing their own Web3 strategy paper around that. To me, they&#8217;re all interrelated and tied, but they&#8217;re one; they&#8217;re connected to each other. Meaning that you do not expect, for instance, that in the short term, you can buy crypto directly in China, but you can do it through Hong Kong, for instance. I think that could be a potential path,</p>
<blockquote><p>but I don&#8217;t think China is going to allow the trading of crypto inside China.</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Speaking on the US falling behind in Web3 and metaverse, as well as if that may change following the upcoming presidential elections.</strong></p>
<p>There&#8217;s so much activity about metaverse, about Web3. They&#8217;re all trying to push it and try to become leaders in this space. And this might be perhaps the first time in a while that the US might possibly find behind in the short term.</p>
<p>&#8230; everyone is looking at the elections, and I think there&#8217;s some truth to the fact that they might provide hope because regardless of who wins, then it&#8217;s about policymaking rather than about politics per se.</p>
<p>But the Ripple case to me is really interesting because it makes the very first distinction that just one token is one per use case. A token can be viewed as nuanced. If the token is used this way, it&#8217;s security. If a token is used another way, it&#8217;s a utility. In other words, context matters.</p>
<blockquote><p>I think the recent ruling by the judge has given new energy to the US, regardless of where the regulator wants it to go.</p></blockquote>
<p>I think post-ripple, everyone who was scared of doing something with tokens is now like, &#8220;maybe that&#8217;s the cost of doing business. We take some risk, but it&#8217;s an acceptable risk as opposed to before when it was unacceptable.&#8221; I&#8217;m quite hopeful about that.</p>
<p><strong>The gamify industry still seems very active in Japan despite the fact that we&#8217;re in a bear market, while here in the West, it seems like it&#8217;s relatively low. Do you agree with this observation? How does Animoca view this, and where is the current geo focus of Animoca Brands?</strong></p>
<figure id="attachment_262892" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-262892" style="width: 528px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class=" wp-image-262892" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504.jpg" alt="1643157797504" width="528" height="528" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504.jpg 800w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-300x300.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-100x100.jpg 100w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-768x768.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-239x239.jpg 239w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-50x50.jpg 50w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/1643157797504-45x45.jpg 45w" sizes="(max-width: 528px) 100vw, 528px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-262892" class="wp-caption-text">Source: LinkedIn</figcaption></figure>
<p>First of all, globally speaking, there&#8217;s still a positive trend on Web3. It comes from a small number, but there&#8217;s still growth everywhere around the world, even in the US. But that&#8217;s, again, because the numbers we&#8217;re starting from are low.</p>
<p>However, having said that, when it comes to consumer opinion, in Asia, it is very friendly. In America, it is not so friendly. In some cases, they are actually even hostile.</p>
<p>I would say that the gamers themselves, which is the majority of young people out there, are sharing their anti-capitalist views from the perspective of crypto. So, in other words, the same opinions that they have about someone who&#8217;s working in banking in New York and Wall Street are how they view people in crypto. So that means that Bitcoin, NFTs, and Bored Apes, to them it&#8217;s digital capitalism.</p>
<p>They may not articulate it in that way, but it&#8217;s the same feeling because when you look at the reactions that gamers have in America to NFTs, it is not a logical reaction. It is a very emotional reaction.</p>
<p><strong>Do you expect a comeback of NFTs? Wave two? How is it going to be different from the previous one? </strong></p>
<p>Absolutely, yes. First of all, I think we&#8217;re going to see more mass adoption. And that comes from culture &#8211; as it always does, right?</p>
<p>The pure financial nature of crypto is appealing to a subset of people who are very financially literate.</p>
<p>But the way that we bring mass adoption is through culture. Entertainment, gaming, fashion, all that kind of stuff. Things that we as humans identify with.</p>
<p>As you know, it takes several years to make a good game. Most of the games were funded in the last 12 to 18 months. Those games are going to be released in the coming 12 to 18 months. When they come out, we think we&#8217;re going to see quite a bit of mass adoption.</p>
<figure id="attachment_163270" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-163270" style="width: 1201px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-163270" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover.jpg" alt="bayc_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bayc_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-163270" class="wp-caption-text">Will The Board Ape Yacht Club Make a Comeback?</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>For entrepreneurs who’re reading this, what are the main criteria you would look for in a project before investing?</strong></p>
<p>First, assume the team is technical, they know their background, and so on. And obviously, product-market fit is always an important one, but in this space, sometimes it&#8217;s hard to know. What I find so exciting about Web3 is that product-market fit can sometimes be something we never thought fit, right?</p>
<p>Because it&#8217;s a new industry. If you think about virtual employment, that&#8217;s not something that people would&#8217;ve thought about as a natural thing. If you thought about <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-play-to-earn/" data-wpel-link="internal">Play-to-Earn</a> or if you thought about digital collectibles, these are all concepts that, five years ago, didn&#8217;t have product market fit.</p>
<blockquote><p>We look for founders who are driven by purpose.[&#8230;] The Web3 investment style is more about shared success. How does what I built to end up creating benefits for the broader ecosystem as a whole?</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Animoca Brands has grown exponentially and become one of the major players in the gaming industry. What, in your opinion, sets Animoca Brands apart from others? What would you say are the key turning points for your company? </strong></p>
<p>I would say the key turning points for Animoca Brands &#8211; obviously our embrace on Web3, but more importantly &#8211; the conviction that what we’re building is of critical importance to the industry broadly.</p>
<p>So even though people say that we’re a gaming company because we made lots of gaming investments (we made over 140 gaming investments, and we are obviously involved with some of the biggest Web3 gaming projects), the purpose of what we’re building, which is digital property rights, and the mission to essentially create the Web3 ecosystem, which is all about what we consider stakeholder capitalism, in which every customer becomes an owner, that’s the broader mission.</p>
<p><strong>What excites you and Animoca Brands?</strong></p>
<p>Outside of the gaming field, I would say one area that we have been looking at is education.</p>
<p>Education today is a $5 trillion market, and almost nobody in crypto is looking at education.</p>
<p><strong>Where will the next big trend come from?</strong></p>
<p>I don&#8217;t think that NFTs are done yet, because they are like the homepage. In other words, everything will have NFTs. Everything will need NFTs in one form or another. To me, it&#8217;s a little bit going to be more like the usage of NFTs will drive mass adoption.</p>
<blockquote><p>The mass onboarding&#8230; it hasn&#8217;t even started yet.</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-will-trigger-cryptos-mass-adoption-next-years-anomicas-yat-siu/" rel="nofollow">This Will Trigger Crypto’s Mass Adoption Next Years: Animoca Brands’ Yat Siu</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Presidential Candidate Ron DeSantis to End Biden&#8217;s &#8216;War on Bitcoin&#8217; if Elected</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-ron-desantis-to-end-bidens-war-on-bitcoin-if-elected/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CBDC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Biden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=263575</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ron_DeSantis.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Ron_DeSantis.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[DeSantis said his eventual administration will not push the brakes on American investors willing to deal with cryptocurrencies. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ron DeSantis &#8211; Governor of Florida and one of the Republicans&#8217; presidential nominees &#8211; stated that the &#8220;war on Bitcoin and cryptocurrency&#8221; that Biden&#8217;s administration has supposedly waged will cease should he become the next political leader of the United States. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also reiterated his hostile stance toward central bank digital currencies, saying such a financial product will not see the light of day if he gets elected.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">DeSantis&#8217; Pro-Bitcoin Promise</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US presidential candidate recently </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/therecount/status/1686049738129653760?s=46" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">presented</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> his economic policy during a campaign event in New Hampshire, paying particular attention to Bitcoin and the digital asset sector.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He vowed that his eventual cabinet will enable Americans to invest in the primary cryptocurrency and the alternative coins. DeSantis also promised to end Joe Biden&#8217;s so-called &#8220;war on Bitcoin&#8221; should he become the 47th President of the States:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Biden&#8217;s war on Bitcoin and cryptocurrency will come to an end when I become President.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_263586" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-263586" style="width: 533px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-263586" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business.webp" alt="Ron DeSantis" width="533" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business.webp 1136w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business-300x225.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business-1024x768.webp 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business-768x576.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Business-50x38.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 533px) 100vw, 533px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-263586" class="wp-caption-text">Ron DeSantis, Source: Business Insider</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">This is not the first time DeSantis has criticized Biden&#8217;s cabinet for its approach to the industry. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://fortune.com/crypto/2023/05/25/ron-desantis-goes-crypto-says-the-biden-administration-will-kill-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claimed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in May that every person has the right &#8220;to do Bitcoin,&#8221; saying the only reason Washington does not support the sector is because they can not control it. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;I think that the current regime, clearly, they have it out for Bitcoin, and if it continues for another four years, you know, they&#8217;ll probably end up killing it,&#8221; he added.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Aside from being a Bitcoin advocate, the Governor is a keen opponent of a CBDC. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/no-cbdc-in-florida-says-governor-ron-desantis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">blasted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the monetary product as a tool for surveillance in March this year, proposing legislation in Florida that could oppose its possible launch in the southern state.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He doubled down on his view during his most recent speech, asserting that throwing CBDC into the &#8220;trash can&#8221; will be among his first duties as President.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Not the Only BTC Fan Within the Candidates</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Robert F. Kennedy Jr. &#8211; nephew of former President John F. Kennedy &#8211; is another presidential nominee who has voiced his support toward the cryptocurrency industry, more specifically, Bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The candidate of the Democratic party, who is a HODLer and has purchased 14 BTC for his seven children, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-to-back-the-us-dollar-with-bitcoin-if-elected/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">promised</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> to strengthen the American dollar by backing it with &#8220;real finite assets,&#8221; such as bitcoin and certain precious metals. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;My plan would be to start very, very small: perhaps 1% of issued T-bills would be backed by hard currency: by gold, silver, platinum, or bitcoin, and then depending on the outcome, we would increase that annually,&#8221; he explained.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Miami&#8217;s mayor &#8211; Francis Suarez &#8211; also has a chance to become America&#8217;s new President. He is an outspoken proponent of Bitcoin, introducing numerous initiatives in the city focused on it. Similar to Kennedy, Suarez is a BTC holder and even </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/miamis-mayor-to-become-the-first-us-politician-to-take-his-salary-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">became</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the first US politician to receive his salary in a digital asset instead of fiat. </span></p>
<p><em>Featured Image Courtesy of CNA</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-presidential-candidate-ron-desantis-to-end-bidens-war-on-bitcoin-if-elected/" rel="nofollow">US Presidential Candidate Ron DeSantis to End Biden&#8217;s &#8216;War on Bitcoin&#8217; if Elected</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
