<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:47:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>DeFi Protocol TiTi Plans to Launch its Ethereum Mainnet in the Upcoming Weeks</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-titi-plans-to-launch-its-ethereum-mainnet-in-the-upcoming-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Press Release]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 04:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249853</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TiTi.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/TiTi.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer] TiTi Protocol announced that it will launch the Ethereum mainnet in the next few weeks and plans to start IDO and 2nd round airdrops. TiTi Protocol plans to start IDO on May 10, and users can visit https://ido.titi.finance to participate in IDO. IDO participating users will receive exclusive NFT [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Please Read Disclaimer]</strong></p>
<p>TiTi Protocol announced that it will launch the Ethereum mainnet in the next few weeks and plans to start IDO and 2nd round airdrops. TiTi Protocol plans to start IDO on May 10, and users can visit <a href="https://ido.titi.finance" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">https://ido.titi.finance</a> to participate in IDO. IDO participating users will receive exclusive NFT and will be eligible for airdrops and other benefits in the future.</p>
<h2>What is TiTi Protocol？</h2>
<p><a href="https://twitter.com/TiTiProtocol/status/1655524820250152962?s=20" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">TiTi Protocol</a> is a fully collateralized, multi-asset reserve, bankrun resistant, use-to-earn decentralized stablecoin. With its new paradigm, TiTi Protocol becomes the first stablecoin that adopts &#8220;Use-to-Earn&#8221; and prevents bank-run inherently. TiUSD is the stablecoin issued by the TiTi protocol, whileTiTi is the protocol&#8217;s governance token.</p>
<p>Previously, TiTi Protocol announced in April 2022 that it had completed a financing of US$3.5 million led by The Spartan Group, with participation from SevenX Ventures, Incuba Alpha, DeFi Alliance, Agnostic Fund, Fourth Revolution Capital (4RCapital), Solidity Venture, and other institutions, as well as other individual investors including 0xb1 (Fold Finance), Tascha and Nipun (Alpha Venture DAO), and Michael (Fantom).</p>
<p>In addition, TiTi Protocol has completed a 3-rounds smart contract Audit by Slowmist, Hacken and Peckshield.</p>
<h2>TiTi Protocol Mainnet &amp; Airdrop &amp; IDO</h2>
<p>TiTi Protocol will launch on the Ethereum mainnet in the next few weeks. Users can use and trade TiUSD to passively or actively earn protocol fees.</p>
<p>After the TiTi mainnet goes live, TiTi Protocol will inject a large amount of TiTi into the mainnet. Users can earn TiTi through yield farming, especially the original unilateral liquidity MMF function created by TiTi Protocol. Users only need to provide unilateral liquidity to earn TiTi. It&#8217;s free of risk and with a rather profitable APY! And in order to give back to early users, early TiTi rewards are very generous!</p>
<p>TiTi Protocol just completed the first round of airdrops a few weeks ago, and plans to start the second round of airdrops after the mainnet goes live.</p>
<p>In addition, TiTi Protocol will kick off IDO on May 10. This IDO provides a total of 10,000,000 TiTi tokens at a price of $0.06.</p>
<h2>About TiTi Protocol</h2>
<p>TiTi Protocol is a decentralized, 100% collateral-backed, crypto-native stablecoin, aiming to provide diversified and decentralized financial services based on the crypto-native stablecoin system and autonomous monetary policy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-titi-plans-to-launch-its-ethereum-mainnet-in-the-upcoming-weeks/" rel="nofollow">DeFi Protocol TiTi Plans to Launch its Ethereum Mainnet in the Upcoming Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fired Coinbase Exec Caught With Insider Trading Sentenced to 2 Years in Prison</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/fired-coinbase-exec-caught-with-insider-trading-sentenced-to-2-years-in-prison/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 00:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249910</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/coinbase_legal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/coinbase_legal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase’s former Product Manager Ishan Wahi will serve a sentence more than twice as long as his brother and co-conspirator, Nikhil Wahi. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After pleading guilty earlier this year, former Coinbase Product Manager Ishan Wahi has been sentenced to 2 years in prison in a landmark case for insider trading with cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The sentence exceeds the 10-month prison sentence of Ishan’s brother – Nikhil Wahi – with whom he conspired for the crime. </span></p>
<h2>Two Years for Crypto Insider Trading</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to a report from </span><a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/coinbase-ex-manager-sentenced-2-years-prison-us-insider-trading-case-2023-05-09/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Reuters</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Ishan Wahi was sentenced by U.S. District Judge Loretta Preska in a Manhattan Federal court on Tuesday. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The sentence follows a guilty plea from Wahi back in February to two counts of conspiracy to commit wire fraud. Preska stated that his scheme was a “massive abuse” of Coinbase’s trust – America’s largest cryptocurrency exchange which has been subject to a plethora of customer and government-launched lawsuits over the past year. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Wahi was arrested and charged by the Department of Justice last July for having tipped his brother – alongside his friend Sameer Ramani – with information about upcoming coin listings at Coinbase that had not yet been made public. Analysis has shown that listings on large crypto exchanges often have a </span><a href="https://medium.com/coinmonks/analysis-a-binance-listing-adds-41-on-crypto-prices-2f6cd72e8dff#:~:text=In%20most%20cases%2C%20a%20Binance,varies%20from%20project%20to%20project." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">dramatic effect</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on an asset’s price </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The group’s scheme netted them roughly $1.5 million in total across 55 different token announcements between June 2021 and April 2022, according to prosecutors. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Assistant U.S. Attorney Noah Solowiejczyk said during the hearing that the ten months of consistent tips demonstrated that Wahi’s actions were “not a one-off mistake.” Meanwhile, Judge Preska added that Wahi and the co-defendants’ attempts at covering their actions proved that they knew what they were doing was wrong. </span></p>
<h2>A “Huge Mistake”</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“I made a huge mistake that will follow me for the rest of my life,&#8221; Wahi said. His comment echoed that of his brother Nikhil from back in January, who said his mistake was “something that I will have to live with forever,” after </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/brother-of-former-coinbase-manager-sentenced-to-10-months-in-prison/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pleading guilty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to his respective charges. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ishan Wahi initially </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ex-coinbase-executive-pleads-not-guilty-to-insider-trading-case-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">pled not guilty</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to wire fraud charges shortly after they were announced, but eventually followed his brother’s lead with a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/former-coinbase-exec-pleads-guilty-to-insider-trading-report/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">guilty plea</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> in February. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Wahi requested a sentence no longer than his brother’s within court papers, citing other insider trading cases where lawbreakers were little prison time. On the other hand, prosecutors called for Wahi to receive 3 years in prison to set an example for other crypto exchange insiders misusing their privileged information. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">OpenSea’s Head of Product was similarly charged with NFT Insider Trading in June – but the ex-employee has since </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/openseas-former-head-of-product-files-motion-to-drop-insider-trading-charges/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">filed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to have those charges dropped. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/fired-coinbase-exec-caught-with-insider-trading-sentenced-to-2-years-in-prison/" rel="nofollow">Fired Coinbase Exec Caught With Insider Trading Sentenced to 2 Years in Prison</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Calls for Revision on &#8216;Misguided&#8217; RIA Rulemaking</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-calls-for-revision-on-misguided-ria-rulemaking/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249812</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Coinbase.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Coinbase's Paul Grewal has criticized SEC's RIA custody rule for unfairly singling out crypto.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase has called for certain modifications to the proposed rule regarding registered investment advisers&#8217; (RIA) obligations to hold client assets at qualified custodians.</p>
<p>Even as the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) deemed Coinbase Custody as a &#8220;qualified custodian,&#8221; the crypto exchange believes the revised RIA rule makes &#8220;unwarranted assumptions about custodial practice.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Revisions Needed</h2>
<p>The chief legal officer of the San Francisco-based company, Paul Grewal, believes the proposal titled &#8216;Safeguarding Advisory Client Assets, Proposed Rule 223-1&#8217; is &#8220;misguided.&#8221;</p>
<p>In a new letter to the securities watchdog, Grewal highlighted the need to make several revisions. He also said that certain assumptions made on the proposal are unnecessary and inappropriate and could prove &#8220;detrimental&#8221; to consumer protection for various asset classes, including crypto, &#8220;whether or not they are securities.&#8221;</p>
<p>The <a href="https://assets.ctfassets.net/c5bd0wqjc7v0/2fyFy6G9j96hN6putNvZMQ/9118ca626f70bef899c25922d04d3c24/QC_Proposal_Comment_Letter_-_Submission_Version.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">letter</a> advocated that the SEC should continue to define state trust companies and other state-regulated financial institutions as &#8220;qualified custodians.&#8221; Grewal also proposes enabling limited exposure to non-qualified custodians and withdrawing the ban on RIA client trades on crypto exchanges, which are not qualified custodians.</p>
<p>The exec further pointed out that &#8220;the SEC&#8217;s rule should tailor standards of care by asset class and client type&#8221; while simultaneously allowing sophisticated clients to negotiate their own contracts.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We appreciate the chance to weigh in and we look forward to engaging with the SEC to get this right – public rulemaking is a critical step in bringing further clarity to the market.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Coinbase vs SEC: Regulatory Tussle</h2>
<p>Coinbase has been under <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-ordered-10-days-to-file-response-to-coinbases-petition/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">tremendous</a> regulatory scrutiny in the country lately. The SEC had also served the crypto exchange with a Wells Notice officially bringing an enforcement action against the exchange. While the company&#8217;s CEO, Brian Armstrong, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-is-100-committed-to-the-us-despite-regulatory-uncertainty-brian-armstrong/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">confirmed</a> that there are no plans to relocate overseas, he also stressed that Europe has been &#8220;incredibly welcoming&#8221; on the regulatory front.</p>
<p>With the US failing to deliver regulatory clarity, Coinbase has ramped up international expansion. It recently <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-officially-launches-platform-for-non-us-institutional-investors-in-bermuda-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">launched</a> Coinbase International Exchange, a Bermuda-based crypto derivatives platform for non-US institutional clients.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-calls-for-revision-on-misguided-ria-rulemaking/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Calls for Revision on &#8216;Misguided&#8217; RIA Rulemaking</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>NBA Icon Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Describes his FTX Summons as &#8216;Inadequate,&#8217; Seeks Dismisal (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/nba-icon-shaquille-oneal-describes-his-ftx-summons-as-inadequate-seeks-dismisal-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 21:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249743</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Shaq1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Shaq1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[O'Neal's lawyers supposedly said the official notice was "tossed" at his moving car and not served at his home.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The lawyers of the American basketball legend &#8211; Shaquille O&#8217;Neal &#8211; reportedly asked a federal court to block a recent summons served regarding his interaction with FTX. They claimed the documents were &#8220;tossed&#8221; at the front of his moving car: an entirely different version than the one presented by attorney Adam M. Moskowitz who supposedly served the sportsman in his home.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Failed investors have claimed that O&#8217;Neal and many other celebrities used their popularity to promote the now-bankrupt exchange, triggering severe losses to inexperienced clients. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;Inadequate&#8217; Summons or Twisting the Facts?</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/shaquille-o-neal-seeks-to-quash-ftx-suit-summons-as-inadequate-1.1917509" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by Bloomberg, the attorneys of the former NBA star argued that the papers notifying a presence in court were &#8220;tossed&#8221; at O&#8217;Neal&#8217;s moving vehicle, and eventually, they &#8220;landed&#8221; on the road. As such, they requested a dismissal of the legal process against him, labeling the summons &#8220;inadequate.&#8221;<br />
</span></p>
<figure id="attachment_249754" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249754" style="width: 711px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249754" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil.jpg" alt="Shaquille O’Neil" width="711" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil.jpg 1280w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil-300x169.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil-768x432.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Shaquille-ONeil-50x28.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 711px) 100vw, 711px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249754" class="wp-caption-text">Shaquille O’Neal, Source: CNN</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The assertion disassociates with Adam Moskowitz&#8217;s thesis. The lawyer leading the lawsuit against O&#8217;Neal <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-legend-shaquille-oneal-served-in-ftx-class-action/" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> he served the athlete at his home in mid-April. He also claimed the whole process happened in front of security cameras:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;The good news is his home video cameras recorded our service, and we have made it very clear he is not to destroy and/or erase any of these security tapes because they must be preserved for our lawsuit.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The class-action lawsuit does not include only the basketball legend. Failed investors at FTX also blamed Tom Brady, Naomi Osaka, Steph Curry, and many other celebrities for endorsing the once-prominent crypto giant, thus prompting investor losses when the platform <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">crashed</a>. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">O&#8217;Neal has previously </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/12/15/shaq-on-crypto-ftx-post-collapse-i-was-just-a-paid-spokesperson.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">asserted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> he does not believe in crypto and engaged with FTX only because the firm paid him to participate in an advert:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;A lot of people think I&#8217;m involved, but I was just a paid spokesperson for a commercial.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Situation With Steph Curry and Tom Brady </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Stephen Curry &#8211; one of the current NBA stars &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/basketball-superstar-stephen-curry-joins-ftx-as-ambassador-and-shareholder/" data-wpel-link="internal">inked</a> a deal with FTX in September 2021. Following the partnership, the 35-year-old American received an equity stake in the company and became its global ambassador. Like O&#8217;Neal, he starred in a commercial displaying FTX as a safe cryptocurrency platform. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Texas State Securities Board </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://basketnews.com/news-182077-stephen-curry-investigated-for-promoting-ftx.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">launched</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> an investigation against Curry to determine the impact of his actions on unfortunate investors.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Arguably the greatest NFL athlete &#8211; Tom Brady &#8211; has also been deeply involved with the former crypto behemoth. Besides serving as a brand ambassador of the exchange, he </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-the-amount-of-ftx-shares-tom-brady-and-gisele-bundchen-will-probably-lose/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">owns</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> over 1.1 million common shares of FTX. His ex-spouse – Gisele Bundchen – has 686,761 stocks. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/nba-icon-shaquille-oneal-describes-his-ftx-summons-as-inadequate-seeks-dismisal-report/" rel="nofollow">NBA Icon Shaquille O&#8217;Neal Describes his FTX Summons as &#8216;Inadequate,&#8217; Seeks Dismisal (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paxful Reopens a Month After Suspending Marketplace</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/paxful-reopens-a-month-after-suspending-marketplace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Anthonia Isichei]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 18:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249715</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/greenlight_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/greenlight_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After closing shop amid regulatory hurdles and internal conflict, the Paxful markerplace is back to serving its customers.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Popular peer-to-peer (P2P) marketplace Paxful is back online after shutting down services in April 2023.</p>
<p dir="ltr">While the platform was suspended, the Paxful Wallet remained active.</p>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">Paxful, in a <a href="https://paxful.com/sign-up-transition" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">blog post</a> on May 8, announced the resumption of the marketplace a month after the platform closed down. An excerpt from the announcement reads:</li>
</ul>
<blockquote>
<p dir="ltr">&#8220;We know it has been a difficult time for many of our users, who were understandably surprised by the sudden suspension, however, we are delighted to be back so that we can continue to serve millions of people without financial access.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<ul>
<li dir="ltr">As previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxful-p2p-marketplace-closes-down-amid-multiple-executive-departures/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> by <em>CryptoPotato</em>, the Bitcoin P2P marketplace shut down in April 2023 while the wallet remained operational. Before the platform&#8217;s troubles came to light, Paxful was one of the most prominent P2P marketplaces in the industry, with over six million users globally.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Meanwhile, Paxful co-founder and former CEO Ray Youssef mentioned regulatory hurdles for the P2P market as part of the reason for the marketplace shutdown.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Youssef also cited key staff departures, adding that a legal tussle between him and another co-founder Artur Schaback further contributed to the forced closed down of the company. Youssef described Schaback&#8217;s litigation as &#8220;nasty,&#8221; stating that the executive sued both the former CEO and the company because he was upset.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Shortly after Paxful&#8217;s suspension, Youssef said he was working towards <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxful-co-founder-will-repay-users-with-his-own-money-doesnt-wanna-go-to-jail/" data-wpel-link="internal">refunding</a> customers from his pocket to avoid jail time.</li>
<li dir="ltr">Before the revival of the marketplace, Paxful was able to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxful-co-founder-says-88-of-customer-accounts-have-been-unfrozen/" data-wpel-link="internal">unfreeze</a> 88% of customers&#8217; accounts, leaving 3% still frozen.</li>
<li dir="ltr">On April 18, the CEO announced his <a href="https://twitter.com/raypaxful/status/1648283151410577409?t=z_golYXYeHaJcX7wLAndfQ&amp;s=19" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">resignation</a> from the top position.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paxful-reopens-a-month-after-suspending-marketplace/" rel="nofollow">Paxful Reopens a Month After Suspending Marketplace</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mike Novogratz&#8217; Galaxy Digital Turns Profitable in Q1 2023: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/mike-novogratz-galaxy-digital-turns-profitable-in-q1-2023-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Novogratz]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249861</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/galaxy_digital_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/galaxy_digital_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The company recorded $288 million losses in the previous quarter, amid a series of industry scandals and bankruptcies in addition to severe market slump.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Galaxy Digital turned profitable in the first quarter of the year as the markets improved. Its founder and CEO, Michael Novogratz, revealed that the crypto financial services firm ended Q1 2023 with a liquidity position of $814 million.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to an official <a href="https://www.newswire.ca/news-releases/galaxy-announces-first-quarter-2023-financial-results-882794769.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">press release</a>, Galaxy Digital reported $134 million in net income for the same period as compared to a net loss of $288 million in the fourth quarter of 2022. The income was attributed to the gains on digital assets as well as unrealized gains on investments.</li>
<li>The company&#8217;s asset management division &#8211; Galaxy Digital Asset Management (GAM) &#8211; registered assets under management of $2.4 billion, representing an increase of 40% from the previous quarter.</li>
<li>On the mining front as well, Galaxy Digital Infrastructure Solutions (GDIS) concluded the quarter with nearly 3.0 exahash per second in Hashrate Under Management (HUM), surging by more than 100% increase QoQ.</li>
<li>Commenting on the first quarter earnings call, Novogratz said,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Galaxy&#8217;s globally diversified platform and longstanding commitment to promoting the responsible adoption of digital assets is resonating with clients more than ever before. Our first quarter 2023 results are a validation of the investments we have made in our business to drive long-term growth and lead the evolution of the digital asset industry.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The New York-based company had been posting negative quarterly revenues since the end of 2021. With the subsequent crypto price slump, Galaxy Digital resorted to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/michael-novogratzs-galaxy-digital-plans-to-reduce-headcount-by-20-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">slashing</a> its headcount by 20%.</li>
<li>Its losses were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/galaxy-digital-held-77-million-in-ftx-exposure-earnings-show/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">exacerbated</a> after the FTX collapse as it held over $76 million worth of exposure to bankrupt exchange.</li>
<li>Amidst heightened regulatory scrutiny, Novogratz revealed the company&#8217;s intention to expand its operations offshore.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/mike-novogratz-galaxy-digital-turns-profitable-in-q1-2023-report/" rel="nofollow">Mike Novogratz&#8217; Galaxy Digital Turns Profitable in Q1 2023: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Ordinals Inscription Exceeds 5M After Doubling in a Week: Data</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fungible Token (NFT)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249759</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/cryptopunks_ordinalpunks_swap_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/02/cryptopunks_ordinalpunks_swap_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Ordinal inscriptions continues to skyrocket amidst network congestion concerns. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ordinal inscriptions are on fire. Users are continuously flooding the Bitcoin network with images, video games, and other content.</p>
<p>There are now more than 5 million inscriptions. Over the past seven days, the total inscription count has more than doubled from 2.5 million.</p>
<h2>Ordinals Skyrocket</h2>
<p>According to <a href="https://dune.com/dgtl_assets/bitcoin-ordinals-analysis" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">data</a> from Dune Analytics, text-based inscriptions, also known as the BRC-20 token standard, accounted for a vast majority of the Bitcoin ordinal inscription. At the time of writing, its dominance was at 86.52%. Image-based inscriptions, on the other hand, had a relatively smaller footprint of 9.5%</p>
<p>The total market cap of BRC-20 tokens was <a href="https://brc-20.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">recorded</a> to be $690 million at the time of writing. Currently, there are a total of 14,200 new tokens hosted on the Bitcoin blockchain. Riding on the hype of PEPE, even a Bitcoin-based version of the meme coin made it to the 3rd rank in terms of market cap. The first two positions were held by Bitcoin-based tokens called &#8220;ordi,&#8221; and &#8220;nals.&#8221;</p>
<p><span style="font-size: 16px; font-weight: 400;">Ordinal Inscriptions are digital assets, similar to NFTs, inscribed on a satoshi in the Bitcoin network, a process that was made possible due to the Taproot</span><span style="font-size: 16px; font-weight: 400;"> activation in 2021. Its introduction has created another use case for the network beyond mere transfers of value. </span></p>
<p>This week, Binance unveiled <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-support-bitcoin-ordinals-in-its-ntf-marketplace/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">plans</a> to add support for Bitcoin Ordinals in its NFT marketplace. The crypto exchange will also be offering royalty support and additional revenue-generating opportunities for creators.</p>
<h2>Positive Side-Effect?</h2>
<p>The resurgence of the ordinals craze has prompted a spike in Bitcoin network activity, including fresh highs in transactions. However, the subsequent congestion in the network has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-75-of-daily-bitcoin-on-chain-transactions-used-taproot-data/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">sparked</a> concerns in the community.</p>
<p>The increased demand for Bitcoin&#8217;s block space resulted in the corresponding rise in transaction fees. Data from BitInfoCharts <a href="https://bitinfocharts.com/comparison/bitcoin-transactionfees.html#3y" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that the Bitcoin network’s transaction fees are skyrocketing to roughly $31, a level that was last seen in April 2021.</p>
<p>Rising transaction fees and longer confirmation wait times have made it harder to use the flagship crypto asset for small transactions. The burst of new activity, however, is being viewed as a positive side effect for the Bitcoin miners as transaction fees surpassed the regular mining subsidy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-ordinals-inscription-exceeds-5m-after-doubling-in-a-week-data/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Ordinals Inscription Exceeds 5M After Doubling in a Week: Data</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple Crashes 8.5% Weekly, Will $0.4 Hold? (XRP Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-crashes-8-5-weekly-will-0-4-hold-xrp-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249842</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After Ripple&#8217;s sudden decline, the price fell below the 100-day moving average. However, it has now reached the critical support level of the 200-day moving average at $0.41, and the bears might just be getting started. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart Following Ripple&#8217;s rejection from the $0.58 resistance level on the daily chart, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After Ripple&#8217;s sudden decline, the price fell below the 100-day moving average. However, it has now reached the critical support level of the 200-day moving average at $0.41, and the bears might just be getting started.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p><strong>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></strong></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>Following Ripple&#8217;s rejection from the $0.58 resistance level on the daily chart, the price experienced a massive decline, dropping below the 100-day moving average. However, the cryptocurrency has found substantial support at the 200-day moving average of $0.41.</p>
<p>The strength of this moving average suggests that the price may enter a consolidation phase. However, if the bears manage to push it below the 200-day moving average, this may trigger a cascade effect and bearish sentiment for Ripple&#8217;s long-term prospects.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249844" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249844" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249844 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0905231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249844" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3><strong>The 4-Hour Chart</strong></h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, Ripple&#8217;s price has formed an ascending channel. The recent rejection caused it to drop below the minor support level of $0.48 and the channel&#8217;s mid-trend line. Currently, XRP faces two crucial support levels: the primary one of $0.4 and the channel&#8217;s lower trendline, approximately at $0.37.</p>
<p>In summary, based on the recent action, the price seems more likely to remain within the range of $0.4 and $0.48 until a breakout occurs.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249845" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249845" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249845 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_0905232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249845" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-crashes-8-5-weekly-will-0-4-hold-xrp-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Ripple Crashes 8.5% Weekly, Will $0.4 Hold? (XRP Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BTC Plunges Toward $27K on Network Congestion Stress, is $25K Next? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/btc-plunges-toward-27k-on-network-congestion-stress-is-25k-next-bitcoin-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249660</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-8-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTCUSDT-Daily-May-8-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been trending to the upside since the beginning of 2023. However, it has been showing signs of a reversal recently, following a clear rejection from the $30K resistance level. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart The price has been consolidating since it failed to break above the $30K resistance level. The [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin&#8217;s price has been trending to the upside since the beginning of 2023. However, it has been showing signs of a reversal recently, following a clear rejection from the $30K resistance level.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>The price has been consolidating since it failed to break above the $30K resistance level. The 50-day moving average has been providing support but is currently getting broken to the downside around the $28K mark.</p>
<p>In the event of a valid bearish breakout, the $25K support level would be the next probable target, followed by the key 200-day moving average, which is trending around the $22K area. The RSI has also dropped below the 50% threshold recently, hinting at a potential decline in the short term as momentum is shifting bearish.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249847" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249847" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249847 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0905231" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-Daily-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249847" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour chart, it is evident that the price has been bouncing in a tight range between the $30K and $28K levels and is testing the latter at the moment. If a breakdown were to occur, a rapid plunge toward the $25K zone could be expected in the near term.</p>
<p>Even so, the RSI is approaching the oversold area, increasing the probability for the price to rebound from the $28K level and push towards the $30K resistance once more. However, all things considered, the bearish scenario seems more likely from a classical price action point of view on both the daily and the 4-hour timeframes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249848" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249848" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249848 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_0905232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/BTC-4H-1-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249848" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>Due to the rise in Bitcoin transactions on Sunday, the fees paid to miners increased significantly. This pattern is uncommon for bear markets but is frequent during bull market tops.</p>
<p>The growing use of the Taproot update, which allows for the inclusion of NFTs and the BRC-20 token on the Bitcoin blockchain, can be related to the increase in transaction fees.  While this may be a drawback for routine transactions, it is advantageous for mining earnings.</p>
<p>Furthermore, this shift has caused changes in other on-chain metrics, such as a significant increase in the number of active addresses and transactions. This could be seen as a positive sign, marking the beginning of a bull market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_249664" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-249664" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-249664 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_fees_chart_0905231" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Bitcoin-Fees-Total-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-249664" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/btc-plunges-toward-27k-on-network-congestion-stress-is-25k-next-bitcoin-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">BTC Plunges Toward $27K on Network Congestion Stress, is $25K Next? (Bitcoin Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>DSCVR Passes 200k User Milestone</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/dscvr-passes-200k-user-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Press Release]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=249829</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Untitled_design_6_1683633854AMJJEb8jS0.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/Untitled_design_6_1683633854AMJJEb8jS0.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Los Angeles, California, May 9th, 2023] Retains Crown as Web3’s Biggest Social Network and SocialFi Platform DSCVR, the largest and most popular Web3 social network and social finance (SocialFi) platform, has surpassed the 200,000 user mark – a key milestone on its journey towards making crypto functionality easily accessible to anyone who [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>[PRESS RELEASE &#8211; Los Angeles, California, May 9th, 2023]</strong></p>
<p><em>Retains Crown as Web3’s Biggest Social Network and SocialFi Platform</em></p>
<p><a href="https://dscvr.one/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DSCVR</a>, the largest and most popular Web3 social network and social finance (SocialFi) platform, has surpassed the 200,000 user mark – a key milestone on its journey towards making crypto functionality easily accessible to anyone who knows how to use social media.</p>
<p>DSCVR’s focus on coupling familiar social media experiences with the most diverse set of crypto features available in Web3 has made it an appealing choice for content creators, crypto projects, and community builders alike.</p>
<p>DSCVR is not just a social media platform, it is also an easy-to-navigate SocialFi economy. In the two years since its launch, a total of 6.7 million tokens have been transacted on the platform: a real demonstration of its users’ growing economic power.</p>
<p>A wide range of easy-to-use tools allow DSCVR’s loyal and expanding user base to create, collaborate on, share, and monetize content, to interact with the creators they admire, and to interact with – and even build – user-governed communities tailored to their interests.</p>
<p>Communities and individual creators can earn digital assets through tips, airdrops, or NFT sales. Users can then choose how to deploy these profits – by putting them back into the community, for instance, or perhaps directing them toward a cause favored by members.</p>
<p>Users, meanwhile, can show their appreciation of content they admire through tips. Users can also send and receive airdrops and transfer tokens throughout the platform – all without ever having to set up a wallet.</p>
<p>DSCVR offers all the features users find most convenient about Web2 social platforms while making Web3 functionality more accessible than ever. Value flows seamlessly through the platform in the form of tokens, which can be easily shared or transacted. Users are building tokenized communities called portals around fungible tokens, NFTs, and Web3 games. Portals give ownership to communities by granting roles and permissions based on token holding.</p>
<p>Further, DSCVR stays true to its Web3 ethos by emphasizing user ownership. With DSCVR, individuals can decide how to monetize their content, and what shows up in their feeds, and can even have a voice in the direction of the platform itself. The network also offers users a degree of financial power unheard of in Web2.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Users, creators, and communities are increasingly frustrated by mainstream social media platforms with their limitations, unexpected rule changes, and opaque power structures,” said DSCVR CEO Rick Porter.</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>Rick added: &#8220;The future of social media lies in giving power back to users. They should be able to make their own decisions about how to structure their communities, how and with whom they connect, and whether and how to monetize their content. By giving users sway over their creations and their communities, DSCVR is leading the way in this movement.”</p></blockquote>
<p>With more than 200k users, 20M posts, comments and upvotes and more than 6.7 million tokens transacted, the network&#8217;s continued growth is a testament to its potential to shape the future of social media.</p>
<p>Join the revolution with <a href="https://dscvr.one/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DSCVR</a> and be part of the future of online communities.</p>
<h2>About DSCVR</h2>
<p><a href="http://dscvr.one/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-wpel-link="external">DSCVR</a> (pronounced “Discover”) is a boundary-breaking Web3 social network that combines a familiar social media context with underlying crypto and fintech functionality. The most rapidly adopted Web3 social media network, DSCVR is also the largest.</p>
<p>By coupling the accessibility of Web2 platforms with the most diverse set of crypto features available in decentralized social media, DSCVR has become the social media and SocialFi network of choice for content creators and community builders. The platform has become a launchpad for tokenized communities where users can gate based on token ownership, configure governance, airdrop token rewards, and earn digital assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/dscvr-passes-200k-user-milestone/" rel="nofollow">DSCVR Passes 200k User Milestone</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
