<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Why is Crypto Going Up – DXY Down, Time to Buy Coins For Altcoin Season?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-going-up-dxy-down-time-buy-coins-for-altcoin-season.htm</link><description>On Friday, a weaker dollar may have helped propel crypto prices upward as stock market investors remained cautious after U.S. inflation numbers came in at historically high levels despite a slight easing, and uncertainty around the upcoming FOMC meeting next week....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-going-up-dxy-down-time-buy-coins-for-altcoin-season.htm"&gt;Read More: Why is Crypto Going Up – DXY Down, Time to Buy Coins For Altcoin Season?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DXY</category><category>Dollar</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Total Crypto Market Cap</category><category>Calvaria</category><category>RIA</category><category>Dash 2 Trade</category><category>D2T</category><category>IMPT</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-crypto-going-up-dxy-down-time-buy-coins-for-altcoin-season.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97538/242458/image15.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="292499"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Sam Bankman-Fried to Testify Next Week, Regulators Postpone FTX Japan’s Suspension, Amber Group Ends $25M Deal with Chelsea FC</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-sam-bankman-fried-to-testify-next-week-regulators-postpone-ftx-japans-suspension-amber-group-ends-25m-deal-with-chelsea-fc.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-sam-bankman-fried-to-testify-next-week-regulators-postpone-ftx-japans-suspension-amber-group-ends-25m-deal-with-chelsea-fc.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Sam Bankman-Fried to Testify Next Week, Regulators Postpone FTX Japan’s Suspension, Amber Group Ends $25M Deal with Chelsea FC&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>USA</category><category>Regulation</category><category>FTX</category><category>Germany</category><category>Exchange</category><category>SEC</category><category>Japan</category><category>Sport</category><category>Career</category><category>Investment</category><category>Mining</category><category>Canada</category><category>DeFi</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-sam-bankman-fried-to-testify-next-week-regulators-postpone-ftx-japans-suspension-amber-group-ends-25m-deal-with-chelsea-fc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97504/242376/adobestock-aerogondo-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="52358"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction $20 Billion Trading Volume Pushes BTC Back Above $17,000 – Here’s Where It’s Headed Next</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-20-billion-trading-volume-pushes-btc-back-above-17000-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm</link><description>On Friday, the BTC/USD pair traded strongly bullish, rising above the $16,750 level to $17,350. However, stronger-than-expected US PPI figures from the Bureau of Labor Statistics have triggered a minor bearish correction, causing BTC to lose nearly 1.50% in the last few hours....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-20-billion-trading-volume-pushes-btc-back-above-17000-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction $20 Billion Trading Volume Pushes BTC Back Above $17,000 – Here’s Where It’s Headed Next&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>BTC/USD</category><category>Bitcoin Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-20-billion-trading-volume-pushes-btc-back-above-17000-heres-where-its-headed-next.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97524/242427/market-roundup-december-9.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="432008"/></item><item><title>Varun Kumar, CEO of Hashflow, on Decentralized Exchanges, AI, and the Future of ETH | Ep. 185</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/varun-kumar-ceo-of-hashflow-decentralized-exchanges-ai-future-of-eth-ep-185.htm</link><description>In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Varun Kumar, CEO of Hashflow, talks about the current state of crypto, growing decentralized exchanges, and the next steps for Ethereum.  &lt;br /&gt;
Varun Kumar is the Co-Founder and CEO of Hashflow, a decentralized exchange designed for users to trade seamlessly across chains while offering zero slippage, improved pricing, and MEV-protection. Varun Kumar is the brains behind Hashflow, having previously served as an aerospace engineer....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/varun-kumar-ceo-of-hashflow-decentralized-exchanges-ai-future-of-eth-ep-185.htm"&gt;Read More: Varun Kumar, CEO of Hashflow, on Decentralized Exchanges, AI, and the Future of ETH | Ep. 185&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Podcast</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/varun-kumar-ceo-of-hashflow-decentralized-exchanges-ai-future-of-eth-ep-185.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97502/242366/varun-kumar-thumb.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="487822"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as XRP Pumps 4% – How High Can it Go?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-pumps-40-how-high-can-it-go.htm</link><description>XRP, the cryptocurrency that underpins Ripple’s global blockchain-based payments system, was last trading lower by just over 1% on Friday, having pulled back from weekly highs in the $0.3950 area to trade around the $0.3900 level. That still leaves the cryptocurrency higher by about 4.2% versus earlier weekly lows....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-pumps-40-how-high-can-it-go.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as XRP Pumps 4% – How High Can it Go?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>XRP</category><category>Ripple</category><category>Cryptocurrency</category><category>SEC</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-xrp-pumps-40-how-high-can-it-go.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97506/242380/xrp-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="791154"/></item><item><title>600 Crypto-related Crimes Reported in Ukraine This Year, Say Police</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/600-crypto-related-crimes-reported-in-ukraine-this-year-say-police.htm</link><description>Ukrainian police officers say they have investigated 600 suspected crimes involving crypto since the start of the year. &lt;br /&gt;
Forklog reported that the claim was made by Evgeny Panchenko, the head of the analytics team at the police force’s cyber division. &lt;br /&gt;
Panchenko claimed that most of the cases involved “cybercriminals” who used coins to “launder criminal proceeds and trade illegal goods on the darkweb.” &lt;br /&gt;
He stated:...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/600-crypto-related-crimes-reported-in-ukraine-this-year-say-police.htm"&gt;Read More: 600 Crypto-related Crimes Reported in Ukraine This Year, Say Police&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/600-crypto-related-crimes-reported-in-ukraine-this-year-say-police.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97461/242327/adobestock-193491644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3486519"/></item><item><title>FTX Token Price Prediction - FTT Pumps as CNBC Suggests FTX Exchange Relaunch</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-token-price-prediction-ftt-pumps-as-cnbc-suggests-ftx-exchange-relaunch.htm</link><description>FTX Token price prediction appears to be turning bullish, as FTT has risen more than 30% in less than 24 hours after CNBC suggests relaunching the FTX exchange. To relaunch FTX and issue new FTT tokens was something that SBF thought would be "a productive path for parties to explore." &lt;br /&gt;
On Friday, Crypto Trader and CNBC host Ran Neuner tweeted that the defunct FTX exchange should reopen, issue a new FTT token, distribute it to creditors, and share all gains with token holders. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-token-price-prediction-ftt-pumps-as-cnbc-suggests-ftx-exchange-relaunch.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Token Price Prediction - FTT Pumps as CNBC Suggests FTX Exchange Relaunch&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>FTT</category><category>FTX Token Price Forecast</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-token-price-prediction-ftt-pumps-as-cnbc-suggests-ftx-exchange-relaunch.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97493/242364/ftt.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="494815"/></item><item><title>The SEC Wants Firms to Publicly Disclose Their Exposure to Crypto – More Regulation Coming?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-wants-firms-publicly-disclose-their-exposure-crypto-more-regulation-coming.htm</link><description>The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has made it clear that they want companies to disclose any crypto-related risks they may be exposed to, saying that both direct and indirect exposure must be described. &lt;br /&gt;
The SEC now says firms should describe how company bankruptcies and subsequent effects “have impacted or may impact your business, financial condition, customers, and counterparties, either directly or indirectly.”...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-wants-firms-publicly-disclose-their-exposure-crypto-more-regulation-coming.htm"&gt;Read More: The SEC Wants Firms to Publicly Disclose Their Exposure to Crypto – More Regulation Coming?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>SEC</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sec-wants-firms-publicly-disclose-their-exposure-crypto-more-regulation-coming.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97499/242361/gary-gensler.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="29851"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Tim Draper Says El Salvador Will Become One of the Richest Countries on Earth For This One Reason</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-tim-draper-says-el-salvador-will-become-one-of-richest-countries-earth-for-one-reason.htm</link><description>American venture capitalist and billionaire Tim Draper argues that bitcoin (BTC) will lead El Salvador to become one of the richest countries in the world. &lt;br /&gt;
In an interview with investor Anthony Pompliano, published on Monday, Draper discussed governments turning to bitcoin and adopting 'the Bitcoin economy', as well as the benefits of that move.  ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-tim-draper-says-el-salvador-will-become-one-of-richest-countries-earth-for-one-reason.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Tim Draper Says El Salvador Will Become One of the Richest Countries on Earth For This One Reason&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>El Salvador</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Blockchain</category><category>Smart Contract</category><category>DAO</category><category>Decentralization</category><category>Tax</category><category>Regulation</category><category>Central African Republic</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-tim-draper-says-el-salvador-will-become-one-of-richest-countries-earth-for-one-reason.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97452/242354/screenshot-2022-12-09-at-13-17-24-tim-draper-on-elon-musk-tesla-bitcoin-the-future-of-the-u-s.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="68496"/></item><item><title>Nomad Bridge Prepares Relaunch Plan After $190 Million Exploit – Partial Refunds for Users?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/nomad-bridge-prepares-relaunch-plan-after-190-million-exploit-partial-refunds-for-users.htm</link><description>Cross-chain messaging protocol Nomad, which was exploited for $190 million back in August, is preparing to relaunch and provide partial refunds to affected users. &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent blog post, the Nomad protocol team announced that the project had upgraded the Nomad protocol to fix the vulnerability that caused the hack and to allow users to bridge back madAssets and access a pro-rata share of recovered funds....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/nomad-bridge-prepares-relaunch-plan-after-190-million-exploit-partial-refunds-for-users.htm"&gt;Read More: Nomad Bridge Prepares Relaunch Plan After $190 Million Exploit – Partial Refunds for Users?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Nomad Bridge</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/nomad-bridge-prepares-relaunch-plan-after-190-million-exploit-partial-refunds-for-users.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97488/242351/meta-image-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="354902"/></item><item><title>Exclusive: Employees of Crypto Firm Koinly Reveal Shocking Details About Surprise Company Layoffs – Executives Kept in the Dark?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-employees-of-crypto-firm-koinly-reveal-shocking-details-about-surprise-company-layoffs-executives-kept-dark.htm</link><description>Koinly, a crypto tax reporting platform, has laid off 14% of its team, citing "the intensifying bear market" – but several employees have claimed that the cuts affected more people and were carried out unprofessionally with poor communication. &lt;br /&gt;
“In a bid to combat the challenging conditions facing the cryptocurrency market and economy at large, Koinly has today announced a round of job cuts to its global team,” said a press release on Tuesday....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-employees-of-crypto-firm-koinly-reveal-shocking-details-about-surprise-company-layoffs-executives-kept-dark.htm"&gt;Read More: Exclusive: Employees of Crypto Firm Koinly Reveal Shocking Details About Surprise Company Layoffs – Executives Kept in the Dark?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Career</category><category>Tax</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/exclusive-employees-of-crypto-firm-koinly-reveal-shocking-details-about-surprise-company-layoffs-executives-kept-dark.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97451/242328/adobestock-kieferpix-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="56689"/></item><item><title>Cardano Price Prediction as Cardano is Named Top Blockchain For Daily Development Activity – ADA to the Moon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-cardano-named-top-blockchain-for-daily-development-activity-ada-moon.htm</link><description>The Cardano price has risen by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, in line with a 2% rise for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. At $0.315694, it's basically flat in the past week but down by 15% in the last 30 days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-cardano-named-top-blockchain-for-daily-development-activity-ada-moon.htm"&gt;Read More: Cardano Price Prediction as Cardano is Named Top Blockchain For Daily Development Activity – ADA to the Moon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/cardano-price-prediction-as-cardano-named-top-blockchain-for-daily-development-activity-ada-moon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97468/242345/cardano-price-prediction-as-cardano-is-named-top-blockchain-for-daily-development-activity-ada-to-the-moon.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1544480"/></item><item><title>Starbucks Unveils Web3 Loyalty Program, Inviting Customers on an 'Odyssey' of Rewards and Benefits</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/starbucks-unveils-web3-loyalty-program-inviting-customers-an-odyssey-of-rewards-benefits.htm</link><description>Starbucks is expanding its exposure to Web3 and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) with the launch of the beta version of Starbucks Odyssey, a new loyalty program available to a select group of waitlist members comprising customers and employees in the US....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/starbucks-unveils-web3-loyalty-program-inviting-customers-an-odyssey-of-rewards-benefits.htm"&gt;Read More: Starbucks Unveils Web3 Loyalty Program, Inviting Customers on an 'Odyssey' of Rewards and Benefits&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/starbucks-unveils-web3-loyalty-program-inviting-customers-an-odyssey-of-rewards-benefits.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97471/242337/adobestock-wachiwit-1-1-media-library-original-1200-800-media-library-original-1200-800.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="142761"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Hit $10 in the Next Bull Market?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-10-next-bull-market.htm</link><description>The Terra Luna Classic price has dropped by 0.5% in the past 24 hours, with its current level of $0.00017176 representing a 2% increase in the past week and a 6% jump in the past fortnight. However, with its community still debating future improvements, and with the FTX collapse still weighing down sentiment, LUNC has dropped by 10% in the last 30 days....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-10-next-bull-market.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic Price Prediction – Can LUNC Hit $10 in the Next Bull Market?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-10-next-bull-market.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97457/242333/terra-luna-classic-price-prediction-can-lunc-hit-10-in-the-next-bull-market.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1329821"/></item><item><title>Regulators in Japan, South Korea Want to Police Stablecoins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-japan-south-korea-want-police-stablecoins.htm</link><description>The top Japanese financial regulator has stated that it intends to police “algorithmic stablecoins.” And the South Korean central bank also wants the power to regulate fiat-pegged tokens....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-japan-south-korea-want-police-stablecoins.htm"&gt;Read More: Regulators in Japan, South Korea Want to Police Stablecoins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>stablecoins</category><category>Japan</category><category>South Korea</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/regulators-japan-south-korea-want-police-stablecoins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97453/242297/adobestock-458520299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="5201449"/></item><item><title>Revealed: Shark Tank Superstar Kevin O’Leary Was Paid This Much by FTX to Promote Platform</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/revealed-shark-tank-superstar-kevin-oleary-was-paid-much-by-ftx-promote-platform.htm</link><description>Investor and Shark Tank star Kevin O'Leary has revealed that he has lost almost all of the $15 million the now-bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX paid him to be its official spokesperson....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/revealed-shark-tank-superstar-kevin-oleary-was-paid-much-by-ftx-promote-platform.htm"&gt;Read More: Revealed: Shark Tank Superstar Kevin O’Leary Was Paid This Much by FTX to Promote Platform&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Kevin O'Leary</category><category>FTX</category><category>Scam</category><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/revealed-shark-tank-superstar-kevin-oleary-was-paid-much-by-ftx-promote-platform.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/97458/242325/107163293-16705077171670507714-27034701265-1080pnbcnews.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="30948"/></item></channel></rss>
