<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:05:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.5</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tether Converts 750M USDT From Tron to Ethereum</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/tether-converts-750m-usdt-from-tron-to-ethereum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tether (USDT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tron]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254839</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Tron_Ethereum_Tether-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Tron_Ethereum_Tether-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The process will have no impact on Tether's total supply.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether announced it will coordinate with a third-party exchange to conduct a chain swap as it wants to convert 750 million USDT from Tron to Ethereum ERC20. The total supply of USDT will not change during this process, as per the firm.</p>
<p>A chain swap process entails moving cryptocurrencies from one blockchain to another, which enables traders to obtain access to the various blockchains that support the cryptocurrency they are holding. In general, it allows the use of their digital assets on these other supporting blockchains.</p>
<h2>1B USDT Mint on Ethereum</h2>
<p>The <a href="https://twitter.com/Tether_to/status/1668233122066907137" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">development</a> follows Tether minting a fresh batch of $1 billion worth of its USDT on the Ethereum blockchain on Monday. Tether&#8217;s chief technology officer Paolo Ardoino <a href="https://twitter.com/paoloardoino/status/1668165749926424580?" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">explained </a>on Twitter that the latest billion-dollar mint is part of the company&#8217;s inventory replenishment on the Ethereum Network. The transaction is authorized but &#8220;not issued,&#8221; meaning that this amount will be used as inventory for the next period of issuance requests and chain swaps.</p>
<p>Tether  previously explained,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Inventory replenishment is the process of creating new USD₮ that are stored in Tether’s treasury inventory as “authorized but not issued” USD₮. These tokens are not part of the total market capitalization of USD₮, as they have not been issued or released into circulation yet.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>USDT has positioned itself as a crucial piece of infrastructure of the crypto ecosystem and is widely used for conducting trading on cryptocurrency exchanges. Its issuer, on the other hand, has been at the receiving end of endless scrutiny over its reserve assets and lack of transparency for years.</p>
<p>But this year&#8217;s banking sector debacle, as well as the increasing crackdown on the asset class, has resulted in investors fleeing to USDT, thereby significantly boosting its dominance.</p>
<h2>Tether&#8217;s Growing Dominance</h2>
<p>USDT&#8217;s circulation <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-circulation-hits-new-peak-as-confidence-in-circle-continues-to-shrink/" data-wpel-link="internal">hit a peak</a> above $83 billion this week. One of the major factors that have catalyzed the surge is the latest price deviation of rival dollar-denominated stablecoin TrueUSD (TUSD).</p>
<p>The shrinking investor confidence in fellow Circle-issued USDC stablecoin is yet another reason that has led to market participants fleeing to the world&#8217;s largest stablecoin, USDT.</p>
<p>Last month, Tether announced <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-expands-presence-in-georgia-with-investment-in-payment-processing-company/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">expanding</a> its footprint in Georgia with an investment in a payment processing company called, CityPay.io. The company also revealed plans to launch sustainable Bitcoin mining operations in Uruguay.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/tether-converts-750m-usdt-from-tron-to-ethereum/" rel="nofollow">Tether Converts 750M USDT From Tron to Ethereum</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uniswap Upgrades to v4: Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s New</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-upgrades-to-v4-heres-whats-new/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255110</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Uniswap.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/Uniswap.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Uniswap v4 features “hooks” that add much more customization to its liquidity pools. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Leading Decentralized Exchange (DEX) protocol Uniswap announced its upgrade to Uniswap v4 on Tuesday, bringing a host of customizable features to the protocol. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The team also open-sourced the protocol’s draft code to invite anybody to build within its ecosystem. </span></p>
<h2>Uniswap v4: What’s Inside?<b><br />
</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As </span><a href="https://blog.uniswap.org/uniswap-v4" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">shared</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by Uniswap Labs, the upgrade’s primary innovation is the inclusion of “hooks,” described as “contracts that run at various points of a pool action&#8217;s lifecycle.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In Uniswap, every liquidity pool has a lifecycle during which a default fee tier is created, liquidity is added and removed, and users swap tokens. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hooks allow for more customizable liquidity within the pool by specifying code to take action at specific points of the lifecycle, such as before or after a swap or LP position change. In Uniswap v3, the organization said lifecycles were “coupled and executed in a very strict sequence.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Developers can innovate on top of the Uniswap Protocol’s liquidity and security to create customized AMM pools through hooks that integrate with v4’s smart contracts,” wrote Uniswap. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The possibilities such contracts present are numerous. Uniswap said it now plans to experiment with a “time-weighted average market maker” (TWAMM), which lets users spread out a buy order over a long period of time. It’s similar to automatic dollar-cost averaging – an investment strategy for spreading out one’s crypto investments over time to defend against temporary volatility. </span></p>
<h2>The Sky is the Limit</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Other features include dynamic fees, on-chain limit orders, and depositing out-of-range liquidity into lending protocols. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“But really, the sky&#8217;s the limit,” wrote Uniswap. “Because each pool is now defined by more than just the tokens and fee tier, we&#8217;ll see pools of all colors, shapes, and sizes.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Uniswap has already provided a set of </span><a href="https://github.com/Uniswap/v4-periphery/tree/main/contracts/hooks/examples" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">sample hook contracts</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> to help developers understand the hook framework, and shared the early implementation of its </span><a href="https://t.co/toy3k7plnU" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">code</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The cost of pool creation on Uniswap v4 will also be </span><a href="https://twitter.com/Uniswap/status/1668603594717667330" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">reduced</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> by 99% since all pools live within a single contract. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In April, Uniswap officially </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-surpasses-1-5t-trading-volume-data/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">passed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> $1.5 trillion in trading volume. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/uniswap-upgrades-to-v4-heres-whats-new/" rel="nofollow">Uniswap Upgrades to v4: Here&#8217;s What&#8217;s New</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>BlockFi Expects to Enable Customer Withdrawals By 2023 Summer</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-expects-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-by-2023-summer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 22:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254936</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockfi_unlock_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/blockfi_unlock_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The withdrawals will be reopened upon the completion of necessary upgrades]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bankrupt lending platform BlockFi needs to conduct updates before enabling customer withdrawals of crypto assets held in its wallet accounts that are not subject to potential preference claims.</p>
<p>In an emailed statement to its clients, BlockFi said it should conclude all the necessary &#8220;work&#8221; to enable customer withdrawals by this summer.</p>
<ul>
<li>The company said it will add a new product functionality to its platform before enabling withdrawals but has not detailed what these features will include.</li>
<li>According to the new <a href="https://twitter.com/LoungeRogue/status/1668351666092146688" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a>, withdrawals must be made in batches, while the eligible users will receive an email.</li>
<li>The lender further advised users to set up a third-party wallet for the process.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;BlockFi needs to build new product functionality and make changes to the platform in order to process these withdrawals. We anticipate that this work and the necessary testing will be completed this summer. At that time, we will be in a position to begin allowing clients to withdraw digital assets held in BlockFi Wallet accounts that are not subject to potential preference claims.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>The development follows an order issued by the Supreme Court in Bermuda on June 9th, allowing the platform to reopen withdrawals for customers with BlockFi Wallet accounts.</li>
<li>Since then, the user interface has been updated to accurately reflect users&#8217; transactions and account balances as of the platform suspension date of November 10, 2022.</li>
<li>BlockFi was one of several crypto lenders to go bankrupt during the market turmoil last year. It owes between $1 billion and $10 billion to its creditors.</li>
<li>Last month, the company <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-to-liquidate-lending-platform-after-futile-sales-attempts/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">requested</a> that a court authorize the sale of its lending arm to help generate funds to repay creditors after failing to receive value-maximizing offers from potential buyers.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/blockfi-expects-to-enable-customer-withdrawals-by-2023-summer/" rel="nofollow">BlockFi Expects to Enable Customer Withdrawals By 2023 Summer</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>eToro Imposes Restrictions on 4 Crypto Assets Labelled as Securities in SEC Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/etoro-imposes-restrictions-on-4-crypto-assets-labelled-as-securities-in-sec-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 20:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decentraland (MANA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eToro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Polygon (MATIC)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254973</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Etoro-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Etoro-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[US customers of eToro will have a month-long window to continue trading the crypto-assets in question. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Financial trading platform eToro issued new guidelines barring US customers from buying four crypto assets that were recently deemed securities by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance.</p>
<p>While eToro did not explicitly cite the securities regulator&#8217;s action as the reason for the latest changes in its crypto offering, it did emphasize the &#8220;rapidly evolving regulatory landscape.&#8221; In doing so, eToro joins the likes of Robinhood as the industry faces the SEC&#8217;s enforcement hammer.</p>
<h2>eToro&#8217;s Latest Update</h2>
<p>According to the new <a href="https://twitter.com/eToroUS/status/1668323755435622405" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">update</a>, eToro said its US customers will no longer be able to purchase Algorand (ALGO), Decentraland (MANA), Dash (DASH), and Polygon (MATIC) starting July 12th. Customers will still be able to retain the ability to &#8220;hold and sell existing positions in these coins.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We remain a supporter of crypto-assets and believe in the importance of offering our users access to a diversified range of asset classes, which includes stocks, ETFs, and options.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Earlier this year, eToro <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-partners-with-etoro-to-enable-users-access-to-financial-instruments/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">partnered</a> with Twitter to enable the users of the social media giant to access stocks, cryptocurrencies, and other financial assets. However, the recent crackdown on the asset class has forced it to evaluate the regulatory environment in the country.</p>
<p>In a statement, the brokerage firm reiterated its commitment to working closely with global regulators in a bid &#8220;to shape the future of the crypto industry and champion access for the ordinary investor.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Heightened Scrutiny</h2>
<p>This isn&#8217;t the first time eToro had restricted its US customers from certain assets. After the SEC&#8217;s lawsuit against blockchain firm Ripple in December 2020, eToro <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/etoro-halts-xrp-trading-for-us-citizens-following-the-sec-charges/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">delisted</a> XRP. A few months later, the company also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/etoro-to-delist-ada-and-trx-for-us-customers-citing-regulatory-concerns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">delisted</a> Cardano (ADA) and Tron (TRX) due to &#8220;business-related considerations in the evolving regulatory environment.&#8221;</p>
<p>The development comes days after another prominent trading firm &#8211; Robinhood &#8211; <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-delists-solana-sol-cardano-ada-polygon-matic-after-secs-claims/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a> plans to end support for Solana (SOL), Cardano (ADA), and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<p>Robinhood’s chief legal officer Dan Gallagher recently testified before the House Agriculture Committee that the firm tried to register with the SEC as a special-purpose broker for digital assets but was shut down by the agency without proper explanation even after going through a 16-month process for the same.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/etoro-imposes-restrictions-on-4-crypto-assets-labelled-as-securities-in-sec-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">eToro Imposes Restrictions on 4 Crypto Assets Labelled as Securities in SEC Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lido Risk to Ethereum Grows as SEC Targets Exchange Staking Services</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/lido-risk-to-ethereum-grows-as-sec-targets-exchange-staking-services/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 19:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lido]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Proof of Stake (PoS)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254940</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/LIDO_Finance.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/LIDO_Finance.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The continued crackdown on crypto exchanges and their services in America could potentially increase risks in the Ethereum staking ecosystem.  ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is convinced that all crypto assets aside from Bitcoin are securities. Its latest war on crypto exchanges has included staking services, which the regulator seeks to shut down.</p>
<p>This could push more staked ETH out of exchanges and onto the market-leading liquid staking provider Lido. This may sound good, but it poses significant risks to the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>
<h2>Lido Staking Risks Exposed</h2>
<p>Lido provides liquid staking services for Ethereum as an alternative to self-staking, which is highly technical, and involves exchanges that take substantial commissions.</p>
<p>It has rapidly become the market leader with 7.18 million staked ETH, or 36% of the total 19.6 million staked.</p>
<p>On June 13, Ethereum advocates at ‘Bankless’ sounded the alarm on Lido, <a href="https://twitter.com/BanklessHQ/status/1668359049187061762" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">calling</a> for the prevention of its domination of ETH staking.</p>
<p>A continued <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/300-million-in-liquidations-in-wake-of-latest-sec-enforcement-action/" data-wpel-link="internal">SEC crackdown</a> on exchanges is likely to push more staked Ethereum to Lido, it noted. There was already a surge in staked ETH redemptions from Coinbase last week after the lawsuit by the regulator.</p>
<p>Kraken was forced to end its Ethereum staking services for U.S. users in February, resulting in an exodus as soon as Shapella rolled out.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Lido’s market share has grown since the Shapella upgrade enabled <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-launches-v2-and-releases-staked-ethereum-for-withdrawals/" data-wpel-link="internal">staking withdrawals</a>.</p>
<p>Ethereum developers such as Danny Ryan have <a href="https://twitter.com/dannyryan/status/1664018289021063168" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">warned</a> about the dangers of staking “cartelization,” in which platforms such as Lido can extract outsized profits compared to non-pooled capital.</p>
<p>Bankless reported that the platform was near the first threshold with around a third of all staked ETH.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Lido is nearing the first of three thresholds at which Ethereum is more easily manipulated by an attacker.”</p></blockquote>
<p>It added that Lido has already voted against self-limiting deposits, but Ethereum advocates are now calling for them to do so.</p>
<blockquote><p>“It&#8217;s unlikely Ethereum will implement such controls at the protocol level, but it is clear Lido must face economic repercussions,” Bankless noted.</p></blockquote>
<p>There is a growing movement to divest from Lido and explore alternative Ethereum staking options.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Etherians must band together and decrease our reliance on Lido to prevent its domination over staking!”</p></blockquote>
<h2>ETH Price Outlook</h2>
<p>Ethereum staking deposits are still outpacing withdrawals, however, asset prices have taken a hit following last week’s regulatory attacks on the industry.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-price-analysis/" data-wpel-link="internal">ETH</a> was trading flat on the day at $1,745 at the time of writing, according to CoinGecko. The asset has lost more than 8% since the SEC sued Binance and Coinbase last week, more than its big brother Bitcoin.</p>
<p>Additionally, it is looking increasingly bearish, having fallen to the lower boundary of its three-month-long range-bound channel.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/lido-risk-to-ethereum-grows-as-sec-targets-exchange-staking-services/" rel="nofollow">Lido Risk to Ethereum Grows as SEC Targets Exchange Staking Services</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Recycle2Earn Crypto Ecoterra Raises Over $5m, Final Presale Stage Imminent</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/new-recycle2earn-crypto-ecoterra-raises-over-5m-final-presale-stage-imminent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Felix Mollen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Projects]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255084</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_cover.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/ecoterra_cover.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Exciting crypto presale project ecoterra is now in its penultimate stage, leaving limited time before the eco-friendly token heads to exchanges. Priced at $0.00925 in stage 8 of its 9-stage presale, over $5 million has been invested in ECOTERRA tokens since the project launched just 11 weeks ago. With the current total standing at $4.815 [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exciting crypto presale project ecoterra is now in its penultimate stage, leaving limited time before the eco-friendly token heads to exchanges.</p>
<p>Priced at $0.00925 in stage 8 of its 9-stage presale, over $5 million has been invested in <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ECOTERRA</a> tokens since the project launched just 11 weeks ago.</p>
<p>With the current total standing at $4.815 million, that leaves less than $900k remaining before the presale ticks into its final stage &#8211; which will spark an 8% price increase to $0.01.</p>
<p>Major global brands such as Vittel, Coca-Cola, Carlsberg, and Evian are partnered with ecoterra, which has developed its unique Recycle-to-Earn concept to allow users to earn rewards simply for recycling household waste.</p>
<h2>Recycle for Rewards and to Fight Climate Change</h2>
<p>Recycle-to-Earn is a simple and novel Web3 concept that will see <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ecoterra</a> users earn ECOTERRA tokens for recycling plastic, glass, cardboard, and other everyday items.</p>
<p>The ecoterra app is supported globally and simply requires users to take plastic bottles, for example, to a Reverse Vending Machine (RVM) &#8211; which can be found in tens of thousands of supermarkets around the world.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-4.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255092" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-4.jpg" alt="Picture5" width="624" height="156" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-4.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-4-300x75.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture5-4-50x13.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>Users then scan the barcode of an item via the mobile app and deposit it in the RVM. The app has an AI-powered algorithm and database that assigns a value to the item, and the user is then rewarded with ECOTERRA items.</p>
<p>Through the app, users are able to either store and stake their tokens to generate a passive income, sell them on exchanges or spend them to fund other green efforts globally.</p>
<p>They can be spent on efforts such as ocean clean-ups or tree planting or by purchasing carbon credits, which remove CO2 from the atmosphere, through its Carbon Offset Marketplace. Users can also earn NFTs that track their environmental contributions.</p>
<p>Furthermore, ecoterra also features a recycled materials marketplace that allows businesses and individuals to connect with manufacturers to purchase recycled goods.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255091" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-1.jpg" alt="Picture6" width="624" height="439" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-1.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-1-300x211.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture6-1-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The app also has an Impact Trackable Profile that will allow users to track their actions &#8211; as well as those of companies and other individuals &#8211; to see how much of a difference they are making.</p>
<p>Environmentally conscious firms will be able to use the profile to boost their own brand image and attract green-thinking customers.</p>
<p>As mentioned above, ecoterra has already partnered with a number of leading brands to bring products into their ecosystem and recently won an award at the <a href="https://twitter.com/ecoterraio/status/1657007919211110401" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Blockchain Econony Istanbul Summit</a>, recognizing their contribution to the sustainable crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>The project has also partnered with Ahold Delhaize, a Dutch supermarket multinational that has more than 7,500 stores in 10 countries &#8211; including Food Lion and Stop &amp; Shop in the US &#8211; to offer RVMs to customers.</p>
<p>Read the <a href="https://www.ecoterra.io/documents/whitepaper-ecoterra.pdf" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ecoterra whitepaper</a> for more info, or visit the <a href="https://t.me/ecoterraio" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Telegram group</a> for the latest news.</p>
<h2>ECOTERRA Presale Nearing Finish Line</h2>
<p>With the <a href="https://twitter.com/ecoterraio/status/1665664772057047045" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">$ECOTERRA presale now in stage 8</a>, there is just one further stage remaining before the token is listed on exchanges.</p>
<p>The presale has raised over $5 million, and tokens now cost $0.00925 but will see one further price increase &#8211; jumping 8% to $0.01 &#8211; in the final stage.</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-255090" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-1.jpg" alt="Picture7" width="624" height="289" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-1.jpg 624w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-1-300x139.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Picture7-1-50x23.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 624px) 100vw, 624px" /></a></p>
<p>The supply is capped at a max of 2 billion, with 50% of those being made available to presale investors with no vesting period and a hard cap of $6.7 million.</p>
<p>The remaining supply is allocated to liquidity (25%), marketing (10%), listings (5%), the team (5%), and company adoption (5%) &#8211; although these tokens have various locking and vesting periods from three months to three years.</p>
<p>The <a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">ecoterra</a> team is doxxed and has been KYC verified, while the token smart contract has been audited by CertiK.</p>
<p>Crypto analyst <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aMpPrZOA70Q&amp;t=8s" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer">Jacob Crypto Bury recently predicted</a> the token could have huge potential when it lists in the near future.</p>
<p><a href="https://bs_d432f031.cryptopotato.care" data-wpel-link="exclude" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"><strong>Visit ecoterra Presale</strong></a></p>
<p><em>Disclaimer: The above article is sponsored content, and it’s written by a third-party, and is intended for promotional purposes only. It does not represent the opinions or the views of CryptoPotato, and nothing in it should be construed as financial advice. Readers are strongly advised to verify the information independently and carefully. Investing in cryptocurrencies carries a risk of capital loss, and readers are also advised to consult a professional before making any decisions that may or may not be based on the above sponsored content.</em></p>
<p><em>Readers are also advised to read CryptoPotato’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/disclaimer/" data-wpel-link="internal">full disclaimer</a>.</em></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-recycle2earn-crypto-ecoterra-raises-over-5m-final-presale-stage-imminent/" rel="nofollow">New Recycle2Earn Crypto Ecoterra Raises Over $5m, Final Presale Stage Imminent</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance.US Calls to Dismiss SEC&#8217;s Restraining Order Request</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-calls-to-dismiss-secs-restraining-order-request/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 17:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Changpeng Zhao (CZ Binance)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255011</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/BinanceUS.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[In a rebuttal against the SEC, Binance.US argued the regulator's motion should be denied. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A week after the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a civil enforcement action against Binance.US, the crypto exchange has hit back, stating that all of the regulator&#8217;s claims are invalid.</p>
<p>Binance argued against the SEC for a temporary restraining order on the company, also known as BAM Trading, and said that such an action would have &#8220;destructive consequences,&#8221; which will subsequently affect the platform&#8217;s ability to even fund its defense to this action.</p>
<h2>Binance Hits Back</h2>
<p>In its latest <a href="https://www.johnreedstark.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/180/2023/06/BamOpposition.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a>, Binance&#8217;s US affiliate argued that the agency has not identified a single security trading on BAM&#8217;s platform. The <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-requests-binance-asset-freeze-exchange-hires-former-agency-director-as-lawyer-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">request</a> for a restraining order would primarily harm BAM&#8217;s customers, effectively put BAM out of business, and subsequently, prevent the company from defending itself in this litigation.</p>
<p>Deeming the SEC&#8217;s request as &#8220;draconian and unduly burdensome,&#8221; Binance.US said the move would hinder the ability to pay its employees, vendors, suppliers, and professionals in the ordinary course of business and to maintain its technology platform.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The SEC suggests that it is a foregone conclusion that cryptocurrency is a security, but that is not the case. That numerous cryptocurrency exchanges, including BAM, have operated in the United States for years without interference by the SEC belies the claim that they are clearly covered by the securities laws.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Binance.US further said the SEC’s motion is &#8220;riddled with mistakes&#8221; and omissions to inappropriately deem that BAM customer assets are &#8220;not secure.&#8221;</p>
<h2>Cooperation With SEC</h2>
<p>Binance.US claimed that it had made significant efforts over more than three years to cooperate with the SEC&#8217;s investigation. BAM Trading was first served with a subpoena on December 17, 2020, that resulted in over two years of document production as well as a series of follow-up requests.</p>
<p>This included additional subpoenas issued on five occasions between September 2021 and October 2022 and a set of twenty-eight written interrogatories on December 28, 2022.</p>
<p>According to the filing, Binance furnished a bevy of informal written and oral requests for the investigation. During the period, the company produced more than 700,000 individual communications, including nearly 11,391 emails, 8,196 email attachments, and 652,817 other messages.</p>
<p>The crypto exchange&#8217;s complaint about fully cooperating with the SEC echoed similar issues faced by its rivals that draw attention to the regulatory agency&#8217;s failure to provide clarity. Last week, Robinhood&#8217;s chief legal officer Dan Gallagher also <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/robinhood-delists-solana-sol-cardano-ada-polygon-matic-after-secs-claims/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">said</a> the popular trading firm tried to register with the agency as a special-purpose broker for digital assets and even went through a 16-month process but &#8220;did not see any fruits of that effort.&#8221;</p>
<p>Paul Grewal, chief legal officer of Coinbase, also expressed his frustration over the matter. The exec said Coinbase failed to secure a registration despite months of discussions and blamed SEC&#8217;s lack of response or any counter-proposal.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-us-calls-to-dismiss-secs-restraining-order-request/" rel="nofollow">Binance.US Calls to Dismiss SEC&#8217;s Restraining Order Request</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ripple v. SEC and the Hinman Speech: What Happened Behind the Scenes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-and-the-hinman-speech-what-happened-behind-the-scenes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255063</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Ripple_SEC.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Hinman was warned by the SEC that his speech would create “greater confusion” as to what constitutes a security within the crypto market. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has released its long-awaited internal documents related to former commissioner William Hinman’s speech on digital assets in 2018. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The reveal incited fury from Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse, who has now accused the SEC of willingly throwing “an entire industry into chaos” by releasing the speech. </span></p>
<h2>Hinman Ignored All Warnings</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to now publicly available </span><a href="https://www.dropbox.com/s/rrnmfue6jf2ubuc/Hinman%20Emails..pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">emails</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from the SEC, the agency warned Hinman multiple times that the wording of his speech could create confusion in the market about why he or the SEC might believe Ether (ETH) is not a security.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“As written, it may not be apparent to the reader which characteristic or factor weigh against it being a security or not,” wrote one of the agency members about the speech. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Released in June 2018, Hinman’s speech provided an “illustrative list” of which factors the SEC might consider when determining whether a digital asset is a security. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Certain agency members criticized the chairman for not tying his criteria “more closely and explicitly to the Howey analysis” – a standard for classifying investment contracts often cited by SEC Chairman Gary Gensler today. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Others noted that the speech was “ambiguously worded,” and seemed to include factors that weren’t clearly relevant to securities laws at all – such as whether an asset can be “hoarded.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Hinman’s speech is central to the SEC’s ongoing lawsuit against Ripple, alleging that the sale of XRP beginning in 2013 constituted an unregistered securities offering. Ripple asserts that Hinman’s speech describing Ether as a commodity would also rule out XRP from being a security since it was sold in a similar fashion. </span></p>
<h2>Ripple’s Response</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">After the reveal, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer Stuart Alderoty called for Hinman’s speech to be removed from the SEC’s website, and never again be invoked in discussions about whether an asset is a security.</span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="500" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">2/ We now can all see Hinman ignored multiple warnings that his speech contained made-up analysis with no basis in law, was divorced from the Howey factors, exposed regulatory gaps, and would create not just confusion, but “greater confusion” in the market.</p>
<p>&mdash; Stuart Alderoty (@s_alderoty) <a href="https://twitter.com/s_alderoty/status/1668601226672623616?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 13, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse called it “absolutely unconscionable” that Hinman would release his speech despite receiving tremendous internal pushback. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Seeing the depth to which the SEC has essentially weaponized the lack of regulatory clarity through enforcement actions since this speech was given – it’s no surprise that we can call bluff on their claims to “just come in and register” as nothing but in bad faith,” he </span><a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1668601653174611968" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">said</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Ripple had private access to the documents months ago, but they weren’t unveiled to the public until today under a </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/another-win-for-ripple-judge-orders-sec-to-hand-over-hinman-speech-documents/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">court order</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> from New York judge Analisa Torres. Garlinhouse had previously </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-ceo-believes-hinman-documents-release-is-worth-the-wait/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">told</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> followers that the documents would be “well worth the wait.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Last week, the SEC </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/as-the-ripple-v-sec-june-13th-deadline-approaches-commission-deletes-hinmans-bio/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">deleted</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> almost all details within Hinman’s biography from its website.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ripple-v-sec-and-the-hinman-speech-what-happened-behind-the-scenes/" rel="nofollow">Ripple v. SEC and the Hinman Speech: What Happened Behind the Scenes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atomic Wallet Hackers Used OFAC-Sanctioned Garantex to Launder Stolen $35M: Report</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hackers-used-ofac-sanctioned-garantex-to-launder-stolen-35m-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 15:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=255025</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Atomic_Wallet.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Atomic_Wallet.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Before moving the stolen funds to Garantex, the hackers used the on-chain trading platform 1inch to exchange the assets for USDT.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto assets stolen during the Atomic Wallet hack have found their way to the sanctioned Russia-based cryptocurrency exchange Garantex, with the attackers trading the tokens for Bitcoin (BTC).</p>
<p>According to a <a href="https://twitter.com/Elliptic_Inv/status/1668338875243085824?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">tweet</a> from blockchain analytics provider Elliptic, the hackers, believed to be part of the North Korean notorious Lazarus Group, have turned to Garantex as several crypto exchanges are working together to freeze funds related to the hack.</p>
<h2>Atomic Wallet Hackers Turn to Garantex</h2>
<p>The Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned Garantex last year, a couple of months after Russian President Vladimir Putin attacked Ukraine. The U.S. Treasury stated that the platform had lax anti-money laundering measures and accommodated illicit players. However, the exchange continued its operations and played a significant role in facilitating illegal crypto transactions.</p>
<p>The non-custodial decentralized Atomic Wallet was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacked-largest-victim-reportedly-lost-2-8m-usdt/" data-wpel-link="internal">compromised</a> earlier this month, with multiple users reporting that their accounts were drained. While losses for the single largest victim <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/over-35-million-reportely-stolen-from-atomic-wallet-users/" data-wpel-link="internal">ran into six figures</a>, more than $35 million in crypto assets were siphoned through the attack. The stolen assets include BTC, Ether (ETH), Tether (USDT), Dogecoin (DOGE), Litecoin (LTC), BNB Coin (BNB), and Polygon (MATIC).</p>
<p>A few days after the exploit, the hackers <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hacker-funnels-stolen-crypto-to-north-korea-tied-coin-mixer-elliptic/" data-wpel-link="internal">funneled</a> the stolen crypto to Sinbad.io, a crypto mixer used by the Lazarus Group to launder crypto assets. Funds from Garantex are still being moved to Sinbad.io.</p>
<p>Before moving the stolen assets to Garantex, the hackers used the on-chain trading platform 1inch to exchange them for USDT. From Garantex, they were swapped for BTC and moved to Sinbad.io.</p>
<h2>Ongoing Investigation</h2>
<p>The Atomic Wallet team claims that the attack affected less than 1% of its monthly active users. The team said they had engaged the services of blockchain security firm Chainalysis as the lead investigator and joined forces with several exchanges and analytics companies to track and freeze the stolen funds.</p>
<p>It remains unclear if Atomic Wallet has involved law enforcement authorities in the matter. Furthermore, the platform has not yet determined the attack vector or indicated whether compensation plans are underway.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/atomic-wallet-hackers-used-ofac-sanctioned-garantex-to-launder-stolen-35m-report/" rel="nofollow">Atomic Wallet Hackers Used OFAC-Sanctioned Garantex to Launder Stolen $35M: Report</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Chief Gary Gensler Called BTC, ETH &#8216;Not Securities&#8217; in 2018</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chief-gary-gensler-called-btc-eth-not-securities-in-2018/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BCHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Litecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=254949</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Gary_Gensler.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SEC Chair said in 2018 that BTC, ETH, LTC, and BCH are "not securities."]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">A newly-surfaced video that dates back to 2018 showed that the current Chairman of the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) &#8211; Gary Gensler &#8211; classified several cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH), as &#8220;not securities.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">His stance from nearly five years ago contrasts with his nowadays vision. Gensler has argued several times that the only digital asset which could categorize as a commodity is BTC. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gensler&#8217;s View Before Becoming SEC Chair</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The video, which went viral on Twitter, reveals how Gensler says four of the leading cryptocurrencies &#8211; Bitcoin (BTC), Ether (ETH), Litecoin (LTC), and Bitcoin Cash (BCH) &#8211; should not be treated as securities. </span></p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Chair Gensler in 2018 at a Bloomberg conference in NYC:</p>
<p>“Bitcoin. Ether. Litecoin. Bitcoin Cash. Why did I name those four? They’re not securities.”</p>
<p>What’s Goldman Gary going to say about this one? Deep fake? <a href="https://t.co/p7DJlYkJIt" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">pic.twitter.com/p7DJlYkJIt</a></p>
<p>— Ryan Selkis <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1fab3.png" alt="🪳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@twobitidiot) <a href="https://twitter.com/twobitidiot/status/1668328519334780928?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">June 12, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The video dates back to 2018 when Gensler served as Chairman of the Maryland Financial Consumer Protection Commission. He was named the Chairman of the SEC in 2021 &#8211; a US government agency that regulates and oversees the securities markets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The agency is also known for its harsh actions against the cryptocurrency industry and recently filed lawsuits against two of the heavyweights in the sector &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-plummets-after-sec-sues-binance-for-securities-violations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-files-a-lawsuit-against-coinbase-day-after-suing-binance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Coinbase</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">. The main accusations are that they offered trading services with unregulated securities, such as BNB, SOL, ADA, MATIC, and other well-known assets.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It is worth noting that in its lawsuits, the agency did not touch upon the four cryptocurrencies labeled as &#8220;not securities&#8221; by Gensler in 2018. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">BTC is a Commodity and Awkward Silence Regarding ETH</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Shortly after joining the SEC, Gensler somewhat changed his stance on the cryptocurrency universe. The American, who admitted his affection to the market in the summer of 2021, later </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://twitter.com/JBSDC/status/1648375658840571914" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">called</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> it &#8220;highly speculative&#8221; and said he had never owned or used digital currencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chairman-is-only-willing-to-call-bitcoin-a-commodity/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">asserted</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> multiple times that &#8220;everything other than Bitcoin&#8221; is a security, whereas the primary cryptocurrency is the only one that operates as a commodity. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Unlike BTC, Gensler has been quite unclear regarding ETH&#8217;s status. He </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/is-ether-a-security-sec-chair-gary-gensler-avoids-a-direct-answer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">avoided</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> a direct answer on whether the second-largest crypto asset should be classified as a commodity or security at the beginning of 2022.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Gensler did the same when </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chair-under-fire-by-congress-is-ether-a-commodity-or-a-security/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">questioned</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the House Financial Services Committee in April this year. He instead gave imprecise answers to the repeated questions asked by Patrick McHenry without specifying in detail.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-chief-gary-gensler-called-btc-eth-not-securities-in-2018/" rel="nofollow">SEC Chief Gary Gensler Called BTC, ETH &#8216;Not Securities&#8217; in 2018</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
