<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy Litecoin? LTC Price Blasts Up 20% and AI Crypto Predictions Platform yPredict Raises $2.7 Million</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-litecoin-ltc-price-blasts-up-20-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC), the cryptocurrency that powers the decentralized payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, has pulled back from the more than one-year highs it hit earlier this week in the $115 area. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC/USD was last exchanging for around $101 across major cryptocurrency exchanges, with LTC down about 2.5% on the day as the broader crypto market pulls back a little. &lt;br /&gt;
But LTC is still looking healthy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-litecoin-ltc-price-blasts-up-20-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy Litecoin? LTC Price Blasts Up 20% and AI Crypto Predictions Platform yPredict Raises $2.7 Million&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-litecoin-ltc-price-blasts-up-20-ai-crypto-predictions-platform-ypredict-raises-27-million.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118795/316389/ltc.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="8272057"/></item><item><title>Value Locked in Solana's Liquid Staking Protocols Surged by 91% in the First Half of the Year</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/value-locked-solanas-liquid-staking-protocols-surged-by-91-first-half-of-year.htm</link><description>As the crypto market returns to form this year, so too has demand for liquid staking – especially in the Solana ecosystem. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/value-locked-solanas-liquid-staking-protocols-surged-by-91-first-half-of-year.htm"&gt;Read More: Value Locked in Solana's Liquid Staking Protocols Surged by 91% in the First Half of the Year&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/value-locked-solanas-liquid-staking-protocols-surged-by-91-first-half-of-year.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118794/316386/adobestock-501211764-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="185709"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: NFT Royalties Reach Lowest Point in Two Years, Two Teens Arrested for BTC and ETH Scam, India and 18 Central Banks Discuss Using Digital Rupee for Cross-Border Payments</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nft-royalties-reach-lowest-point-in-two-years-two-teens-arrested-for-btc-and-eth-scam-india-and-18-central-banks-discuss-using-digital-rupee-for-cross-border-payments.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nft-royalties-reach-lowest-point-in-two-years-two-teens-arrested-for-btc-and-eth-scam-india-and-18-central-banks-discuss-using-digital-rupee-for-cross-border-payments.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: NFT Royalties Reach Lowest Point in Two Years, Two Teens Arrested for BTC and ETH Scam, India and 18 Central Banks Discuss Using Digital Rupee for Cross-Border Payments&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Banking</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>CBDC</category><category>China</category><category>Denmark</category><category>Saxo Bank</category><category>India</category><category>Central Bank</category><category>Digital Rupee</category><category>Reserve Bank of India</category><category>Canada</category><category>USA</category><category>Crime</category><category>Fraud</category><category>Investment</category><category>Middle East</category><category>Africa</category><category>UAE</category><category>Exchange</category><category>Charity</category><category>Nansen</category><category>NFT</category><category>BNB Chain</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-nft-royalties-reach-lowest-point-in-two-years-two-teens-arrested-for-btc-and-eth-scam-india-and-18-central-banks-discuss-using-digital-rupee-for-cross-border-payments.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118744/316365/adobestock-vadimalekcandr-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="110593"/></item><item><title>DBS Bank China Launches Digital Yuan Merchant Collection Solution</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dbs-bank-china-launches-digital-yuan-merchant-collection-solution.htm</link><description>Crypto-friendly bank DBS announced the launch of a digital yuan merchant collection solution for business clients.  &lt;br /&gt;
The new payment solution will allow mainland Chinese businesses to receive payments in the central bank digital currency (CBDC). &lt;br /&gt;
The DBS merchant collection platform allows businesses automated settlement of e-CNY into their bank deposit accounts....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dbs-bank-china-launches-digital-yuan-merchant-collection-solution.htm"&gt;Read More: DBS Bank China Launches Digital Yuan Merchant Collection Solution&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CBDC</category><category>China</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dbs-bank-china-launches-digital-yuan-merchant-collection-solution.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118793/316385/digital-yuan-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="99790"/></item><item><title>India Fosters Global Cross-Border Payments For The Digital Rupee</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/india-fosters-global-cross-border-payments-for-the-digital-rupee.htm</link><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is on course to expand the frontiers of its Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC), the “digital rupee” as it negotiates with foreign countries to adopt cross-border payment systems. &lt;br /&gt;
The bank is currently in talks with its counterpart in at least 18 countries on ways to facilitate trade between countries that lack US dollar reserves. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/india-fosters-global-cross-border-payments-for-the-digital-rupee.htm"&gt;Read More: India Fosters Global Cross-Border Payments For The Digital Rupee&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>RBI</category><category>Digital Rupee</category><category>Payment</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/india-fosters-global-cross-border-payments-for-the-digital-rupee.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118786/316355/rupees-g13cc2fc26-1280.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="117205"/></item><item><title>Crypto Whales Are Accumulating Green Crypto Ecoterra Before It Lists on Exchanges – $5.8 Million Raised Already</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-green-crypto-ecoterra-before-it-lists-exchanges-58-million-raised-already.htm</link><description>Green blockchain initiative ecoterra is seeing massive adoption amongst sustainability-centric crypto investors.  &lt;br /&gt;
At press time, the recycle-to-earn (R2E) initiative has raised over $5.85 million as it prepares for an exchange listing in the coming weeks.  &lt;br /&gt;
$ECOTERRA has gained considerable attention and support since the start of its presale, which is reflected in its impressive fundraising milestone of $5.85 million....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-green-crypto-ecoterra-before-it-lists-exchanges-58-million-raised-already.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Whales Are Accumulating Green Crypto Ecoterra Before It Lists on Exchanges – $5.8 Million Raised Already&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-whales-are-accumulating-green-crypto-ecoterra-before-it-lists-exchanges-58-million-raised-already.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118783/316350/ecoterra.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="375948"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Introduces BRC-69 Standard, Promising 90% Cost Reduction</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-launchpad-introduces-brc-69-standard-promising-90-cost-reduction.htm</link><description>Luminex, a launchpad platform for Bitcoin Ordinals, has proposed a new BRC-69 standard which promises a staggering reduction of more than 90% on inscription costs. &lt;br /&gt;
Ordinal inscriptions are digital assets similar to NFTs, inscribed on a Satoshi, the lowest denomination of a Bitcoin (BTC). Bitcoin Ordinals are on-chain, directly written on the Bitcoin network. Ordinals previously had a 4-megabyte limit on inscriptions....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-launchpad-introduces-brc-69-standard-promising-90-cost-reduction.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Ordinals Launchpad Introduces BRC-69 Standard, Promising 90% Cost Reduction&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-ordinals-launchpad-introduces-brc-69-standard-promising-90-cost-reduction.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118763/316324/pexels-pixabay-315788.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2235966"/></item><item><title>Binance Australia Under Investigation, Offices Searched by Regulator</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-australia-under-investigation-offices-searched-by-regulator.htm</link><description>Australia's financial regulator has visited Binance offices as part of an ongoing probe into the company's defunct local derivatives business.  &lt;br /&gt;
On Tuesday, officials from the Australian Securities and Investments Commission (ASIC) conducted searches at Binance Australia's offices, Bloomberg reported, citing people familiar with the matter.  &lt;br /&gt;
The investigation revolves around Binance Australia's classification of clients as retail or wholesale investors. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-australia-under-investigation-offices-searched-by-regulator.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Australia Under Investigation, Offices Searched by Regulator&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Binance</category><category>Australia</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-australia-under-investigation-offices-searched-by-regulator.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118779/316343/1de6a786b2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="55946"/></item><item><title>Two Canadian Teens Charged for Impersonating Coinbase Support to Steal $4.2m in Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/two-canadian-teens-charged-for-impersonating-coinbase-support-steal-42m-crypto.htm</link><description>A pair of teens from Hamilton, Canada, was recently arrested and charged with theft and possession of criminally obtained property after the authorities managed to trace $4.2 million in Bitcoin and Ethereum back to them.  &lt;br /&gt;
The two individuals in question are both seventeen-year-old boys who defrauded a US investor by pretending to be Coinbase customer support....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/two-canadian-teens-charged-for-impersonating-coinbase-support-steal-42m-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Two Canadian Teens Charged for Impersonating Coinbase Support to Steal $4.2m in Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/two-canadian-teens-charged-for-impersonating-coinbase-support-steal-42m-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118776/316342/two-canadian-teens-charge.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="83180"/></item><item><title>While KSI Token Shoots Up 50,000% Crypto Experts are Stacking This New Meme Coin as the Next Crypto to Explode – What Do They Know?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-ksi-token-shoots-up-50000-crypto-experts-are-stacking-new-meme-coin-as-next-crypto-explode-what-do-they-know.htm</link><description>The KSI Token has risen by 430% in the past 24 hours, with the new meme token – themed after YouTuber/boxer KSI – exploding by more than 50,000% since listing directly on Uniswap yesterday. &lt;br /&gt;
In previous years, such astronomical gains would be mightily impressive, but 2023 has seen no shortage of new meme tokens rising up the charts, with the vast majority being little more than thinly veiled pump-and-dumps....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/while-ksi-token-shoots-up-50000-crypto-experts-are-stacking-new-meme-coin-as-next-crypto-explode-what-do-they-know.htm"&gt;Read More: While KSI Token Shoots Up 50,000% Crypto Experts are Stacking This New Meme Coin as the Next Crypto to Explode – What Do They Know?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/while-ksi-token-shoots-up-50000-crypto-experts-are-stacking-new-meme-coin-as-next-crypto-explode-what-do-they-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118762/316341/while-ksi-token-shoots-up.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="457560"/></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs: Bitcoin, Ether Supply on Exchanges Fell in June – Bull Market Back?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-bitcoin-ether-supply-exchanges-fell-june-bull-market-back.htm</link><description>Exchange balances of Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH) fell significantly in June as more crypto holders chose to take self-custody, a report by investment bank Goldman Sachs has said. &lt;br /&gt;
Analyzing on-chain data, the Goldman Sachs report said it is likely that many crypto investors have moved their holdings away from exchanges due to fears over regulatory crackdowns and potential security issues related to hacking and theft....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-bitcoin-ether-supply-exchanges-fell-june-bull-market-back.htm"&gt;Read More: Goldman Sachs: Bitcoin, Ether Supply on Exchanges Fell in June – Bull Market Back?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Goldman Sachs</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/goldman-sachs-bitcoin-ether-supply-exchanges-fell-june-bull-market-back.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118769/316333/bull-market.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="285142"/></item><item><title>Binance Halts Transfers of Multichain-Linked Tokens Following May Incident – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-halts-transfers-of-multichain-linked-tokens-following-may-incident-heres-the-latest.htm</link><description>Starting July 7, 2023, Binance will cease to facilitate deposits and withdrawals of several cross-chain bridge tokens associated with the Multichain project across specified networks.  &lt;br /&gt;
This suspension will remain in effect until further notice. &lt;br /&gt;
The decision to suspend support for these tokens comes after the recent issues with the Multichain (MULTI) protocol, leading to the earlier suspension of deposits for multiple Multichain-bridged tokens on May 24, 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-halts-transfers-of-multichain-linked-tokens-following-may-incident-heres-the-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: Binance Halts Transfers of Multichain-Linked Tokens Following May Incident – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>DeFi News</category><category>Binance</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/binance-halts-transfers-of-multichain-linked-tokens-following-may-incident-heres-the-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118761/316326/screenshot-2023-07-05-125539.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="743583"/></item><item><title>Terra Luna Classic is Going to Zero as LUNC Price Keeps Falling But All Attention is on This Lesser Known Crypto – 12 Day Countdown Begins</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-going-zero-as-lunc-price-keeps-falling-but-all-attention-lesser-known-crypto-12-day-countdown-begins.htm</link><description>The Terra Luna Classic price has dropped by 3% in the past 24 hours, with the coin slipping to $0.00008443 and marking a 4.5% loss in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
LUNC is also down by 13.5% in the past month and by 42% since the beginning of the year, with this latter decline standing in stark contrast to most other major tokens (e.g. BTC is up by 83% since January)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-going-zero-as-lunc-price-keeps-falling-but-all-attention-lesser-known-crypto-12-day-countdown-begins.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Luna Classic is Going to Zero as LUNC Price Keeps Falling But All Attention is on This Lesser Known Crypto – 12 Day Countdown Begins&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-luna-classic-going-zero-as-lunc-price-keeps-falling-but-all-attention-lesser-known-crypto-12-day-countdown-begins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118751/316322/terra-luna-classic-is-goi.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1157433"/></item><item><title>Billionaire Mark Cuban And Ex SEC Official Argue Over FTX Collapse And Crypto Regulations</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-ex-sec-official-argue-over-ftx-collapse-crypto-regulations.htm</link><description>American billionaire Mark Cuban and the former US Securities Exchange Commission official John Reed Stark argued over what actually caused the collapse of FTX and how US customers could have been protected better.  &lt;br /&gt;
Shark Tank star Mark Cuban suggested in a tweet that had the US SEC adopted similar regulations as Japan, US customers wouldn’t have lost money in the FTX collapse. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-ex-sec-official-argue-over-ftx-collapse-crypto-regulations.htm"&gt;Read More: Billionaire Mark Cuban And Ex SEC Official Argue Over FTX Collapse And Crypto Regulations&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Mark Cuban</category><category>US SEC</category><category>Crypto Regulation</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/billionaire-mark-cuban-ex-sec-official-argue-over-ftx-collapse-crypto-regulations.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118755/316312/mark-cuban-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="101877"/></item><item><title>Rate Limit Cut on Twitter to Diminish Crypto Visibility on Google</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rate-limit-cut-twitter-diminish-crypto-visibility-google.htm</link><description>Twitter's new rate limits have severely affected the indexing and display of tweets on Google's search engine.  &lt;br /&gt;
According to a recent report from Search Engine Land, Google Search has witnessed a drop of more than half of the indexed URLs from Twitter in recent days, resulting in a significant limitation of reach for the shared information....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rate-limit-cut-twitter-diminish-crypto-visibility-google.htm"&gt;Read More: Rate Limit Cut on Twitter to Diminish Crypto Visibility on Google&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Twitter</category><category>Elon Musk</category><category>Google</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rate-limit-cut-twitter-diminish-crypto-visibility-google.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118757/316309/ae97fd0a8b-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="54320"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: Mark Cuban and Former SEC Official Voice Opinions on Crypto Regulation</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-mark-cuban-former-sec-official-voice-opinions-crypto-regulation.htm</link><description>Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, is currently trading at $30,869, experiencing a 1.10% decrease on Wednesday.  &lt;br /&gt;
In the midst of this price movement, notable figures such as Mark Cuban and a former SEC official have shared their perspectives on crypto regulation, offering valuable insights into the evolving regulatory landscape and its potential impact on Bitcoin. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-mark-cuban-former-sec-official-voice-opinions-crypto-regulation.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: Mark Cuban and Former SEC Official Voice Opinions on Crypto Regulation&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-mark-cuban-former-sec-official-voice-opinions-crypto-regulation.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118723/316265/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1489296"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $0.48 Level – Where is XRP Heading Now?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-048-level-where-xrp-heading-now.htm</link><description>The XRP price has dipped by 0.4% in the past 24 hours, amid a slightly bigger dip for the cryptocurrency market as a whole. &lt;br /&gt;
Despite today's wobble, XRP has held strongly to the $0.480 support level, with its price of $0.488240 representing a 3% gain in the last seven days. &lt;br /&gt;
The altcoin is also down by 8% in the last 30 days, although it remains up by 49% in the last 12 months, pushed higher by positve expectations surrounding Ripple's long-running legal case with the SEC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-048-level-where-xrp-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as Bulls Hold $0.48 Level – Where is XRP Heading Now?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-bulls-hold-048-level-where-xrp-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118736/316295/xrp-price-prediction-as-b.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1426244"/></item><item><title>Current CBDC Models Aren't Viable for Everyday Transactions: Copper's Research Head</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/current-cbdc-models-arent-viable-for-everyday-transactions-coppers-research-head.htm</link><description>In an interview with The Block, Fadi Aboualfa, the head of research at crypto brokerage Copper, expressed that the existing Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) models are "not a viable cash equivalent that people could use in daily transactions." &lt;br /&gt;
Aboualfa raised doubts about CBDCs despite the recent proposal for Hong Kong to launch its (CBDCs) and the Bank of International Settlements (BIS) unveiling a blueprint for a global "unified ledger" to support CBDCs and tokenized assets. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/current-cbdc-models-arent-viable-for-everyday-transactions-coppers-research-head.htm"&gt;Read More: Current CBDC Models Aren't Viable for Everyday Transactions: Copper's Research Head&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Stablecoin</category><category>stablecoins</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/current-cbdc-models-arent-viable-for-everyday-transactions-coppers-research-head.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118741/316294/screenshot-2023-07-05-112831.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="605000"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Users Propose ERC 7265 to Thwart DeFi Hacks – How Does it Work?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-users-propose-erc-7265-thwart-defi-hacks-how-does-it-work.htm</link><description>Members of the Ethereum community have proposed a new standard meant to improve the security of decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols and mitigate hacks.  &lt;br /&gt;
The attacks on DeFi protocols have become all too common, draining billions in user funds. According to DeFiLlama, around $6.6 billion was stolen in exploits so far, with $5.31 billion of that going to DeFi protocol hackers....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-users-propose-erc-7265-thwart-defi-hacks-how-does-it-work.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Users Propose ERC 7265 to Thwart DeFi Hacks – How Does it Work?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Smart Contract</category><category>Security</category><category>Hack</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-users-propose-erc-7265-thwart-defi-hacks-how-does-it-work.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/118734/316307/adobestock-sergey-nivens-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="343466"/></item><item><title>The Top Crypto Gainers Today July 2023 - Biggest Price Gainers List</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency investing continues to remain a speculative endeavor. Nevertheless, this industry can be lucrative for those willing to take risks in the hopes of a big payout - and with the Bitcoin price reclaiming the $30,000 level, investor confidence is returning to the market. &lt;br /&gt;
In this guide, we explore the top crypto gainers for investors to watch right now.  &lt;br /&gt;
Below is a selection of the top crypto gainers on the market now. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers.htm"&gt;Read More: The Top Crypto Gainers Today July 2023 - Biggest Price Gainers List&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/top-crypto-gainers.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/93660/234682/best-crypto-gainers.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="319238"/></item></channel></rss>
