<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Found not Guilty on Charges of Fraud (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-owner-found-not-guilty-on-charges-of-fraud-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bithumb]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231464</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/Bithumb-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Lee Jung-hoon will not go to prison after Judge Kang Gyu-Tae proclaimed him not guilty of committing fraud.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Seoul Central District Court reportedly ruled that the owner and former Chairman of the South Korean cryptocurrency exchange &#8211; Lee Jung-hoon &#8211; has not defrauded Kim Byung-gun for 112 billion won ($87.5 million).</p>
<p>Had he been found guilty, he could have faced a prison sentence of up to eight years.</p>
<h2>The Court&#8217;s Final Word</h2>
<p>According to a local <a href="https://www.hankyung.com/finance/article/202301038848B" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">coverage</a>, the 34th Division of the Criminal Agreement of the Seoul Central District Court found Lee not guilty of the accusations of violating the Act on the Aggravated Punishment Of Specific Economic Crimes (committing fraud).</p>
<p>The authorities ruled that he did not embezzle over $87 million from the Chairman of BK Group &#8211; Kim Byung-gun &#8211; during negotiations regarding the takeover of Bithumb in 2018. Judge Kang Gyu-Tae stated:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It cannot be admitted that the stock trading proceeds were disposed of due to a mistake caused by fraudulent acts, such as the facts of the prosecution, based only on the evidence submitted by the prosecutor.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Bithumb &#8211; which is among the leading cryptocurrency exchanges in South Korea &#8211; said it respects the outcome of the legal case.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Bithumb is operated under a professional management system, and former chairman Lee Jeong-hoon is not involved in Bithumb&#8217;s management at all,&#8221; the company added.</p></blockquote>
<p>Prosecutors previously <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-ex-chair-faces-8-years-in-prison-for-alleged-70m-crypto-fraud-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">insisted</a> that Kim paid the sum as an upfront &#8220;contract fee&#8221; to acquire the Korean trading venue, while Lee assured that Bithumb would list BXA tokens and use the capital from the assets&#8217; sale in the deal. The coin, though, was not issued by the platform but by the Blockchain Exchange Alliance, and the agreement collapsed.</p>
<h2>The Death of Park Mo</h2>
<p>The court ruling comes less than a week after Park Mo was <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vp-of-bithumb-linked-company-found-dead-in-seoul-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">found dead</a> near his home in Seoul. The South Korean served as Vice President of Vidente, the largest shareholder of Bithumb Holdings Co.</p>
<p>Initial investigation disclosed that Park&#8217;s death resulted from suicide. However, some doubted that version since he was under investigation on charges of stealing funds from Bithumb-related firms and manipulating stock prices.</p>
<p>In addition, the platform had a close relation to the fallen crypto giant FTX. While the latter <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumb-owner-confirms-acquisition-discussions-with-ftx/" data-wpel-link="internal">displayed</a> intentions to purchase it during the summer, the liquidity crisis and the eventual filing for bankruptcy protection foiled such plans.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bithumbs-owner-found-not-guilty-on-charges-of-fraud-report/" rel="nofollow">Bithumb&#8217;s Owner Found not Guilty on Charges of Fraud (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Erik Voorhees Predicts When the Next Bitcoin Bull Market Will Start</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/erik-voorhees-predicts-when-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market-will-start/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bear Market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bull Run]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231445</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/bitcoinbull_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[ShapeShaft's CEO claimed bitcoin could rise to $40,000 by this summer if macroeconomic conditions improve.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Erik Voorhees &#8211; CEO of ShapeShaft and an outspoken proponent of bitcoin &#8211; believes it could take between six months and three years before the next crypto bull run occurs. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He also predicted that the primary cryptocurrency could surge to $40,000 by the summer, representing a 140% increase compared to current valuations.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8216;It Won&#8217;t be Ten Years&#8217;</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In a recent </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FxDSFBhetw0" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">interview</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> for Bankless Shows, Voorhees argued that the reigning crypto winter will not last for another decade. However, if this is the case, then &#8220;probably the whole thing failed,&#8221; he added.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The American thinks crypto could enter into a bull run as early as half a year since &#8220;that&#8217;s generally how long it takes people&#8217;s minds to start changing and speculative cycles to return.&#8221;</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">He believes the volatility of the market in the near future will depend on multiple key factors, including the interest rates announced by the Federal Reserve, the macroeconomic environment, and the implementation of possible regulations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">If conditions improve, bitcoin could soar to $40,000 by the summer. Assuming his forecast comes true, this would result in 2.5X profit for investors who decide to enter the ecosystem now:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;It also has a lot to do with the macro environment. As long as interest rates are held high and monetary conditions are tighter, it&#8217;s going to be a headwind. That&#8217;ll start changing in early to mid [2023]. So I wouldn&#8217;t be surprised if bitcoin was at like $40,000 by the summer. That wouldn&#8217;t surprise me at all. And that&#8217;s like 2.5X from here. So it&#8217;s a great return.&#8221;<br />
</span></p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_231460" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231460" style="width: 722px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees.webp" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231460" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees.webp" alt="Erik Voorhees" width="722" height="400" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees.webp 843w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees-300x166.webp 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees-768x425.webp 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Erik-Voorhees-50x28.webp 50w" sizes="(max-width: 722px) 100vw, 722px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231460" class="wp-caption-text">Erik Voorhees, Source: CNN</figcaption></figure>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Voorhees touched upon some severe catastrophes that shuttered the industry in 2022, such as the collapse of centralized organizations (with </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">FTX</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, Three Arrows Capital, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/cel-dumped-50-after-celsius-filed-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy-protection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Celsius Network</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">, and </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-suspending-withdrawals-voyager-digital-files-for-chapter-11-bankruptcy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Voyager Digital</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">). He advised consumers to protect themselves by relying on self-custody methods:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;But that lesson is really the one because if the majority of crypto funds and crypto wealth reside with intermediaries: A) we will never escape the regulation that this stuff is meant to escape, and B) we will never escape the need to trust humans.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Other Predictions</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Some estimate that the prolonged bear market for bitcoin will end in 2024 when the next BTC halving will occur. One proponent of that thesis is Mark Yusko &#8211; CEO of Morgan Creek Capital Management &#8211; who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-next-bull-run-to-come-in-2024-predicts-morgan-creeks-mark-yusko/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true">:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;Then when we get to summer, that&#8217;s when we&#8217;ll get the next speculative move, and guess is that will come in anticipation of the next halving in 2024.&#8221;</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hunter Horsley – CEO of Bitwise &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoins-next-bull-run-will-start-in-2023-according-to-bitwise-ceo/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">believes</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the next bull run will happen this year, adding that price declines are a great opportunity for people to increase their exposure to the primary digital asset. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/erik-voorhees-predicts-when-the-next-bitcoin-bull-market-will-start/" rel="nofollow">Erik Voorhees Predicts When the Next Bitcoin Bull Market Will Start</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Name Service (ENS) Wrapped 2022 With Over 2.2M Registrations</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-ens-wrapped-2022-with-over-2-2m-registrations/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 21:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231318</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/ens_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[September recorded the largest number of ENS registrations created for the year.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum Name Service (ENS) clocked in over 2.2 million domain names in 2022 despite the devastating turmoil in the crypto market. This also represented nearly 80% of all of the domains created since its inception.</p>
<p>Data from Dune Analytics <a href="https://dune.com/makoto/ens" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">revealed</a> that the Ethereum-based distributed domain name service registered more than 2.82 million names as of January 2nd.</p>
<p>ENS domain name purchases are made with Ether tokens. With the fall in the price of the crypto-asset significantly over the year, the cost of gas fees for transactions on the network also plummeted, which at certain stages throughout the year prompted an appreciation in the number of .eth domain name registrations as users capitalized the lower fees.</p>
<h2>ENS Trend Throughout 2022</h2>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/what-is-ens-ethereum-name-service/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">Ethereum Name Service</a> figures were on a consistent uptrend for the first five months of the year. The first prominent high in terms of in .eth domain registrations formed in May. However, the TerraUSD (UST) crash and the subsequent contagion fears gripped the market, which coincided with a drop.</p>
<p>The recovery, however, was quick. July broke the earlier record. Shortly thereafter, it logged a monthly high of 437,365 in September. The Merge may have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-ens-domains-exceed-2-million-after-record-breaking-july/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">played</a> a crucial role in the increased activity.</p>
<p>On the other hand, ENS wrapped up the year at its lowest level, with December being the worst-performing month. A little over 52,000 names were created. Meanwhile, the count of monthly registrations dropped by 88% since its peak just two months prior.</p>
<p>One of the major boosts came from Coinbase <a href="https://www.coinbase.com/blog/what-web3-identity-needs" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">leveraging</a> ENS service to enable users to claim &#8220;name.cb.id&#8221; usernames using Coinbase Wallet’s browser extension. The idea was to facilitate the creation of a free web3 identity for everyone.</p>
<h2>Lawsuit Against GoDaddy</h2>
<p>Another win came in the form of regaining control of the eth.link domain name. The ENS <a href="https://twitter.com/ensdomains/status/1571683432144711680" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">scored</a> a victory on an injunction in its lawsuit against domain provider GoDaddy last September in the US District Court for the District of Arizona.</p>
<p>True Names Ltd., the company behind ENS, sued GoDaddy for allegedly transferring the ENS&#8217;s eth.link name to domain name registrar Dynadot before its expiration date and putting the name up for auction. According to the <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/592846369/Complaint#from_embed" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">complaint</a>, ENS accused GoDaddy of breaching the contract and claimed that the latter&#8217;s action violated the agreement to &#8220;respect, acknowledge, and protect&#8221; the eth.link name.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-name-service-ens-wrapped-2022-with-over-2-2m-registrations/" rel="nofollow">Ethereum Name Service (ENS) Wrapped 2022 With Over 2.2M Registrations</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Partners With Ukrainian Pharmacies to Allow Crypto Payments</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-partners-with-ukrainian-pharmacies-to-allow-crypto-payments/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ukraine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231494</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/binance_ukraine_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/binance_ukraine_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The Ukrainian ANC Pharmacy enables crypto settlements via Binance Pay.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One of the largest pharmacy chains in Ukraine &#8211; ANC Pharmacy &#8211; joined forces with Binance to enable customers to pay for medical products and supplies in cryptocurrencies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The exchange has provided its services to the war-torn country numerous times over the past several months. It donated $10 million worth of digital assets to Ukraine shortly after the launch of the Russian &#8220;special military operation&#8221; and introduced a crypto card designated for Ukrainian refugees.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Buying Pills in Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">ANC Pharmacy <a href="https://anc.ua/blog/binance-krypto-anc" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> that customers can purchase medical products in digital currencies instead of fiat. To do so, they should place their order via the company&#8217;s official website. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The initiative became possible after a collaboration with the world&#8217;s largest crypto platform &#8211; Binance. Users can download the exchange application, choose a certain product, settle the bill using Binance Pay, and can pick up the medicine at any convenient ANC location.</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;First of all, the Binance Pay technology becomes available in pharmacies in Kyiv. We take care of your health while you take care of your cryptocurrency,&#8221; the firm announced.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Binance was among the first to financially stimulate Ukraine after Putin&#8217;s troops invaded the country in February last year. It <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-commits-10-million-to-ukraine-overall-crypto-donations-near-20m/" data-wpel-link="internal">distributed</a> $10 million worth of crypto to support locals affected by the military conflict and established a donation web portal called Ukraine Emergency Relief Fund. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It has amassed nearly 2,936 BTC (as of writing these lines), equaling almost $50 million.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The trading venue also partnered with the financial service provider &#8211; Contis &#8211; to </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-introduces-new-crypto-card-for-ukrainian-refugees/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">release</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the Binance Refugee Crypto Card. The feature enables departing Ukrainians to conduct digital asset transactions and complete payments at retailers in the European Economic Area, which accept cryptocurrency settlements.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Hard Stance on Russians</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Initially, Binance was unwilling to freeze the accounts of Russian-based customers, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-will-not-halt-servicing-russian-accounts-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">claiming</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that many have no relation to the war in Eastern Europe.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The severe monetary sanctions that the EU imposed on Russia in April changed the trends, and the platform </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-updates-its-policy-for-russians-amid-latest-eu-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">limited</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> its services to Russian residents whose crypto holdings exceed the value of 10,000 euros.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">It also </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-terminates-accounts-associated-with-top-russian-officials-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">terminated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the accounts of some individuals associated with high-ranked Russian politicians. Examples are Elizaveta Peskova (the daughter of Vladimir Putin&#8217;s spokesman Dmitry Peskov) and Polina Kovaleva (the stepdaughter of Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov).</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-partners-with-ukrainian-pharmacies-to-allow-crypto-payments/" rel="nofollow">Binance Partners With Ukrainian Pharmacies to Allow Crypto Payments</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Turns 14: Genesis Day and Satoshi&#8217;s Idea of Monetary Sovereignty</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-turns-14-genesis-day-and-satoshis-idea-of-monetary-sovereignty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231459</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin-birthday.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/bitcoin-birthday.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After an annus horribilis of a year, Bitcoin stands resilient. In fact, it just turned 14!]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The streak of bankruptcies and price declines has dampened glimmers of positive progress. But Bitcoin just turned 14 today. January 3 is known as Bitcoin Genesis Day for the first block of BTC ever mined by Satoshi way back in 2009, which paved the way for the cryptocurrency as we know it today.</p>
<p>The first block on the network hosts a single transaction &#8211; the 50 BTC block reward &#8211; sent to the pseudonymous creator(s) for mining it. The BTC mining rewards are yet to be touched.</p>
<p>Since the creation of Satoshi&#8217;s revolutionary monetary system and its intrinsic currency, a lot has changed.</p>
<h1 class="typography__StyledTypography-owin6q-0 hjHKEC">&#8216;Chancellor on the Brink of Second Bailout for Banks&#8217;</h1>
<p>The Genesis block essentially reflects Satoshi&#8217;s rejection of the centralized infrastructures of the current fiat system. The developer, instead, believed in decentralized pillars that were cryptographically secured in a mathematically verifiable digital system.</p>
<p>Clearly, the old system was failing, shaking people&#8217;s faith in banks. Building a new one without all of the controls and perils meant that coincided with the climactic unraveling of the global economy was a major milestone.</p>
<p>Satoshi did not stop there. Before mysteriously disappearing, they covertly coded into the genesis block with an &#8220;Easter Egg.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The Times 03/Jan/2009 Chancellor on brink of second bailout for banks.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The above text is a headline for an article in the edition of The [London] Times about the British government&#8217;s failure to stimulate the economy after the 2007-08 financial crisis. The message was clear. The creation of genesis block on the same day as news of an imminent bank bailout is certainly symbolic.</p>
<p>Bitcoin was designed to serve the exact purpose that financial institutions, which are considered too big to fail, failed to do. Unlike traditional banks, Bitcoin cannot be bailed out. There is no middleman, no third party, nor any sort of corporate entity to meddle between the asset and the consumer.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Consistent Popularity</h2>
<p>No amount of doomsayers and mainstream media declaring Bitcoin dead can actually make the blockchain stop. The crypto-asset has experienced four major bull/bear cycles since its inception.</p>
<p>More than a decade later, Bitcoin remains the most popular cryptocurrency option, despite the creation of thousands.</p>
<p>Data from Nasdaq and Ycharts, as <a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/101hnkr/ethereum_outperformed_bitcoin_by_338_in_number_of/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">shared</a> on Reddit this week, revealed that there is no dethroning the king coin any time soon. While Ethereum recorded more than fourfold with 408.5 million ETH transactions in 2022, Bitcoin still remains the most searched crypto. It even reported a steadier transaction volume in its network than its rival.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-turns-14-genesis-day-and-satoshis-idea-of-monetary-sovereignty/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Turns 14: Genesis Day and Satoshi&#8217;s Idea of Monetary Sovereignty</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>ETH Price Analysis: Ethereum Bulls Gathering Confidence at the Start of 2023, What&#8217;s Next?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/eth-price-analysis-ethereum-bulls-gathering-confidence-at-the-start-of-2023-whats-next/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231483</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ethereum&#8217;s price has been oscillating in a very tight range over the past couple of weeks as the markets were heading into the new year&#8217;s holidays. However, a decisive move may be on the horizon, as the cryptocurrency now resides in a critical area. Technical Analysis By: Edris The Daily Chart: On the daily chart, [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price has been oscillating in a very tight range over the past couple of weeks as the markets were heading into the new year&#8217;s holidays. However, a decisive move may be on the horizon, as the cryptocurrency now resides in a critical area.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Edris</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart:</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, the price has been testing a significant resistance level recently, where the $1250 zone and the 50-day moving average have a confluence.</p>
<p>While the market is yet to break this fundamental level to the upside, a potential bullish breakout would pave the way for a rise toward the 200-day moving average, around a psychologically significant price the $1400. A valid breakout from the mentioned 200-day MA would likely lead to a short-term rally which can drive ETH&#8217;s price toward $1800.</p>
<p>On the other hand, if the price gets rejected to the downside from the $1250 level and the 50-day moving average, a rapid decline toward the bulls&#8217; last resort, which is the $1000 support level, would be more likely.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231486" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231486" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231486 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_030123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-Daily-Jan-3-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231486" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart:</h3>
<p>Looking at the 4-hour timeframe, the recent consolidation pattern has become more evident, as the price has bounced inside a symmetrical triangle forming below the $1250 mark. A valid breakout from either side of the pattern could lead to a further continuation in the direction of the initial breakout.</p>
<p>The $1350 resistance zone would be the likely target for a bullish breakout, while a break below the pattern could potentially lead to a drop toward the $1100 support level.</p>
<p>The RSI indicator can also provide helpful insight, as the momentum is approaching the overbought area, and a potential bearish divergence could form soon, signaling a high probability for a bearish reversal. All in all, the market&#8217;s short-term future is still hanging in the balance, yet a breakout or rejection from the $1250 level could shape the short-term to mid-term price trend, as liquidity will soon return to the markets after the holidays.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231485" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231485" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231485 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_price_chart_030123" width="2560" height="1465" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-300x172.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-1024x586.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-768x440.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-1536x879.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-2048x1172.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/ETHUSDT-4H-Jan-3-2023-50x29.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231485" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Sentiment Analysis</h2>
<p>By: <a href="https://twitter.com/TradingRage" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><strong>Edris</strong></a></p>
<h3>Ethereum Taker Buy Sell Ratio</h3>
<p>Ethereum&#8217;s price is still reluctant to decline further and create a new lower low, and the futures market sentiment is highlighting one of the reasons for this relative strength.</p>
<p>This chart displays the 100-day moving average of the <strong>Taker Buy Sell Ratio</strong>, a metric predominantly used for assessing the futures market sentiment, as it indicates whether the bulls or bears are engaging more aggressively with their orders. Values above 1 show bullish sentiment, and conversely, values below 1 indicate the bears&#8217; dominance. Moves above or below this threshold are also significant, as the metrics&#8217; decline below 1 usually signals a crash in the short term.</p>
<p>This metric has been holding above 1 over the last few months, pointing to the bulls&#8217; resilience in the futures market, as their orders create sufficient demand to prevent the price from dropping below the $1000 mark. If this behavior continues, even higher prices could be expected in the short term, as the price is seemingly forming a base however, if the metric drops below 1, a further continuation of the bear market would be highly probable.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231484" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231484" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231484 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg" alt="eth_buysellratio_chart_030123" width="2560" height="1613" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-1536x968.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-2048x1291.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Ethereum-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-SMA-100-Jan-3-2023-50x32.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231484" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/eth-price-analysis-ethereum-bulls-gathering-confidence-at-the-start-of-2023-whats-next/" rel="nofollow">ETH Price Analysis: Ethereum Bulls Gathering Confidence at the Start of 2023, What&#8217;s Next?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Calm Before the Storm or Will Bitcoin Continue Consolidating? (BTC Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-or-will-bitcoin-continue-consolidating-btc-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 15:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTC Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231340</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The market is currently suffering from insufficient activity and liquidity. Meanwhile, Bitcoin’s price is up against a crucial resistance zone and is about to break out. The move should determine the upcoming direction and end the current close-to-neutral state between selling and buying pressure in the market. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart After [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The market is currently suffering from insufficient activity and liquidity. Meanwhile, Bitcoin’s price is up against a crucial resistance zone and is about to break out. The move should determine the upcoming direction and end the current close-to-neutral state between selling and buying pressure in the market.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>After getting rejected by the 50-day moving average and consolidating for a few days, the price finally tested the blue trendline for the third time and failed to break it to the downside.</p>
<p>Next, the price started a small rally and reached the 50-day moving average at $16.8K. Bitcoin is now struggling within a significant resistance zone between the 50-day moving average and the blue trendline.</p>
<p>A breakout from the moving average will result in a rally with bullish momentum; contrarily, if the price drops below the trendline, a shakeout toward the $15K yearly low will be anticipated.</p>
<p>Yet, the upcoming price action should end the recent confusion between the bears and the bulls in deciding the mid-term market direction.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231480" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231480" style="width: 2428px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231480 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_030123" width="2428" height="1500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1.jpg 2428w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-300x185.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-1024x633.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-768x474.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-1536x949.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-2048x1265.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-1D-1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2428px) 100vw, 2428px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231480" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-hour time frame, the $16.4K region has become a promising support zone for the last couple of days. Most recently, the price initiated a small rally after retesting this level. However, the momentum is not promising, as Bitcoin has been printing small candles.</p>
<p>There is a static resistance level in Bitcoin’s path toward $18K, at $17K. Considering the weak momentum and the fragile neutral sentiment, the price will possibly consolidate in the range between the $16.4K support and the $17K resistance levels on a mid-term basis.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231481" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231481" style="width: 2428px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231481 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1.jpg" alt="btc_price_chart_030123" width="2428" height="1500" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1.jpg 2428w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-300x185.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1024x633.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-768x474.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-1536x949.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-2048x1265.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTC-4H-1-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2428px) 100vw, 2428px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231481" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Onchain Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="http://twitter.com/Greatest_Trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<p>The chart below illustrates the <strong>Taker Buy/Sell Ratio</strong> metric alongside Bitcoin’s price. The metric is the ratio of buy volume divided by the sell volume for takers in perpetual swap trades tracing the overall sentiment in the derivative market. Values over 1 indicate predominant bullish sentiment, while values under 1 indicate bearish sentiment is prevailing.</p>
<p>As the chart shows, there are two apparent static levels; 1.03 (in green) and 0.97 (in red). The price has experienced a bullish surge whenever the metric surpassed the 1.03 level. Alternatively, Bitcoin has plunged while the metric tumbled below the red line as more sell orders were filled.</p>
<p>The current value has been consolidating around one since August 2022, denoting long-time neutrality in the perpetual market due to a lack of liquidity. Bitcoin is far-fetched to initiate a promising rally if liquidity or sufficient demand doesn’t return to the market.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231335" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231335" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-231335 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-scaled.jpg" alt="btc_buysellratio_chart_030123" width="2560" height="1612" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-300x189.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-1024x645.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-768x484.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-1536x967.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-2048x1290.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Bitcoin-Taker-Buy-Sell-Ratio-All-Exchanges-SMA-14-50x31.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231335" class="wp-caption-text">Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/calm-before-the-storm-or-will-bitcoin-continue-consolidating-btc-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Calm Before the Storm or Will Bitcoin Continue Consolidating? (BTC Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bahamas Regulator SCB Denies Asking FTX to Mint New Tokens</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-regulator-scb-denies-asking-ftx-to-mint-new-tokens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231472</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bahamas.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/11/FTX_Bahamas.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The SCB said it did not order FTX to create new crypto tokens worth hundreds of millions, as alleged by the exchange. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">The Securities Commission of The Bahamas (SCB) has refuted the claims made by FTX debtors that it had instructed the crypto exchange to mint tokens worth hundreds of millions.</p>
<p class="p2">In an <a href="https://twitter.com/SCBgov_bs/status/1610084773472485380" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">official statement</span></a> released on Jan. 3, the regulator sought to correct the material misstatements of FTX&#8217;s new CEO, John J. Ray III, in a series of court filings that received global media coverage.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>SCB Allegedly Asked SBF to Mint New Tokens</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Last month, FTX lawyers made several public <span class="s1"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-bahamas-asked-sbf-to-mint-new-crypto-worth-hundreds-of-millions-us-lawyers-claim/" data-wpel-link="internal">statements</a> alleging</span> that Bahamian authorities reportedly ordered the exchange&#8217;s founder, Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), to issue a new cryptocurrency to the tune of $300 million, which local officials would control.</p>
<p class="p2">The SCB statement also pointed out that the Chapter 11 Debtors had debated the value of seized digital assets held by the regulator in November.</p>
<p class="p2">Recall that last month, the <span class="s1">regulator <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-seized-3-5-billion-from-ftx-to-keep-them-from-vanishing/" data-wpel-link="internal">announced</a></span> that it had seized more than $3.5 billion worth of digital assets from the exchange&#8217;s Bahamian arm, FTX Digital Markets, which it was holding with the intent of using them to repay customers and other creditors.</p>
<p class="p2">However, FTX <span class="s1">quickly <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/ftx-debtors-provide-information-concerning-bahamas-crypto-seizure-301711610.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">disputed</a></span> the SCB&#8217;s calculations, claiming that its digital assets seized were worth just $296 million and not the $3.5 billion reported by the securities watchdog.</p>
<h2 class="p4"><b>FTX&#8217;s Claims Were Based on &#8220;Incomplete Information&#8221; </b></h2>
<p class="p2">In the statement, the SCB argued that these claims were based on &#8220;incomplete information,&#8221; adding that the debtors had failed to do due diligence before making such accusations.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;The Chapter 11 Debtors chose not to utilize their ability to request information from the Joint Provisional Liquidators pursuant to a court order of the Supreme Court of The Bahamas that the Commission obtained in an effort to allow the Chapter 11 Debtors to obtain this information… The US Debtors&#8217; continued lack of diligence when making public statements concerning the Commission is disappointing,&#8221; the regulator said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">The SCB further expressed concerns that its investigation is being jeopardized by the Chapter 11 Debtors&#8217; insistence on denying the Court Supervised Joint Provisional Liquidators access to FTX&#8217;s AWS System.</p>
<p class="p2">The regulator urged Chapter 11 Debtors to proceed with matters bearing the best interest of FTX customers and creditors.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-regulator-scb-denies-asking-ftx-to-mint-new-tokens/" rel="nofollow">Bahamas Regulator SCB Denies Asking FTX to Mint New Tokens</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>3AC Co-Founder Zhu Su Accuses DCG of Being Criminally Fraudulent</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founder-zhu-su-accuses-dcg-of-being-criminally-fraudulent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 11:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Currency Group]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231442</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/ThreeArrows-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/ThreeArrows-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The founder of the hedge fund Three Arrows Capital which went bust last year has leveled fresh allegations against Digital Currency Group. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Three Arrows Capital (3AC), a Singapore-based crypto hedge fund, became one of the many industry participants that went bankrupt in the bear market. At its peak, 3AC managed more than $10 billion worth of assets. Its undoing was disastrous but wasn’t purely a market-driven phenomenon.</p>
<p>In the latest Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/zhusu/status/1610093549651136512" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">thread</a>, Zhu Su said the parent firm of Grayscale Investments and Genesis Trading conspired with FTX to bring down Terra’s LUNA token and Staked Ether (stETH).</p>
<h2>Zhu Su Blasts DCG and FTX</h2>
<p>Both firms &#8211; DCG and FTX &#8211; suffered hefty losses as 3AC went bankrupt after the Terra collapse. The contagion spurred troubles in other firms involved in GBTC, including Babel Finance. The 3AC founder alleged that DCG could have &#8220;calmly restructured&#8221; during the turmoil but chose not to do so.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Instead they fabricated a left pocket right pocket callable promissory note that magically filled the hole. This is like a kid losing at poker and saying &#8220;I am fine, my dad will pay you, let me keep playing,&#8221; but if your dad is actually yourself.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Zhu, who was recently claimed to have been on the run, also accused DCG and FTX of misdirecting for months and using different techniques to attack the hedge fund. He further alleged that the two companies raked in more deposits while being insolvent in anticipation that the market would go up.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;dcg value is 0, criminal fraud, ftx creditors also have a case for fraudulent conveyance on Alameda returns of capital to Genesis. most OGs are well aware of how close Barry and SBF were since the beginning (SBF is on board of genesis, they gave him his first ftt backed loan).&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Backlash Against DCG Founder</h2>
<p>The aftermath of Sam Bankman-Fried’s crypto empire has become a lot messier. Gemini co-founder and crypto magnate Cameron Winklevoss accused DCG chief Barry Silbert of &#8220;bad faith stall tactics and claimed that his parent company owed $1.675 billion to its subsidiary Genesis.</p>
<p>In a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cameron-winklevoss-calls-out-barry-silbert-on-1-675b-debt-latter-fires-back/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">letter</a> addressed to Silbert on January 2nd, Winklevoss said Gemini tried to hash out a resolution with the exec and the company on numerous occasions but was unable to do so despite repeated efforts. While accusing the DCG founder of &#8220;hiding behind lawyers, investment bankers,&#8221; he sought answers with regards to the $900 million inaccessible funds that Gemini&#8217;s 340,000 earn customers had deposited via the Earn program.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/3ac-co-founder-zhu-su-accuses-dcg-of-being-criminally-fraudulent/" rel="nofollow">3AC Co-Founder Zhu Su Accuses DCG of Being Criminally Fraudulent</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Stopped Ahead of $17K, Solana Taps 10-Day High (Market Watch)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stopped-ahead-of-17k-solana-taps-10-day-high-market-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 09:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231452</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Solana-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/Solana-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Solana's price performance has been quite positive ever since Vitalik Buterin's comments.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin tried to challenge $17,000 hours ago but was stopped before having the chance to come close, at least for now.</p>
<p>The altcoins have calmed since yesterday&#8217;s impressive gains, except for Solana, which continues to recover its recent losses and LDO.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin Came Close to $17K</h2>
<p>The end of 2022 was untypically calm for the primary cryptocurrency, which remained around $16,500 after losing a few hundred dollars throughout the week.</p>
<p>Although the first day of the new year brought a similar lack of volatility, the landscape started to change yesterday. Amid some quite <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/four-great-and-one-terrible-bitcoin-price-predictions-for-2023/" data-wpel-link="internal">promising predictions</a> for 2023, BTC added almost 2% of value and tapped a 5-day high of just over $16,750.</p>
<p>The asset went slightly higher hours later but was stopped before having the chance to challenge $17,000. As such, it stays on familiar ground now.</p>
<p>Its market capitalization has remained inches above $320 billion, while its dominance over the alternative coins is just shy of 40%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231453" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231453" style="width: 1834px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231453" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1834" height="850" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2.png 1834w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2-300x139.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2-1024x475.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2-768x356.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2-1536x712.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/BTCUSD-2-50x23.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1834px) 100vw, 1834px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231453" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>SOL Keeps Pumping</h2>
<p>Solana became one of the most affected victims of the FTX-Alameda crash, given its relationship with the former SBF-led crypto empire. The past few days of 2022 were violent as well, with SOL <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dips-below-16-5k-solana-down-23-weekly-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">dumping</a> to $8 for the first time in about a month.</p>
<p>Despite the unfavorable price performances, though, Ethereum&#8217;s Vitalik Buterin had some <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereums-vitalik-buterin-comments-on-solanas-future/" data-wpel-link="internal">positive comments</a> for Solana at the time. Since then, the asset has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/solana-recovers-15-okb-skyrockets-to-1-year-high-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">outperformed</a> the rest of the market and now trades close to $12. This means SOL has increased by roughly 50% in days.</p>
<p>Lido&#8217;s native cryptocurrency is another impressive gainer now, following the protocol&#8217;s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-protocol-lido-reaches-5-9b-in-tvl-dethroning-makerdao/" data-wpel-link="internal">surpassing</a> of MakerDAO as the leading DeFi project in terms of TVL. LDO has jumped by 7% and sits close to $1.25.</p>
<p>Terra Classic (LUNC) is up by over 5% in the past 24 hours, nearing $0.0002.</p>
<p>The larger-cap alts have stalled since yesterday&#8217;s gains, with ETH standing at just over $1,200 and Binance Coin trading close to $250.</p>
<p>The cumulative market cap of all crypto assets has remained above $800 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231454" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231454" style="width: 1870px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231454" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins.png" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1870" height="826" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins.png 1870w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-1024x452.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-768x339.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-1536x678.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/01/Allcoins-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1870px) 100vw, 1870px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231454" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-stopped-ahead-of-17k-solana-taps-10-day-high-market-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Stopped Ahead of $17K, Solana Taps 10-Day High (Market Watch)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
