<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 04:08:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The May Investment Trifecta: Big Eyes Coin, Binance Coin, and Litecoin are Crypto Picks for the Month]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-may-investment-trifecta-big-eyes-coin-binance-coin-and-litecoin-are-crypto-picks-for-the-month</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-16-at-005839.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-16-at-005839.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-16-at-005839.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-may-investment-trifecta-big-eyes-coin-binance-coin-and-litecoin-are-crypto-picks-for-the-month</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Meme coin, stablecoin, or altcoin, which one is the right pick? This is the question that every crypto enthusiast and investor has when it comes to cryptocurrency, and luckily for you, this article has the insight you are looking for.</p>
<p>The three hot picks in terms of investment opportunities for today based on trending news are as follows. Your recommended picks for May include Big Eyes Coin (BIG), Binance Coin (BNB), and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin: Presale Blowout!</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin will be ending its presale on June 3rd, and to end things in the best way possible, investors can apply code END300 during checkout, which will grant users an additional 300% of the meme coin. BIG is a cat-themed meme coin with the biggest eyes you ever saw. Don&rsquo;t worry, and it&rsquo;s not the big bad wolf from &ldquo;Little Red Riding Hood&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Instead, the feline possesses BIG blue eyes similar to Tweety Bird but even cuter. BIG has secured over $35 million during the 13 stages of presale and has been certified and audited by CoinSniper. The Know Your Coin (KYC) certification from CoinSniper adds an extra layer of protection to safeguard against fraud and scams and is a welcomed certification.</p>
<p>BIG has developed a large community following and will be contributing 5% towards ocean-based charities. The Large community also helps ensure the token&rsquo;s success and is now a requirement, as seen by Dogecoin&rsquo;s success. Doge is the current king of the meme coin. However, BIG is a worthy queen to overthrow the king and usher in a new era of profitability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum Fall While Binance Coin Shines</p>
<p>The headline from Yahoo Finance is that Bitcoin (BTC) dropped in value by 2.2% and Ethereum (ETH) by 2.83%. The biggest loser of the day was Solana (SOL), which fell by 4.72%, followed by Litecoin (LTC), which dropped by 3.42% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The only resilient stable coin was the Binance Coin which gained 3.71%, increasing its value to $333 and gaining 1.39% over the week. The reason behind the strength of the BNB is introducing the SUI blockchain token to its launch pool. Users can now stake their BNB and TrueUSD (TUSD) to farm SUI.</p>
<p>BNB is currently trading at $324.26 and has seen a 3% drop in the last 24 hours; however, it has gained 2.8 in the previous 30 days. The decline witnessed in the crypto market concerns the unclear rules and regulations regarding crypto.</p>
<p>Chainlink To Ride the Bull&nbsp;</p>
<p>Chainlink has been favoured and is predicted to go on a bull run due to its recent ecosystem expansion. Chainlink shared the news of the ten integrations via Twitter, featuring three services across five unique blockchain protocols. The integration included Ethereum, Avalanche, Polygon, Solan, and BNB blockchains.</p>
<p>Chainlink is a must-watch oracle power Web 2.0 ecosystem that has secured $7 million in Total Vale Enabled (TVW). Chainlink is known for its lower volatility and is trading at $6.93, with a 1.1% decline in the last 34 hours. Based on its stability and network growth, the token is at a 30-day low of -8.3% and is expected to take off for a bull run.</p>
<p>Picking the right cryptocurrency to invest in can be daunting, but with the right information, investors can make informed decisions. Based on the trending news, the recommended picks for May are Big Eyes Coin (BIG), Binance Coin (BNB), and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Use Promo Code &lsquo;END300&rsquo; during checking for 300% Bonus</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/ &nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/ &nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL &nbsp;</p>
<p>Opensea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meme coin, stablecoin, or altcoin, which one is the right pick? This is the question that every crypto enthusiast and investor has when it comes to cryptocurrency, and luckily for you, this article has the insight you are looking for.</p>
<p>The three hot picks in terms of investment opportunities for today based on trending news are as follows. Your recommended picks for May include Big Eyes Coin (BIG), Binance Coin (BNB), and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin: Presale Blowout!</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin will be ending its presale on June 3rd, and to end things in the best way possible, investors can apply code END300 during checkout, which will grant users an additional 300% of the meme coin. BIG is a cat-themed meme coin with the biggest eyes you ever saw. Don&rsquo;t worry, and it&rsquo;s not the big bad wolf from &ldquo;Little Red Riding Hood&rdquo;.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Instead, the feline possesses BIG blue eyes similar to Tweety Bird but even cuter. BIG has secured over $35 million during the 13 stages of presale and has been certified and audited by CoinSniper. The Know Your Coin (KYC) certification from CoinSniper adds an extra layer of protection to safeguard against fraud and scams and is a welcomed certification.</p>
<p>BIG has developed a large community following and will be contributing 5% towards ocean-based charities. The Large community also helps ensure the token&rsquo;s success and is now a requirement, as seen by Dogecoin&rsquo;s success. Doge is the current king of the meme coin. However, BIG is a worthy queen to overthrow the king and usher in a new era of profitability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin and Ethereum Fall While Binance Coin Shines</p>
<p>The headline from Yahoo Finance is that Bitcoin (BTC) dropped in value by 2.2% and Ethereum (ETH) by 2.83%. The biggest loser of the day was Solana (SOL), which fell by 4.72%, followed by Litecoin (LTC), which dropped by 3.42% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The only resilient stable coin was the Binance Coin which gained 3.71%, increasing its value to $333 and gaining 1.39% over the week. The reason behind the strength of the BNB is introducing the SUI blockchain token to its launch pool. Users can now stake their BNB and TrueUSD (TUSD) to farm SUI.</p>
<p>BNB is currently trading at $324.26 and has seen a 3% drop in the last 24 hours; however, it has gained 2.8 in the previous 30 days. The decline witnessed in the crypto market concerns the unclear rules and regulations regarding crypto.</p>
<p>Chainlink To Ride the Bull&nbsp;</p>
<p>Chainlink has been favoured and is predicted to go on a bull run due to its recent ecosystem expansion. Chainlink shared the news of the ten integrations via Twitter, featuring three services across five unique blockchain protocols. The integration included Ethereum, Avalanche, Polygon, Solan, and BNB blockchains.</p>
<p>Chainlink is a must-watch oracle power Web 2.0 ecosystem that has secured $7 million in Total Vale Enabled (TVW). Chainlink is known for its lower volatility and is trading at $6.93, with a 1.1% decline in the last 34 hours. Based on its stability and network growth, the token is at a 30-day low of -8.3% and is expected to take off for a bull run.</p>
<p>Picking the right cryptocurrency to invest in can be daunting, but with the right information, investors can make informed decisions. Based on the trending news, the recommended picks for May are Big Eyes Coin (BIG), Binance Coin (BNB), and Chainlink (LINK).&nbsp;</p>
<p>Use Promo Code &lsquo;END300&rsquo; during checking for 300% Bonus</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/ &nbsp;</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/ &nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL &nbsp;</p>
<p>Opensea: https://opensea.io/collection/big-eyes-lootbox-cards&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Your Path To Free Crypto Rewards With DogeMiyagi, Avalanche, And Cosmos]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/your-path-to-free-crypto-rewards-with-dogemiyagi-avalanche-and-cosmos</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-583.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-583.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-583.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/your-path-to-free-crypto-rewards-with-dogemiyagi-avalanche-and-cosmos</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of blockchain, there's a powerful way to secure and strengthen public networks while reaping lucrative rewards. It's called staking, and it's a journey that can take you to the forefront of the crypto revolution.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Enter Avalanche (AVAX) and Comsos (ATOM), two cryptos offering staking rewards like no other. Newcomer DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) is also offering its own rewards: a referral system that lets users indulge in the thrill of earning free crypto by enjoying a whopping 10% of the commission. The popular soundbite of &ldquo;passive income&rdquo; is very apt when it comes to these cryptocurrencies!</p>
<p>Avalanche - Unleashing An Avalanche Of Staking Rewards</p>
<p>Avalanche (AVAX) sets itself apart from the crowd with its unique Proof-of-Stake&nbsp; (PoS) consensus mechanism, offering unparalleled scalability and efficiency. Comparable to the likes of Polkadot and Cosmos, Avalanche surpasses its competitors with its remarkable throughput and lightning-quick transaction finality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Avalanche's architecture revolves around its ingenious Proof-of-Stake consensus mechanism. This means that AVAX token holders have the exciting opportunity to earn staking rewards by pledging their holdings to secure the blockchain. Staking is the act of locking up your AVAX tokens, fortifying the Avalanche network's economic security. By incentivizing token holders to act in the network's best interests, Avalanche establishes a bond of trust and integrity that safeguards the network's value.</p>
<p>So, whether you're a crypto enthusiast looking to ride the Avalanche wave or a developer eager to unleash your dApp on a high-speed, tailor-made blockchain, Avalanche beckons you with open arms. Join the revolution, stake your claim, and experience a blockchain adventure like no other.</p>
<p>Cosmos - Revolutionises Connectivity And Collaboration</p>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) has emerged as a trailblazer, smashing through the barriers that once kept different blockchains from chatting and doing business with each other. It's like watching an otherworldly dance of interconnectedness, and investors and developers are absolutely captivated. With a mind-boggling 400 projects in its vibrant ecosystem, Cosmos is a bona fide hotbed of innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the heart of staking lies the concept of economic security. By locking up your ATOM, you become a guardian of the blockchain, ensuring its protection. But here's where the adventure begins: not only do you play a vital role in securing the network, but you also get to earn crypto assets in return. Through staking Cosmos, you can earn rewards that will leave you grinning from ear to ear.</p>
<p>Once you complete the staking transaction, a world of crypto rewards unfolds before your eyes. As a staker, you hold the reins, deciding when the time is right to claim your accumulated rewards. With a simple transaction sent through your wallet, you unlock the treasure trove that's been patiently waiting for you.</p>
<p></p>
<p>DogeMiyagi - The Sensei Sensation&nbsp;</p>
<p>Looking to add a little extra punch to your crypto journey? Say hello to DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI), the fresh-faced contender that's turning heads with its groundbreaking approach to sustainability and ethical practices. Brace yourselves for a whirlwind of innovation and principles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the helm of this new innovative crypto stands none other than the charismatic Mr. Dogemiyagi. With a twinkle in his eye and a heart full of determination, this is no ordinary crypto crusader. DogeMiyagi has learned from the mistakes of other meme coins and is all about prioritizing principles before diving headfirst into the wild crypto waters.</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi knows how to reward its members in style. With its special referral program, DogeMiyagi enthusiasts can turn their network into a source of substantial benefits. It's simple: refer others to join the DogeMiyagi community and watch the rewards flow into your wallet. When you successfully refer someone to DogeMiyagi, you'll earn a juicy 10% commission on their investment. That's right, a sweet slice of the pie that's automatically awarded to your wallet with no fuss or hassle.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi's referral program isn't just a token gesture; it's a genuine opportunity to supercharge your investments. So, gather your friends, family, and fellow crypto enthusiasts, and invite them to join the DogeMiyagi community. Not only will they gain access to an exciting and vibrant ecosystem, but they'll also reap the rewards and revel in the thrill of building a thriving network.</p>
<p>For more information on DogeMiyagi:</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of blockchain, there's a powerful way to secure and strengthen public networks while reaping lucrative rewards. It's called staking, and it's a journey that can take you to the forefront of the crypto revolution.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Enter Avalanche (AVAX) and Comsos (ATOM), two cryptos offering staking rewards like no other. Newcomer DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI) is also offering its own rewards: a referral system that lets users indulge in the thrill of earning free crypto by enjoying a whopping 10% of the commission. The popular soundbite of &ldquo;passive income&rdquo; is very apt when it comes to these cryptocurrencies!</p>
<p>Avalanche - Unleashing An Avalanche Of Staking Rewards</p>
<p>Avalanche (AVAX) sets itself apart from the crowd with its unique Proof-of-Stake&nbsp; (PoS) consensus mechanism, offering unparalleled scalability and efficiency. Comparable to the likes of Polkadot and Cosmos, Avalanche surpasses its competitors with its remarkable throughput and lightning-quick transaction finality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Avalanche's architecture revolves around its ingenious Proof-of-Stake consensus mechanism. This means that AVAX token holders have the exciting opportunity to earn staking rewards by pledging their holdings to secure the blockchain. Staking is the act of locking up your AVAX tokens, fortifying the Avalanche network's economic security. By incentivizing token holders to act in the network's best interests, Avalanche establishes a bond of trust and integrity that safeguards the network's value.</p>
<p>So, whether you're a crypto enthusiast looking to ride the Avalanche wave or a developer eager to unleash your dApp on a high-speed, tailor-made blockchain, Avalanche beckons you with open arms. Join the revolution, stake your claim, and experience a blockchain adventure like no other.</p>
<p>Cosmos - Revolutionises Connectivity And Collaboration</p>
<p>Cosmos (ATOM) has emerged as a trailblazer, smashing through the barriers that once kept different blockchains from chatting and doing business with each other. It's like watching an otherworldly dance of interconnectedness, and investors and developers are absolutely captivated. With a mind-boggling 400 projects in its vibrant ecosystem, Cosmos is a bona fide hotbed of innovation.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the heart of staking lies the concept of economic security. By locking up your ATOM, you become a guardian of the blockchain, ensuring its protection. But here's where the adventure begins: not only do you play a vital role in securing the network, but you also get to earn crypto assets in return. Through staking Cosmos, you can earn rewards that will leave you grinning from ear to ear.</p>
<p>Once you complete the staking transaction, a world of crypto rewards unfolds before your eyes. As a staker, you hold the reins, deciding when the time is right to claim your accumulated rewards. With a simple transaction sent through your wallet, you unlock the treasure trove that's been patiently waiting for you.</p>
<p></p>
<p>DogeMiyagi - The Sensei Sensation&nbsp;</p>
<p>Looking to add a little extra punch to your crypto journey? Say hello to DogeMiyagi (MIYAGI), the fresh-faced contender that's turning heads with its groundbreaking approach to sustainability and ethical practices. Brace yourselves for a whirlwind of innovation and principles.&nbsp;</p>
<p>At the helm of this new innovative crypto stands none other than the charismatic Mr. Dogemiyagi. With a twinkle in his eye and a heart full of determination, this is no ordinary crypto crusader. DogeMiyagi has learned from the mistakes of other meme coins and is all about prioritizing principles before diving headfirst into the wild crypto waters.</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi knows how to reward its members in style. With its special referral program, DogeMiyagi enthusiasts can turn their network into a source of substantial benefits. It's simple: refer others to join the DogeMiyagi community and watch the rewards flow into your wallet. When you successfully refer someone to DogeMiyagi, you'll earn a juicy 10% commission on their investment. That's right, a sweet slice of the pie that's automatically awarded to your wallet with no fuss or hassle.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DogeMiyagi's referral program isn't just a token gesture; it's a genuine opportunity to supercharge your investments. So, gather your friends, family, and fellow crypto enthusiasts, and invite them to join the DogeMiyagi community. Not only will they gain access to an exciting and vibrant ecosystem, but they'll also reap the rewards and revel in the thrill of building a thriving network.</p>
<p>For more information on DogeMiyagi:</p>
<p>Website: https://dogemiyagi.com&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/_Dogemiyagi_&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/dogemiyagi&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Merov Introduces a Suite of Services for the Bitcoin Mining Industry]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Merov_1684182194tTAeJU4VcN.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Merov_1684182194tTAeJU4VcN.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Merov_1684182194tTAeJU4VcN.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:02:12 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/merov-introduces-a-suite-of-services-for-the-bitcoin-mining-industry</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Salem, Oregon, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Merov is proud to announce the launch of its comprehensive suite of services designed for the Bitcoin mining industry. The suite of services includes Merov Hosting, Rejuvit Systems by Merov, and Merov Marketplace, each providing solutions to the needs of the Bitcoin mining industry.</p><p>&ldquo;As a pioneer in the industry, we are excited about the opportunities these services present, and we look forward to continuing to innovate and provide exceptional services to the Bitcoin mining community,&rdquo; said Montana L. Dukes, Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Merov.</p><p></p><p>Merov Hosting offers state-of-the-art colocation facilities designed to provide the highest levels of performance, reliability, and security for Bitcoin miners.</p><p>Rejuvit Systems by Merov is a US-based parts distributor and ASIC repair company with high-quality repair, training, and tools at competitive prices.</p><p>Merov Marketplace is an innovative platform that provides due diligence, asset sale, distribution, and procurement services to the Bitcoin mining industry. It is currently in beta testing and will launch in Q3 &lsquo;23.</p><p>Milestones Achieved</p><ul><li>$771.96mm in ASIC mining infrastructure deals closed or currently engaged in.</li><li>105,455 ASICs processed through Merov&rsquo;s acquisition, verification, repair, or fulfillment services.</li><li>400+ megawatts of colocation capacity becoming available '23-'24.</li></ul><p>About Merov:</p><p>Merov is a team of passionate and experienced professionals committed to enhancing the Bitcoin industry. With a deep understanding of the industry and a range of expertise in related fields, we strive to deliver innovative, reliable, and comprehensive solutions tailored to our clients' needs.</p><p>Our mission is to bridge gaps and streamline operations, enabling businesses and individuals to thrive in the rapidly evolving world of Bitcoin. By pushing the boundaries of technology and staying at the forefront of industry developments, we are dedicated to driving growth, fostering innovation, and empowering our clients to reach their full potential.</p><p>Follow Merov on Telegram and Twitter.</p><p>Merov is a proud sponsor of the Bitcoin Conference, May 18-20, 2023. Come meet the Merov team at booth 1206.</p>ContactChief Creative OfficerRachel SchimelmanMerovpress@merov.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Salem, Oregon, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Merov is proud to announce the launch of its comprehensive suite of services designed for the Bitcoin mining industry. The suite of services includes Merov Hosting, Rejuvit Systems by Merov, and Merov Marketplace, each providing solutions to the needs of the Bitcoin mining industry.</p><p>&ldquo;As a pioneer in the industry, we are excited about the opportunities these services present, and we look forward to continuing to innovate and provide exceptional services to the Bitcoin mining community,&rdquo; said Montana L. Dukes, Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Merov.</p><p></p><p>Merov Hosting offers state-of-the-art colocation facilities designed to provide the highest levels of performance, reliability, and security for Bitcoin miners.</p><p>Rejuvit Systems by Merov is a US-based parts distributor and ASIC repair company with high-quality repair, training, and tools at competitive prices.</p><p>Merov Marketplace is an innovative platform that provides due diligence, asset sale, distribution, and procurement services to the Bitcoin mining industry. It is currently in beta testing and will launch in Q3 &lsquo;23.</p><p>Milestones Achieved</p><ul><li>$771.96mm in ASIC mining infrastructure deals closed or currently engaged in.</li><li>105,455 ASICs processed through Merov&rsquo;s acquisition, verification, repair, or fulfillment services.</li><li>400+ megawatts of colocation capacity becoming available '23-'24.</li></ul><p>About Merov:</p><p>Merov is a team of passionate and experienced professionals committed to enhancing the Bitcoin industry. With a deep understanding of the industry and a range of expertise in related fields, we strive to deliver innovative, reliable, and comprehensive solutions tailored to our clients' needs.</p><p>Our mission is to bridge gaps and streamline operations, enabling businesses and individuals to thrive in the rapidly evolving world of Bitcoin. By pushing the boundaries of technology and staying at the forefront of industry developments, we are dedicated to driving growth, fostering innovation, and empowering our clients to reach their full potential.</p><p>Follow Merov on Telegram and Twitter.</p><p>Merov is a proud sponsor of the Bitcoin Conference, May 18-20, 2023. Come meet the Merov team at booth 1206.</p>ContactChief Creative OfficerRachel SchimelmanMerovpress@merov.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) to drop to $25K, Polygon (MATIC) Hits 90-Day Low as Yachtify (YCHT) Shines]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-btc-to-drop-to-25k-polygon-matic-hits-90-day-low-as-yachtify-ycht-shines</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204037.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204037.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204037.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-btc-to-drop-to-25k-polygon-matic-hits-90-day-low-as-yachtify-ycht-shines</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Yachtify (YCHT) is rapidly gaining attention in the cryptocurrency space as a beacon of innovation and growth, while other prominent cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Polygon (MATIC) are facing a downturn. With Bitcoin's price speculated to drop to $25K and Polygon (MATIC) hitting a 90-day low, investors are increasingly seeking alternative investment opportunities. </p>
<p class="s5">Amidst this uncertain market landscape, Yachtify (YCHT) shines as a promising platform, revolutionizing the way investors engage with luxury yacht investments and offering a unique value proposition in the ever-evolving world of digital assets.</p>
<p class="s8">Yachtify (YCHT) Shines: A New Era of Fractionalized Yacht Investment</p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify (YCHT) is making waves in the cryptocurrency market with its innovative approach to fractional yacht ownership. Offering an exciting opportunity for investors, the YCHT presale boasts a token price of just $0.12 and a 30% bonus on purchases made during this stage. Yachtify's unique model provides a more accessible and cost-effective way for individuals to invest in luxury yachts.</p>
<p class="s5">The YCHT token brings several benefits to the table, including the ability to participate in the profitable world of yacht ownership without the need for substantial capital. Through fractionalization, Yachtify enables investors to buy and sell shares in yachts, which helps to democratize the traditionally exclusive yacht market.</p>
<p class="s5">One of the key features of Yachtify is the utilization of blockchain technology to create a transparent and secure platform for fractional yacht investment. This ensures that investors can confidently trade their YCHT tokens without worrying about potential fraud or discrepancies in ownership records.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s8">Bitcoin (BTC) Will Drop to $25K?</p>
<p class="s5">Cryptocurrency trader and analyst, Altcoin Sherpa, recently took to Twitter to predict a drop in Bitcoin's (BTC) price to $25K in the near future. Citing the $25K level as a confluent level for Bitcoin (BTC) price, the analyst's tweet comes amidst a 2.67% drop in Bitcoin (BTC) value in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p class="s5">Currently trading at $27,520.99, Bitcoin (BTC) price faces the possibility of a further downturn as Bitcoin (BTC) heads toward the key support level at $26,800. As bearish signals emerge from technical indicators, the market leader could soon reach the predicted $25K price point, potentially providing traders an opportunity to capitalize on Bitcoin (BTC) decline.</p>
<p class="s8">Polygon (MATIC) Hits 90-Day Low</p>
<p class="s5">Polygon (MATIC) price recently plunged to a 90-day low of $0.886 amid bearish market dominance. With a 3.69% drop to $0.8945 at press time, the increased volatility has attracted short-term traders to the Polygon (MATIC) market. </p>
<p class="s5">The market capitalization of Polygon (MATIC) decreased by 3.77% to $8,254,089,404, while the 24-hour trading volume rose by 15.65% to $436,899,775. The Arnaud Legoux Moving Average (ALMA) indicator reveals a bearish momentum and the Aroon down reading of 71.43% indicates a stronger selling pressure. However, the Keltner Channel bands suggest that the Polygon (MATIC) market is oversold, which may lead to an upward reversal soon.</p>
<p class="s12">Join Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s5">Yachtify (YCHT) is rapidly gaining attention in the cryptocurrency space as a beacon of innovation and growth, while other prominent cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Polygon (MATIC) are facing a downturn. With Bitcoin's price speculated to drop to $25K and Polygon (MATIC) hitting a 90-day low, investors are increasingly seeking alternative investment opportunities. </p>
<p class="s5">Amidst this uncertain market landscape, Yachtify (YCHT) shines as a promising platform, revolutionizing the way investors engage with luxury yacht investments and offering a unique value proposition in the ever-evolving world of digital assets.</p>
<p class="s8">Yachtify (YCHT) Shines: A New Era of Fractionalized Yacht Investment</p>
<p class="s5">Yachtify (YCHT) is making waves in the cryptocurrency market with its innovative approach to fractional yacht ownership. Offering an exciting opportunity for investors, the YCHT presale boasts a token price of just $0.12 and a 30% bonus on purchases made during this stage. Yachtify's unique model provides a more accessible and cost-effective way for individuals to invest in luxury yachts.</p>
<p class="s5">The YCHT token brings several benefits to the table, including the ability to participate in the profitable world of yacht ownership without the need for substantial capital. Through fractionalization, Yachtify enables investors to buy and sell shares in yachts, which helps to democratize the traditionally exclusive yacht market.</p>
<p class="s5">One of the key features of Yachtify is the utilization of blockchain technology to create a transparent and secure platform for fractional yacht investment. This ensures that investors can confidently trade their YCHT tokens without worrying about potential fraud or discrepancies in ownership records.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY YACHTIFY TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s8">Bitcoin (BTC) Will Drop to $25K?</p>
<p class="s5">Cryptocurrency trader and analyst, Altcoin Sherpa, recently took to Twitter to predict a drop in Bitcoin's (BTC) price to $25K in the near future. Citing the $25K level as a confluent level for Bitcoin (BTC) price, the analyst's tweet comes amidst a 2.67% drop in Bitcoin (BTC) value in the last 24 hours. </p>
<p class="s5">Currently trading at $27,520.99, Bitcoin (BTC) price faces the possibility of a further downturn as Bitcoin (BTC) heads toward the key support level at $26,800. As bearish signals emerge from technical indicators, the market leader could soon reach the predicted $25K price point, potentially providing traders an opportunity to capitalize on Bitcoin (BTC) decline.</p>
<p class="s8">Polygon (MATIC) Hits 90-Day Low</p>
<p class="s5">Polygon (MATIC) price recently plunged to a 90-day low of $0.886 amid bearish market dominance. With a 3.69% drop to $0.8945 at press time, the increased volatility has attracted short-term traders to the Polygon (MATIC) market. </p>
<p class="s5">The market capitalization of Polygon (MATIC) decreased by 3.77% to $8,254,089,404, while the 24-hour trading volume rose by 15.65% to $436,899,775. The Arnaud Legoux Moving Average (ALMA) indicator reveals a bearish momentum and the Aroon down reading of 71.43% indicates a stronger selling pressure. However, the Keltner Channel bands suggest that the Polygon (MATIC) market is oversold, which may lead to an upward reversal soon.</p>
<p class="s12">Join Presale: https://buy.yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s12">Website: https://yachtify.market</p>
<p class="s12">Telegram: https://t.me/yachtify</p>
<p class="s5">Twitter: https://twitter.com/yachtify_market</p>
<p class="s5">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Frax Share (FXS) and IOTA Plummet As Holders Look to Tradecurveâ€™s (TCRV) Presale for Reconciliation]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/frax-share-fxs-and-iota-plummet-as-holders-look-to-tradecurves-tcrv-presale-for-reconciliation</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204720.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204720.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-204720.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/frax-share-fxs-and-iota-plummet-as-holders-look-to-tradecurves-tcrv-presale-for-reconciliation</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market undergoes rapid shifts, Frax Share (FXS) faced a 6% drop, while IOTA (MIOTA) holders have been turning their attention to the promising Tradecurve presale. With its innovative trading platform and real world utilization experts predict Tradecurve will see 40x gains once it&rsquo;s presale has completed .</p>
<p>This in-depth analysis will explore the latest developments and market trends for each project, with a particular focus on the burgeoning interest in Tradecurve as the next big investment opportunity.</p>
<p class="s10">Frax Share (FXS)</p>
<p>Frax Share (FXS), an innovative stablecoin project, has recently experienced a 6% decline in its value. While the Frax Share's (FXS) algorithmic model has been praised for its unique approach to maintaining stability, it appears that recent market trends have shifted investor interest towards more lucrative options like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>Frax Share's (FXS) current challenges can be traced back to a few factors to Increased Competition. The stablecoin market has become increasingly saturated, making it difficult for Frax Share (FXS) to maintain its unique selling points. As new and innovative projects like Tradecurve enter the scene, FXS faces an uphill battle to stay relevant.</p>
<p>Unlike Tradecurve, which offers a diverse range of high-yield investment options, Frax Share (FXS) provides limited opportunities for investors to maximize their returns. This lack of diverse investment choices may be driving Frax Share (FXS) holders to explore more dynamic projects like TCRV.</p>
<p class="s10">IOTA (MIOTA)</p>
<p>IOTA (MIOTA), known for its innovative Tangle technology that eliminates the need for a blockchain, has been facing its share of difficulties in the market. While the project has been working tirelessly to expand its use cases and forge industry partnerships, it seems to be struggling to keep pace with emerging competitors like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>The reasons behind IOTA (MIOTA) holders shifting their investments is the possibility of 100x gain prediction, IOTA (MIOTA) investors may be looking to capitalize on these potential returns instead.</p>
<p>Despite IOTA's unique technology, the project has not experienced the widespread adoption it had initially anticipated. The lack of mainstream adoption may be driving MIOTA holders to seek out projects with faster growth trajectories, like TCRV.</p>
<p>Tradecurve Presale Continues Gaining Massive Momentum</p>
<p>Tradecurve has captured the attention of the crypto community due to its groundbreaking decentralized finance platform, which is poised to disrupt the digital finance landscape. The platform is built on a foundation of advanced yield farming strategies, secure staking options, and an impressive tokenomics model, all designed to drive significant value for its holders.</p>
<p>The growing interest in Tradecurve can be attributed to enhanced User Experience. The platform has prioritized traders by implementing an intuitive interface and seamless navigation. This approach ensures that both novice and experienced investors can take full advantage of the platform's features without any difficulties.</p>
<p>Beyond that, there are also lucrative earning opportunities with a diverse array of high-yield investment options on Tradecurve which sets it apart from other DeFi projects. The native token of the platform is called $TCRV, and this token serves as a utility and a governance token on the platform. </p>
<p>Tradecurve&rsquo;s native utility token $TCRV has also been audited by Cyber Scope, whilst a team KYC was carried out by AssureDeFi further providing security and transparency to investors.</p>
<p>Currently in its presale stage $TCRV is trading at $0.01, analysts predict that Tradecurve will surge 40x-50x once the token launches, providing investors and traders with a unique opportunity to generate fast profits from a transparent crypto project.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale here:</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://www.tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s13">Presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market undergoes rapid shifts, Frax Share (FXS) faced a 6% drop, while IOTA (MIOTA) holders have been turning their attention to the promising Tradecurve presale. With its innovative trading platform and real world utilization experts predict Tradecurve will see 40x gains once it&rsquo;s presale has completed .</p>
<p>This in-depth analysis will explore the latest developments and market trends for each project, with a particular focus on the burgeoning interest in Tradecurve as the next big investment opportunity.</p>
<p class="s10">Frax Share (FXS)</p>
<p>Frax Share (FXS), an innovative stablecoin project, has recently experienced a 6% decline in its value. While the Frax Share's (FXS) algorithmic model has been praised for its unique approach to maintaining stability, it appears that recent market trends have shifted investor interest towards more lucrative options like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>Frax Share's (FXS) current challenges can be traced back to a few factors to Increased Competition. The stablecoin market has become increasingly saturated, making it difficult for Frax Share (FXS) to maintain its unique selling points. As new and innovative projects like Tradecurve enter the scene, FXS faces an uphill battle to stay relevant.</p>
<p>Unlike Tradecurve, which offers a diverse range of high-yield investment options, Frax Share (FXS) provides limited opportunities for investors to maximize their returns. This lack of diverse investment choices may be driving Frax Share (FXS) holders to explore more dynamic projects like TCRV.</p>
<p class="s10">IOTA (MIOTA)</p>
<p>IOTA (MIOTA), known for its innovative Tangle technology that eliminates the need for a blockchain, has been facing its share of difficulties in the market. While the project has been working tirelessly to expand its use cases and forge industry partnerships, it seems to be struggling to keep pace with emerging competitors like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>The reasons behind IOTA (MIOTA) holders shifting their investments is the possibility of 100x gain prediction, IOTA (MIOTA) investors may be looking to capitalize on these potential returns instead.</p>
<p>Despite IOTA's unique technology, the project has not experienced the widespread adoption it had initially anticipated. The lack of mainstream adoption may be driving MIOTA holders to seek out projects with faster growth trajectories, like TCRV.</p>
<p>Tradecurve Presale Continues Gaining Massive Momentum</p>
<p>Tradecurve has captured the attention of the crypto community due to its groundbreaking decentralized finance platform, which is poised to disrupt the digital finance landscape. The platform is built on a foundation of advanced yield farming strategies, secure staking options, and an impressive tokenomics model, all designed to drive significant value for its holders.</p>
<p>The growing interest in Tradecurve can be attributed to enhanced User Experience. The platform has prioritized traders by implementing an intuitive interface and seamless navigation. This approach ensures that both novice and experienced investors can take full advantage of the platform's features without any difficulties.</p>
<p>Beyond that, there are also lucrative earning opportunities with a diverse array of high-yield investment options on Tradecurve which sets it apart from other DeFi projects. The native token of the platform is called $TCRV, and this token serves as a utility and a governance token on the platform. </p>
<p>Tradecurve&rsquo;s native utility token $TCRV has also been audited by Cyber Scope, whilst a team KYC was carried out by AssureDeFi further providing security and transparency to investors.</p>
<p>Currently in its presale stage $TCRV is trading at $0.01, analysts predict that Tradecurve will surge 40x-50x once the token launches, providing investors and traders with a unique opportunity to generate fast profits from a transparent crypto project.</p>
<p>Find out more about the Tradecurve (TCRV) presale here:</p>
<p class="s13">Website: https://www.tradecurve.io/</p>
<p class="s13">Presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up</p>
<p class="s13">Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Sparklo (SPRK) Increases Investor's Confidence In Crypto Space Compared To Avalanche (AVAX) And Aptos (APT)]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-increases-investors-confidence-in-crypto-space-compared-to-avalanche-avax-and-aptos-apt</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-205006.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-205006.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-15-at-205006.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/sparklo-sprk-increases-investors-confidence-in-crypto-space-compared-to-avalanche-avax-and-aptos-apt</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The world of crypto is constantly in flux and investors are working double-time to get ahead of the curve. The quest for the next blue chip token has been long and fruitless until Sparklo bursts onto the scene. The crypto community is divided and sees Sparklo's potential for tremendous growth. </p>
<p>They're scouring the landscape for any glimmer of hope that could lead them to a major score and that's where Sparklo comes in. It is a new coin and it's got everyone buzzing with excitement. However, Avalanche (AVAX) sees an increase in the number of daily users while Aptos (APT) adds new functions. </p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo (SPRK) offers a golden opportunity to Invest in premium metals</p>
<p>Sparklo is a game-changing investment platform where you can invest in real-world assets like gold, silver and platinum. With fractionalized NFTs backed by these precious metals. And as early adopters, investors are in a prime position to ride the wave and watch Sparklo become the next blue chip token. </p>
<p>Sparklo is poised to revolutionize the precious metals investment industry. What's more, Sparklo's presale price is just $0.022 means the potential for return on investment is huge. Experts predict a 1,500% increase in value in the coming year. </p>
<p>Investment security is a top priority for the Sparklo team and they've taken steps to ensure it. With locked liquidity for 100 years, smart contracts audited by InterFi Network and a completed KYC audit, investors can rest assured that their portfolio is in good hands.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s7">Avalanche's (AVAX) number of daily active users goes up</p>
<p>Several new additions in the number of people using Avalanche (AVAX) this past week. The number of people who use Avalanche (AVAX) every day has reached a 6-month high, according to the most recent statistics. Experts say that Avalanche's (AVAX) new development work is the main reason for its strong performance on the market. </p>
<p>In April, there were a lot more NFT deals on the Avalanche (AVAX) network. So, the price of Avalanche (AVAX) has been going up this month and it has been in the green zone. On the monthly price chart, the value of Avalanche (AVAX) has gone up by 5%. Right now, Avalanche (AVAX) is worth $17.22.</p>
<p class="s7">Aptos (APT) adds a new function</p>
<p>Concerns have been raised in the Aptos (APT) community as of late due to the network rolling back all the gains it gained at the turn of the year 2023. Aptos (APT) has been going down since January when it reached an all-time high of $19.90 and a growth rate of over 400%. In the past week, the price of Aptos (APT) has dropped by 20%. </p>
<p>Because of this, Aptos (APT) has lost about 50% of its value since its high point and is now worth $9.98. Aptos (APT) recently added a new feature called "delegated staking" to stop this drop and get more people to join its network. The purpose of this new function added is to make it easier for people to stake on the Aptos (APT) network. But the effect on the price of Aptos (APT) is not likely to be seen for a few weeks.</p>
<p class="s11">Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
â— Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance
â— Website: https://sparklo.finance
â— Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance
â— Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world of crypto is constantly in flux and investors are working double-time to get ahead of the curve. The quest for the next blue chip token has been long and fruitless until Sparklo bursts onto the scene. The crypto community is divided and sees Sparklo's potential for tremendous growth. </p>
<p>They're scouring the landscape for any glimmer of hope that could lead them to a major score and that's where Sparklo comes in. It is a new coin and it's got everyone buzzing with excitement. However, Avalanche (AVAX) sees an increase in the number of daily users while Aptos (APT) adds new functions. </p>
<p class="s7">Sparklo (SPRK) offers a golden opportunity to Invest in premium metals</p>
<p>Sparklo is a game-changing investment platform where you can invest in real-world assets like gold, silver and platinum. With fractionalized NFTs backed by these precious metals. And as early adopters, investors are in a prime position to ride the wave and watch Sparklo become the next blue chip token. </p>
<p>Sparklo is poised to revolutionize the precious metals investment industry. What's more, Sparklo's presale price is just $0.022 means the potential for return on investment is huge. Experts predict a 1,500% increase in value in the coming year. </p>
<p>Investment security is a top priority for the Sparklo team and they've taken steps to ensure it. With locked liquidity for 100 years, smart contracts audited by InterFi Network and a completed KYC audit, investors can rest assured that their portfolio is in good hands.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; BUY SPRK TOKENS &lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p class="s7">Avalanche's (AVAX) number of daily active users goes up</p>
<p>Several new additions in the number of people using Avalanche (AVAX) this past week. The number of people who use Avalanche (AVAX) every day has reached a 6-month high, according to the most recent statistics. Experts say that Avalanche's (AVAX) new development work is the main reason for its strong performance on the market. </p>
<p>In April, there were a lot more NFT deals on the Avalanche (AVAX) network. So, the price of Avalanche (AVAX) has been going up this month and it has been in the green zone. On the monthly price chart, the value of Avalanche (AVAX) has gone up by 5%. Right now, Avalanche (AVAX) is worth $17.22.</p>
<p class="s7">Aptos (APT) adds a new function</p>
<p>Concerns have been raised in the Aptos (APT) community as of late due to the network rolling back all the gains it gained at the turn of the year 2023. Aptos (APT) has been going down since January when it reached an all-time high of $19.90 and a growth rate of over 400%. In the past week, the price of Aptos (APT) has dropped by 20%. </p>
<p>Because of this, Aptos (APT) has lost about 50% of its value since its high point and is now worth $9.98. Aptos (APT) recently added a new feature called "delegated staking" to stop this drop and get more people to join its network. The purpose of this new function added is to make it easier for people to stake on the Aptos (APT) network. But the effect on the price of Aptos (APT) is not likely to be seen for a few weeks.</p>
<p class="s11">Find out about the Sparklo presale using the links below</p>
â— Buy Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance
â— Website: https://sparklo.finance
â— Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance
â— Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[NCET Director: DOJ Will Crackdown on Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ncet-director-doj-will-crackdown-on-crypto-exchanges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doj-1920-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doj-1920-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/doj-1920-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ncet-director-doj-will-crackdown-on-crypto-exchanges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The director of the DOJ&rsquo;s National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team (NCET) said the US is stepping up scrutiny of crypto exchanges. </p>
<p>Eun Young Choi, director of the Department of Justice&rsquo;s NCET, said the United States is stepping up scrutiny of cryptocurrency exchanges and mixers to target illicit behaviour on the platforms, the Financial Times (FT) reports.</p>
<p>The crypto enforcement tsar told the FT the department would crack down on companies that engage in criminal activity themselves or allow crimes such as money laundering to take place on their platforms.</p>
<p>Choi said:</p>

<p>But on top of that, they&rsquo;re allowing for all the other criminal actors to easily profit from their crimes and cash out in ways that are obviously problematic to us. And so we hope that by focusing on those types of platforms, we&rsquo;re going to have a multiplier effect.</p>

<p>Director Choi further noted with the novel crackdown on cryptocurrency firms, the agency is looking to increase scrutiny to send a &ldquo;deterrent message&rdquo; to businesses that have thus far been able to avoid AML and client identification rules.</p>
<p>She added the agency hopes the same message gets across to platforms that do not invest in concrete risk mitigation and compliance procedures.</p>
<p>Choi also told the FT the DOJ would focus on crimes related to DeFi, specifically &ldquo;chain bridges&rdquo;, which allow users to exchange different tokens or projects with vulnerable codes.</p>
DOJ Is Actively Investigating Numerous Major Crypto Firms
<p>The department announced in February that it had launched an investigation into Silvergate Capital and its business with defunct crypto exchange FTX and its sister company Alameda Research. Silvergate Capital is the parent company of crypto-focused Silvergate Bank, which saw over two-thirds of its customers withdraw deposits of over $8 billion after FTX collapsed. Silvergate Bank was one of the principal backers of FTX.</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports the DOJ said it would probe into Binance Holdings to investigate whether the platform was used to help Russians outwit US sanctions.</p>
<p>The department also announced last month that it seized $112 million worth of digital assets found to be related to crypto scams. In its crackdown on fraudulent crypto activities, the department confiscated the contents of six crypto wallets believed to have been used to launder the proceeds from several crypto confidence schemes.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The director of the DOJ&rsquo;s National Cryptocurrency Enforcement Team (NCET) said the US is stepping up scrutiny of crypto exchanges. </p>
<p>Eun Young Choi, director of the Department of Justice&rsquo;s NCET, said the United States is stepping up scrutiny of cryptocurrency exchanges and mixers to target illicit behaviour on the platforms, the Financial Times (FT) reports.</p>
<p>The crypto enforcement tsar told the FT the department would crack down on companies that engage in criminal activity themselves or allow crimes such as money laundering to take place on their platforms.</p>
<p>Choi said:</p>

<p>But on top of that, they&rsquo;re allowing for all the other criminal actors to easily profit from their crimes and cash out in ways that are obviously problematic to us. And so we hope that by focusing on those types of platforms, we&rsquo;re going to have a multiplier effect.</p>

<p>Director Choi further noted with the novel crackdown on cryptocurrency firms, the agency is looking to increase scrutiny to send a &ldquo;deterrent message&rdquo; to businesses that have thus far been able to avoid AML and client identification rules.</p>
<p>She added the agency hopes the same message gets across to platforms that do not invest in concrete risk mitigation and compliance procedures.</p>
<p>Choi also told the FT the DOJ would focus on crimes related to DeFi, specifically &ldquo;chain bridges&rdquo;, which allow users to exchange different tokens or projects with vulnerable codes.</p>
DOJ Is Actively Investigating Numerous Major Crypto Firms
<p>The department announced in February that it had launched an investigation into Silvergate Capital and its business with defunct crypto exchange FTX and its sister company Alameda Research. Silvergate Capital is the parent company of crypto-focused Silvergate Bank, which saw over two-thirds of its customers withdraw deposits of over $8 billion after FTX collapsed. Silvergate Bank was one of the principal backers of FTX.</p>
<p>Bloomberg reports the DOJ said it would probe into Binance Holdings to investigate whether the platform was used to help Russians outwit US sanctions.</p>
<p>The department also announced last month that it seized $112 million worth of digital assets found to be related to crypto scams. In its crackdown on fraudulent crypto activities, the department confiscated the contents of six crypto wallets believed to have been used to launder the proceeds from several crypto confidence schemes.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Xapo Bank provides cheaper crypto payments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/xapo-bank-provides-cheaper-crypto-payments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xapo.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xapo.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/xapo.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:58:38 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/xapo-bank-provides-cheaper-crypto-payments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency may be experiencing some challenges right now but one company is not being deterred by all the uncertainty: Xapo Bank based in Gibraltar is forging ahead with expanding support for different types of digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO Seamus Rocca remains optimistic about industry volatility and sees plenty of room for growth - particularly when it comes to cheaper international payments which he believes are ripe for development.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The great news here lies in the fact that as an already established regulated institution serving both as bank and cryptocurrency firm combined; there are potentially huge benefits from using its platform especially as regards cross border transactions - something customers are increasingly seeking out across various industries worldwide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo Bank was founded under Gibraltar&rsquo;s regulatory framework which takes a proactive approach towards cryptocurrency regulation - so there&rsquo;s no question about whether they&rsquo;re authorised or not to engage in crypto and other digital payment activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As part of its expansion plans the bank recently integrated Tether (USDT) with a view to facilitating even faster and cheaper payments. Xapo previously adopted the USDC stablecoin earlier this year which has boosted its offerings and these stablecoins now have an impressive combined market capitalisation exceeding $100 billion.</p>
<p>Xapo Bank allows customers to deposit and withdraw USDT without any fees whatsoever, promising an annual interest rate of 4.1% on deposits along with a 1:1 conversion rate straight into US dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo Bank has taken another step forward by integrating stablecoins into its offerings complementing Bitcoin&rsquo;s Lightning Network which it is already supporting through its Lightspark collaboration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo&rsquo;s Gibraltar licence issued eight years ago bolsters its commitment towards providing secure cryptocurrency services, thereby making them reliable platforms for customers wanting trustworthiness when dealing with cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite challenges faced by the industry such as frequent occurrences of fraud on various crypto exchanges, Xapo is still devoted to growth within the market for crypto payment gateways, currently valued at $1 billion and projected to expand to $5.4 billion by 2031.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By collaborating with financial institutions that have an extensive background in blockchain technology and cryptocurrency Xapo aims to handle international transactions using this technology, which eventually will help in curtailing settlement costs for fees incurred today.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, Faster Payments &ndash; the UK's real-time settlement network &ndash; is supported by Xapo Bank, where instant payments are processed using digital assets or traditional currencies alike.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As global payment systems continue their shift towards blockchain technology and digital assets, Xapo Bank joins other forward-thinking companies such as Ripple who've successfully leveraged these tools for streamlined currency conversions, while eliminating correspondent banks altogether via their XRP technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Exciting examples like Ripple's recent collaboration on a central bank digital currency with Montenegro further illustrate the growing prevalence of digital assets in our current payment landscape; even stablecoin payments are becoming more common across Latin America using XRP tech.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Yet achieving full-scale adoption requires seamless access points between traditional finance systems alongside blockchain-based ones where users can transition easily - creating a mutually beneficial relationship between both sectors where each recognizes their unique strengths.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With regulatory compliance status plus strategic partnerships already enabling it to reap benefits from embracing digital assets such as stablecoins, Xapo Bank continues to empower users with faster and cheaper options for international payments that contribute to the industry's growth and wider adoption.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency may be experiencing some challenges right now but one company is not being deterred by all the uncertainty: Xapo Bank based in Gibraltar is forging ahead with expanding support for different types of digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>CEO Seamus Rocca remains optimistic about industry volatility and sees plenty of room for growth - particularly when it comes to cheaper international payments which he believes are ripe for development.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The great news here lies in the fact that as an already established regulated institution serving both as bank and cryptocurrency firm combined; there are potentially huge benefits from using its platform especially as regards cross border transactions - something customers are increasingly seeking out across various industries worldwide.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo Bank was founded under Gibraltar&rsquo;s regulatory framework which takes a proactive approach towards cryptocurrency regulation - so there&rsquo;s no question about whether they&rsquo;re authorised or not to engage in crypto and other digital payment activities.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As part of its expansion plans the bank recently integrated Tether (USDT) with a view to facilitating even faster and cheaper payments. Xapo previously adopted the USDC stablecoin earlier this year which has boosted its offerings and these stablecoins now have an impressive combined market capitalisation exceeding $100 billion.</p>
<p>Xapo Bank allows customers to deposit and withdraw USDT without any fees whatsoever, promising an annual interest rate of 4.1% on deposits along with a 1:1 conversion rate straight into US dollars.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo Bank has taken another step forward by integrating stablecoins into its offerings complementing Bitcoin&rsquo;s Lightning Network which it is already supporting through its Lightspark collaboration.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Xapo&rsquo;s Gibraltar licence issued eight years ago bolsters its commitment towards providing secure cryptocurrency services, thereby making them reliable platforms for customers wanting trustworthiness when dealing with cryptocurrencies.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Despite challenges faced by the industry such as frequent occurrences of fraud on various crypto exchanges, Xapo is still devoted to growth within the market for crypto payment gateways, currently valued at $1 billion and projected to expand to $5.4 billion by 2031.&nbsp;</p>
<p>By collaborating with financial institutions that have an extensive background in blockchain technology and cryptocurrency Xapo aims to handle international transactions using this technology, which eventually will help in curtailing settlement costs for fees incurred today.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, Faster Payments &ndash; the UK's real-time settlement network &ndash; is supported by Xapo Bank, where instant payments are processed using digital assets or traditional currencies alike.&nbsp;</p>
<p>As global payment systems continue their shift towards blockchain technology and digital assets, Xapo Bank joins other forward-thinking companies such as Ripple who've successfully leveraged these tools for streamlined currency conversions, while eliminating correspondent banks altogether via their XRP technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Exciting examples like Ripple's recent collaboration on a central bank digital currency with Montenegro further illustrate the growing prevalence of digital assets in our current payment landscape; even stablecoin payments are becoming more common across Latin America using XRP tech.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Yet achieving full-scale adoption requires seamless access points between traditional finance systems alongside blockchain-based ones where users can transition easily - creating a mutually beneficial relationship between both sectors where each recognizes their unique strengths.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With regulatory compliance status plus strategic partnerships already enabling it to reap benefits from embracing digital assets such as stablecoins, Xapo Bank continues to empower users with faster and cheaper options for international payments that contribute to the industry's growth and wider adoption.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Zero Fees and Infinite Liquidity - Finrex is the Ultimate Crypto Trading App]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zero-fees-and-infinite-liquidity-finrex-is-the-ultimate-crypto-trading-app</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trading-app.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trading-app.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/trading-app.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zero-fees-and-infinite-liquidity-finrex-is-the-ultimate-crypto-trading-app</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of cryptocurrencies, more and more people are looking to invest in them. However, trading cryptocurrencies can be complicated and risky, especially for those who are new to the game. That's where Finrex comes in. Finrex is a trading app offering unique features for pros and beginners, making it the best trading app for crypto traders.</p>
Zero Transaction Fees
<p>One of the most significant advantages of using Finrex is that it offers zero fees for trading. This means you can buy and sell cryptocurrencies without worrying about paying any fees. This is a huge advantage for active traders who make multiple daily trades, as fees can add up quickly and eat into their profits.</p>
<p>Another unique feature of Finrex is its infinite liquidity. This means the exchange has a vast pool of buyers and sellers, making it easy to buy and sell cryptocurrencies anytime. Unlike other trading apps with limited liquidity, Finrex ensures that traders can always find someone to buy or sell their cryptocurrencies to.</p>
<p>In addition to its unique features, Finrex is also incredibly easy to use. The app has a user-friendly interface makes it easy for beginners to navigate and understand. This is a significant advantage for those new to trading cryptocurrencies, as it can initially be overwhelming and confusing.</p>
Advanced Features For Pro Traders
<p>For more experienced traders, Finrex offers a range of advanced features that allow them to take their trading to the next level. For example, the exchange allows traders to buy stocks on weekends, which is impossible with other trading apps. This means traders can exploit market movements even when the stock market is closed.</p>
<p>Finrex also allows traders to trade beyond pre-market and intraday, another advantage for those who want to make trades outside of traditional trading hours. This feature allows traders to act on breaking news over the weekend, which can be a significant advantage in the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency trading.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Finrex is the best trading app for crypto traders because it offers unique features for both pros and beginners, zero fees, infinite liquidity, and ease of use. Whether you are new to trading or an experienced trader, Finrex has something to offer. So why not give it a try and see for yourself why Finrex is the best trading app for crypto traders?</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the rise of cryptocurrencies, more and more people are looking to invest in them. However, trading cryptocurrencies can be complicated and risky, especially for those who are new to the game. That's where Finrex comes in. Finrex is a trading app offering unique features for pros and beginners, making it the best trading app for crypto traders.</p>
Zero Transaction Fees
<p>One of the most significant advantages of using Finrex is that it offers zero fees for trading. This means you can buy and sell cryptocurrencies without worrying about paying any fees. This is a huge advantage for active traders who make multiple daily trades, as fees can add up quickly and eat into their profits.</p>
<p>Another unique feature of Finrex is its infinite liquidity. This means the exchange has a vast pool of buyers and sellers, making it easy to buy and sell cryptocurrencies anytime. Unlike other trading apps with limited liquidity, Finrex ensures that traders can always find someone to buy or sell their cryptocurrencies to.</p>
<p>In addition to its unique features, Finrex is also incredibly easy to use. The app has a user-friendly interface makes it easy for beginners to navigate and understand. This is a significant advantage for those new to trading cryptocurrencies, as it can initially be overwhelming and confusing.</p>
Advanced Features For Pro Traders
<p>For more experienced traders, Finrex offers a range of advanced features that allow them to take their trading to the next level. For example, the exchange allows traders to buy stocks on weekends, which is impossible with other trading apps. This means traders can exploit market movements even when the stock market is closed.</p>
<p>Finrex also allows traders to trade beyond pre-market and intraday, another advantage for those who want to make trades outside of traditional trading hours. This feature allows traders to act on breaking news over the weekend, which can be a significant advantage in the fast-paced world of cryptocurrency trading.</p>
<p>In conclusion, Finrex is the best trading app for crypto traders because it offers unique features for both pros and beginners, zero fees, infinite liquidity, and ease of use. Whether you are new to trading or an experienced trader, Finrex has something to offer. So why not give it a try and see for yourself why Finrex is the best trading app for crypto traders?</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[From $22M To $111K: SEC Revises LBRY Fine]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/from-22-m-usd-to-111-k-usd-sec-revises-lbry-fine</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lbry-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lbry-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/lbry-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/from-22-m-usd-to-111-k-usd-sec-revises-lbry-fine</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Following a legal dispute, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has revised its fine against LBRY from $22 million to just over $111,000.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Vs. LBRY
<p>The SEC has cited financial hardship on the part of the defendants as the reason for the significant reduction in the fine amount. The regulatory body brought the case against the blockchain-based content-sharing platform in March 2021, over allegations that the latter sold unregistered securities through its cryptocurrency, LBRY Credits (LBC). The SEC presented its usual argument that LBC constituted a security and should have been registered with the agency before being sold to investors.</p>
<p>LBRY had disputed the SEC's claims, arguing that LBC was not a security but a utility token that could be used to access and transact on the LBRY platform. The company also claimed that the SEC's enforcement action was an attempt to stifle innovation and harm small businesses.</p>
<p>In response to LBRY's arguments, the SEC sought a fine of $22 million and an injunction to prevent the company from selling LBC in the future.&nbsp;</p>
LBRY Claims &ldquo;Unreasonable&rdquo; Fine
<p>Following a months-long legal battle, in November 2022, the SEC emerged victorious, and the judge presiding over the case ruled that LBC was a security. Soon after, LBRY approached the SEC with a request to reduce the fine amount. The crypto company claimed that the $22 million fine was not reasonable, as it vastly overstated the scope of LBRY&rsquo;s treasury and did not account for any of the company&rsquo;s legitimate business expenses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The agency has taken LBRY&rsquo;s concern to heart and decided to revise the fine amount to a much-lower $111,614. In the latest filing, the SEC wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Commission acknowledges LBRY&rsquo;s representations that it is defunct, ceasing operations, and without the funds to pay a larger fine, and recognizes that a defendant&rsquo;s ability to pay is a factor when imposing a civil penalty.&rdquo;</p>

SEC&rsquo;s Increasing Crypto Obsession
<p>The SEC's case against LBRY is just one example of the agency's increasing scrutiny of the cryptocurrency and blockchain industries. Industry experts have also questioned the reasoning behind the SEC&rsquo;s actions which cost millions of dollars in legal fees and hit a financial blow to the company for a mere fine of $111K. However, it is becoming clear that as these industries continue to grow and evolve, it is likely that the SEC and other regulatory bodies will become even more involved in regulating them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following a legal dispute, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has revised its fine against LBRY from $22 million to just over $111,000.&nbsp;</p>
SEC Vs. LBRY
<p>The SEC has cited financial hardship on the part of the defendants as the reason for the significant reduction in the fine amount. The regulatory body brought the case against the blockchain-based content-sharing platform in March 2021, over allegations that the latter sold unregistered securities through its cryptocurrency, LBRY Credits (LBC). The SEC presented its usual argument that LBC constituted a security and should have been registered with the agency before being sold to investors.</p>
<p>LBRY had disputed the SEC's claims, arguing that LBC was not a security but a utility token that could be used to access and transact on the LBRY platform. The company also claimed that the SEC's enforcement action was an attempt to stifle innovation and harm small businesses.</p>
<p>In response to LBRY's arguments, the SEC sought a fine of $22 million and an injunction to prevent the company from selling LBC in the future.&nbsp;</p>
LBRY Claims &ldquo;Unreasonable&rdquo; Fine
<p>Following a months-long legal battle, in November 2022, the SEC emerged victorious, and the judge presiding over the case ruled that LBC was a security. Soon after, LBRY approached the SEC with a request to reduce the fine amount. The crypto company claimed that the $22 million fine was not reasonable, as it vastly overstated the scope of LBRY&rsquo;s treasury and did not account for any of the company&rsquo;s legitimate business expenses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The agency has taken LBRY&rsquo;s concern to heart and decided to revise the fine amount to a much-lower $111,614. In the latest filing, the SEC wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Commission acknowledges LBRY&rsquo;s representations that it is defunct, ceasing operations, and without the funds to pay a larger fine, and recognizes that a defendant&rsquo;s ability to pay is a factor when imposing a civil penalty.&rdquo;</p>

SEC&rsquo;s Increasing Crypto Obsession
<p>The SEC's case against LBRY is just one example of the agency's increasing scrutiny of the cryptocurrency and blockchain industries. Industry experts have also questioned the reasoning behind the SEC&rsquo;s actions which cost millions of dollars in legal fees and hit a financial blow to the company for a mere fine of $111K. However, it is becoming clear that as these industries continue to grow and evolve, it is likely that the SEC and other regulatory bodies will become even more involved in regulating them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[NFTfi Launches Earn Season 1: Promoting Responsible NFT Lending]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nftfi-launches-earn-season-1-promoting-responsible-nft-lending</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Twitter_thread_NFTfi_Earn_season_1_16841526332YekaquyI3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Twitter_thread_NFTfi_Earn_season_1_16841526332YekaquyI3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Twitter_thread_NFTfi_Earn_season_1_16841526332YekaquyI3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:01:19 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nftfi-launches-earn-season-1-promoting-responsible-nft-lending</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Cape Town, South Africa, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi, a leading NFT lending platform, has launched the next phase of its loyalty program NFTfi Rewards. In Earn Season 1, users can get rewarded with exclusive reward points for borrower-friendly loans and responsible lending behavior.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The NFT space is growing rapidly, and healthy credit markets are fundamental to its overall growth. NFTfi&rsquo;s Earn Season 1 reward structure has been designed with this in mind, to incentivize responsible NFT lending and contribute positively to the overall NFT ecosystem.</p>Stephen Young, Co-Founder and CEO at NFTfi says: "We believe that NFT lending is a crucial part of the future of the NFT space, and we're committed to promoting a healthy and non-predatory lending environment through our new loyalty program."<p class="ql-align-justify">The principles by which Earn Points are calculated are the following:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Only repaid loans earn points: Aims at motivating lenders to carefully manage default risk via conservative LTVs, and borrowers to not take out excessive debt they might not be able to repay.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Larger and longer loans earn more points: Aims at motivating lenders to provide borrowers with flexible access to various loan sizes and loan durations.&nbsp;</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Lower interest rate (APR) loans earn the most points: Aims at motivating lenders to provide borrower-friendly interest rates and risk-adequate LTVs as a consequence.&nbsp;</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Points are earned by repaying an eligible loan. Upon taking out a new loan, the associated Earn Points can be seen under &ldquo;unsecured points&rdquo; in the NFTfi Rewards cockpit. If the loan gets repaid, these points turn into &ldquo;secured points&rdquo;.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The NFTfi Leaderboard shows unsecured Earn Points (upon starting a loan) and secured Earn Points (upon repayment). The 500 wallets with the most secured points by the end of Season 1 will get a multiplier of 2.5x max. on their final balance.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi is committed to rewarding real users, not washlenders. The program disincentivizes wash loans through various measures, including no points for loans with APRs below 2%, no points for loans with a duration of fewer than 3 days, and no points for related wallets.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Points are non-transferable and not redeemable at present. They merely reflect the loyalty level of NFTfi users. Certain persons, such as US residents, other US persons, and persons located in the US, are not eligible to participate in the NFTfi Rewards loyalty program.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Season 1 is only the beginning of a long and exciting #NFTfiSummer. NFTfi has many surprises planned for all NFT collectors out there. For more information, check the Earn Points cockpit and the FAQs section.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Market Information</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFT lending is a rapidly growing market, with the global NFT market expected to reach $13.6 billion USD by 2027, according to MarketsandMarkets. NFT lending offers benefits such as liquidity, enabling NFT holders to use their assets as collateral for loans. It also helps tackle issues such as the lack of traditional financing options for NFT holders and the need for a healthy credit market in the NFT space.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Investments in loans carry inherent risks, and the value of NFTs can be highly volatile. Users should carefully consider their risk tolerance and investment objectives before taking out loans.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About NFTfi</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi.com is a decentralized peer-to-peer lending platform that enables NFT holders to borrow ETH, USDC, and DAI cryptocurrency, secured by their non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The platform is non-custodial and built on the Ethereum blockchain, where smart contracts&nbsp;facilitate secure and transparent transactions directly between borrowers and lenders. NFTfi provides a new way for NFT holders to unlock the value of their assets and access liquidity while also enabling lenders to earn interest on their funds. Since its first loan in May 2020, users have transacted over $400 million on the NFTfi smart contracts.&nbsp;</p><p>Twitter | Discord | Website</p>ContactStephen Youngpress@nftfi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cape Town, South Africa, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi, a leading NFT lending platform, has launched the next phase of its loyalty program NFTfi Rewards. In Earn Season 1, users can get rewarded with exclusive reward points for borrower-friendly loans and responsible lending behavior.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The NFT space is growing rapidly, and healthy credit markets are fundamental to its overall growth. NFTfi&rsquo;s Earn Season 1 reward structure has been designed with this in mind, to incentivize responsible NFT lending and contribute positively to the overall NFT ecosystem.</p>Stephen Young, Co-Founder and CEO at NFTfi says: "We believe that NFT lending is a crucial part of the future of the NFT space, and we're committed to promoting a healthy and non-predatory lending environment through our new loyalty program."<p class="ql-align-justify">The principles by which Earn Points are calculated are the following:</p><ul><li class="ql-align-justify">Only repaid loans earn points: Aims at motivating lenders to carefully manage default risk via conservative LTVs, and borrowers to not take out excessive debt they might not be able to repay.</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Larger and longer loans earn more points: Aims at motivating lenders to provide borrowers with flexible access to various loan sizes and loan durations.&nbsp;</li><li class="ql-align-justify">Lower interest rate (APR) loans earn the most points: Aims at motivating lenders to provide borrower-friendly interest rates and risk-adequate LTVs as a consequence.&nbsp;</li></ul><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Points are earned by repaying an eligible loan. Upon taking out a new loan, the associated Earn Points can be seen under &ldquo;unsecured points&rdquo; in the NFTfi Rewards cockpit. If the loan gets repaid, these points turn into &ldquo;secured points&rdquo;.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The NFTfi Leaderboard shows unsecured Earn Points (upon starting a loan) and secured Earn Points (upon repayment). The 500 wallets with the most secured points by the end of Season 1 will get a multiplier of 2.5x max. on their final balance.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi is committed to rewarding real users, not washlenders. The program disincentivizes wash loans through various measures, including no points for loans with APRs below 2%, no points for loans with a duration of fewer than 3 days, and no points for related wallets.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Points are non-transferable and not redeemable at present. They merely reflect the loyalty level of NFTfi users. Certain persons, such as US residents, other US persons, and persons located in the US, are not eligible to participate in the NFTfi Rewards loyalty program.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Earn Season 1 is only the beginning of a long and exciting #NFTfiSummer. NFTfi has many surprises planned for all NFT collectors out there. For more information, check the Earn Points cockpit and the FAQs section.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Market Information</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFT lending is a rapidly growing market, with the global NFT market expected to reach $13.6 billion USD by 2027, according to MarketsandMarkets. NFT lending offers benefits such as liquidity, enabling NFT holders to use their assets as collateral for loans. It also helps tackle issues such as the lack of traditional financing options for NFT holders and the need for a healthy credit market in the NFT space.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Investments in loans carry inherent risks, and the value of NFTs can be highly volatile. Users should carefully consider their risk tolerance and investment objectives before taking out loans.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About NFTfi</p><p class="ql-align-justify">NFTfi.com is a decentralized peer-to-peer lending platform that enables NFT holders to borrow ETH, USDC, and DAI cryptocurrency, secured by their non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The platform is non-custodial and built on the Ethereum blockchain, where smart contracts&nbsp;facilitate secure and transparent transactions directly between borrowers and lenders. NFTfi provides a new way for NFT holders to unlock the value of their assets and access liquidity while also enabling lenders to earn interest on their funds. Since its first loan in May 2020, users have transacted over $400 million on the NFTfi smart contracts.&nbsp;</p><p>Twitter | Discord | Website</p>ContactStephen Youngpress@nftfi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Hit Above 27353 - 16 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-hit-above-27353-16-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-15-may-2023-240-1920-1080-2.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-hit-above-27353-16-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Escalates to 27556:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) maintained some upward momentum early in the Asian session as the pair moved back above the 27000 area and reached the 27556.40 level, representing a test of a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 28334.75 level.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 27353.28 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 29850 to 25810.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.</p>
<p>Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives related to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27503.47 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27554.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Escalates to 27556:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 16 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) maintained some upward momentum early in the Asian session as the pair moved back above the 27000 area and reached the 27556.40 level, representing a test of a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure that emerged around the 28334.75 level.&nbsp; Stops were elected above the 27353.28 level, representing the 38.2% retracement of the depreciating range from 29850 to 25810.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.</p>
<p>Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives related to recent buying pressure around the 27194.51 and 28161.74 areas include the 30420.74, 31237.11, and 32556.73 levels.&nbsp; Additional downside price objectives related to recent depreciating ranges and levels include the 26085, 25604, and 24103 levels.&nbsp; Additional upside price objectives include the 31477.37, 32501.23, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 100-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27503.47 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 27554.43.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[LOVESNOOPY' Token Lists on MEXC Exchange]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/MEXC_and_LOVESNOOPY_1684132163CeXdaaKBnj.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/MEXC_and_LOVESNOOPY_1684132163CeXdaaKBnj.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/MEXC_and_LOVESNOOPY_1684132163CeXdaaKBnj.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:48:37 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/lovesnoopy-token-lists-on-mexc-exchange</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Seattle, USA, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>The recent surge of meme coins in the cryptocurrency market is nothing short of a phenomena, as meme coins have taken center stage in the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the impressive performance of PEPE, a coin that took the center of the meme coin ecosystem, is a new protagonist -the beloved original dog character, Snoopy, who has garnered worldwide affection over a long period of time.</p><p>Today, the LOVESNOOPY project ($LOVESNOOPY) has announced the token will be listed on the MEXC exchange on May 16th of 10:00 UTC.</p><p>Right from its launch, $LOVESNOOPY expressed its ambitious goal of worldwide expansion through multilingual support on its website. Next, the $LOVESNOOPY team hired CERTIK to conduct an audit, according to their Twitter. In addition, the team will be burning 10% of its total token supply.</p><p></p><p>With its ambitious goal of world expansion through the power of memes, $LOVESNOOPY aspires to capture the hearts of individuals worldwide, infusing their lives with joy, warmth, and a renewed appreciation for the enduring magic of Snoopy.</p>About LOVESNOOPY<p>The main utility of $LOVESNOOPY is to establish a vibrant and impassioned meme community that we can embrace with all our hearts. LOVESNOOPY&rsquo;s path to global domination is simple! Just enjoy and &lsquo;LOVE SNOOPY&rsquo;! The more people enjoy and LOVE SNOOPY, the more indelible his legacy as a beloved meme will become.</p><p>LOVESNOOPY is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>ContactI LOVE SNOOPY teamilovesnoopy1949@gmail.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Seattle, USA, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>The recent surge of meme coins in the cryptocurrency market is nothing short of a phenomena, as meme coins have taken center stage in the world of cryptocurrencies. Amidst the impressive performance of PEPE, a coin that took the center of the meme coin ecosystem, is a new protagonist -the beloved original dog character, Snoopy, who has garnered worldwide affection over a long period of time.</p><p>Today, the LOVESNOOPY project ($LOVESNOOPY) has announced the token will be listed on the MEXC exchange on May 16th of 10:00 UTC.</p><p>Right from its launch, $LOVESNOOPY expressed its ambitious goal of worldwide expansion through multilingual support on its website. Next, the $LOVESNOOPY team hired CERTIK to conduct an audit, according to their Twitter. In addition, the team will be burning 10% of its total token supply.</p><p></p><p>With its ambitious goal of world expansion through the power of memes, $LOVESNOOPY aspires to capture the hearts of individuals worldwide, infusing their lives with joy, warmth, and a renewed appreciation for the enduring magic of Snoopy.</p>About LOVESNOOPY<p>The main utility of $LOVESNOOPY is to establish a vibrant and impassioned meme community that we can embrace with all our hearts. LOVESNOOPY&rsquo;s path to global domination is simple! Just enjoy and &lsquo;LOVE SNOOPY&rsquo;! The more people enjoy and LOVE SNOOPY, the more indelible his legacy as a beloved meme will become.</p><p>LOVESNOOPY is the source of this content. This Press Release is for informational purposes only. The information does not constitute investment advice or an offer to invest.</p>ContactI LOVE SNOOPY teamilovesnoopy1949@gmail.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Ignores IMF, Sells Millions Of Gold-Backed Crypto Tokens]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zimbabwe-ignores-imf-sells-millions-of-gold-backed-crypto-tokens</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/zimbabwe-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/zimbabwe-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/zimbabwe-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zimbabwe-ignores-imf-sells-millions-of-gold-backed-crypto-tokens</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe&rsquo;s first gold-backed cryptocurrency sale has been a resounding success. The country&rsquo;s central bank managed to sell around 14 billion Zimbabwe dollars&rsquo; worth of gold-backed tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This puts the value of the digital tokens sold at around $39 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Resounding Success
<p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe went ahead with the sale of the gold-backed tokens despite a stern warning from the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The bank announced on the 12th of May, 2023, that it received 135 applications for a total of around 14.07 Zimbabwean dollars to purchase the gold-backed cryptocurrency. The Reserve Bank had announced plans to introduce a gold-backed digital currency as legal tender in an effort to help stabilize the local currency. The digital tokens will function as a type of electric money that will be backed by the country&rsquo;s gold reserves held by the central bank.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto tokens were first introduced in April and are backed by 139.57 kilograms of gold. The sale in question ran from the 8th of May to the 12th of May. The minimum selling price of the tokens was set at $10 for individuals and $5000 for entities such as corporations and businesses. The minimum vesting period for the tokens has been set at 180 days, during which they can be held in e-gold wallets or e-gold cards.&nbsp;</p>
An Attempt To Stabilize The Economy&nbsp;
<p>The Zimbabwean Dollar is trading at an official rate of 362 Zimbabwean Dollars to $1. However, their value is far higher in unofficial markets. The move to issue gold-backed crypto tokens is viewed as an effort to stabilize the country&rsquo;s faltering economy and the depreciation of its local currency against the US Dollar. The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe added that there will be a second round of digital token sales and has already requested that applications be submitted by the end of the week. All applications submitted during the week would be settled by the 18th of May. Dr. John Mangudya, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe Governor, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The issuance of the gold-backed digital tokens is meant to expand the value-preserving instruments available in the economy and enhance divisibility of the investment instruments and widen their access and usage by the public.&rdquo;</p>

The International Monetary Fund Warning&nbsp;
<p>Zimbabwe went ahead with its plans to sell gold-backed crypto tokens despite a stern warning from the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The IMF had stated that the country should redirect its efforts towards liberalizing its foreign exchange markets instead of adopting a gold-backed currency. An IMF spokesperson stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A careful assessment should be conducted to ensure the benefits from this measure outweigh the costs and potential risks including, for instance, macroeconomic and financial stability risks, legal and operational risks, governance risks, cost of forgone FX reserves.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Zimbabwe has been reeling under heavy inflation and extreme currency volatility for the better part of a decade. The country adopted the United States Dollar as its currency in 2009 following a prolonged phase of hyperinflation that left its original currency in ruins. The Zimbabwe Dollar saw a reintroduction after a decade in 2019, but volatility issues continue to plague the currency.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe&rsquo;s first gold-backed cryptocurrency sale has been a resounding success. The country&rsquo;s central bank managed to sell around 14 billion Zimbabwe dollars&rsquo; worth of gold-backed tokens.&nbsp;</p>
<p>This puts the value of the digital tokens sold at around $39 million.&nbsp;</p>
A Resounding Success
<p>The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe went ahead with the sale of the gold-backed tokens despite a stern warning from the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The bank announced on the 12th of May, 2023, that it received 135 applications for a total of around 14.07 Zimbabwean dollars to purchase the gold-backed cryptocurrency. The Reserve Bank had announced plans to introduce a gold-backed digital currency as legal tender in an effort to help stabilize the local currency. The digital tokens will function as a type of electric money that will be backed by the country&rsquo;s gold reserves held by the central bank.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The crypto tokens were first introduced in April and are backed by 139.57 kilograms of gold. The sale in question ran from the 8th of May to the 12th of May. The minimum selling price of the tokens was set at $10 for individuals and $5000 for entities such as corporations and businesses. The minimum vesting period for the tokens has been set at 180 days, during which they can be held in e-gold wallets or e-gold cards.&nbsp;</p>
An Attempt To Stabilize The Economy&nbsp;
<p>The Zimbabwean Dollar is trading at an official rate of 362 Zimbabwean Dollars to $1. However, their value is far higher in unofficial markets. The move to issue gold-backed crypto tokens is viewed as an effort to stabilize the country&rsquo;s faltering economy and the depreciation of its local currency against the US Dollar. The Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe added that there will be a second round of digital token sales and has already requested that applications be submitted by the end of the week. All applications submitted during the week would be settled by the 18th of May. Dr. John Mangudya, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe Governor, stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The issuance of the gold-backed digital tokens is meant to expand the value-preserving instruments available in the economy and enhance divisibility of the investment instruments and widen their access and usage by the public.&rdquo;</p>

The International Monetary Fund Warning&nbsp;
<p>Zimbabwe went ahead with its plans to sell gold-backed crypto tokens despite a stern warning from the International Monetary Fund (IMF). The IMF had stated that the country should redirect its efforts towards liberalizing its foreign exchange markets instead of adopting a gold-backed currency. An IMF spokesperson stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;A careful assessment should be conducted to ensure the benefits from this measure outweigh the costs and potential risks including, for instance, macroeconomic and financial stability risks, legal and operational risks, governance risks, cost of forgone FX reserves.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Zimbabwe has been reeling under heavy inflation and extreme currency volatility for the better part of a decade. The country adopted the United States Dollar as its currency in 2009 following a prolonged phase of hyperinflation that left its original currency in ruins. The Zimbabwe Dollar saw a reintroduction after a decade in 2019, but volatility issues continue to plague the currency.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Manchester Cityâ€™s Alex Greenwood Drops Three Original NFT Trainers at OKX Collective Metaverse Exhibition]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/manchester-citys-alex-greenwood-drops-three-original-nft-trainers-at-okx-collective-metaverse-exhibition</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Alex170005_1684153794RqTvZjw69B.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Alex170005_1684153794RqTvZjw69B.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Alex170005_1684153794RqTvZjw69B.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:31:40 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/manchester-citys-alex-greenwood-drops-three-original-nft-trainers-at-okx-collective-metaverse-exhibition</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>MANCHESTER, UK, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Greenwood-designed trainers are available free as NFTs as part of AG5 x OKX collection on the OKX NFT Marketplace</p><p>OKX, a world-leading Web3 technology company, together with Manchester City women&rsquo;s player Alex Greenwood, today launched an exhibition in the OKX Collective metaverse to showcase three original NFT trainers designed by Greenwood.</p><p>The NFT trainers, which were designed collaboratively by Greenwood and NFT designer Nas, are focused on key traits that lead to success on the football pitch and in life. Entitled &lsquo;Adaptable&rsquo;, &lsquo;Calm &amp; Patience&rsquo; and &lsquo;Commitment &amp; Passion,&rsquo; the NFTs are available for free via airdrop and as part of the &lsquo;AG5 x OKX&rsquo; NFT collection on the OKX NFT Marketplace. </p>Alex Greenwood said: &ldquo;Working closely with OKX on these trainer designs has been great. They give a sense of how I approach challenges on the pitch. I&rsquo;m excited to see them launch in my personal OKX metaverse showroom!&rdquo;Haider Rafique, Global Chief Marketing Officer at OKX, said: &ldquo;With any metaverse, the next step after creating the environment is to enhance the experience by curating objects and items that fans are eager to engage with and collect. This is an incredible way to bring fans into the experience and let them interact with their favorite athletes or public figures in a way they haven&rsquo;t experienced before. This is how we make the metaverse a living, breathing environment.&rdquo;<p>Visitors to the OKX Collective metaverse will be able to watch exclusive behind-the-scenes content on Alex and Nas&rsquo;s creative process while entering competitions to win prizes, including passes to team trainings, match tickets and much more.</p><p>Fans will also be able to revisit the metaverse DJ set performed by Jack Grealish and Oliver Heldens as well as the instructive metaverse experiences with Manchester City Captain &#304;lkay G&uuml;ndo&#287;an and defender R&uacute;ben Dias.</p><p>To enter the OKX Collective metaverse, simply click this link.</p><p>OKX is the official training kit partner of Manchester City for the 2022/23 season.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Note to editors&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The AG5 x OKX Non-Fungible Token ("NFT") is a digital asset that was created as a collectible; it is free, not tradeable and it is not intended to be used as investment. The NFT has no value nor is there any guarantee that it can or will ever have monetary value. NFTs are not regulated instruments in the UK.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as the fastest and most reliable crypto trading platform for traders everywhere, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>Disclaimer</p><p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION.&nbsp;THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.&nbsp;PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>ContactOKXmedia@okx.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MANCHESTER, UK, May 15th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Greenwood-designed trainers are available free as NFTs as part of AG5 x OKX collection on the OKX NFT Marketplace</p><p>OKX, a world-leading Web3 technology company, together with Manchester City women&rsquo;s player Alex Greenwood, today launched an exhibition in the OKX Collective metaverse to showcase three original NFT trainers designed by Greenwood.</p><p>The NFT trainers, which were designed collaboratively by Greenwood and NFT designer Nas, are focused on key traits that lead to success on the football pitch and in life. Entitled &lsquo;Adaptable&rsquo;, &lsquo;Calm &amp; Patience&rsquo; and &lsquo;Commitment &amp; Passion,&rsquo; the NFTs are available for free via airdrop and as part of the &lsquo;AG5 x OKX&rsquo; NFT collection on the OKX NFT Marketplace. </p>Alex Greenwood said: &ldquo;Working closely with OKX on these trainer designs has been great. They give a sense of how I approach challenges on the pitch. I&rsquo;m excited to see them launch in my personal OKX metaverse showroom!&rdquo;Haider Rafique, Global Chief Marketing Officer at OKX, said: &ldquo;With any metaverse, the next step after creating the environment is to enhance the experience by curating objects and items that fans are eager to engage with and collect. This is an incredible way to bring fans into the experience and let them interact with their favorite athletes or public figures in a way they haven&rsquo;t experienced before. This is how we make the metaverse a living, breathing environment.&rdquo;<p>Visitors to the OKX Collective metaverse will be able to watch exclusive behind-the-scenes content on Alex and Nas&rsquo;s creative process while entering competitions to win prizes, including passes to team trainings, match tickets and much more.</p><p>Fans will also be able to revisit the metaverse DJ set performed by Jack Grealish and Oliver Heldens as well as the instructive metaverse experiences with Manchester City Captain &#304;lkay G&uuml;ndo&#287;an and defender R&uacute;ben Dias.</p><p>To enter the OKX Collective metaverse, simply click this link.</p><p>OKX is the official training kit partner of Manchester City for the 2022/23 season.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Note to editors&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify">The AG5 x OKX Non-Fungible Token ("NFT") is a digital asset that was created as a collectible; it is free, not tradeable and it is not intended to be used as investment. The NFT has no value nor is there any guarantee that it can or will ever have monetary value. NFTs are not regulated instruments in the UK.</p><p>About OKX</p><p>OKX is a world-leading technology company building the future of Web3. Known as the fastest and most reliable crypto trading platform for traders everywhere, OKX&rsquo;s crypto exchange is the second largest globally by trading volume.</p><p>OKX&rsquo;s leading self-custody solutions include the Web3-compatible OKX Wallet, which allows users greater control of their assets while expanding access to DEXs, NFT marketplaces, DeFi, GameFi and thousands of dApps.</p><p>OKX partners with a number of the world&rsquo;s top brands and athletes, including: English Premier League champions Manchester City F.C., McLaren Formula 1, The Tribeca Festival, golfer Ian Poulter, Olympian Scotty James, and F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo.</p><p>OKX is committed to transparency and security and publishes its Proof of Reserves on a monthly basis.</p><p>To learn more about OKX, download our app or visit: okx.com</p><p>Disclaimer</p><p>THIS ANNOUNCEMENT IS PROVIDED FOR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. IT IS NOT INTENDED TO PROVIDE ANY INVESTMENT, TAX, OR LEGAL ADVICE, NOR SHOULD IT BE CONSIDERED AN OFFER TO PURCHASE, SELL, OR HOLD DIGITAL ASSETS. DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, INVOLVE A HIGH DEGREE OF RISK, CAN FLUCTUATE GREATLY, AND CAN EVEN BECOME WORTHLESS. OKX IS NOT REGULATED BY THE FCA, THUS, PROTECTIONS SUCH AS THE FINANCIAL OMBUDSMAN SERVICE OR FINANCIAL SERVICES COMPENSATION SCHEME WILL NOT BE AVAILABLE. YOU SHOULD CONSIDER WHETHER YOU UNDERSTAND HOW CRYPTO WORKS AND WHETHER TRADING OR HOLDING DIGITAL ASSETS IS SUITABLE FOR YOU IN LIGHT OF YOUR FINANCIAL CONDITION.&nbsp;THE VALUE OF YOUR DIGITAL ASSETS, INCLUDING STABLECOINS, CAN INCREASE OR DECREASE AND PROFITS MAY BE SUBJECT TO CAPITAL GAINS TAX. PAST PERFORMANCE DOES NOT INDICATE FUTURE RESULTS.&nbsp;PLEASE CONSULT YOUR LEGAL/TAX/INVESTMENT PROFESSIONAL FOR QUESTIONS ABOUT YOUR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES.</p>ContactOKXmedia@okx.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Secures $100M Funding For Worldcoin Crypto Project]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/openai-ceo-secures-100m-funding-for-worldcoin-crypto-project</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/worldcoin-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:55:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/openai-ceo-secures-100m-funding-for-worldcoin-crypto-project</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin project has reportedly secured $100 million in fresh funding. Worldcoin is Altman&rsquo;s planned iris-scanning cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Worldcoin also debuted a new crypto wallet last month called World App.&nbsp;</p>
$100 Million Funding Reportedly Secured&nbsp;
<p>Securing $100 million in funding by Altman ahead of Worldcoin&rsquo;s launch is no small feat, considering it comes at a testing time in the cryptocurrency markets. Many believe that securing such large funding is a feat in itself, given the prevailing market conditions.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s a bear market, a crypto winter. It&rsquo;s remarkable for a project in this space to get this amount of investment.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The turbulence prevailing in the crypto space was acknowledged by the head of payment products at Ripple, Brendan Berry, who stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;What happened through 2022 was a lot of layoffs, companies going under, and consumer losses. We are coming out of that period with a healthy skepticism separating what was a large amount of hype and speculative investment driving bull market activity from real companies and technologies solving real customer pain points.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Worldcoin was founded in 2019 by Alex Blania and Altman. The project aims to use eyeball-scanning technology to launch a global identification system that would allow everyone in the world to access cryptocurrencies. Worldcoin has been quietly working on various crypto-related products since its inception. However, the company has been in the shadows of Altman&rsquo;s other project, OpenAI.&nbsp;</p>
The World App Crypto Wallet&nbsp;
<p>The funding announcement comes hot on the heels of a significant product release by Worldcoin. The company debuted a new crypto wallet called World App. According to the company, World App will help expand the availability of global finance and digital identity. The wallet is designed specifically for the Worldcoin ecosystem and can be used to authenticate a user&rsquo;s identity through World ID. Wallet users can also receive Worldcoin tokens and send digital currencies to users across the globe. World ID acts as a digital passport, enabling users to prove their identity as unique individuals without sacrificing their privacy and anonymity by divulging excessive personal information. In a blog post, Worldcoin talked about World App, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;World App is a different kind of wallet. It doesn&rsquo;t support every token or functionality crypto has to offer, and it doesn&rsquo;t expose every possible configuration. Instead, it is designed by TFH [Tools for Humanity] to focus on a handful of key functionalities for Worldcoin and Ethereum to keep things simple and familiar so anyone can use them.&rdquo;</p>

Biometric Crypto Verification&nbsp;
<p>Ultimately, Worldcoin aims to bring in some sort of biometric verification standards that are common and at power with banking applications to the larger crypto ecosystem. So far, crypto wallets need to catch up when it comes to biometric verification and its implementation. The company behind the project, Tools for Humanity, aims to retain the accessibility and privacy of cryptocurrencies. These do not need any identification numbers or official documents for transactions. With Worldcoin, Altman hopes to introduce a stronger level of user verification, one that is based on biometric authentication.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To achieve this goal, Worldcoin has developed a biometric imaging service called &ldquo;The Orb.&rdquo; However, unlike traditional finance, The Orb does not link biometric profiles to other identifying factors. Instead, The Orb is used as a way to simply verify humannes. All of the data captured is recorded on the Polygon Network. However, it is not linked with other information such as user names, etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman&rsquo;s Worldcoin project has reportedly secured $100 million in fresh funding. Worldcoin is Altman&rsquo;s planned iris-scanning cryptocurrency.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Worldcoin also debuted a new crypto wallet last month called World App.&nbsp;</p>
$100 Million Funding Reportedly Secured&nbsp;
<p>Securing $100 million in funding by Altman ahead of Worldcoin&rsquo;s launch is no small feat, considering it comes at a testing time in the cryptocurrency markets. Many believe that securing such large funding is a feat in itself, given the prevailing market conditions.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s a bear market, a crypto winter. It&rsquo;s remarkable for a project in this space to get this amount of investment.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The turbulence prevailing in the crypto space was acknowledged by the head of payment products at Ripple, Brendan Berry, who stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;What happened through 2022 was a lot of layoffs, companies going under, and consumer losses. We are coming out of that period with a healthy skepticism separating what was a large amount of hype and speculative investment driving bull market activity from real companies and technologies solving real customer pain points.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Worldcoin was founded in 2019 by Alex Blania and Altman. The project aims to use eyeball-scanning technology to launch a global identification system that would allow everyone in the world to access cryptocurrencies. Worldcoin has been quietly working on various crypto-related products since its inception. However, the company has been in the shadows of Altman&rsquo;s other project, OpenAI.&nbsp;</p>
The World App Crypto Wallet&nbsp;
<p>The funding announcement comes hot on the heels of a significant product release by Worldcoin. The company debuted a new crypto wallet called World App. According to the company, World App will help expand the availability of global finance and digital identity. The wallet is designed specifically for the Worldcoin ecosystem and can be used to authenticate a user&rsquo;s identity through World ID. Wallet users can also receive Worldcoin tokens and send digital currencies to users across the globe. World ID acts as a digital passport, enabling users to prove their identity as unique individuals without sacrificing their privacy and anonymity by divulging excessive personal information. In a blog post, Worldcoin talked about World App, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;World App is a different kind of wallet. It doesn&rsquo;t support every token or functionality crypto has to offer, and it doesn&rsquo;t expose every possible configuration. Instead, it is designed by TFH [Tools for Humanity] to focus on a handful of key functionalities for Worldcoin and Ethereum to keep things simple and familiar so anyone can use them.&rdquo;</p>

Biometric Crypto Verification&nbsp;
<p>Ultimately, Worldcoin aims to bring in some sort of biometric verification standards that are common and at power with banking applications to the larger crypto ecosystem. So far, crypto wallets need to catch up when it comes to biometric verification and its implementation. The company behind the project, Tools for Humanity, aims to retain the accessibility and privacy of cryptocurrencies. These do not need any identification numbers or official documents for transactions. With Worldcoin, Altman hopes to introduce a stronger level of user verification, one that is based on biometric authentication.&nbsp;</p>
<p>To achieve this goal, Worldcoin has developed a biometric imaging service called &ldquo;The Orb.&rdquo; However, unlike traditional finance, The Orb does not link biometric profiles to other identifying factors. Instead, The Orb is used as a way to simply verify humannes. All of the data captured is recorded on the Polygon Network. However, it is not linked with other information such as user names, etc.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Quadriga Users To Get 13% Of Claim, Crypto Daily TV 15/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/quadriga-users-to-get-13-of-claim-crypto-daily-tv-15-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-quadriga.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-quadriga.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-quadriga.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/quadriga-users-to-get-13-of-claim-crypto-daily-tv-15-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Quadriga CX bankruptcy claimers to get 13% on the dollar</p>
<p>Former users of the bankrupt Canadian crypto exchange Quadriga CX will soon get a check for 13% of their claim, according to a notice to creditors published late Friday by accounting giant EY.</p>
<p>Binance announces exit from Canada</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance has announced that it would cease operations in Canada, citing the challenging regulatory environment. The world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange by volume said new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits prompted the exit.</p>
<p>BTC miner Rhodium faces lawsuit</p>
<p>Crypto mining firm Riot Platforms &mdash; formerly Riot Blockchain &mdash; has taken legal action against Texas-based Bitcoin miner Rhodium Enterprises to recover &ldquo;more than $26 million&rdquo; in alleged unpaid mining facility fees</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.6% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair rose 0.6% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.5% during the session. The RSI is giving a negative signal.  Support is at 265041 and resistance is at 272081.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained a moderate 0.2% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained 0.2% in the last session after rising as much as 1.5% during the session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1770.1967 and resistance is at 1827.0367.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair rose 0.3% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.8% during the session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4187 and resistance is at 0.4331.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 3.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 3.0% in the last session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 79.3967, and resistance is at 81.4967.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Total Net TIC Flows</p>
<p>The Total Net Treasury International Capital (TIC) Flows show in and out flows of financial resources. The US Total Net TIC Flows will be released at 20:00 GMT, the Eurozone's Industrial Production at 09:00 GMT, the US 6-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of the industrial production.</p>
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by the US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive.</p>
<p>JP Machine Tool Orders</p>
<p>The Machine Tool Orders show movements in tool orders by manufacturers. It indicates the state of the Japanese economy. Japan's Machine Tool Orders will be released at 06:00 GMT, the Eurozone's Eurogroup Meeting at 07:00 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Eurogroup Meeting</p>
<p>Eurogroup meetings are attended by the Eurogroup President, the Finance Minister of each Member State of the Euro area, the Commissioner for economic and monetary affairs, and the President of the European Central Bank.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Quadriga CX bankruptcy claimers to get 13% on the dollar</p>
<p>Former users of the bankrupt Canadian crypto exchange Quadriga CX will soon get a check for 13% of their claim, according to a notice to creditors published late Friday by accounting giant EY.</p>
<p>Binance announces exit from Canada</p>
<p>Crypto exchange Binance has announced that it would cease operations in Canada, citing the challenging regulatory environment. The world&rsquo;s largest crypto exchange by volume said new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits prompted the exit.</p>
<p>BTC miner Rhodium faces lawsuit</p>
<p>Crypto mining firm Riot Platforms &mdash; formerly Riot Blockchain &mdash; has taken legal action against Texas-based Bitcoin miner Rhodium Enterprises to recover &ldquo;more than $26 million&rdquo; in alleged unpaid mining facility fees</p>
BTC/USD gained 0.6% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair rose 0.6% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.5% during the session. The RSI is giving a negative signal.  Support is at 265041 and resistance is at 272081.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained a moderate 0.2% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained 0.2% in the last session after rising as much as 1.5% during the session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1770.1967 and resistance is at 1827.0367.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair rose 0.3% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.8% during the session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 0.4187 and resistance is at 0.4331.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD exploded 3.0% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 3.0% in the last session. The CCI is giving a positive signal. Support is at 79.3967, and resistance is at 81.4967.</p>
<p>The CCI is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>US Total Net TIC Flows</p>
<p>The Total Net Treasury International Capital (TIC) Flows show in and out flows of financial resources. The US Total Net TIC Flows will be released at 20:00 GMT, the Eurozone's Industrial Production at 09:00 GMT, the US 6-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Industrial Production</p>
<p>Industry is a basic category of business activity. Changes in the volume of the physical output of the nation's factories, mines, and utilities are measured by the index of the industrial production.</p>
<p>US 6-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>The auction sets the average yield on the bills auctioned by the US Department of Treasury. Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive.</p>
<p>JP Machine Tool Orders</p>
<p>The Machine Tool Orders show movements in tool orders by manufacturers. It indicates the state of the Japanese economy. Japan's Machine Tool Orders will be released at 06:00 GMT, the Eurozone's Eurogroup Meeting at 07:00 GMT, and the US 3-Month Bill Auction at 15:30 GMT.</p>
<p>EMU Eurogroup Meeting</p>
<p>Eurogroup meetings are attended by the Eurogroup President, the Finance Minister of each Member State of the Euro area, the Commissioner for economic and monetary affairs, and the President of the European Central Bank.</p>
<p>US 3-Month Bill Auction</p>
<p>Treasury bills are short-term securities maturing in one year or less. The yield on the bills represents the return an investor will receive by holding the bond until maturity.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and crypto are weathering the storm]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-and-crypto-are-weathering-the-storm</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-44.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-44.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bit-44.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:00:13 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-and-crypto-are-weathering-the-storm</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Even while facing the wrath of the US government, regulators, and mainstream press, Bitcoin and crypto continue to hold strongly.</p>
Mainstream press down on crypto
<p>Hardly a day goes by when yet another article appears in the mainstream press heralding such and such a misdemeanour in the crypto sector. Whether it be that Bitcoin uses more energy than this or that country, or another crypto exchange is sent a notice informing it of impending litigation from the SEC.</p>
<p>Everything appears designed to malign the crypto industry and make it seem that it is all a den of thieves and brigands. Perhaps the strategy is that while the public is fed such ideas by the mainstream press, this can help to take the focus off of what is happening in the banking industry.</p>
Banking sector dead in the water
<p>It would seem a decent strategy considering the widespread decay to be found in the banking sector. Many banks are underwater after buying long term bonds when the interest rate was at zero percent. Now the US is looking at 5.25% these banks are severely in debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Regulators allowed these banks to not have to mark to market these losses and so that is why many banks are where they are today. If such goings on were happening in crypto it can be assured that a full account would be plastered across the mainstream press.</p>
<p>It is no longer a mystery as to why the Biden administration is pursuing the crypto industry with such fervour. With the banks under such extreme duress there is the chance that the public starts to get wise and begins to put part of its wealth into Bitcoin.</p>
Bitcoin is the logical play
<p>Once it's known that you cannot get wealthy on dollars (or any other fiat currency) and that inflation and money printing is stripping away purchasing power, a move into sound monies such as gold, silver and Bitcoin is the most logical step.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has started the week well and is up 1.75% at time of going to press. There may be downside still to come but if Bitcoin can stay above the $25,000 support level another surge upwards could be on the cards.</p>
<p>The weekly Stochastic RSI is on the way down and when it gets to the bottom and turns up, the momentum would likely give a strong impetus to price.</p>
<p>The rest of the cryptocurrency market is also in the green for the start of the week. Some cryptocurrencies have already seen a resetting of the RSIs so perhaps some breakouts could happen over the next few days.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even while facing the wrath of the US government, regulators, and mainstream press, Bitcoin and crypto continue to hold strongly.</p>
Mainstream press down on crypto
<p>Hardly a day goes by when yet another article appears in the mainstream press heralding such and such a misdemeanour in the crypto sector. Whether it be that Bitcoin uses more energy than this or that country, or another crypto exchange is sent a notice informing it of impending litigation from the SEC.</p>
<p>Everything appears designed to malign the crypto industry and make it seem that it is all a den of thieves and brigands. Perhaps the strategy is that while the public is fed such ideas by the mainstream press, this can help to take the focus off of what is happening in the banking industry.</p>
Banking sector dead in the water
<p>It would seem a decent strategy considering the widespread decay to be found in the banking sector. Many banks are underwater after buying long term bonds when the interest rate was at zero percent. Now the US is looking at 5.25% these banks are severely in debt.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Regulators allowed these banks to not have to mark to market these losses and so that is why many banks are where they are today. If such goings on were happening in crypto it can be assured that a full account would be plastered across the mainstream press.</p>
<p>It is no longer a mystery as to why the Biden administration is pursuing the crypto industry with such fervour. With the banks under such extreme duress there is the chance that the public starts to get wise and begins to put part of its wealth into Bitcoin.</p>
Bitcoin is the logical play
<p>Once it's known that you cannot get wealthy on dollars (or any other fiat currency) and that inflation and money printing is stripping away purchasing power, a move into sound monies such as gold, silver and Bitcoin is the most logical step.</p>
<p>Bitcoin has started the week well and is up 1.75% at time of going to press. There may be downside still to come but if Bitcoin can stay above the $25,000 support level another surge upwards could be on the cards.</p>
<p>The weekly Stochastic RSI is on the way down and when it gets to the bottom and turns up, the momentum would likely give a strong impetus to price.</p>
<p>The rest of the cryptocurrency market is also in the green for the start of the week. Some cryptocurrencies have already seen a resetting of the RSIs so perhaps some breakouts could happen over the next few days.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Regulations Around the World]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/regulations-around-the-world</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-17.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-17.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/dusk-17.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 11:01:54 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/regulations-around-the-world</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>While blockchain and cryptocurrencies may transcend borders, the regulatory framework varies hugely from country to country and what is permitted in one jurisdiction may be prohibited in another.</p>
<p>Dusk Network is dedicated to enabling secure, compliant, and scalable decentralized finance and facilitating the tokenization of securities and other financial instruments. While our focus has largely been on Europe due to its significance for our target audience and the impact of the upcoming MiCA regulations on the blockchain industry in the region, we are actively monitoring and staying up to date with evolving global regulations dealing with blockchain. Ryan King, Head of Business Development, wrote extensively about MiCA in this 5-part series (click here for part one) if you would like a deep-dive into what&rsquo;s going on in the EU.</p>
<p>Though the US typically dominates the news, different countries have different needs and situations and as such are responding to cryptocurrencies and blockchain in different ways, with some making steps towards adopting the technology, others creating business-friendly environments with taxes, and others being HODLers themselves.</p>
<p>In this post, we will explore the diverse approaches countries are taking to regulate and engage with blockchain technology, highlighting some key challenges and opportunities this presents for the global community.</p>
El Salvador
<p>El Salvador, quite possibly the most overtly pro-crypto country, has demonstrated a strong openness toward Bitcoin. President Nayib Bukele goes as far as regularly tweeting about it and even playing along with&nbsp;crypto Twitter culture.</p>
<p>In a groundbreaking move, El Salvador recognized $BTC as legal tender in September 2021, becoming the first country to do so. This means that Bitcoin can be used to pay for goods and services as well as to settle debts. According to&nbsp;this report&nbsp;by PwC, the three main reasons for doing so are to increase the efficiency of remittances, reduce the number of unbanked people, and reduce the reliance on the US Dollar.</p>
<p>It is important to consider the unique motivations and needs of countries outside the West when examining the impact of cryptocurrencies.t. People all over the world rely on remittances but the process for sending remittances back home can be slow, expensive, and time-consuming. The&nbsp;value of remittances globally&nbsp;reached $796 billion in 2022, more than the GDP of Turkey, Saudi Arabia, and Switzerland, and if &ldquo;Global Remittances&rdquo; was a country it would have the 17th biggest GDP just after Indonesia.</p>
Australia
<p>Australia has adopted a proactive approach to cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, with regulatory frameworks and innovation from both the public and private sectors, where severely regulated institutions like banks have been venturing into stablecoin experimentation.</p>
<p>In Australia, cryptocurrencies are&nbsp;treated like property, meaning that they are subject to capital gain taxation, and can be used for transactions while being legally traded, stored, and even included in training for KYC and CTF procedures. Unlike El Salvador which has classified $BTC as legal tender, Australia views cryptocurrencies as investments.</p>
<p>In a significant development, the National Australian Bank partnered with renowned crypto company Fireblocks to launch AUDN, a stablecoin on the Ethereum and Algorand networks, which was&nbsp;recently used for cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>Australia seems to be taking great steps by not over-regulating the industry, and even having an environment where national banks feel they can get involved.</p>
Portugal
<p>Portugal is known for its crypto-friendly tax laws, which have contributed to the growth of FinTech companies and investment in the country. As part of the European Union, Portugal is not only covered by the MiCA regulations, but has also been adopting blockchain technology,&nbsp;using blockchain&nbsp;in the public services, healthcare, and supply chain industries. The Government is at work to put together a&nbsp;blockchain strategy, recognizing the value and potential of the technology.</p>
India
<p>Home to the world's largest population, India has been cautious in its approach to cryptocurrency regulations, with the government observing international developments before committing to a clear framework. The Minister of State Finance&nbsp;declared&nbsp;&ldquo;Crypto assets are by definition borderless and require international collaboration to prevent regulatory arbitrage. Therefore, any legislation on the subject can be effective only with significant international collaboration on evaluation of the risks and benefits and evolution of common taxonomy and standards&rdquo;</p>
<p>As it currently stands there are no concrete rules on cryptocurrency in India, with the space currently being unregulated (but crypto profits are taxed at 30%). India recently overtook China as having the biggest population in the world and has already embraced electronic payments for goods, so it might be just a matter of time until India begins to regulate and enter the crypto and blockchain space.</p>
China
<p>While Bitcoin is classified as a virtual commodity in China, its use as legal tender is prohibited, and there are restrictions on cryptocurrency-related activities.</p>
<p>China has had an interesting journey with cryptocurrencies and blockchain and was initially very enthusiastic. However, the Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs) mania led to a blanket ban, and Binance - which was started in China - was also forced to leave.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin is classified as a&nbsp;virtual commodity&nbsp;in China, its use as legal tender is prohibited, and there are restrictions on cryptocurrency-related activities. In 2021 China &ldquo;banned Bitcoin&rdquo; and prohibited mining, although it&rsquo;s worth noting that China has been banning Bitcoin since 2013. Currently, the buying of Bitcoin is banned, but holding cryptocurrencies isn&rsquo;t.</p>
<p>However&hellip;.</p>
<p>Hong Kong looks to be&nbsp;opening up to crypto&nbsp;and working on crypto-friendly regulation so we could see Hong Kong become a thriving hub for crypto and potentially benefit from China&rsquo;s talent.</p>
The UAE
<p>The UAE, especially Dubai, is emerging as a hub for business, innovation, and cryptocurrency activities, attracting influencers and traders from around the world (those low/no tax rates work!).</p>
<p>With regard to blockchain and cryptocurrency regulation, the UAE&rsquo;s approach seems to focus on facilitating the trading and ownership of digital assets, as well as fostering innovation&nbsp;in the blockchain space. Institutions in the UAE (as well in collaboration with Saudi Arabia) are embracing cryptocurrencies, with many new departments being set up as well as pre-existing ones including cryptocurrencies within their remit.</p>
Other Notable Legislations
<p>Earlier this year Indonesia&nbsp;updated its laws&nbsp;to be more up-to-date with the current context and shows a deeper understanding of the tech and its potential than just trading.</p>
<p>Singapore has long had a reputation for being crypto-friendly (and business-friendly too) with the&nbsp;authorities working with banks&nbsp;to provide clarity on crypto moving forward.</p>
<p>Malta is another country that has a reputation for being crypto-friendly and is implementing&nbsp;three new laws&nbsp;to help regulate and develop blockchain technology; The Malta Digital Innovation Authority Bill, The Technology Arrangements and Services Bill, and the Virtual Financial Assets Bill. These could see Malta really lead the way, however as a member of the EU Malta will fall under the MiCA regulations too.</p>
What does this mean?
<p>The diverse approaches we analyzed to cryptocurrency and blockchain regulation offer valuable insights into the future of mass adoption and institutional involvement in this rapidly evolving sector and there&rsquo;s a lot to be excited about. In many ways, mass adoption relies on institutional adoption, and institutions can&rsquo;t get too involved in crypto until they have a clear regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Across the world, we see different approaches to this new technology and the opportunities it brings, with some countries making it easier to do business and trade, while others are looking to develop the underlying technology in addition to trading.</p>
<p>There is also a difference between countries that are &ldquo;crypto-friendly&rdquo; due to not yet having clear regulations and countries that are actively crypto-friendly and have created regulations.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s noteworthy that countries like India appear to be hanging back. A country like India could be primed for mass adoption of blockchain (amazing engineers, the tech hub of Bangalore, a lot of QR code payment apps for digital payments, and a lot of unbanked people/limited access to banking) but it seems to be hanging back to see what other countries do and how that works out.</p>
<p>As MiCA takes effect and other countries develop their own regulations, it will be fascinating to observe how the global landscape of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology evolves, with some countries potentially benefiting from international stablecoin trading and near-instant settlements, while others may lag behind.</p>
<p>It is certainly an exciting time for blockchain and crypto, and we&rsquo;re thrilled that the EU has laid out a clear plan and are happy to be involved in the process of making blockchain normal and usable.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While blockchain and cryptocurrencies may transcend borders, the regulatory framework varies hugely from country to country and what is permitted in one jurisdiction may be prohibited in another.</p>
<p>Dusk Network is dedicated to enabling secure, compliant, and scalable decentralized finance and facilitating the tokenization of securities and other financial instruments. While our focus has largely been on Europe due to its significance for our target audience and the impact of the upcoming MiCA regulations on the blockchain industry in the region, we are actively monitoring and staying up to date with evolving global regulations dealing with blockchain. Ryan King, Head of Business Development, wrote extensively about MiCA in this 5-part series (click here for part one) if you would like a deep-dive into what&rsquo;s going on in the EU.</p>
<p>Though the US typically dominates the news, different countries have different needs and situations and as such are responding to cryptocurrencies and blockchain in different ways, with some making steps towards adopting the technology, others creating business-friendly environments with taxes, and others being HODLers themselves.</p>
<p>In this post, we will explore the diverse approaches countries are taking to regulate and engage with blockchain technology, highlighting some key challenges and opportunities this presents for the global community.</p>
El Salvador
<p>El Salvador, quite possibly the most overtly pro-crypto country, has demonstrated a strong openness toward Bitcoin. President Nayib Bukele goes as far as regularly tweeting about it and even playing along with&nbsp;crypto Twitter culture.</p>
<p>In a groundbreaking move, El Salvador recognized $BTC as legal tender in September 2021, becoming the first country to do so. This means that Bitcoin can be used to pay for goods and services as well as to settle debts. According to&nbsp;this report&nbsp;by PwC, the three main reasons for doing so are to increase the efficiency of remittances, reduce the number of unbanked people, and reduce the reliance on the US Dollar.</p>
<p>It is important to consider the unique motivations and needs of countries outside the West when examining the impact of cryptocurrencies.t. People all over the world rely on remittances but the process for sending remittances back home can be slow, expensive, and time-consuming. The&nbsp;value of remittances globally&nbsp;reached $796 billion in 2022, more than the GDP of Turkey, Saudi Arabia, and Switzerland, and if &ldquo;Global Remittances&rdquo; was a country it would have the 17th biggest GDP just after Indonesia.</p>
Australia
<p>Australia has adopted a proactive approach to cryptocurrency and blockchain technology, with regulatory frameworks and innovation from both the public and private sectors, where severely regulated institutions like banks have been venturing into stablecoin experimentation.</p>
<p>In Australia, cryptocurrencies are&nbsp;treated like property, meaning that they are subject to capital gain taxation, and can be used for transactions while being legally traded, stored, and even included in training for KYC and CTF procedures. Unlike El Salvador which has classified $BTC as legal tender, Australia views cryptocurrencies as investments.</p>
<p>In a significant development, the National Australian Bank partnered with renowned crypto company Fireblocks to launch AUDN, a stablecoin on the Ethereum and Algorand networks, which was&nbsp;recently used for cross-border transactions.</p>
<p>Australia seems to be taking great steps by not over-regulating the industry, and even having an environment where national banks feel they can get involved.</p>
Portugal
<p>Portugal is known for its crypto-friendly tax laws, which have contributed to the growth of FinTech companies and investment in the country. As part of the European Union, Portugal is not only covered by the MiCA regulations, but has also been adopting blockchain technology,&nbsp;using blockchain&nbsp;in the public services, healthcare, and supply chain industries. The Government is at work to put together a&nbsp;blockchain strategy, recognizing the value and potential of the technology.</p>
India
<p>Home to the world's largest population, India has been cautious in its approach to cryptocurrency regulations, with the government observing international developments before committing to a clear framework. The Minister of State Finance&nbsp;declared&nbsp;&ldquo;Crypto assets are by definition borderless and require international collaboration to prevent regulatory arbitrage. Therefore, any legislation on the subject can be effective only with significant international collaboration on evaluation of the risks and benefits and evolution of common taxonomy and standards&rdquo;</p>
<p>As it currently stands there are no concrete rules on cryptocurrency in India, with the space currently being unregulated (but crypto profits are taxed at 30%). India recently overtook China as having the biggest population in the world and has already embraced electronic payments for goods, so it might be just a matter of time until India begins to regulate and enter the crypto and blockchain space.</p>
China
<p>While Bitcoin is classified as a virtual commodity in China, its use as legal tender is prohibited, and there are restrictions on cryptocurrency-related activities.</p>
<p>China has had an interesting journey with cryptocurrencies and blockchain and was initially very enthusiastic. However, the Initial Coin Offerings (ICOs) mania led to a blanket ban, and Binance - which was started in China - was also forced to leave.</p>
<p>While Bitcoin is classified as a&nbsp;virtual commodity&nbsp;in China, its use as legal tender is prohibited, and there are restrictions on cryptocurrency-related activities. In 2021 China &ldquo;banned Bitcoin&rdquo; and prohibited mining, although it&rsquo;s worth noting that China has been banning Bitcoin since 2013. Currently, the buying of Bitcoin is banned, but holding cryptocurrencies isn&rsquo;t.</p>
<p>However&hellip;.</p>
<p>Hong Kong looks to be&nbsp;opening up to crypto&nbsp;and working on crypto-friendly regulation so we could see Hong Kong become a thriving hub for crypto and potentially benefit from China&rsquo;s talent.</p>
The UAE
<p>The UAE, especially Dubai, is emerging as a hub for business, innovation, and cryptocurrency activities, attracting influencers and traders from around the world (those low/no tax rates work!).</p>
<p>With regard to blockchain and cryptocurrency regulation, the UAE&rsquo;s approach seems to focus on facilitating the trading and ownership of digital assets, as well as fostering innovation&nbsp;in the blockchain space. Institutions in the UAE (as well in collaboration with Saudi Arabia) are embracing cryptocurrencies, with many new departments being set up as well as pre-existing ones including cryptocurrencies within their remit.</p>
Other Notable Legislations
<p>Earlier this year Indonesia&nbsp;updated its laws&nbsp;to be more up-to-date with the current context and shows a deeper understanding of the tech and its potential than just trading.</p>
<p>Singapore has long had a reputation for being crypto-friendly (and business-friendly too) with the&nbsp;authorities working with banks&nbsp;to provide clarity on crypto moving forward.</p>
<p>Malta is another country that has a reputation for being crypto-friendly and is implementing&nbsp;three new laws&nbsp;to help regulate and develop blockchain technology; The Malta Digital Innovation Authority Bill, The Technology Arrangements and Services Bill, and the Virtual Financial Assets Bill. These could see Malta really lead the way, however as a member of the EU Malta will fall under the MiCA regulations too.</p>
What does this mean?
<p>The diverse approaches we analyzed to cryptocurrency and blockchain regulation offer valuable insights into the future of mass adoption and institutional involvement in this rapidly evolving sector and there&rsquo;s a lot to be excited about. In many ways, mass adoption relies on institutional adoption, and institutions can&rsquo;t get too involved in crypto until they have a clear regulatory framework.</p>
<p>Across the world, we see different approaches to this new technology and the opportunities it brings, with some countries making it easier to do business and trade, while others are looking to develop the underlying technology in addition to trading.</p>
<p>There is also a difference between countries that are &ldquo;crypto-friendly&rdquo; due to not yet having clear regulations and countries that are actively crypto-friendly and have created regulations.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s noteworthy that countries like India appear to be hanging back. A country like India could be primed for mass adoption of blockchain (amazing engineers, the tech hub of Bangalore, a lot of QR code payment apps for digital payments, and a lot of unbanked people/limited access to banking) but it seems to be hanging back to see what other countries do and how that works out.</p>
<p>As MiCA takes effect and other countries develop their own regulations, it will be fascinating to observe how the global landscape of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology evolves, with some countries potentially benefiting from international stablecoin trading and near-instant settlements, while others may lag behind.</p>
<p>It is certainly an exciting time for blockchain and crypto, and we&rsquo;re thrilled that the EU has laid out a clear plan and are happy to be involved in the process of making blockchain normal and usable.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bakkt Axes 25 DeFi and NFT Tokens from Apex Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bakkt-axes-25-tokens-from-apex-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bakkt-delisting-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bakkt-delisting-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/bakkt-delisting-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bakkt-axes-25-tokens-from-apex-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Digital asset firm Bakkt has delisted 25 out of the 36 tokens on its recently acquired Apex Crypto platform. The decision was presumably made in compliance with regulatory guidance, and the delisted tokens mainly belong to popular decentralized finance (DeFi) and nonfungible token (NFT) ecosystems.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The announcement comes after the digital asset firm's finalized acquisition of Apex Crypto in April, with negotiations that began in November 2022. Another influence to the decision is a perceived shift on Bakkt's overall strategy from crypto retail towards business-to-business (B2B) services.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Bakkt spokesperson claims that the delisting decision was made in the interest of consumer and client protection, based on the firm's regular, internal review of listed coins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Among the tokens delisted are Aave (AAVE), ApeCoin (APE), Avalanche (AVAX), Bancor Network Token (BNT), Basic Attention Token (BAT), Chainlink (LINK), Chiliz (CHZ), Compound Token (COMP), Cosmos (ATOM), Curve DAO (CRV), Enjin Coin (ENJ), Fantom (FTM), Filecoin (FIL), GALA (GALA), The Graph (GRT), Internet Computer (ICP), Loopring (LRC), Maker DAO (MKR), Republic (REN), Stellar (XLM), Sushiswap (SUSHI), Synthetix (SNX), Tezos (XTZ), Uniswap (UNI), and Yearn Finance (YFI).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bakkt's acquisition of Apex Crypto, an unprofitable platform, cost the company $55 million in cash and $145 million in stock. Apex Crypto is a "turnkey" service that provides execution, clearing, custody, cost basis, and tax services to 5 million customers through 30 financial technology partners.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bakkt secured a broker-dealer license from Bumped Financial earlier in February this year, which it disclosed in a financial statement. The license was part of Bakkt's strategy to expand its presence in the fintech market, catering to a growing clientele. However, Bakkt's focus shifted when it decided to shut down its retail-oriented app in March, concentrating instead on business-to-business (B2B) operations. Bakkt now aims to provide crypto and loyalty solutions to businesses through Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) and API solutions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Intercontinental Exchange, the majority owner of Bakkt, also owns the New York Stock Exchange. Bakkt's stock experienced a 7% decline on May 12, the day of the announcement. However, it is also down by 40% over the last six months, although it is up 3.45% on a year-to-date basis.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Digital asset firm Bakkt has delisted 25 out of the 36 tokens on its recently acquired Apex Crypto platform. The decision was presumably made in compliance with regulatory guidance, and the delisted tokens mainly belong to popular decentralized finance (DeFi) and nonfungible token (NFT) ecosystems.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The announcement comes after the digital asset firm's finalized acquisition of Apex Crypto in April, with negotiations that began in November 2022. Another influence to the decision is a perceived shift on Bakkt's overall strategy from crypto retail towards business-to-business (B2B) services.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Bakkt spokesperson claims that the delisting decision was made in the interest of consumer and client protection, based on the firm's regular, internal review of listed coins.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Among the tokens delisted are Aave (AAVE), ApeCoin (APE), Avalanche (AVAX), Bancor Network Token (BNT), Basic Attention Token (BAT), Chainlink (LINK), Chiliz (CHZ), Compound Token (COMP), Cosmos (ATOM), Curve DAO (CRV), Enjin Coin (ENJ), Fantom (FTM), Filecoin (FIL), GALA (GALA), The Graph (GRT), Internet Computer (ICP), Loopring (LRC), Maker DAO (MKR), Republic (REN), Stellar (XLM), Sushiswap (SUSHI), Synthetix (SNX), Tezos (XTZ), Uniswap (UNI), and Yearn Finance (YFI).</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bakkt's acquisition of Apex Crypto, an unprofitable platform, cost the company $55 million in cash and $145 million in stock. Apex Crypto is a "turnkey" service that provides execution, clearing, custody, cost basis, and tax services to 5 million customers through 30 financial technology partners.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Bakkt secured a broker-dealer license from Bumped Financial earlier in February this year, which it disclosed in a financial statement. The license was part of Bakkt's strategy to expand its presence in the fintech market, catering to a growing clientele. However, Bakkt's focus shifted when it decided to shut down its retail-oriented app in March, concentrating instead on business-to-business (B2B) operations. Bakkt now aims to provide crypto and loyalty solutions to businesses through Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) and API solutions.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Intercontinental Exchange, the majority owner of Bakkt, also owns the New York Stock Exchange. Bakkt's stock experienced a 7% decline on May 12, the day of the announcement. However, it is also down by 40% over the last six months, although it is up 3.45% on a year-to-date basis.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
