<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:16:28 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Community Update: Chain Of Alliance Alpha 1.0 Is Live; Roadmap And More]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/community-update-chain-of-alliance-alpha-10-is-live-roadmap-and-more</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_5_8703841625_1684949675xPLuqksKCd.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_5_8703841625_1684949675xPLuqksKCd.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_5_8703841625_1684949675xPLuqksKCd.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:19:05 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/community-update-chain-of-alliance-alpha-10-is-live-roadmap-and-more</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Chain of Alliance Launches Public Alpha 1.0 on Chromia Testnet Sigma, Paving the Way to Become the Premier Turn-Based, Party-Builder RPG Multiverse</p><p>Chain of Alliance is thrilled to unveil the next phase of its remarkable journey as it solidifies its position as the leading turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse, catering to both Web3 and traditional players. This momentous milestone marks the beginning of an extraordinary adventure for Chain of Alliance as it sets its sights on redefining the landscape of turn-based RPG gaming. The company is committed to fostering a vibrant and inclusive community driven by a shared passion for the genre.</p><p>Building upon a foundation of innovation and community engagement, Chain of Alliance has implemented strategic structural adjustments and bolstered its team to propel the project forward. With a clear and attainable roadmap for the remainder of the year, the company is proud to announce the official launch of its highly anticipated Public Alpha 1.0, now available on the Chromia Testnet Sigma. Experience the game firsthand by visiting the official website.</p><p>Chain of Alliance invites players to immerse themselves in a captivating world of strategic combat. The game's innovative features and engaging gameplay mechanics aim to captivate both Web3 enthusiasts and traditional gamers.</p><p>The team is extending its gratitude to its esteemed badge holders, who have been granted an exclusive preview of the game, providing valuable feedback that has contributed to its refinement.</p><p>Introducing The New Team</p><p>Joining Chain of Alliance as the Lead Producer is Nicholas St. Louis, a seasoned professional with six years of industry experience. Nicholas has successfully managed projects at prestigious companies such as Sega, Moon Studios, and Rockstar and now brings his expertise to the team.</p><p>Overseeing the design of all new features is Cl&eacute;ment Fitoussi, an exceptionally talented Game Designer with over six years of experience in the gaming industry. Cl&eacute;ment's impressive portfolio includes collaborations with renowned companies like Mattel, Ubisoft, and Seascape.&nbsp;</p><p>Leading the marketing and community management efforts is Jorn Wisman, a Marketing Lead with over 15 years of experience in the gaming industry. Jorn's invaluable insights and expertise have been cultivated through his previous positions at PlayStation and Rockstar Games.&nbsp;</p><p>Game Redesign: Alpha 1.0</p><p>With the release of Alpha 1.0, Chain of Alliance invites players to experience a transformed gaming landscape. The latest Alpha build introduces significant changes and improvements. View the Chain of Alliance onboarding guide here, along with the following exciting new features:</p><ol><li>Character Creation: The introduction of the Blessing and Fragment system empowers players to customize their characters, adding depth and personalization to their gameplay experience.</li><li>Crafting System: Players can now select from various rare materials to craft items, offering enhanced gameplay depth and personalization.</li><li>New User Experience: The user interface has been revamped to provide step-by-step guidance within the game, ensuring seamless immersion for new and experienced players.</li><li>Core Game Mechanics: Based on valuable feedback from the previous public version, Chain of Alliance has implemented substantial changes to the core game mechanics, enhancing the gameplay and overall player experience.</li></ol><p></p><p class="ql-indent-5">A glimpse of the first Multiverse realm</p><p>Roadmap</p><p>Looking ahead, Chain of Alliance is thrilled to share its exciting roadmap, which balances community excitement and achievable milestones. Get first-hand news and a detailed roadmap here.</p><p>About Chain of Alliance&nbsp;</p><p>Chain of Alliance is an innovative and immersive turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse that aims to redefine the gaming landscape. With a focus on appealing to Web3 enthusiasts and traditional players, Chain of Alliance offers a captivating gaming experience that combines strategic combat, engaging storytelling, and a robust multiverse. Creators have the long-term vision of allowing players to create their own campaigns and stories using the game's API and leveraging characters and land offered by other players.</p><p>Website | Medium | Twitter | Discord</p>ContactFati HakimChromaWayfati.hakim@chromaway.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stockholm, Sweden, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Chain of Alliance Launches Public Alpha 1.0 on Chromia Testnet Sigma, Paving the Way to Become the Premier Turn-Based, Party-Builder RPG Multiverse</p><p>Chain of Alliance is thrilled to unveil the next phase of its remarkable journey as it solidifies its position as the leading turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse, catering to both Web3 and traditional players. This momentous milestone marks the beginning of an extraordinary adventure for Chain of Alliance as it sets its sights on redefining the landscape of turn-based RPG gaming. The company is committed to fostering a vibrant and inclusive community driven by a shared passion for the genre.</p><p>Building upon a foundation of innovation and community engagement, Chain of Alliance has implemented strategic structural adjustments and bolstered its team to propel the project forward. With a clear and attainable roadmap for the remainder of the year, the company is proud to announce the official launch of its highly anticipated Public Alpha 1.0, now available on the Chromia Testnet Sigma. Experience the game firsthand by visiting the official website.</p><p>Chain of Alliance invites players to immerse themselves in a captivating world of strategic combat. The game's innovative features and engaging gameplay mechanics aim to captivate both Web3 enthusiasts and traditional gamers.</p><p>The team is extending its gratitude to its esteemed badge holders, who have been granted an exclusive preview of the game, providing valuable feedback that has contributed to its refinement.</p><p>Introducing The New Team</p><p>Joining Chain of Alliance as the Lead Producer is Nicholas St. Louis, a seasoned professional with six years of industry experience. Nicholas has successfully managed projects at prestigious companies such as Sega, Moon Studios, and Rockstar and now brings his expertise to the team.</p><p>Overseeing the design of all new features is Cl&eacute;ment Fitoussi, an exceptionally talented Game Designer with over six years of experience in the gaming industry. Cl&eacute;ment's impressive portfolio includes collaborations with renowned companies like Mattel, Ubisoft, and Seascape.&nbsp;</p><p>Leading the marketing and community management efforts is Jorn Wisman, a Marketing Lead with over 15 years of experience in the gaming industry. Jorn's invaluable insights and expertise have been cultivated through his previous positions at PlayStation and Rockstar Games.&nbsp;</p><p>Game Redesign: Alpha 1.0</p><p>With the release of Alpha 1.0, Chain of Alliance invites players to experience a transformed gaming landscape. The latest Alpha build introduces significant changes and improvements. View the Chain of Alliance onboarding guide here, along with the following exciting new features:</p><ol><li>Character Creation: The introduction of the Blessing and Fragment system empowers players to customize their characters, adding depth and personalization to their gameplay experience.</li><li>Crafting System: Players can now select from various rare materials to craft items, offering enhanced gameplay depth and personalization.</li><li>New User Experience: The user interface has been revamped to provide step-by-step guidance within the game, ensuring seamless immersion for new and experienced players.</li><li>Core Game Mechanics: Based on valuable feedback from the previous public version, Chain of Alliance has implemented substantial changes to the core game mechanics, enhancing the gameplay and overall player experience.</li></ol><p></p><p class="ql-indent-5">A glimpse of the first Multiverse realm</p><p>Roadmap</p><p>Looking ahead, Chain of Alliance is thrilled to share its exciting roadmap, which balances community excitement and achievable milestones. Get first-hand news and a detailed roadmap here.</p><p>About Chain of Alliance&nbsp;</p><p>Chain of Alliance is an innovative and immersive turn-based, party-builder RPG multiverse that aims to redefine the gaming landscape. With a focus on appealing to Web3 enthusiasts and traditional players, Chain of Alliance offers a captivating gaming experience that combines strategic combat, engaging storytelling, and a robust multiverse. Creators have the long-term vision of allowing players to create their own campaigns and stories using the game's API and leveraging characters and land offered by other players.</p><p>Website | Medium | Twitter | Discord</p>ContactFati HakimChromaWayfati.hakim@chromaway.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Gary Vee excited by NFT potential for event ticketing]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/gary-vee-excited-by-nft-potential-for-event-ticketing</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ticket.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ticket.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ticket.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 19:04:20 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/gary-vee-excited-by-nft-potential-for-event-ticketing</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>NFTs have become synonymous with digital collectibles, art, and even virtual real estate. However, according to the renowned entrepreneur and digital asset advocate, Gary Vee, their potential extends far beyond these realms.</p>
NFTs to revolutionise ticketing
<p>Vee expressed his belief that NFTs have the power to revolutionise the ticketing industry. Paper tickets have hitherto been the method for gaining entry to events, concerts, and sporting matches, but the shortcomings of paper tickets have become increasingly evident.</p>
<p>NFTs originally sprang from blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, although Vee stated in a Cointelegraph interview that he doesn&rsquo;t own much crypto. He said that he is more of an art and baseball card collector</p>
<p>As for the use case for ticketing, Vee is very excited. He stated to Cointelegraph:</p>

<p>"Ticketing will be a huge use case for NFTs. I think that, by nature, tickets are collectibles. For instance, if you were to go on eBay now and look at how many ticket stubs are being bought, you may be surprised. People love memories and holding on to certain things, which is why I think ticketing will be a major [use] case for NFTs. I want to be at the forefront of this."</p>

Eradication of counterfeiting
<p>One of the key advantages of NFT-based tickets is their enhanced authenticity. Every NFT is unique and can be securely stored on a blockchain, making it virtually impossible to counterfeit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Counterfeiting has plagued the ticketing industry for years, but with NFTs, this problem could finally be eradicated, providing both artists and fans with peace of mind. By leveraging NFT technology, event organisers can ensure that each ticket is legitimate, eliminating the possibility of fake tickets flooding the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, NFTs can also empower artists and event organisers by enabling them to retain control over their tickets' resale and distribution. Through the implementation of smart contracts, creators can receive royalties every time a ticket is resold, preventing scalpers from profiting off inflated secondary market prices.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NFTs have become synonymous with digital collectibles, art, and even virtual real estate. However, according to the renowned entrepreneur and digital asset advocate, Gary Vee, their potential extends far beyond these realms.</p>
NFTs to revolutionise ticketing
<p>Vee expressed his belief that NFTs have the power to revolutionise the ticketing industry. Paper tickets have hitherto been the method for gaining entry to events, concerts, and sporting matches, but the shortcomings of paper tickets have become increasingly evident.</p>
<p>NFTs originally sprang from blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, although Vee stated in a Cointelegraph interview that he doesn&rsquo;t own much crypto. He said that he is more of an art and baseball card collector</p>
<p>As for the use case for ticketing, Vee is very excited. He stated to Cointelegraph:</p>

<p>"Ticketing will be a huge use case for NFTs. I think that, by nature, tickets are collectibles. For instance, if you were to go on eBay now and look at how many ticket stubs are being bought, you may be surprised. People love memories and holding on to certain things, which is why I think ticketing will be a major [use] case for NFTs. I want to be at the forefront of this."</p>

Eradication of counterfeiting
<p>One of the key advantages of NFT-based tickets is their enhanced authenticity. Every NFT is unique and can be securely stored on a blockchain, making it virtually impossible to counterfeit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Counterfeiting has plagued the ticketing industry for years, but with NFTs, this problem could finally be eradicated, providing both artists and fans with peace of mind. By leveraging NFT technology, event organisers can ensure that each ticket is legitimate, eliminating the possibility of fake tickets flooding the market.</p>
<p>Furthermore, NFTs can also empower artists and event organisers by enabling them to retain control over their tickets' resale and distribution. Through the implementation of smart contracts, creators can receive royalties every time a ticket is resold, preventing scalpers from profiting off inflated secondary market prices.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Zebec's Modular L3 Nautilus Chain Debuts on Mainnet, Paving the Way for the Future of DeFi and Continuous Payments]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zebecs-modular-l3-nautilus-chain-debuts-on-mainnet-paving-the-way-for-the-future-of-defi-and-continuous-payments</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/nautilus-chain-to-mainnet-V2_1684842047KgWCZvkdNn.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/nautilus-chain-to-mainnet-V2_1684842047KgWCZvkdNn.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/nautilus-chain-to-mainnet-V2_1684842047KgWCZvkdNn.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 18:02:52 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/zebecs-modular-l3-nautilus-chain-debuts-on-mainnet-paving-the-way-for-the-future-of-defi-and-continuous-payments</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>New York, United States, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Following months of battle-testing by partner projects, developers, and community, production-ready Nautilus Chain graduates from testnet.</p><p>Zebec, a pioneer in streaming finance, announced today the launch of Nautilus Chain - soon to be Zebec Chain - on mainnet, an important milestone in building its continuous payments infrastructure and global ecosystem. The first of its kind as an L3, Nautilus Chain offers the fastest EVM environment in web3 capable of parallel transaction processing, combining the speeds of Solana with the stability and functionality of EVM-based Solidity smart contracts, paving the way to the next generation of DeFi and consumer applications with a continuous stream of transactions or payments.</p><p>Nautilus Chain&rsquo;s settlement layer is currently built on Solana node, its execution layer on Neon EVM and Solidity smart contract, with data availability hash stored off-chain in order to keep Nautilus&rsquo; modular blockchain architecture. With plans to transition settlement layer to optimistic roll-up and data availability stored on layer 1 chains such as Etherium, BSC or Bitcoin to further maximize throughput while remaining stable and reliable to support high-throughput payment applications such as payroll, DeFi applications, and on-chain gaming.</p><p>The mainnet upgrade brings over 80 projects, such as Coral Finance, Witnet, and PoseiSwap to name a few, with dozens more in the process of onboarding and a track record of seamlessly processing over 40 million transactions on testnet to date.</p>"Zebec is helping to create a future where money is able to move more freely; giving individuals, businesses, investors, and teams faster and easier access to funds and tokens," said Sam Thapaliya, Founder of Zebec. "The launch of Nautilus on mainnet is another breakthrough on the path towards this vision."<p>Key features of the Nautilus Chain</p><p>High Throughput</p><p>Through parallelizing transactions instead of processing them linearly, Nautilus delivers an initial TPS of 2,000 with much higher rates soon to come.</p><p>Developer-friendly</p><p>Solidity developers are able to build high-throughput applications in an EVM environment. While the chain's modular structure supports customization and gives developers control of the tech stack &mdash; or chain stack &mdash; in building dApps. The chain is highly interoperable and extensible and, with app-specific rollups, enables projects to strike the perfect balance between decentralization, throughput, performance, cost, and efficiency.</p><p>Reliable</p><p>The high speeds and performance of the Nautilus chain, because it is a sovereign rollup, do not compromise the overall reliability and security of the infrastructure. Its robust design ensures optimal uptime and resilience, even under the most demanding conditions.</p><p>Built for the real world</p><p>With its core innovation in performance and security, Zebec&rsquo;s technology has transformative potential in the world of traditional finance, blockchain adoption and smart contract-based digital financial applications.</p>"Zebec&rsquo;s progress with Nautilus Chain development has the potential to bridge the gap between traditional finance and web2 payroll applications and the emerging web3 ecosystem." - said Steve Chen, Head of Blockchain Development for Nautilus"By harnessing the unparalleled speed, security, and interoperability of Nautilus, Zebec&rsquo;s technology is poised to revolutionize traditional finance, bringing the benefits of blockchain technology to mainstream industries. As we continue to explore the potential of Zebec&rsquo;s L3 chain, we foresee a future where seamless integration between web2 and web3 applications leads to the eventual replacement of conventional financial systems with blockchain technology and creating a more inclusive and efficient global economy."- Chen continued.<p>As Zebec continues to innovate and expand its ecosystem, it invites developers, companies, and projects from around the world to join it in creating a more connected, efficient, and accessible financial future.&nbsp;</p><p>About Zebec</p><p>Zebec enables real-time and continuous streams of payments and financial transactions for payroll, investments and more.&nbsp;Founded in 2021, with investments by Circle, Coinbase, Solana Ventures, Breyer Capital, Republic, and Lightspeed Venture Partners among others, Zebec services hundreds of companies, running thousands of continuous payment streams and bringing the blockchain to everyday lives.</p><p>For more information about Zebec: Official Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram</p><p>About Nautilus</p><p>Nautilus is a high-performance modular blockchain built for real-world DeFi and Web3 applications delivering high speed and low cost of processing transactions within a highly secure and stable decentralized system.</p><p>For more information about Nautilus: Official Website | Twitter | Telegram</p>ContactElena SolovyovZebecelena@zebec.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York, United States, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Following months of battle-testing by partner projects, developers, and community, production-ready Nautilus Chain graduates from testnet.</p><p>Zebec, a pioneer in streaming finance, announced today the launch of Nautilus Chain - soon to be Zebec Chain - on mainnet, an important milestone in building its continuous payments infrastructure and global ecosystem. The first of its kind as an L3, Nautilus Chain offers the fastest EVM environment in web3 capable of parallel transaction processing, combining the speeds of Solana with the stability and functionality of EVM-based Solidity smart contracts, paving the way to the next generation of DeFi and consumer applications with a continuous stream of transactions or payments.</p><p>Nautilus Chain&rsquo;s settlement layer is currently built on Solana node, its execution layer on Neon EVM and Solidity smart contract, with data availability hash stored off-chain in order to keep Nautilus&rsquo; modular blockchain architecture. With plans to transition settlement layer to optimistic roll-up and data availability stored on layer 1 chains such as Etherium, BSC or Bitcoin to further maximize throughput while remaining stable and reliable to support high-throughput payment applications such as payroll, DeFi applications, and on-chain gaming.</p><p>The mainnet upgrade brings over 80 projects, such as Coral Finance, Witnet, and PoseiSwap to name a few, with dozens more in the process of onboarding and a track record of seamlessly processing over 40 million transactions on testnet to date.</p>"Zebec is helping to create a future where money is able to move more freely; giving individuals, businesses, investors, and teams faster and easier access to funds and tokens," said Sam Thapaliya, Founder of Zebec. "The launch of Nautilus on mainnet is another breakthrough on the path towards this vision."<p>Key features of the Nautilus Chain</p><p>High Throughput</p><p>Through parallelizing transactions instead of processing them linearly, Nautilus delivers an initial TPS of 2,000 with much higher rates soon to come.</p><p>Developer-friendly</p><p>Solidity developers are able to build high-throughput applications in an EVM environment. While the chain's modular structure supports customization and gives developers control of the tech stack &mdash; or chain stack &mdash; in building dApps. The chain is highly interoperable and extensible and, with app-specific rollups, enables projects to strike the perfect balance between decentralization, throughput, performance, cost, and efficiency.</p><p>Reliable</p><p>The high speeds and performance of the Nautilus chain, because it is a sovereign rollup, do not compromise the overall reliability and security of the infrastructure. Its robust design ensures optimal uptime and resilience, even under the most demanding conditions.</p><p>Built for the real world</p><p>With its core innovation in performance and security, Zebec&rsquo;s technology has transformative potential in the world of traditional finance, blockchain adoption and smart contract-based digital financial applications.</p>"Zebec&rsquo;s progress with Nautilus Chain development has the potential to bridge the gap between traditional finance and web2 payroll applications and the emerging web3 ecosystem." - said Steve Chen, Head of Blockchain Development for Nautilus"By harnessing the unparalleled speed, security, and interoperability of Nautilus, Zebec&rsquo;s technology is poised to revolutionize traditional finance, bringing the benefits of blockchain technology to mainstream industries. As we continue to explore the potential of Zebec&rsquo;s L3 chain, we foresee a future where seamless integration between web2 and web3 applications leads to the eventual replacement of conventional financial systems with blockchain technology and creating a more inclusive and efficient global economy."- Chen continued.<p>As Zebec continues to innovate and expand its ecosystem, it invites developers, companies, and projects from around the world to join it in creating a more connected, efficient, and accessible financial future.&nbsp;</p><p>About Zebec</p><p>Zebec enables real-time and continuous streams of payments and financial transactions for payroll, investments and more.&nbsp;Founded in 2021, with investments by Circle, Coinbase, Solana Ventures, Breyer Capital, Republic, and Lightspeed Venture Partners among others, Zebec services hundreds of companies, running thousands of continuous payment streams and bringing the blockchain to everyday lives.</p><p>For more information about Zebec: Official Website | Twitter | Discord | Telegram</p><p>About Nautilus</p><p>Nautilus is a high-performance modular blockchain built for real-world DeFi and Web3 applications delivering high speed and low cost of processing transactions within a highly secure and stable decentralized system.</p><p>For more information about Nautilus: Official Website | Twitter | Telegram</p>ContactElena SolovyovZebecelena@zebec.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Cited Below 26351 - 25 May 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-cited-below-26351-25-may-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-24-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-cited-below-26351-25-may-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Below 26351:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 25 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continue to suffer from bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated back below the 27000 figure and reached the 26611.43 area after Stops were elected below the 26641.58 area, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 27234.83 level.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 27455.52 area during the recent appreciation, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure that strengthened around the 28334.75 area.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, additional downside price objectives include the 26308, 26093, 25885, and 25604 levels.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27002.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26960.81.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Below 26351:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 25 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) continue to suffer from bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair depreciated back below the 27000 figure and reached the 26611.43 area after Stops were elected below the 26641.58 area, a downside price objective associated with recent selling pressure around the 27234.83 level.&nbsp; &nbsp;Stops were elected above the 27455.52 area during the recent appreciation, a previous downside price objective associated with selling pressure that strengthened around the 28334.75 area.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 28011, 28591, 29171, 29889, and 29997 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28428, 28564, 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, and 29299 areas. &nbsp;Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;</p>
<p>Following recent selling pressure, additional downside price objectives include the 26308, 26093, 25885, and 25604 levels.&nbsp; Stops were recently elected below the 27145, 27108, 26765, 26729, 26380, 26309, and 26203 levels during the recent depreciation, downside price objectives related to recent selling pressure around the 30500, 30050, 29850, 28334, and 27647 levels.&nbsp; Related downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 25124, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;below the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 200-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27002.99 and the&nbsp;100-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26960.81.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Hestia Launches a Blockchain based Freelance Platform, Redefining the Crypto Landscape]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/hestia-launches-a-blockchain-based-freelance-platform-redefining-the-crypto-landscape</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Banner_1684866399ZK5k8AfqMd.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Banner_1684866399ZK5k8AfqMd.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Banner_1684866399ZK5k8AfqMd.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:00:45 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/hestia-launches-a-blockchain-based-freelance-platform-redefining-the-crypto-landscape</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Marseille, France, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In an age where the crypto world is dominated by GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins, Hestia is revolutionizing the industry by demonstrating how cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology can be applied to traditional economic projects.</p><p>Hestia, a groundbreaking decentralized freelance platform, is harnessing the power of decentralization to hustle the gig economy and empower freelancers and clients alike.</p><p>The Hestia project stands out from its crypto counterparts by focusing on real-world applications and creating a sustainable ecosystem for a broad range of industries. By leveraging the advantages of blockchain technology, Hestia offers an innovative economic model that enables fair distribution of power, wealth, and community governance.</p><p>A New Economic Model: Decentralization at Its Core</p><p>Hestia's decentralized approach sets it apart from traditional freelance platforms, which often suffer from centralization issues and associated inefficiencies. By eliminating the need for a central authority, Hestia provides a more transparent, equitable, and efficient ecosystem for freelancers and clients to connect and collaborate.</p><p>Hestia's dual-token system, comprising the stable HTX token and the growth-focused HTI token, enables seamless transactions within the platform while fostering the development of the ecosystem. The HTX token is indexed to USDT, providing a stable medium of exchange, while the HTI token is designed for use in exchanging HTX for other tokens or fiat currencies, as well as financing the Hestia ecosystem.</p><p>The platform's unique tokenomics ensures that users can access its services without subscription fees or hidden costs. A modest 5% fee on token swaps between HTX and HTI is the only charge, which is used to support the platform's ongoing operation, maintenance, and evolution.</p><p>Community Governance: Empowering Users</p><p>Hestia's commitment to community governance allows users to participate directly in decision- making processes, creating a more inclusive, transparent, and democratic ecosystem. Token holders can vote on proposals, contribute to platform development, and help shape the future of the Hestia network.</p><p>Bridging the Gap Between Crypto and Traditional Industries</p><p>By combining the best of blockchain technology with a focus on real-world applications, Hestia is challenging the notion that cryptocurrencies are only suitable for niche projects like GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins. The platform's innovative approach demonstrates how blockchain can transform traditional industries and drive meaningful change in people's lives.</p><p>About Hestia</p><p>Hestia is a testament to the versatility and potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. By creating a decentralized, user-driven freelance platform, Hestia is paving the way for a more equitable, transparent, and efficient future for freelancers and clients around the globe.</p><p>For more information please visit the Hestia project, website: https://hestia-project.com/</p>ContactLou ThierryHestiacontact@hestia-project.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marseille, France, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In an age where the crypto world is dominated by GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins, Hestia is revolutionizing the industry by demonstrating how cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology can be applied to traditional economic projects.</p><p>Hestia, a groundbreaking decentralized freelance platform, is harnessing the power of decentralization to hustle the gig economy and empower freelancers and clients alike.</p><p>The Hestia project stands out from its crypto counterparts by focusing on real-world applications and creating a sustainable ecosystem for a broad range of industries. By leveraging the advantages of blockchain technology, Hestia offers an innovative economic model that enables fair distribution of power, wealth, and community governance.</p><p>A New Economic Model: Decentralization at Its Core</p><p>Hestia's decentralized approach sets it apart from traditional freelance platforms, which often suffer from centralization issues and associated inefficiencies. By eliminating the need for a central authority, Hestia provides a more transparent, equitable, and efficient ecosystem for freelancers and clients to connect and collaborate.</p><p>Hestia's dual-token system, comprising the stable HTX token and the growth-focused HTI token, enables seamless transactions within the platform while fostering the development of the ecosystem. The HTX token is indexed to USDT, providing a stable medium of exchange, while the HTI token is designed for use in exchanging HTX for other tokens or fiat currencies, as well as financing the Hestia ecosystem.</p><p>The platform's unique tokenomics ensures that users can access its services without subscription fees or hidden costs. A modest 5% fee on token swaps between HTX and HTI is the only charge, which is used to support the platform's ongoing operation, maintenance, and evolution.</p><p>Community Governance: Empowering Users</p><p>Hestia's commitment to community governance allows users to participate directly in decision- making processes, creating a more inclusive, transparent, and democratic ecosystem. Token holders can vote on proposals, contribute to platform development, and help shape the future of the Hestia network.</p><p>Bridging the Gap Between Crypto and Traditional Industries</p><p>By combining the best of blockchain technology with a focus on real-world applications, Hestia is challenging the notion that cryptocurrencies are only suitable for niche projects like GameFi, DeFi, NFTs, and meme coins. The platform's innovative approach demonstrates how blockchain can transform traditional industries and drive meaningful change in people's lives.</p><p>About Hestia</p><p>Hestia is a testament to the versatility and potential of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology. By creating a decentralized, user-driven freelance platform, Hestia is paving the way for a more equitable, transparent, and efficient future for freelancers and clients around the globe.</p><p>For more information please visit the Hestia project, website: https://hestia-project.com/</p>ContactLou ThierryHestiacontact@hestia-project.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[IOSCO Unveils First Global Approach to Crypto Asset Regulation]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/iosco-unveils-first-global-approach-to-crypto-asset-regulation</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/iosco.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/iosco.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/iosco.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/iosco-unveils-first-global-approach-to-crypto-asset-regulation</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Global policy forum IOSCO on Tuesday released the first global approach to crypto asset and digital market regulation. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the International Organisation of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) unveiled the first global approach to regulating the crypto and digital asset market.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">IOSCO announces global crypto regulation recommendations. 📍 Link to the Consultation Report 🔗 https://t.co/Je0UQulWFs📍 Link to Press Release 🔗 https://t.co/gf9qXuYdwE📍 Link to the Crypto-Asset Roadmap 2022/2023 🔗 https://t.co/Rcth0NkMmt#CryptoAssets #Regulation pic.twitter.com/aqXPmUmQJN</p>
&mdash; IOSCO Press (@IOSCOPress) May 23, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a consultation report, the Commission suggests 18 recommendations covering six areas, including cross-border risk and regulatory cooperation, conflicts of interest stemming from the vertical integration of functions and activities, insider trading, fraud, as well as market manipulation, Decrypt reports.</p>
<p>The Commission specifically advised regulators to prohibit crypto firms &ldquo;from combining certain functions in a single legal entity or group of affiliated entities.&rdquo;</p>
<p>IOSCO&rsquo;s report, which outlines policy recommendations for a global approach to crypto and digital asset regulation, comes amid concerns over consumer protection after the collapse of crypto exchange FTX. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The Commission, a policy forum comprising global regulators such as the US SEC, the UK&rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority, and Japan&rsquo;s Financial Services Agency, oversees 95% of global securities markets across 130 jurisdictions.</p>
<p>IOSCO chair Jean-Paul Servais said in a press release that the recommendations represent a &ldquo;turning point&rdquo; in addressing the risks associated with crypto assets such as bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH). Servais added:</p>

<p>Crypto business has been allowed to grow on a flawed basis, and it has to be corrected.</p>

<p>LIM Tuang Lee, Chairperson of the IOSCO Board-Level Fintech Task Force (FTF) - set up last year to develop its crypto policy recommendations, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Recommendations in IOSCO&rsquo;s Consultation Report set expectations and guardrails to regulate and supervise crypto-asset markets, which are inherently cross-border in nature.</p>
<p>Crypto-asset service providers need to address unacceptable conflicts of interest and take far more seriously the right of clients to have their monies and assets carefully minded and accounted for.</p>
<p>It is time for Regulators to work together across borders and various jurisdictions to ensure that investor protection and market integrity are upheld in crypto-asset markets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The watchdog said members of the public have until July 31 to send comments and feedback and aims to finalize standards by the end of the year.</p>
Members of the Crypto Industry React Well to IOSCO&rsquo;s Recommendations
<p>Members of the community have responded well to IOSCO&rsquo;s proposed policy framework. In a comment shared with Crypto Daily, Chris Perkins, President, and Managing Partner at CoinFund, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;In April, CoinFund released a whitepaper where we put forth ten policy principles for the digital financial system.&nbsp; As such, we remain fully supportive of principles-based regulation and commend IOSCO for their desire for a globally synchronized approach that seeks to protect client assets, offers reasonable and transparent disclosures, and roots out abusive behaviors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We further commend IOSCO for not commingling DeFi in today&rsquo;s policy paper covering crypto asset service providers (CASPs).&nbsp; Finally, we are hopeful that subject matter experts, including trade associations, respond to the numerous queries in the proposal in order to help inform the best policy outcomes.&nbsp; Clearly, as global policies for digital assets are crystalized, details will matter.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Global policy forum IOSCO on Tuesday released the first global approach to crypto asset and digital market regulation. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the International Organisation of Securities Commissions (IOSCO) unveiled the first global approach to regulating the crypto and digital asset market.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">IOSCO announces global crypto regulation recommendations. 📍 Link to the Consultation Report 🔗 https://t.co/Je0UQulWFs📍 Link to Press Release 🔗 https://t.co/gf9qXuYdwE📍 Link to the Crypto-Asset Roadmap 2022/2023 🔗 https://t.co/Rcth0NkMmt#CryptoAssets #Regulation pic.twitter.com/aqXPmUmQJN</p>
&mdash; IOSCO Press (@IOSCOPress) May 23, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>In a consultation report, the Commission suggests 18 recommendations covering six areas, including cross-border risk and regulatory cooperation, conflicts of interest stemming from the vertical integration of functions and activities, insider trading, fraud, as well as market manipulation, Decrypt reports.</p>
<p>The Commission specifically advised regulators to prohibit crypto firms &ldquo;from combining certain functions in a single legal entity or group of affiliated entities.&rdquo;</p>
<p>IOSCO&rsquo;s report, which outlines policy recommendations for a global approach to crypto and digital asset regulation, comes amid concerns over consumer protection after the collapse of crypto exchange FTX. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The Commission, a policy forum comprising global regulators such as the US SEC, the UK&rsquo;s Financial Conduct Authority, and Japan&rsquo;s Financial Services Agency, oversees 95% of global securities markets across 130 jurisdictions.</p>
<p>IOSCO chair Jean-Paul Servais said in a press release that the recommendations represent a &ldquo;turning point&rdquo; in addressing the risks associated with crypto assets such as bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH). Servais added:</p>

<p>Crypto business has been allowed to grow on a flawed basis, and it has to be corrected.</p>

<p>LIM Tuang Lee, Chairperson of the IOSCO Board-Level Fintech Task Force (FTF) - set up last year to develop its crypto policy recommendations, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Recommendations in IOSCO&rsquo;s Consultation Report set expectations and guardrails to regulate and supervise crypto-asset markets, which are inherently cross-border in nature.</p>
<p>Crypto-asset service providers need to address unacceptable conflicts of interest and take far more seriously the right of clients to have their monies and assets carefully minded and accounted for.</p>
<p>It is time for Regulators to work together across borders and various jurisdictions to ensure that investor protection and market integrity are upheld in crypto-asset markets.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The watchdog said members of the public have until July 31 to send comments and feedback and aims to finalize standards by the end of the year.</p>
Members of the Crypto Industry React Well to IOSCO&rsquo;s Recommendations
<p>Members of the community have responded well to IOSCO&rsquo;s proposed policy framework. In a comment shared with Crypto Daily, Chris Perkins, President, and Managing Partner at CoinFund, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;In April, CoinFund released a whitepaper where we put forth ten policy principles for the digital financial system.&nbsp; As such, we remain fully supportive of principles-based regulation and commend IOSCO for their desire for a globally synchronized approach that seeks to protect client assets, offers reasonable and transparent disclosures, and roots out abusive behaviors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>We further commend IOSCO for not commingling DeFi in today&rsquo;s policy paper covering crypto asset service providers (CASPs).&nbsp; Finally, we are hopeful that subject matter experts, including trade associations, respond to the numerous queries in the proposal in order to help inform the best policy outcomes.&nbsp; Clearly, as global policies for digital assets are crystalized, details will matter.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[The Web3.Conference United Industry’s Brightest Minds in Amsterdam]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-web3conference-united-industrys-brightest-minds-in-amsterdam</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Frame_890_1684929977AFYpJuMJI3.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Frame_890_1684929977AFYpJuMJI3.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Frame_890_1684929977AFYpJuMJI3.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:49:56 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/the-web3conference-united-industrys-brightest-minds-in-amsterdam</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>The organizers of The Web3.Conference are celebrating a successful day-long event that brought together the industry&rsquo;s leading lights. Held in Amsterdam on May 19th, the annual event from the AroundB team discussed hot topics and gathered industry insights from Web3 experts.</p><p>With more than 20 speakers, four panel discussions, and six startup pitch sessions during seven hours, the agenda contained something to suit every guest. Mark Eid from Qlindo, the main sponsor of the event, spoke about green real estate and renewable energy investment opportunities. The subject of how to invest in Web3 was continued by a lively panel discussion between Rachel Pipan (Maneuvre), Nick van der Heiden (Hodl), Sofia Chikara (4wrdtech), and Sandro Potenza (Global Coin Research).</p><p>Nirmala Shome&rsquo;s (The Fabricant) speech was dedicated to Web3 fashion and its possibilities. The future of Web3 identity and social networks was covered by&nbsp;Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab) as well as panel participants Gijs Ertemann (Secret Network), Joonatan Lintala, (Phaver), Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab), Nico Gallardo (Troop Labs), and Sara Anna Mamel (KILT Protocol).</p><p>An intense panel discussion titled &ldquo;The Role of NFTs and the Metaverse in Web3&rdquo; was conducted by Nishera Sachdev from Luna PR, Lianna Adams (Web3/NFT GTM Advisor), Cosmin Gafta (YOM), and Mickelle Weber (House of Peregrine). The topic &ldquo;Metaverses as Jurisdictions&rdquo; was led by James Haft (DLTX), while the section &ldquo;Web3 Infrastructure: Building DAOs&rdquo; was supported by Philippe Honigman (Mangrove DAO), Jamie Holmes (Perpetual Protocol), Soumaya Erradi (Scaling Parrots), Vincent Plaisier (The Graph AdvocatesDAO), and Ben Hoelzl (FTW DAO).</p><p>One of the special panels was dedicated to startups that presented their future-proofed vision: TrueBlocks, Rail, Ping, Tribal.market, Tide, Aidonic, and 1inch hardware wallet.</p><p>Natalie Gavrilenko, AroundB CEO, said: &ldquo;Thank you to everyone who attended. The AroundB team is grateful for every participant at The Web3.Conference. The goal of the event was to bring together people from different countries, with their own vision of the Web3 future, to share their thoughts with the audience, and make our own impact on the Web3 development industry.&rdquo;</p><p>The Web3.Conference was held in Felix Meritis, known for its winning design by the architect Jacob Otten Husly. He built it for a new society called Felix Meritis that was established in 1776 for Music, Drawing, Physics, Commerce and Literature in the modern neo-classical style.</p><p>AroundB thanks the main sponsor of the event Qlindo that bridges the gap between blockchain and green real estate investment opportunities, paving the way to a sustainable future, and thanks all the participants, speakers, and media partners for making this event happen.</p>ContactPR ManagerMaria PrykolotaAroundBpr@theconference.exchange]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amsterdam, Netherlands, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>The organizers of The Web3.Conference are celebrating a successful day-long event that brought together the industry&rsquo;s leading lights. Held in Amsterdam on May 19th, the annual event from the AroundB team discussed hot topics and gathered industry insights from Web3 experts.</p><p>With more than 20 speakers, four panel discussions, and six startup pitch sessions during seven hours, the agenda contained something to suit every guest. Mark Eid from Qlindo, the main sponsor of the event, spoke about green real estate and renewable energy investment opportunities. The subject of how to invest in Web3 was continued by a lively panel discussion between Rachel Pipan (Maneuvre), Nick van der Heiden (Hodl), Sofia Chikara (4wrdtech), and Sandro Potenza (Global Coin Research).</p><p>Nirmala Shome&rsquo;s (The Fabricant) speech was dedicated to Web3 fashion and its possibilities. The future of Web3 identity and social networks was covered by&nbsp;Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab) as well as panel participants Gijs Ertemann (Secret Network), Joonatan Lintala, (Phaver), Sharon Sciammas (W3B Lab), Nico Gallardo (Troop Labs), and Sara Anna Mamel (KILT Protocol).</p><p>An intense panel discussion titled &ldquo;The Role of NFTs and the Metaverse in Web3&rdquo; was conducted by Nishera Sachdev from Luna PR, Lianna Adams (Web3/NFT GTM Advisor), Cosmin Gafta (YOM), and Mickelle Weber (House of Peregrine). The topic &ldquo;Metaverses as Jurisdictions&rdquo; was led by James Haft (DLTX), while the section &ldquo;Web3 Infrastructure: Building DAOs&rdquo; was supported by Philippe Honigman (Mangrove DAO), Jamie Holmes (Perpetual Protocol), Soumaya Erradi (Scaling Parrots), Vincent Plaisier (The Graph AdvocatesDAO), and Ben Hoelzl (FTW DAO).</p><p>One of the special panels was dedicated to startups that presented their future-proofed vision: TrueBlocks, Rail, Ping, Tribal.market, Tide, Aidonic, and 1inch hardware wallet.</p><p>Natalie Gavrilenko, AroundB CEO, said: &ldquo;Thank you to everyone who attended. The AroundB team is grateful for every participant at The Web3.Conference. The goal of the event was to bring together people from different countries, with their own vision of the Web3 future, to share their thoughts with the audience, and make our own impact on the Web3 development industry.&rdquo;</p><p>The Web3.Conference was held in Felix Meritis, known for its winning design by the architect Jacob Otten Husly. He built it for a new society called Felix Meritis that was established in 1776 for Music, Drawing, Physics, Commerce and Literature in the modern neo-classical style.</p><p>AroundB thanks the main sponsor of the event Qlindo that bridges the gap between blockchain and green real estate investment opportunities, paving the way to a sustainable future, and thanks all the participants, speakers, and media partners for making this event happen.</p>ContactPR ManagerMaria PrykolotaAroundBpr@theconference.exchange]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[CEDEN acquires Galaxy Rendered Expanding the Content Ecosystem]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ceden-acquires-galaxy-rendered-expanding-the-content-ecosystem</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/TW__RM__1_16847698939AqCdTbBZF.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/TW__RM__1_16847698939AqCdTbBZF.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/TW__RM__1_16847698939AqCdTbBZF.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:00:56 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ceden-acquires-galaxy-rendered-expanding-the-content-ecosystem</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Tortola, British Virgin Islands, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>CEDEN Network Ltd has acquired Galaxy Rendered Limited for an undisclosed sum, strengthening the foundation of the EDEN Content Creation Ecosystem with a wholly owned subsidiary Web3 development studio and its debut metaverse game title, Rocket Monsters.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered Limited is an innovator in Web3 gaming, developing the Play to Earn (P2E) PVP game, Rocket Monsters, which currently features two playable alpha levels, and is nearing launch of the full playable beta open world experience.</p><p>Andrew Woodward, Founder and CEO of Galaxy Rendered Limited, has joined the CEDEN Advisory Board, following the sale of his company to CEDEN. In this capacity, Andrew will continue to advise on the development of Rocket Monsters and the dynamic ecosystem that the Galaxy Rendered team has cultivated over time.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered development and art teams have also remained with the company following the ownership transition, adding significant experience and depth to the CEDEN team.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered has crafted a unique digital gaming universe with Rocket Monsters, featuring both PVP and PVE immersive environments. Rocket Monsters is a multi-faceted game in which the bears and other extraterrestrial monsters navigate the vast playable environments using interstellar vehicles, engage in thrilling open-world PVP confrontations with the enemies, and battle for the opportunity to harvest valuable resources. All the in-game characters, weapons, vehicles and resources can be purchased, sold, and transferred as digital assets.</p><p>CEDEN will refine and continue to deliver the existing roadmap of Rocket Monsters, including consolidating and growing the vast NFT collections that exist in the ecosystem currently, and preparing the Rocket Monsters universe for the beta launch of the open world which will include the introduction of playable NFT vehicles called Star Racers, player owned land and shops, and the vast resource collection system that is the foundation of the ecosystem.</p><p></p>&ldquo;With the successful acquisition of Galaxy Rendered, CEDEN&rsquo;s vision of being a Network-as-a-Service (NaaS) infrastructure powerhouse, serving a vast and diverse range of content creators, is coming to fruition,&rdquo; remarked Alex Moody, CEO of CEDEN. &ldquo;Our team and the advisory board have experts from both Web2 and Web3 gaming, marketing resources, and the tools to empower interactive games like Rocket Monsters. We are excited for what this adds to the CEDEN Network&rsquo;s content delivery network (CDN), along with offering CEDEN Mint Pass holders preferential access to minting opportunities, airdrops and rewards from games within the ecosystem, including Rocket Monsters.&rdquo;<p>Andrew Woodward, the CEO of Galaxy Rendered Limited, expressed enthusiasm about the acquisition, emphasizing Rocket Monsters&rsquo; ambition to evolve into a Web3 game that transcends traditional blockchain limitations and embraces a multi-chain future for Web3 gaming. He anticipates a seamless, engaging gaming experience, made possible through the use of CEDEN&rsquo;s Web3 toolkits and peer-to-peer network.</p><p>Since launching two months ago, CEDEN has announced two additional significant partnerships and investments, including with the up-and-coming Brooklyn-based game development studio, K11 UNLIMITED, and the LA-based game studio, Gammaker Inc.</p>Michael Haller, CEDEN&rsquo;s Head of Gaming and the Executive Chairman of Gammaker Inc, commented: &ldquo;The strategic value of these partnerships is invaluable as they leverage CEDEN&rsquo;s infrastructure toolkit while delivering a steady flow of high-quality content for NFT node operators.&rdquo;<p>Throughout the month of April, CEDEN successfully minted 3,333 CEDEN Mint Passes, each providing entry into the dynamic CEDEN ecosystem. Looking forward, the third quarter will herald the arrival of Keystone NFT Nodes at CEDEN. This collection, comprising 10,000 NFT Nodes, will lay the groundwork for the CEDEN Network&#8202;&mdash;&#8202;a decentralized, peer-to-peer (P2P) Content Delivery Network (CDN)&#8202;&mdash;&#8202;designed to help the gaming industry to transcend the limitations of the past.</p><p>It&rsquo;s time to move beyond the machine.</p><p>About CEDEN</p><p>CEDEN is a Network-as-a-Service (NaaS) open-source infrastructure company empowering content creators in gaming and the metaverse industry. CEDEN is empowering a diverse array of content creators such as gamers, designers, NFT artists, and game publishers. The CEDEN team continues to grow the ecosystem, providing support through gaming distribution channels, monetization opportunities, and expanding their interactive entertainment toolkits, agency and publishing services, and Web3-as-a-Service (W3aaS) products to the broader industry.</p><p>For more information please visit linktr.ee/ceden_network</p>ContactCMOSook HwangCEDENsook@ceden.network]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tortola, British Virgin Islands, May 24th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>CEDEN Network Ltd has acquired Galaxy Rendered Limited for an undisclosed sum, strengthening the foundation of the EDEN Content Creation Ecosystem with a wholly owned subsidiary Web3 development studio and its debut metaverse game title, Rocket Monsters.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered Limited is an innovator in Web3 gaming, developing the Play to Earn (P2E) PVP game, Rocket Monsters, which currently features two playable alpha levels, and is nearing launch of the full playable beta open world experience.</p><p>Andrew Woodward, Founder and CEO of Galaxy Rendered Limited, has joined the CEDEN Advisory Board, following the sale of his company to CEDEN. In this capacity, Andrew will continue to advise on the development of Rocket Monsters and the dynamic ecosystem that the Galaxy Rendered team has cultivated over time.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered development and art teams have also remained with the company following the ownership transition, adding significant experience and depth to the CEDEN team.</p><p>Galaxy Rendered has crafted a unique digital gaming universe with Rocket Monsters, featuring both PVP and PVE immersive environments. Rocket Monsters is a multi-faceted game in which the bears and other extraterrestrial monsters navigate the vast playable environments using interstellar vehicles, engage in thrilling open-world PVP confrontations with the enemies, and battle for the opportunity to harvest valuable resources. All the in-game characters, weapons, vehicles and resources can be purchased, sold, and transferred as digital assets.</p><p>CEDEN will refine and continue to deliver the existing roadmap of Rocket Monsters, including consolidating and growing the vast NFT collections that exist in the ecosystem currently, and preparing the Rocket Monsters universe for the beta launch of the open world which will include the introduction of playable NFT vehicles called Star Racers, player owned land and shops, and the vast resource collection system that is the foundation of the ecosystem.</p><p></p>&ldquo;With the successful acquisition of Galaxy Rendered, CEDEN&rsquo;s vision of being a Network-as-a-Service (NaaS) infrastructure powerhouse, serving a vast and diverse range of content creators, is coming to fruition,&rdquo; remarked Alex Moody, CEO of CEDEN. &ldquo;Our team and the advisory board have experts from both Web2 and Web3 gaming, marketing resources, and the tools to empower interactive games like Rocket Monsters. We are excited for what this adds to the CEDEN Network&rsquo;s content delivery network (CDN), along with offering CEDEN Mint Pass holders preferential access to minting opportunities, airdrops and rewards from games within the ecosystem, including Rocket Monsters.&rdquo;<p>Andrew Woodward, the CEO of Galaxy Rendered Limited, expressed enthusiasm about the acquisition, emphasizing Rocket Monsters&rsquo; ambition to evolve into a Web3 game that transcends traditional blockchain limitations and embraces a multi-chain future for Web3 gaming. He anticipates a seamless, engaging gaming experience, made possible through the use of CEDEN&rsquo;s Web3 toolkits and peer-to-peer network.</p><p>Since launching two months ago, CEDEN has announced two additional significant partnerships and investments, including with the up-and-coming Brooklyn-based game development studio, K11 UNLIMITED, and the LA-based game studio, Gammaker Inc.</p>Michael Haller, CEDEN&rsquo;s Head of Gaming and the Executive Chairman of Gammaker Inc, commented: &ldquo;The strategic value of these partnerships is invaluable as they leverage CEDEN&rsquo;s infrastructure toolkit while delivering a steady flow of high-quality content for NFT node operators.&rdquo;<p>Throughout the month of April, CEDEN successfully minted 3,333 CEDEN Mint Passes, each providing entry into the dynamic CEDEN ecosystem. Looking forward, the third quarter will herald the arrival of Keystone NFT Nodes at CEDEN. This collection, comprising 10,000 NFT Nodes, will lay the groundwork for the CEDEN Network&#8202;&mdash;&#8202;a decentralized, peer-to-peer (P2P) Content Delivery Network (CDN)&#8202;&mdash;&#8202;designed to help the gaming industry to transcend the limitations of the past.</p><p>It&rsquo;s time to move beyond the machine.</p><p>About CEDEN</p><p>CEDEN is a Network-as-a-Service (NaaS) open-source infrastructure company empowering content creators in gaming and the metaverse industry. CEDEN is empowering a diverse array of content creators such as gamers, designers, NFT artists, and game publishers. The CEDEN team continues to grow the ecosystem, providing support through gaming distribution channels, monetization opportunities, and expanding their interactive entertainment toolkits, agency and publishing services, and Web3-as-a-Service (W3aaS) products to the broader industry.</p><p>For more information please visit linktr.ee/ceden_network</p>ContactCMOSook HwangCEDENsook@ceden.network]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Japan Gears Up To Enforce AML Measures For Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/japan-gears-up-to-enforce-aml-measures-for-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/japan-regulation-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/japan-regulation-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/japan-regulation-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/japan-gears-up-to-enforce-aml-measures-for-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Japan has announced the implementation of new anti-money laundering (AML) measures for cryptocurrencies to combat increasing fraudulent activities in the industry.&nbsp;</p>
Japan Revises AML Measures, Tightens Crypto Regulation
<p>In an effort to combat the rise in crypto-related crimes and ensure the integrity of its financial system, Japan will be enforcing strict anti-money laundering (AML) measures across the country&rsquo;s crypto industry. These measures, which were first proposed earlier this year, are set to take effect from June 1st.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There has been an ever-increasing rate of illicit activities like money laundering and terrorism financing, especially in crypto. With Japan being such a significant player in the global cryptocurrency market, the country&rsquo;s cabinet is seeking to address potential risks associated with the anonymity and decentralized nature of digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The country&rsquo;s existing legal framework has come under criticism by the international financial watchdog, Financial Action Task Force (FATF). As a result, the country&rsquo;s cabinet revised the relevant laws in December, focusing on monitoring the movement of illicit funds under the guise of legal crypto transactions.&nbsp;</p>
New Measures Include &ldquo;Travel Rule&rdquo;&nbsp;
<p>The enforcement of the "Travel Rule" is a significant aspect of the new measures aimed at ensuring more precise monitoring of illicit proceeds. The proposal of the rule was extensively deliberated at the G7 meeting held recently in Japan and has received unequivocal support from the G7 committee. Under the Travel Rule, any financial institution processing cryptocurrency transfers exceeding $3,000 must share customer information with the recipient exchange or institution. This information comprises the sender and recipient's names, addresses, and account details.</p>
<p>FATF President T. Raja Kumar had addressed the G7 leaders prior to the summit, saying</p>

<p>&ldquo;G7 countries should lead by example and regulate the crypto sector so that no safe havens exist for illicit crypto transactions.&rdquo;</p>

FSA Japan In Charge Of New Measures
<p>The new framework will also include measures to implement robust know-your-customer (KYC) procedures, closely mimicking those of traditional financial institutions. Furthermore, crypto exchanges registered in Japan will also need to verify customer identity and maintain detailed transaction records that are in line with AML standards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Japan's Financial Services Agency (FSA) has been entrusted with the responsibility of establishing compliance with the new framework by regular audits checking the efficacy of the AML measures. The FSA will also be taking action in non-compliance cases, using methods of official warnings, corrective measures, penalties, potential suspension, or even revocation of operating licenses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Japan has announced the implementation of new anti-money laundering (AML) measures for cryptocurrencies to combat increasing fraudulent activities in the industry.&nbsp;</p>
Japan Revises AML Measures, Tightens Crypto Regulation
<p>In an effort to combat the rise in crypto-related crimes and ensure the integrity of its financial system, Japan will be enforcing strict anti-money laundering (AML) measures across the country&rsquo;s crypto industry. These measures, which were first proposed earlier this year, are set to take effect from June 1st.&nbsp;</p>
<p>There has been an ever-increasing rate of illicit activities like money laundering and terrorism financing, especially in crypto. With Japan being such a significant player in the global cryptocurrency market, the country&rsquo;s cabinet is seeking to address potential risks associated with the anonymity and decentralized nature of digital assets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The country&rsquo;s existing legal framework has come under criticism by the international financial watchdog, Financial Action Task Force (FATF). As a result, the country&rsquo;s cabinet revised the relevant laws in December, focusing on monitoring the movement of illicit funds under the guise of legal crypto transactions.&nbsp;</p>
New Measures Include &ldquo;Travel Rule&rdquo;&nbsp;
<p>The enforcement of the "Travel Rule" is a significant aspect of the new measures aimed at ensuring more precise monitoring of illicit proceeds. The proposal of the rule was extensively deliberated at the G7 meeting held recently in Japan and has received unequivocal support from the G7 committee. Under the Travel Rule, any financial institution processing cryptocurrency transfers exceeding $3,000 must share customer information with the recipient exchange or institution. This information comprises the sender and recipient's names, addresses, and account details.</p>
<p>FATF President T. Raja Kumar had addressed the G7 leaders prior to the summit, saying</p>

<p>&ldquo;G7 countries should lead by example and regulate the crypto sector so that no safe havens exist for illicit crypto transactions.&rdquo;</p>

FSA Japan In Charge Of New Measures
<p>The new framework will also include measures to implement robust know-your-customer (KYC) procedures, closely mimicking those of traditional financial institutions. Furthermore, crypto exchanges registered in Japan will also need to verify customer identity and maintain detailed transaction records that are in line with AML standards.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Japan's Financial Services Agency (FSA) has been entrusted with the responsibility of establishing compliance with the new framework by regular audits checking the efficacy of the AML measures. The FSA will also be taking action in non-compliance cases, using methods of official warnings, corrective measures, penalties, potential suspension, or even revocation of operating licenses.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bears Dominate Arbitrum (ARB), Cardano (ADA) Gets New DeFi Partner, Crypto Whales Invest in Sparklo (SPRK) Presale]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bears-dominate-arbitrum-arb-cardano-ada-gets-new-defi-partner-crypto-whales-invest-in-sparklo-sprk-presale</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-604.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-604.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-604.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bears-dominate-arbitrum-arb-cardano-ada-gets-new-defi-partner-crypto-whales-invest-in-sparklo-sprk-presale</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The bullish momentum of the crypto market began the year with has begun to wane, leaving many digital assets like Arbitrum (ARB) to the mercy of the bears. Despite the bearish market, Cardano (ADA) has sealed a new partnership with a major DeFi player while investors are trooping into Sparklo (SPRK) as it shows signs to become the next blue-chip crypto project.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Crypto whales buy into Sparklo (SPRK) Presale</p>
<p>Creating the first alternative investment platform where cryptocurrency investors can buy and sell gold, silver, and platinum, Sparklo is quickly becoming one of the preferred options for investors. Sparklo&rsquo;s fractionalized investment and trading platform will allow investors to own gold, silver, and platinum bars for as little as $100.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sparklo will leverage the security infrastructure of the Ethereum blockchain. The team has also passed its audit to add to a successful smart contracts audit performed by the Interfi Network. Furthermore, the liquidity of Sparklo will be locked for a remarkable duration of 100 years, promoting stability and trust in the platform.</p>
<p>Identifying the unique potential of Sparklo, whales are buying early into the project. Stage one of Sparklo&rsquo;s presale gathered massive support from investors, pushing it into the second phase. The SPRK token currently sells for $0.026 apiece and you can get as much as 50% rewards as an early investor.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Arbitrum (ARB) price declines as bears dominate the market</p>
<p>Once one of the top crypto contenders, Arbitrum (ARB) has slowly gone the pecking order because of the dominance of bears. In the last week, the price of Arbitrum has fallen by 7% and more than 23% in the last 30 days. Even now, bears still dominate the market for Arbitrum (ARB).</p>
<p>The recent price drop which sent the Arbitrum (ARB) under $1.3 now puts it at a critical level. With its current price of $1.13, Arbitrum sits very close to its next support level at $1.0396. If the bearish sentiment persists, the price of Arbitrum (ARB) could break below $1.0 in the next few days. However, investors would hope enough bullish momentum take &nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) gets a new DeFi partner</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA), has announced a new partnership with Acredius, a Swiss fintech company. According to the announcement, Acredius will work with Cardano (ADA) to advance the development of decentralized finance on the network. Cardano (ADA) is already outperforming expectations, adding over 1,000 smart contracts to its network.</p>
<p>The increasing activity on the Cardano (ADA) network has not been followed by a correlating price increase. Instead, the price of Cardano (ADA) has consolidated between $0.36 and $0.40 over the last 30 days. The lack of price movement is the fuel driving investors to the Sparklo presale.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find out about the Sparklo (SPRK) presale using the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bullish momentum of the crypto market began the year with has begun to wane, leaving many digital assets like Arbitrum (ARB) to the mercy of the bears. Despite the bearish market, Cardano (ADA) has sealed a new partnership with a major DeFi player while investors are trooping into Sparklo (SPRK) as it shows signs to become the next blue-chip crypto project.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Crypto whales buy into Sparklo (SPRK) Presale</p>
<p>Creating the first alternative investment platform where cryptocurrency investors can buy and sell gold, silver, and platinum, Sparklo is quickly becoming one of the preferred options for investors. Sparklo&rsquo;s fractionalized investment and trading platform will allow investors to own gold, silver, and platinum bars for as little as $100.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sparklo will leverage the security infrastructure of the Ethereum blockchain. The team has also passed its audit to add to a successful smart contracts audit performed by the Interfi Network. Furthermore, the liquidity of Sparklo will be locked for a remarkable duration of 100 years, promoting stability and trust in the platform.</p>
<p>Identifying the unique potential of Sparklo, whales are buying early into the project. Stage one of Sparklo&rsquo;s presale gathered massive support from investors, pushing it into the second phase. The SPRK token currently sells for $0.026 apiece and you can get as much as 50% rewards as an early investor.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Arbitrum (ARB) price declines as bears dominate the market</p>
<p>Once one of the top crypto contenders, Arbitrum (ARB) has slowly gone the pecking order because of the dominance of bears. In the last week, the price of Arbitrum has fallen by 7% and more than 23% in the last 30 days. Even now, bears still dominate the market for Arbitrum (ARB).</p>
<p>The recent price drop which sent the Arbitrum (ARB) under $1.3 now puts it at a critical level. With its current price of $1.13, Arbitrum sits very close to its next support level at $1.0396. If the bearish sentiment persists, the price of Arbitrum (ARB) could break below $1.0 in the next few days. However, investors would hope enough bullish momentum take &nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; PURCHASE HERE &lt;&lt;&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA) gets a new DeFi partner</p>
<p>Cardano (ADA), has announced a new partnership with Acredius, a Swiss fintech company. According to the announcement, Acredius will work with Cardano (ADA) to advance the development of decentralized finance on the network. Cardano (ADA) is already outperforming expectations, adding over 1,000 smart contracts to its network.</p>
<p>The increasing activity on the Cardano (ADA) network has not been followed by a correlating price increase. Instead, the price of Cardano (ADA) has consolidated between $0.36 and $0.40 over the last 30 days. The lack of price movement is the fuel driving investors to the Sparklo presale.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find out about the Sparklo (SPRK) presale using the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Presale: https://invest.sparklo.finance</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/sparklo_finance</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/sparklofinance</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[More Chaos On Bitcoin(BTC). What Could This Mean For Uwerx(WERX)?]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/more-chaos-on-bitcoinbtc-what-could-this-mean-for-uwerxwerx</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-603.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-603.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-603.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/more-chaos-on-bitcoinbtc-what-could-this-mean-for-uwerxwerx</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With over 40% dominance in the crypto market, Bitcoin's price action directly affects market movement. It's the most liquid asset in the market and a mirror of the market at large. Price trends have shown over the years that the market dumps when BTC dumps. Therefore, with the recent developments with BTC, crypto enthusiasts are weighing their chances for their other crypto bags. However, Uwerx remains a solid go-to crypto asset regardless of the market condition.</p>
<p>Bitcoin(BTC) Developers Debate</p>
<p>Bitcoin(BTC) has been in a bit of a dilemma over the recent spike in transaction fees due to ordinals hype. Recent news reports that the massive number of BRC-20 tokens created by the Ordinals protocol, which choked the Bitcoin(BTC) network and drove transaction fees skyrocketing, has ignited a debate among blockchain engineers about how to control the on-chain frenzy.</p>
<p>The dispute is taking place on the Bitcoin-dev mailing list, which handles Bitcoin development conversations. Opinions differ on whether more stringent measures should be implemented to stem the unexpected increase of BRC-20 mints.</p>
<p>The rising costs have compelled some Bitcoin(BTC) users to explore alternative payment methods such as stablecoins. Following Binance halting Bitcoin transactions for a while, it has announced that it is in the process of implementing the Lightning Network "layer 2" scaling solution for Bitcoin. The spike in transaction fees has been a blessing for Bitcoin miners. However, it has created nothing but an existential crisis for traditionalists of a blockchain supposed to be a peer-to-peer payments network that is also free of censorship.</p>
<p>Uwerx(WERX) Is A Guaranteed Pump</p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX) is creating a new market in the crypto landscape with its emergence as a freelance platform looking to decentralize and revolutionize the industry. Using the blockchain as an underlying resource will be a new approach to providing a solution for the global gig economy and is seeing quite the adoption towards launch.</p>
<p>Smart investors are quick to see the opportunity for early adopters of this new solution. The global gig economy is valued at several billion dollars, and expert prediction projects the freelance market could be valued at $9192.2 million by 2026. The industry is growing at a Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) of 15.3%, and at that rate, it could become the primary labor market in several years to come.</p>
<p>Uwerx will be looking to reduce fees and solve issues around payment limitations across predominant freelance platforms. At a 1% flat fee, users are able to keep more money to themselves. Fees charged by Uwerx usually rotate back to the liquidity pool to create more value for users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx is currently offering its native token WERX on presale, allowing early adopters to get in below market price. Once presale is done, the liquidity is locked for 25 years as an anti-rug mechanism. And having been audited by InterFi Network and SolidProof, the presale is a secure event to join, and you can be guaranteed profit by launch. Enter Uwerx presale now at $0.0315 for additional 20% bonus tokens.</p>
<p>Don't miss out:</p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over 40% dominance in the crypto market, Bitcoin's price action directly affects market movement. It's the most liquid asset in the market and a mirror of the market at large. Price trends have shown over the years that the market dumps when BTC dumps. Therefore, with the recent developments with BTC, crypto enthusiasts are weighing their chances for their other crypto bags. However, Uwerx remains a solid go-to crypto asset regardless of the market condition.</p>
<p>Bitcoin(BTC) Developers Debate</p>
<p>Bitcoin(BTC) has been in a bit of a dilemma over the recent spike in transaction fees due to ordinals hype. Recent news reports that the massive number of BRC-20 tokens created by the Ordinals protocol, which choked the Bitcoin(BTC) network and drove transaction fees skyrocketing, has ignited a debate among blockchain engineers about how to control the on-chain frenzy.</p>
<p>The dispute is taking place on the Bitcoin-dev mailing list, which handles Bitcoin development conversations. Opinions differ on whether more stringent measures should be implemented to stem the unexpected increase of BRC-20 mints.</p>
<p>The rising costs have compelled some Bitcoin(BTC) users to explore alternative payment methods such as stablecoins. Following Binance halting Bitcoin transactions for a while, it has announced that it is in the process of implementing the Lightning Network "layer 2" scaling solution for Bitcoin. The spike in transaction fees has been a blessing for Bitcoin miners. However, it has created nothing but an existential crisis for traditionalists of a blockchain supposed to be a peer-to-peer payments network that is also free of censorship.</p>
<p>Uwerx(WERX) Is A Guaranteed Pump</p>
<p>Uwerx (WERX) is creating a new market in the crypto landscape with its emergence as a freelance platform looking to decentralize and revolutionize the industry. Using the blockchain as an underlying resource will be a new approach to providing a solution for the global gig economy and is seeing quite the adoption towards launch.</p>
<p>Smart investors are quick to see the opportunity for early adopters of this new solution. The global gig economy is valued at several billion dollars, and expert prediction projects the freelance market could be valued at $9192.2 million by 2026. The industry is growing at a Compound Annual Growth Rate (CAGR) of 15.3%, and at that rate, it could become the primary labor market in several years to come.</p>
<p>Uwerx will be looking to reduce fees and solve issues around payment limitations across predominant freelance platforms. At a 1% flat fee, users are able to keep more money to themselves. Fees charged by Uwerx usually rotate back to the liquidity pool to create more value for users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Uwerx is currently offering its native token WERX on presale, allowing early adopters to get in below market price. Once presale is done, the liquidity is locked for 25 years as an anti-rug mechanism. And having been audited by InterFi Network and SolidProof, the presale is a secure event to join, and you can be guaranteed profit by launch. Enter Uwerx presale now at $0.0315 for additional 20% bonus tokens.</p>
<p>Don't miss out:</p>
<p>Presale: invest.uwerx.network</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/uwerx_network&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/uwerx_network</p>
<p>Website: https://www.uwerx.network&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[3 Hot DeFi Tokens: UniSwap, Tradecurve, PancakeSwap]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/3-hot-defi-tokens-uniswap-tradecurve-pancakeswap</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-602.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-602.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-602.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/3-hot-defi-tokens-uniswap-tradecurve-pancakeswap</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of decentralized finance (DeFi), three tokens are currently standing out as ones to watch: Uniswap (UNI), Tradecurve (TCRV), and PancakeSwap (CAKE). Most notable is the Tradecurve presale, which is attracting the attention of retail investors and institutional funds alike. Let's take a look at what these three DeFi projects have to offer.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV)</p>
<p>Tradecurve, developed on the Ethereum blockchain, serves as a Web3 trading platform where a vast variety of assets like stocks, forex, commodities, and indices can be traded. Its distinctive advantage is the preservation of user privacy by utilizing decentralized finance (DeFi) technology.</p>
<p>Instead of mandating long-drawn and stringent KYC norms, Tradecurve allows users to simply deposit cryptocurrency to use as collateral and start trading. Now, privacy-oriented traders can take advantage of the DeFi system to trade in traditional markets without having to hand over their personal information.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is more than a simple exchange &mdash; it's a complete trading ecosystem. It offers a rich selection of tools such as AI-enabled trading algorithms, 'copy trading' capabilities, and a sophisticated trading academy, making it conducive for both seasoned traders and newcomers.</p>
<p>Tradecurve's native token, TCRV, is integral to this ecosystem. Holding TCRV comes with a series of benefits like the right to copy successful traders, opportunities for earning passive income through staking, and enjoying lower trading fees.</p>
<p>Currently, TCRV is being offered at a nominal price of $0.012 during its presale phase. Market experts suggest a significant increase in its value &ndash; potentially up to $0.60 by the end of the presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI)</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI) is a decentralized system that enables you to directly exchange different cryptocurrencies in an environment free from central oversight or control. UniSwap (UNI) is built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) blockchain, which serves as its underlying technology platform.</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI) allows users to contribute their own cryptocurrency into shared pools, to facilitate others' trades. By providing liquidity to UniSwap (UNI), users stand to gain rewards in UNI tokens. This is thanks to UniSwap (UNI)'s use of an Automated Market Maker system, an innovation that lets trades occur without needing a buyer and a seller for each trade.</p>
<p>Pricewise, UniSwap (UNI) is trading at $5.31 &mdash; 88% down from the all-time high of $44.97 set in 2021. Analysts note that UniSwap (UNI) is sitting above the strong support level of $4.80, with an overall bullish sentiment due to the crypto community seeking out decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE)</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is another leading DeFi protocol that operates on the Binance Smart Chain. PancakeSwap (CAKE)'s primary purpose is to provide liquidity for tokens listed in its native network.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) isn't just known for its services; it has also been in the spotlight for the native CAKE token. In 2020-2021, PancakeSwap (CAKE)'s value skyrocketed over 10,000%, marking it as one of the most profitable cryptocurrencies of the year.</p>
<p>One of the distinguishing features of PancakeSwap (CAKE) is the Syrup Pools, where users can stake their tokens in exchange for a share of the fees generated from trading activities. This feature has made PancakeSwap (CAKE) one of the most rewarding defi protocols and an attractive option for yield farming.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is 95% down from its all-time high, a drop that has made it a tempting investment opportunity. However, it's important to recognize the volatility of PancakeSwap (CAKE), which is why many investors are turning to DeFi tokens that are just starting their journey, like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>For more information on Tradecurve&rsquo;s presale, check out the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the ever-evolving world of decentralized finance (DeFi), three tokens are currently standing out as ones to watch: Uniswap (UNI), Tradecurve (TCRV), and PancakeSwap (CAKE). Most notable is the Tradecurve presale, which is attracting the attention of retail investors and institutional funds alike. Let's take a look at what these three DeFi projects have to offer.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV)</p>
<p>Tradecurve, developed on the Ethereum blockchain, serves as a Web3 trading platform where a vast variety of assets like stocks, forex, commodities, and indices can be traded. Its distinctive advantage is the preservation of user privacy by utilizing decentralized finance (DeFi) technology.</p>
<p>Instead of mandating long-drawn and stringent KYC norms, Tradecurve allows users to simply deposit cryptocurrency to use as collateral and start trading. Now, privacy-oriented traders can take advantage of the DeFi system to trade in traditional markets without having to hand over their personal information.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve is more than a simple exchange &mdash; it's a complete trading ecosystem. It offers a rich selection of tools such as AI-enabled trading algorithms, 'copy trading' capabilities, and a sophisticated trading academy, making it conducive for both seasoned traders and newcomers.</p>
<p>Tradecurve's native token, TCRV, is integral to this ecosystem. Holding TCRV comes with a series of benefits like the right to copy successful traders, opportunities for earning passive income through staking, and enjoying lower trading fees.</p>
<p>Currently, TCRV is being offered at a nominal price of $0.012 during its presale phase. Market experts suggest a significant increase in its value &ndash; potentially up to $0.60 by the end of the presale.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI)</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI) is a decentralized system that enables you to directly exchange different cryptocurrencies in an environment free from central oversight or control. UniSwap (UNI) is built on top of the Ethereum (ETH) blockchain, which serves as its underlying technology platform.</p>
<p>UniSwap (UNI) allows users to contribute their own cryptocurrency into shared pools, to facilitate others' trades. By providing liquidity to UniSwap (UNI), users stand to gain rewards in UNI tokens. This is thanks to UniSwap (UNI)'s use of an Automated Market Maker system, an innovation that lets trades occur without needing a buyer and a seller for each trade.</p>
<p>Pricewise, UniSwap (UNI) is trading at $5.31 &mdash; 88% down from the all-time high of $44.97 set in 2021. Analysts note that UniSwap (UNI) is sitting above the strong support level of $4.80, with an overall bullish sentiment due to the crypto community seeking out decentralized platforms.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;Register For The Tradecurve Presale&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE)</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is another leading DeFi protocol that operates on the Binance Smart Chain. PancakeSwap (CAKE)'s primary purpose is to provide liquidity for tokens listed in its native network.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) isn't just known for its services; it has also been in the spotlight for the native CAKE token. In 2020-2021, PancakeSwap (CAKE)'s value skyrocketed over 10,000%, marking it as one of the most profitable cryptocurrencies of the year.</p>
<p>One of the distinguishing features of PancakeSwap (CAKE) is the Syrup Pools, where users can stake their tokens in exchange for a share of the fees generated from trading activities. This feature has made PancakeSwap (CAKE) one of the most rewarding defi protocols and an attractive option for yield farming.</p>
<p>PancakeSwap (CAKE) is 95% down from its all-time high, a drop that has made it a tempting investment opportunity. However, it's important to recognize the volatility of PancakeSwap (CAKE), which is why many investors are turning to DeFi tokens that are just starting their journey, like Tradecurve.</p>
<p>For more information on Tradecurve&rsquo;s presale, check out the links below:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Buy presale: https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[News Round-Up: Ripple Buys Swiss Start-Up, TOADS Passes $ 4.2m Sold, PEPE Becomes 2nd most traded crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/news-round-up-ripple-buys-swiss-start-up-toads-passes-42m-sold-pepe-becomes-2nd-most-traded-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-601.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-601.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-601.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/news-round-up-ripple-buys-swiss-start-up-toads-passes-42m-sold-pepe-becomes-2nd-most-traded-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a world that is quickly rushing to adopt digital currency, meme-coins are showing high innovation through utility. DigiToads stands out as a modern meme-coin that will help shape the future of digital assets. Its pre-sale, currently at $ 4.2m is a significant testament to its potential.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads Surpasses the $4.2 Million Mark in Pre-sale</p>
<p>DigiToads has continued to break massive milestones in a presale streak that has hit over $4.2 million so far. The milestone is a demonstration of innovation in the current era that combines traditional meme coins that have dominated the crypto space and more modern utility cryptocurrencies that provide various services to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TOADS, its native token has played a crucial role in the massive milestone, which might beat expectations ahead of the official launch. The native token dominates transactions in the DigiToads ecosystem, which involves an NFT staking pool and P2E gaming. TOADS is also the sole currency in the metaverse that incorporates NFTs as characters for activities such as gaming, interactions, and sales.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads centers transparency as the key driving force for its burgeoning eco-system that promises massive rewards for those taking part in the pre-sale. In a statement, the platform will allow users to stake NFTs, which will be key in sustainability and creating new prize pools for bringing in more investors.</p>
<p>From its website, about 585 million TOADS will go towards maintaining the platform as it seeks to invite more investors. The pre-sale has garnered a lot of attention so far, which prompted an allocation of about 69% of the total tokens. Currently&nbsp; on 7 out of 10&nbsp; stages. DigiToads community has received about 13% of tokens that will act as a liquidity pool.</p>
<p>To invite more stockholders, and to keep the community involved, DigiToads has set aside about 7% of tokens to reward customers taking part in the pre-sale and those in competitions that run on social media such as Twitter, Telegram, and Discord.</p>
<p>The pre-sale has witnessed impressive numbers being thrown around. DigiToads announced a total of $150, 000 in giveaways, which will be in batches of $1000, $2000, and $5000. Earlier adopters also have a share of about 10% of the profits given monthly, which will come from the prize pools created and overseen by the treasury.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Ripple Completes the Acquisition of Swiss Firm Metaco</p>
<p>In a move that will see it expand its services to also span digital assets, Ripple has invested an impressive $250 million to acquire the firm Metaco. The Swiss-based firm deals in digital assets, which it helps secure on behalf of clients in the financial space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The deal is a testament to the potential of the growing digital space, and also a way for Ripple to strengthen its standing in the market it seeks to dominate. Metaco holds an impressive reputation in the financial digital space, as it provides services for the likes of BBVA, BNP Paribas, Citi, and Societe Generale.</p>
<p>The digital space has had a rough patch in the past year, Ripple's attempt is a massive confidence move that sets to cement the position of digital coins in the market and insurance for their future that is under attack by regulation. The demonstration is also a massive confidence booster to the markets that are picking momentum heading into the third quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PEPE Becomes the Second Most Traded Meme Coin</p>
<p>PEPE's recent runs have made it the second-most preferred meme-coin in the coin market in 24 hours. While the coin has shed about 5% in the same period, and also performed dismally in the past weeks, considering its all-time high. Previous highs of $00000431 and volumes of up to 220 million are a testament to potential rallies that might make the coin cement its position against potential rivals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Noteworthy, the coin's current goal of securing a listing in some of the most popular exchanges will determine its future value and trading position in the markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recent developments in PEPE highlight that pure meme coins also have potential. Its lack of utility in the form of NFT staking and P2E game support like its rival TOADS, forces it to rely on the community&rsquo;s Fear of Missing Out (FOMO) for growth.</p>
<p>The evolution of the crypto market will force PEPE to adopt, and other factors will be crucial to its growth. Sustaining an interest from the community is an arduous task, but the key highlight to its future will be its ability to convince big exchanges to provide it with a platform to fight it out with other meme-coins already listed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads Utility Key to its Future</p>
<p>PEPE&rsquo;s fight for a top spot, DigiToads impressive march to $3.7 million, and the massive investments Ripple has made give credibility to the crypto market now and in the future. DigiToads is innovating in the meme-coin space with utility included, meaning it puts sustainability and transparency at the forefront. The future seems bright for the coin, as it will continue to attract investors who have sustainability in mind.</p>
<p>Final Note</p>
<p>Crypto is geared towards a cashless future, which is set in virtual worlds. NFTs, being the center of these worlds, will require a sustainable Token to make them transferable. TOADS, surpassing the $4.2 million mark, is a testament that people are accepting the reality of future technologies. Its support for NFT staking and P2E gaming makes it a fine addition for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The presale stage provides the perfect entry to the DigiToads ecosystem, which promises investors massive discounts and great prizes. There will never be a time like this in the sustainable existence of DigiToads.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a world that is quickly rushing to adopt digital currency, meme-coins are showing high innovation through utility. DigiToads stands out as a modern meme-coin that will help shape the future of digital assets. Its pre-sale, currently at $ 4.2m is a significant testament to its potential.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads Surpasses the $4.2 Million Mark in Pre-sale</p>
<p>DigiToads has continued to break massive milestones in a presale streak that has hit over $4.2 million so far. The milestone is a demonstration of innovation in the current era that combines traditional meme coins that have dominated the crypto space and more modern utility cryptocurrencies that provide various services to customers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TOADS, its native token has played a crucial role in the massive milestone, which might beat expectations ahead of the official launch. The native token dominates transactions in the DigiToads ecosystem, which involves an NFT staking pool and P2E gaming. TOADS is also the sole currency in the metaverse that incorporates NFTs as characters for activities such as gaming, interactions, and sales.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads centers transparency as the key driving force for its burgeoning eco-system that promises massive rewards for those taking part in the pre-sale. In a statement, the platform will allow users to stake NFTs, which will be key in sustainability and creating new prize pools for bringing in more investors.</p>
<p>From its website, about 585 million TOADS will go towards maintaining the platform as it seeks to invite more investors. The pre-sale has garnered a lot of attention so far, which prompted an allocation of about 69% of the total tokens. Currently&nbsp; on 7 out of 10&nbsp; stages. DigiToads community has received about 13% of tokens that will act as a liquidity pool.</p>
<p>To invite more stockholders, and to keep the community involved, DigiToads has set aside about 7% of tokens to reward customers taking part in the pre-sale and those in competitions that run on social media such as Twitter, Telegram, and Discord.</p>
<p>The pre-sale has witnessed impressive numbers being thrown around. DigiToads announced a total of $150, 000 in giveaways, which will be in batches of $1000, $2000, and $5000. Earlier adopters also have a share of about 10% of the profits given monthly, which will come from the prize pools created and overseen by the treasury.</p>
<p>&gt;&gt; Buy DigiToads Now &lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Ripple Completes the Acquisition of Swiss Firm Metaco</p>
<p>In a move that will see it expand its services to also span digital assets, Ripple has invested an impressive $250 million to acquire the firm Metaco. The Swiss-based firm deals in digital assets, which it helps secure on behalf of clients in the financial space.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The deal is a testament to the potential of the growing digital space, and also a way for Ripple to strengthen its standing in the market it seeks to dominate. Metaco holds an impressive reputation in the financial digital space, as it provides services for the likes of BBVA, BNP Paribas, Citi, and Societe Generale.</p>
<p>The digital space has had a rough patch in the past year, Ripple's attempt is a massive confidence move that sets to cement the position of digital coins in the market and insurance for their future that is under attack by regulation. The demonstration is also a massive confidence booster to the markets that are picking momentum heading into the third quarter.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PEPE Becomes the Second Most Traded Meme Coin</p>
<p>PEPE's recent runs have made it the second-most preferred meme-coin in the coin market in 24 hours. While the coin has shed about 5% in the same period, and also performed dismally in the past weeks, considering its all-time high. Previous highs of $00000431 and volumes of up to 220 million are a testament to potential rallies that might make the coin cement its position against potential rivals.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Noteworthy, the coin's current goal of securing a listing in some of the most popular exchanges will determine its future value and trading position in the markets.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Recent developments in PEPE highlight that pure meme coins also have potential. Its lack of utility in the form of NFT staking and P2E game support like its rival TOADS, forces it to rely on the community&rsquo;s Fear of Missing Out (FOMO) for growth.</p>
<p>The evolution of the crypto market will force PEPE to adopt, and other factors will be crucial to its growth. Sustaining an interest from the community is an arduous task, but the key highlight to its future will be its ability to convince big exchanges to provide it with a platform to fight it out with other meme-coins already listed.&nbsp;</p>
<p>DigiToads Utility Key to its Future</p>
<p>PEPE&rsquo;s fight for a top spot, DigiToads impressive march to $3.7 million, and the massive investments Ripple has made give credibility to the crypto market now and in the future. DigiToads is innovating in the meme-coin space with utility included, meaning it puts sustainability and transparency at the forefront. The future seems bright for the coin, as it will continue to attract investors who have sustainability in mind.</p>
<p>Final Note</p>
<p>Crypto is geared towards a cashless future, which is set in virtual worlds. NFTs, being the center of these worlds, will require a sustainable Token to make them transferable. TOADS, surpassing the $4.2 million mark, is a testament that people are accepting the reality of future technologies. Its support for NFT staking and P2E gaming makes it a fine addition for investors.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The presale stage provides the perfect entry to the DigiToads ecosystem, which promises investors massive discounts and great prizes. There will never be a time like this in the sustainable existence of DigiToads.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information on DigiToads visit the website, join the presale or join the community for regular updates.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitpapa – Business and Private Gateway into a P2P Crypto Payment Reality]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitpapa-business-and-private-gateway-into-a-p2p-crypto-payment-reality</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-600.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-600.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-600.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitpapa-business-and-private-gateway-into-a-p2p-crypto-payment-reality</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The crypto industry may have taken a back seat to its bedrock blockchain technology in terms of application and media coverage, but the use of cryptocurrencies continues unabated. Businesses and individuals alike are resorting to cryptocurrencies for making everyday transactions and the use of Peer-to-Peer trading venues is taking center stage for such operations. True to the original ideals of the blockchain industry, P2P transfers of cryptocurrencies are fully decentralized, transparent, and, most importantly &ndash; intermediary-free.</p>
<p>With the volume of transactions in cryptocurrencies growing across developing countries, Bitpapa &ndash; a leading P2P platform &ndash; is offering a unique and convenient instrument for fast-tracking the integration of cryptocurrency payment acceptance.</p>
<p>All in the Widget</p>
<p>As one of the leading P2P service providers in Africa and a rapidly growing enterprise, Bitpapa provides its clients with a simple and holistic solution, ideally suited for businesses willing to enter the crypto domain. Bitpapa offers a widget integration software package for any type of website that accepts payment from customers using any number of methods.</p>
<p>The workflow and client journey on a merchant resource using the Bitpapa solution adds to existing payment methods the option of paying via P2P transfer using one of the local popular banks in the host country. This approach gives customers the convenience of resorting to classic card payment and processing alongside cryptocurrencies when purchasing goods and services on merchant websites. From the seller&rsquo;s standpoint, integration of the Bitpapa software suite allows them to tap into the audience of crypto users and thus expand client bases.</p>
<p>If the client selects P2P transfer to make the payment, they will be provided with the number of a bank card for transferring the sum of their order. In essence, the procedure is boiled down to a simple internal bank transfer from card to card, freeing clients from having to pay commission fees, and merchants from incurring acquiring charges. Such P2P transfers are usually carried out in under 30 seconds and clients receive payment confirmations that allow their orders to be processed.</p>
<p>Merchants using the Bitpapa software suite get access to a personal account containing their wallet with a display of cryptocurrency balances. The latter are reflected in the currency the merchant uses, allowing for instant conversion of customers&rsquo; cryptocurrencies into fiat. At present, the application supports Bitcoin, the USDT stablecoin, and Monero as means of payment. Merchants are then free to withdraw funds from their balances at will to any external digital wallet or bank account.</p>
<p>The Business Benefits</p>
<p>In addition to expanding client audiences to crypto users, businesses receive a host of other advantages when applying the Bitpapa service for their crypto acquiring needs.</p>
<p>The first and foremost of the benefits is the service&rsquo;s competitive pricing and commission policy, which makes it considerably cheaper than traditional payment processing systems. Bitpapa charges a fixed fee for withdrawing payments, as opposed to a percentage that is withheld by traditional processing gateways.</p>
<p>Another notable advantage of using Bitpapa is complete independence from the traditional financial and banking system &ndash; a trait true of the blockchain industry&rsquo;s core qualities and principles. Merchants often have a hard time negotiating terms with banks regarding commissions and have to cope with often long processing times. Transactions processed on Bitpapa are almost instantaneous and save merchants considerable time and effort as a result.</p>
<p>However, the most important advantage of the Bitpapa suite is its versatility, which includes over one hundred different payment methods. The integration of such a variety of payment gateways opens immense opportunities for merchants and gives their clients almost complete freedom to choose the way they wish to pay, ranging from bank cards to e-wallet services.</p>
<p>Peer-to-Peer Trade as a Must</p>
<p>The proliferation of blockchain technologies and the adoption of cryptocurrencies is going uphill around the world, especially in developing countries. Wise merchants will realize that tapping into such a tech-savvy audience of potential buyers by wooing them with the ability to pay using cryptocurrencies is a sound and profitable business move. With Bitpapa, the process of integrating such an option becomes hassle-free and convenient, while the benefits far outweigh the adage of sticking to traditional financial gateways.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The crypto industry may have taken a back seat to its bedrock blockchain technology in terms of application and media coverage, but the use of cryptocurrencies continues unabated. Businesses and individuals alike are resorting to cryptocurrencies for making everyday transactions and the use of Peer-to-Peer trading venues is taking center stage for such operations. True to the original ideals of the blockchain industry, P2P transfers of cryptocurrencies are fully decentralized, transparent, and, most importantly &ndash; intermediary-free.</p>
<p>With the volume of transactions in cryptocurrencies growing across developing countries, Bitpapa &ndash; a leading P2P platform &ndash; is offering a unique and convenient instrument for fast-tracking the integration of cryptocurrency payment acceptance.</p>
<p>All in the Widget</p>
<p>As one of the leading P2P service providers in Africa and a rapidly growing enterprise, Bitpapa provides its clients with a simple and holistic solution, ideally suited for businesses willing to enter the crypto domain. Bitpapa offers a widget integration software package for any type of website that accepts payment from customers using any number of methods.</p>
<p>The workflow and client journey on a merchant resource using the Bitpapa solution adds to existing payment methods the option of paying via P2P transfer using one of the local popular banks in the host country. This approach gives customers the convenience of resorting to classic card payment and processing alongside cryptocurrencies when purchasing goods and services on merchant websites. From the seller&rsquo;s standpoint, integration of the Bitpapa software suite allows them to tap into the audience of crypto users and thus expand client bases.</p>
<p>If the client selects P2P transfer to make the payment, they will be provided with the number of a bank card for transferring the sum of their order. In essence, the procedure is boiled down to a simple internal bank transfer from card to card, freeing clients from having to pay commission fees, and merchants from incurring acquiring charges. Such P2P transfers are usually carried out in under 30 seconds and clients receive payment confirmations that allow their orders to be processed.</p>
<p>Merchants using the Bitpapa software suite get access to a personal account containing their wallet with a display of cryptocurrency balances. The latter are reflected in the currency the merchant uses, allowing for instant conversion of customers&rsquo; cryptocurrencies into fiat. At present, the application supports Bitcoin, the USDT stablecoin, and Monero as means of payment. Merchants are then free to withdraw funds from their balances at will to any external digital wallet or bank account.</p>
<p>The Business Benefits</p>
<p>In addition to expanding client audiences to crypto users, businesses receive a host of other advantages when applying the Bitpapa service for their crypto acquiring needs.</p>
<p>The first and foremost of the benefits is the service&rsquo;s competitive pricing and commission policy, which makes it considerably cheaper than traditional payment processing systems. Bitpapa charges a fixed fee for withdrawing payments, as opposed to a percentage that is withheld by traditional processing gateways.</p>
<p>Another notable advantage of using Bitpapa is complete independence from the traditional financial and banking system &ndash; a trait true of the blockchain industry&rsquo;s core qualities and principles. Merchants often have a hard time negotiating terms with banks regarding commissions and have to cope with often long processing times. Transactions processed on Bitpapa are almost instantaneous and save merchants considerable time and effort as a result.</p>
<p>However, the most important advantage of the Bitpapa suite is its versatility, which includes over one hundred different payment methods. The integration of such a variety of payment gateways opens immense opportunities for merchants and gives their clients almost complete freedom to choose the way they wish to pay, ranging from bank cards to e-wallet services.</p>
<p>Peer-to-Peer Trade as a Must</p>
<p>The proliferation of blockchain technologies and the adoption of cryptocurrencies is going uphill around the world, especially in developing countries. Wise merchants will realize that tapping into such a tech-savvy audience of potential buyers by wooing them with the ability to pay using cryptocurrencies is a sound and profitable business move. With Bitpapa, the process of integrating such an option becomes hassle-free and convenient, while the benefits far outweigh the adage of sticking to traditional financial gateways.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Solana Integrates ChatGPT Plug-in, Launches AI Accelerator]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/solana-integrates-chatgpt-plug-in-launches-ai-accelerator</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/solana-rpc-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 12:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/solana-integrates-chatgpt-plug-in-launches-ai-accelerator</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The Solana Foundation has announced the official integration of a ChatGPT plug-in developed by Solana Labs, marking the official integration of AI into its network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes as the artificial intelligence (AI) space has seen interest from crypto players, big and small, increase in recent months.&nbsp;</p>
Solana And AI&nbsp;
<p>According to the Solana Foundation, the open-source reference implementation allows users to interact with the Solana network directly from ChatGPT through a plug-in. The plug-in is available for download on GitHub. Solana Labs first revealed the new plug-in in a teaser in Late April and will be targeted towards end users during its initial phase, helping them onboard into the growing Web 3.0 ecosystem. It can also be used to purchase and list NFTs, find NFT collections by floor price, check out transactions, and transfer tokens. The Solana Foundation, in a statement, said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This integration from Solana Labs serves as a reference for how AI can make it easier to understand Solana data and protocols or surface data about Solana&rsquo;s computing infrastructure and DeFi projects.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana Labs CEO and Solana Co-founder Anatoly Yakovenko added that AI integration would help in making the Solana blockchain more understandable and usable.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Every developer building consumer-oriented apps should be thinking about how their app is going to be interacted with through an AI model because this is a new paradigm for telling computers what to do.&rdquo;</p>

Simplicity For Users And Developers&nbsp;
<p>According to Tal Tchwella, the head of product at Solana Labs, Solana will plug ChatGPT into an RPC node that can access data from multiple sources on-chain and answer user questions. Users can ask the AI questions regarding NFT collections and which ones they can buy. The initial focus of the plug-in will be on NFTs, thanks to Solana&rsquo;s growing volume of NFT sales. However, there is also an effort on the developer front to help accelerate AI growth within its ecosystem. The integration offers a new way for developers and users to ask service questions while simplifying the entire experience.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe that the blockchain space is way too technical. Bringing the popular ChatGPT service to Solana &ldquo;offers a new opportunity for people to engage with it and understand what&rsquo;s really happening.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Instead of reading mountains of documentation, AI could access it and answer queries posted to it.&nbsp;</p>
Solana&rsquo;s AI Accelerator Program&nbsp;
<p>Apart from the plug-in, Solana also announced an AI-focused accelerator program for university-level students. The announcement was made in early April.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Solana Foundation also kicked off a 3-month long accelerator program for university students that has a full cohort dedicated to experimenting with blockchain and AI.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana separately announced that it was expanding its grant program for AI-focused projects building on Solana from $1 million to $10 million. Following the announcement, Solana has received over 50 applications, with the foundation already approving grants for some projects. The update was made through Solana Foundation&rsquo;s official Twitter handle.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Update: The fund supporting projects at the intersection of the @Solana blockchain and AI has been expanded to $10 million.&rdquo;</p>

Solana Sees Surge In Activity&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, Solana has registered a surge in activity on its network during the current month. This can be attributed to high fees on Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have pushed users to find other alternatives. Last week, the seven-day moving average of new addresses hit 323,000, which is the highest figure recorded since June 2022, according to data sourced from The Block. The data shows that Solana has added more new addresses this month than what it registered in each of the past six months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The protocol&rsquo;s native SOL token has also dramatically recovered, rising 101% year-to-date. Currently, the token is trading at $19.48.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Solana Foundation has announced the official integration of a ChatGPT plug-in developed by Solana Labs, marking the official integration of AI into its network.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes as the artificial intelligence (AI) space has seen interest from crypto players, big and small, increase in recent months.&nbsp;</p>
Solana And AI&nbsp;
<p>According to the Solana Foundation, the open-source reference implementation allows users to interact with the Solana network directly from ChatGPT through a plug-in. The plug-in is available for download on GitHub. Solana Labs first revealed the new plug-in in a teaser in Late April and will be targeted towards end users during its initial phase, helping them onboard into the growing Web 3.0 ecosystem. It can also be used to purchase and list NFTs, find NFT collections by floor price, check out transactions, and transfer tokens. The Solana Foundation, in a statement, said,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This integration from Solana Labs serves as a reference for how AI can make it easier to understand Solana data and protocols or surface data about Solana&rsquo;s computing infrastructure and DeFi projects.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana Labs CEO and Solana Co-founder Anatoly Yakovenko added that AI integration would help in making the Solana blockchain more understandable and usable.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Every developer building consumer-oriented apps should be thinking about how their app is going to be interacted with through an AI model because this is a new paradigm for telling computers what to do.&rdquo;</p>

Simplicity For Users And Developers&nbsp;
<p>According to Tal Tchwella, the head of product at Solana Labs, Solana will plug ChatGPT into an RPC node that can access data from multiple sources on-chain and answer user questions. Users can ask the AI questions regarding NFT collections and which ones they can buy. The initial focus of the plug-in will be on NFTs, thanks to Solana&rsquo;s growing volume of NFT sales. However, there is also an effort on the developer front to help accelerate AI growth within its ecosystem. The integration offers a new way for developers and users to ask service questions while simplifying the entire experience.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We believe that the blockchain space is way too technical. Bringing the popular ChatGPT service to Solana &ldquo;offers a new opportunity for people to engage with it and understand what&rsquo;s really happening.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Instead of reading mountains of documentation, AI could access it and answer queries posted to it.&nbsp;</p>
Solana&rsquo;s AI Accelerator Program&nbsp;
<p>Apart from the plug-in, Solana also announced an AI-focused accelerator program for university-level students. The announcement was made in early April.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The Solana Foundation also kicked off a 3-month long accelerator program for university students that has a full cohort dedicated to experimenting with blockchain and AI.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Solana separately announced that it was expanding its grant program for AI-focused projects building on Solana from $1 million to $10 million. Following the announcement, Solana has received over 50 applications, with the foundation already approving grants for some projects. The update was made through Solana Foundation&rsquo;s official Twitter handle.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Update: The fund supporting projects at the intersection of the @Solana blockchain and AI has been expanded to $10 million.&rdquo;</p>

Solana Sees Surge In Activity&nbsp;
<p>Meanwhile, Solana has registered a surge in activity on its network during the current month. This can be attributed to high fees on Bitcoin and Ethereum, which have pushed users to find other alternatives. Last week, the seven-day moving average of new addresses hit 323,000, which is the highest figure recorded since June 2022, according to data sourced from The Block. The data shows that Solana has added more new addresses this month than what it registered in each of the past six months.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The protocol&rsquo;s native SOL token has also dramatically recovered, rising 101% year-to-date. Currently, the token is trading at $19.48.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Winklevoss twins advise UK not to follow US crypto stance]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/winklevoss-twins-advise-uk-not-to-follow-us-crypto-stance</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wink.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wink.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/wink.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 12:01:05 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/winklevoss-twins-advise-uk-not-to-follow-us-crypto-stance</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>With the UK seeking to become a crypto hub, the Winklevoss twins are advising the UK government to not let itself be influenced by the politicisation of crypto in the US.</p>
UK regulation is encouraging
<p>The Winklevoss twins, American billionaire owners of the Gemini crypto exchange, are in London holding talks with various British financial bodies such as the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).</p>
<p>While in London, the Gemini owners gave an interview to City A.M., in which they advised UK politicians not to &ldquo;politicise&rdquo; the government&rsquo;s regulatory stance towards cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss twins were said to be &ldquo;encouraged&rdquo; by the direction the UK is taking on crypto regulation and were of the opinion that it was &ldquo;forward thinking&rdquo;. They said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are encouraged [by] the state of regulation here. We know obviously the UK has a huge tradition of being a thoughtful regulator and a forward thinking regulator. And that&rsquo;s why we chose to be here &ndash; there&rsquo;s a lot of credibility,&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We made that decision to invest here years ago, and we&rsquo;re here to express that we want to continue to do that and make the UK a home for crypto.&rdquo;</p>

<p>They remarked that they were &ldquo;surprised&rdquo; by the recent report by the UK Treasury Select Committee stating that cryptocurrencies should be treated as &ldquo;gambling&rdquo;, and made the comment that if this were the case then perhaps commodities like oil and gold might go into the same category.</p>
Mixed noises from the UK financial institutions
<p>The UK has so far made as many positive noises on crypto as it has negative, with Prime Minister Sunak declaring that the UK wished to become a worldwide hub for crypto (when he was Chancellor).&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, it would seem for a country so embedded in the traditional financial system, with its City banking operation one of the most powerful in the world, that to go the path of inviting crypto companies to set up shop there might be an extremely difficult route to take.</p>
<p>In the past, the governor of the Bank of England, Andrew Bailey, has called crypto &ldquo;dangerous&rdquo;, even while acknowledging that a lot of innovation was coming out of the sector. He has said that he doesn&rsquo;t believe crypto will provide a future payments network.</p>
<p>The Bank of England is very pro a central bank digital currency (CBDC) which has many issues around privacy, although counter to what Europe is doing with MiCA, the BoE is considering zero-knowledge proofs in its implementation of a CBDC.</p>
<p>With the US likely to be applying pressure on the British government in the background, and with what has been termed an &ldquo;overly bureaucratic regulatory environment&rdquo; by CEO of Revolut, Nik Storonsky, as the BoE looks to be in the process of turning down a banking licence for the UK&rsquo;s largest startup, the next few weeks and months are going to be critical for the UK&rsquo;s fledging crypto sector.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the UK seeking to become a crypto hub, the Winklevoss twins are advising the UK government to not let itself be influenced by the politicisation of crypto in the US.</p>
UK regulation is encouraging
<p>The Winklevoss twins, American billionaire owners of the Gemini crypto exchange, are in London holding talks with various British financial bodies such as the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA).</p>
<p>While in London, the Gemini owners gave an interview to City A.M., in which they advised UK politicians not to &ldquo;politicise&rdquo; the government&rsquo;s regulatory stance towards cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The Winklevoss twins were said to be &ldquo;encouraged&rdquo; by the direction the UK is taking on crypto regulation and were of the opinion that it was &ldquo;forward thinking&rdquo;. They said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are encouraged [by] the state of regulation here. We know obviously the UK has a huge tradition of being a thoughtful regulator and a forward thinking regulator. And that&rsquo;s why we chose to be here &ndash; there&rsquo;s a lot of credibility,&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;We made that decision to invest here years ago, and we&rsquo;re here to express that we want to continue to do that and make the UK a home for crypto.&rdquo;</p>

<p>They remarked that they were &ldquo;surprised&rdquo; by the recent report by the UK Treasury Select Committee stating that cryptocurrencies should be treated as &ldquo;gambling&rdquo;, and made the comment that if this were the case then perhaps commodities like oil and gold might go into the same category.</p>
Mixed noises from the UK financial institutions
<p>The UK has so far made as many positive noises on crypto as it has negative, with Prime Minister Sunak declaring that the UK wished to become a worldwide hub for crypto (when he was Chancellor).&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, it would seem for a country so embedded in the traditional financial system, with its City banking operation one of the most powerful in the world, that to go the path of inviting crypto companies to set up shop there might be an extremely difficult route to take.</p>
<p>In the past, the governor of the Bank of England, Andrew Bailey, has called crypto &ldquo;dangerous&rdquo;, even while acknowledging that a lot of innovation was coming out of the sector. He has said that he doesn&rsquo;t believe crypto will provide a future payments network.</p>
<p>The Bank of England is very pro a central bank digital currency (CBDC) which has many issues around privacy, although counter to what Europe is doing with MiCA, the BoE is considering zero-knowledge proofs in its implementation of a CBDC.</p>
<p>With the US likely to be applying pressure on the British government in the background, and with what has been termed an &ldquo;overly bureaucratic regulatory environment&rdquo; by CEO of Revolut, Nik Storonsky, as the BoE looks to be in the process of turning down a banking licence for the UK&rsquo;s largest startup, the next few weeks and months are going to be critical for the UK&rsquo;s fledging crypto sector.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ledger To Delay Key Recovery Service Launch, Open-Source Code]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ledger-to-delay-key-recovery-service-launch-open-source-code</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ledger-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ledger-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/ledger-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:58:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ledger-to-delay-key-recovery-service-launch-open-source-code</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Hardware wallet provider Ledger has announced that it is pushing back the launch of its key-recovery feature after mounting criticism from the larger crypto community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The hardware wallet provider also stated that it would open the source code before it releases the update.&nbsp;</p>
Key-Recovery Service Delayed&nbsp;
<p>The decision was conveyed to wallet users in a letter by Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier. In the letter, Gauthier stated that the company would only launch the new feature after releasing its code to the community. Furthermore, Ledger also scheduled a Twitter Spaces session to discuss the issue with the community and reach a consensus on the way forward. The Twitter Spaces session was joined by over 13,000 users, with the CEO calling it a humbling experience and a lesson in communication. Gauthier stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This experience has been very humbling. We miscommunicated on the launch of this product; it was not our intention to take people by surprise. So because of that, we understand the community&rsquo;s direction and apologize for the miscommunication.&rdquo;</p>

Codebase To Be Open-Source
<p>Gauthier also stated that as a response to concerns raised by the community, Ledger would be accelerating plans to open-source its codebase, starting with the core components of its operating system and Ledger Recover. Additionally, Ledger Recover will not be released until this is completed.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have made the decision to accelerate the open-sourcing roadmap! We will include as much of the Ledger operating system as possible, starting with core components of the OS, and Ledger Recover, which won&rsquo;t be released until this work is complete. Furthermore, we will open-source the Ledger Recover protocol, enabling the community to have as much choice as possible over your self-custody, in addition to the service being fully optional. This roadmap will be shared and updated by our CTO and engineering team.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Chief Technology Officer at Ledger, Charles Guillemet, revealed that over the next few days, the company would make a white paper on the Recover Protocol public, along with technical blog posts. These would explain the principles governing Recover and give a detailed explanation of how the process works. Guillemet stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s going to be very easy and clear for every single cryptography and security expert to have a look at the protocol to get more guarantees and understand how it works.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also added that developers could build their own backup provider for the seed phrase shards rather than using the ones provided by Ledger.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This has always been something important for Ledger, but this recent event showed how important it is for the community, and this is why we decided to prioritize this open-sourcing process.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Gauthier also stressed that offering key recovery services is critical to onboarding new users for whom self-custody may be difficult.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The majority of users in crypto today either don&rsquo;t own their private keys and/or are putting their private keys at risk using less secure forms of self-custody and hard-to-use forms of storing and securing their seed phrase.&rdquo;</p>

Ledger&rsquo;s PR Nightmare&nbsp;
<p>Ledger announced its Ledger Recover service last week, allowing users to store encrypted backups of their seed phrases with third-party custodians. This would enable Ledger users to restore their private keys even if they lost their seed phrases. The feature was announced as an opt-in feature and would require a KYC (Know Your Customer) verification. However, if Ledger was expecting a supportive reaction, it got quite the opposite.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Almost immediately after the announcement, Ledger came under heavy criticism from the crypto community. The main point of criticism was sharing seed phrases with third parties. Multiple users posted angry reactions on social media, stating that they felt betrayed by Ledger. Ledger had previously stated that the wallet&rsquo;s private keys would never leave the device. Critics also pointed out the potential threats that could arise from such an arrangement, such as the hack of custodians entrusted with the private keys, data leaks from KYC service providers, and user data being compromised.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other community members also pointed out that the code for Ledger&rsquo;s Recover feature is not open-source, meaning there is no way to audit and test the feature&rsquo;s safety. Unlike its competitors, Ledger does not publish all its code. Instead, its products are tested by a team of select security researchers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hardware wallet provider Ledger has announced that it is pushing back the launch of its key-recovery feature after mounting criticism from the larger crypto community.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The hardware wallet provider also stated that it would open the source code before it releases the update.&nbsp;</p>
Key-Recovery Service Delayed&nbsp;
<p>The decision was conveyed to wallet users in a letter by Ledger CEO Pascal Gauthier. In the letter, Gauthier stated that the company would only launch the new feature after releasing its code to the community. Furthermore, Ledger also scheduled a Twitter Spaces session to discuss the issue with the community and reach a consensus on the way forward. The Twitter Spaces session was joined by over 13,000 users, with the CEO calling it a humbling experience and a lesson in communication. Gauthier stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This experience has been very humbling. We miscommunicated on the launch of this product; it was not our intention to take people by surprise. So because of that, we understand the community&rsquo;s direction and apologize for the miscommunication.&rdquo;</p>

Codebase To Be Open-Source
<p>Gauthier also stated that as a response to concerns raised by the community, Ledger would be accelerating plans to open-source its codebase, starting with the core components of its operating system and Ledger Recover. Additionally, Ledger Recover will not be released until this is completed.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We have made the decision to accelerate the open-sourcing roadmap! We will include as much of the Ledger operating system as possible, starting with core components of the OS, and Ledger Recover, which won&rsquo;t be released until this work is complete. Furthermore, we will open-source the Ledger Recover protocol, enabling the community to have as much choice as possible over your self-custody, in addition to the service being fully optional. This roadmap will be shared and updated by our CTO and engineering team.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The Chief Technology Officer at Ledger, Charles Guillemet, revealed that over the next few days, the company would make a white paper on the Recover Protocol public, along with technical blog posts. These would explain the principles governing Recover and give a detailed explanation of how the process works. Guillemet stated,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It&rsquo;s going to be very easy and clear for every single cryptography and security expert to have a look at the protocol to get more guarantees and understand how it works.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He also added that developers could build their own backup provider for the seed phrase shards rather than using the ones provided by Ledger.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This has always been something important for Ledger, but this recent event showed how important it is for the community, and this is why we decided to prioritize this open-sourcing process.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Gauthier also stressed that offering key recovery services is critical to onboarding new users for whom self-custody may be difficult.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;The majority of users in crypto today either don&rsquo;t own their private keys and/or are putting their private keys at risk using less secure forms of self-custody and hard-to-use forms of storing and securing their seed phrase.&rdquo;</p>

Ledger&rsquo;s PR Nightmare&nbsp;
<p>Ledger announced its Ledger Recover service last week, allowing users to store encrypted backups of their seed phrases with third-party custodians. This would enable Ledger users to restore their private keys even if they lost their seed phrases. The feature was announced as an opt-in feature and would require a KYC (Know Your Customer) verification. However, if Ledger was expecting a supportive reaction, it got quite the opposite.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Almost immediately after the announcement, Ledger came under heavy criticism from the crypto community. The main point of criticism was sharing seed phrases with third parties. Multiple users posted angry reactions on social media, stating that they felt betrayed by Ledger. Ledger had previously stated that the wallet&rsquo;s private keys would never leave the device. Critics also pointed out the potential threats that could arise from such an arrangement, such as the hack of custodians entrusted with the private keys, data leaks from KYC service providers, and user data being compromised.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Other community members also pointed out that the code for Ledger&rsquo;s Recover feature is not open-source, meaning there is no way to audit and test the feature&rsquo;s safety. Unlike its competitors, Ledger does not publish all its code. Instead, its products are tested by a team of select security researchers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Daily BTC Transactions Hit ATH, Crypto Daily TV 24/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/daily-btc-transactions-hit-ath-crypto-daily-tv-24-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-ath.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-ath.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-ath.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/daily-btc-transactions-hit-ath-crypto-daily-tv-24-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Daily bitcoin transactions hit an all-time high</p>
<p>Things are heating up on the Bitcoin blockchain. Daily transactions have rocketed to an all-time high of 682,000 this month, according to data from Glassnode, almost 40% higher than the previous peak in 2017.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKX sets up shop in Paris</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKX has applied for regulatory approval in France and plans to build out its European hub in Paris, making it the latest overseas crypto firm to pick the French capital as its base on the continent.</p>
<p>EU banks could access stablecoins more easily</p>
<p>The European Commission wants to make it easier for commercial lenders to hold stablecoins and tokenized assets after lawmakers pushed to discourage crypto holdings as part of a wider banking reform.</p>
BTC/USD skyrocketed 1.2% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.2% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 263051 and resistance is at 273831.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 1.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.9% in the last session. According to the CCI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1777.2567 and resistance is at 1847.3167.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair rose 0.3% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.2% during the session. The ROC gives a positive signal. Support is at 0.4428 and resistance is at 0.4767.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 88.3167 and resistance is at 94.0567.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Current Assessment</p>
<p>The IFO Current Assessment is regarded as an indicator of current conditions and business expectations in Germany. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the current business situation and their short-term planning. Germany's IFO &ndash; Current Assessment will be released at 08:00 GMT, Japan's Foreign Bond Investment at 23:50 GMT, and the UK's Consumer Price Index at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Bond Investment</p>
<p>Foreign Bond Investment refers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>UK Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services. </p>
<p>UK Core Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy. The UK's Core Consumer Price Index will be released at 06:00 GMT, the US MBA Mortgage Applications at 11:00 GMT, and the US EIA Crude Oil Stocks Change at 14:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market.</p>
<p>US EIA Crude Oil Stocks Change</p>
<p>The EIA Crude Oil stockpiles report is a weekly measure of the change in the number of barrels in stock of crude oil and its derivates, released by the Energy Information Administration. </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Daily bitcoin transactions hit an all-time high</p>
<p>Things are heating up on the Bitcoin blockchain. Daily transactions have rocketed to an all-time high of 682,000 this month, according to data from Glassnode, almost 40% higher than the previous peak in 2017.</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKX sets up shop in Paris</p>
<p>Crypto exchange OKX has applied for regulatory approval in France and plans to build out its European hub in Paris, making it the latest overseas crypto firm to pick the French capital as its base on the continent.</p>
<p>EU banks could access stablecoins more easily</p>
<p>The European Commission wants to make it easier for commercial lenders to hold stablecoins and tokenized assets after lawmakers pushed to discourage crypto holdings as part of a wider banking reform.</p>
BTC/USD skyrocketed 1.2% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.2% in the last session. The MACD is giving a positive signal. Support is at 263051 and resistance is at 273831.</p>
<p>The MACD is giving a positive signal.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD skyrocketed 1.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair exploded 1.9% in the last session. According to the CCI, we are in an overbought market. Support is at 1777.2567 and resistance is at 1847.3167.</p>
<p>The CCI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD gained 0.3% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair rose 0.3% in the last session after gaining as much as 1.2% during the session. The ROC gives a positive signal. Support is at 0.4428 and resistance is at 0.4767.</p>
<p>The ROC is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD traded sideways in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair traded sideways in the last session. The Williams indicator is giving a negative signal. Support is at 88.3167 and resistance is at 94.0567.</p>
<p>The Williams indicator is currently in the negative zone.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>DE IFO &ndash; Current Assessment</p>
<p>The IFO Current Assessment is regarded as an indicator of current conditions and business expectations in Germany. The Institute surveys enterprises on their assessment of the current business situation and their short-term planning. Germany's IFO &ndash; Current Assessment will be released at 08:00 GMT, Japan's Foreign Bond Investment at 23:50 GMT, and the UK's Consumer Price Index at 06:00 GMT.</p>
<p>JP Foreign Bond Investment</p>
<p>Foreign Bond Investment refers to bonds issued in a domestic market by a foreign entity in the domestic market&rsquo;s currency.</p>
<p>UK Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Consumer Price Index is a measure of price movements made by comparing the retail prices of a representative shopping basket of goods and services. </p>
<p>UK Core Consumer Price Index</p>
<p>The Core Consumer Price Index (CPI) measures the changes in the prices of goods and services, excluding food and energy. The UK's Core Consumer Price Index will be released at 06:00 GMT, the US MBA Mortgage Applications at 11:00 GMT, and the US EIA Crude Oil Stocks Change at 14:30 GMT.</p>
<p>US MBA Mortgage Applications</p>
<p>The MBA Mortgage Applications released by the Mortgage Bankers Association presents various mortgage applications. It is considered a leading indicator of the U.S Housing Market.</p>
<p>US EIA Crude Oil Stocks Change</p>
<p>The EIA Crude Oil stockpiles report is a weekly measure of the change in the number of barrels in stock of crude oil and its derivates, released by the Energy Information Administration. </p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Core Scientific to Exit Bankruptcy by September]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/core-scientific-to-exit-bankruptcy-by-september</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/core-scientific-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/core-scientific-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/core-scientific-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/core-scientific-to-exit-bankruptcy-by-september</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">After filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy last December, the Bitcoin (BTC) miner is now set to finalize a restructuring plan which it expects will net at least a $46 million boost.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In its May 22 filing to the Texas Bankruptcy Court, the miner cites increasing Bitcoin prices, increased hashrate, and decreasing power costs as the reasons for its shift to a new business plan. The bankruptcy filing was necessitated by the prolonged bear market, which caused Bitcoin's price to plummet and Core Scientific's stock to decline by 98%.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Chapter 11 bankruptcy, according to Investopedia will still allow a business to operate while its shareholders agree on a suitable plan to reorganize. In this context, Core Scientific says that it is ready to move forward with a new plan and exit from bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Core Scientific, once one of the largest Bitcoin miners, was forced to file for bankruptcy because of the prolonged crypto winter which saw Bitcoin&rsquo;s price dip to as low as $16,000. This saw Core&rsquo;s stock plummeting by 98%.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Apart from the crypto winter, there is also the ongoing legal debacle with the bankrupt lending platform Celsius which saw Core Scientific being pushed to cut off power supply to the 37,000 mining rigs it hosted for the former. This move came after months of Celsius defaulting on its power bills after its collapse mid-2022, causing Core Scientific to file a motion to reject the contract due to breach of payment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By terminating the Celsius contract, Core Scientific hopes to generate revenue by renting out the space previously occupied by the mining rigs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The lack of payments, Core says, indirectly contributed to their liquidity issues which influenced their subsequent filing for bankruptcy. Celsius (or Celsius Network) is also currently under Chapter 11 bankruptcy, which they filed last July 2022 and which saw 2 million investors&rsquo; investments go up in smoke.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p"> While Core Scientific hopes that its move towards a new schedule for its bankruptcy exit would work, an underlying concern remains the volatility of Bitcoin itself. The alpha cryptocurrency's current slump affects miners like Core Scientific, highlighting the challenges they face in maintaining profitability amid price fluctuations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The declining profitability of Bitcoin mining is another significant factor impacting Core Scientific and other miners. The costs of production, particularly electricity expenses, have risen, while the value of Bitcoin has dropped. Company share prices for the miner have also suffered, with Core Scientific experiencing a substantial decline in its share prices throughout 2022 and Q1 2023. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at the $26,600 range. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">After filing for Chapter 11 bankruptcy last December, the Bitcoin (BTC) miner is now set to finalize a restructuring plan which it expects will net at least a $46 million boost.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In its May 22 filing to the Texas Bankruptcy Court, the miner cites increasing Bitcoin prices, increased hashrate, and decreasing power costs as the reasons for its shift to a new business plan. The bankruptcy filing was necessitated by the prolonged bear market, which caused Bitcoin's price to plummet and Core Scientific's stock to decline by 98%.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A Chapter 11 bankruptcy, according to Investopedia will still allow a business to operate while its shareholders agree on a suitable plan to reorganize. In this context, Core Scientific says that it is ready to move forward with a new plan and exit from bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Core Scientific, once one of the largest Bitcoin miners, was forced to file for bankruptcy because of the prolonged crypto winter which saw Bitcoin&rsquo;s price dip to as low as $16,000. This saw Core&rsquo;s stock plummeting by 98%.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Apart from the crypto winter, there is also the ongoing legal debacle with the bankrupt lending platform Celsius which saw Core Scientific being pushed to cut off power supply to the 37,000 mining rigs it hosted for the former. This move came after months of Celsius defaulting on its power bills after its collapse mid-2022, causing Core Scientific to file a motion to reject the contract due to breach of payment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">By terminating the Celsius contract, Core Scientific hopes to generate revenue by renting out the space previously occupied by the mining rigs.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The lack of payments, Core says, indirectly contributed to their liquidity issues which influenced their subsequent filing for bankruptcy. Celsius (or Celsius Network) is also currently under Chapter 11 bankruptcy, which they filed last July 2022 and which saw 2 million investors&rsquo; investments go up in smoke.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p"> While Core Scientific hopes that its move towards a new schedule for its bankruptcy exit would work, an underlying concern remains the volatility of Bitcoin itself. The alpha cryptocurrency's current slump affects miners like Core Scientific, highlighting the challenges they face in maintaining profitability amid price fluctuations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The declining profitability of Bitcoin mining is another significant factor impacting Core Scientific and other miners. The costs of production, particularly electricity expenses, have risen, while the value of Bitcoin has dropped. Company share prices for the miner have also suffered, with Core Scientific experiencing a substantial decline in its share prices throughout 2022 and Q1 2023. At the time of writing, Bitcoin is trading at the $26,600 range. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Vitalik Warns of Risks in Extending Social Consensus In Ethereum]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/vitalik-warns-of-risks-in-extending-social-consensus-in-ethereum</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/vitalik-on-ethereum-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/vitalik-on-ethereum-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/vitalik-on-ethereum-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/vitalik-warns-of-risks-in-extending-social-consensus-in-ethereum</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin's recent blog post has raised concerns about the potential risks associated with expanding the scope of social consensus within the Ethereum network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In his post, Buterin highlights the importance of maintaining a clear distinction between reusing validators and overloading social consensus for ostensibly external purposes. Buterin nuances his arguments by emphasizing the need for caution and the preservation of Ethereum's core functionality.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Buterin expressed his reservations about certain proposals that aim to utilize Ethereum's consensus and social consensus for purposes beyond the network's core functionality. While acknowledging the well-intentioned nature of these ideas, Buterin emphasizes the need to carefully evaluate the potential risks such proposals may pose to the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Don't overload Ethereum's consensus:https://t.co/07tzyCrZcJ</p>
&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) May 21, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Validator Reuse and Social Consensus</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The blog post focuses on distinguishing between two concepts: reusing validators, which Buterin considers to be low-risk, and overloading social consensus, which he identifies as high-risk. Reusing validators involves utilizing Ethereum validators in different contexts without jeopardizing the network's stability. On the other hand, overloading social consensus refers to attempts to enlist Ethereum's social consensus for applications that extend beyond the protocol's intended scope.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin provides various examples to illustrate this distinction. He mentions scenarios such as leveraging Ethereum validator status for social network verification, demonstrating the low-risk nature of reusing validators. However, he cautions against situations where Ethereum social consensus is recruited to resolve external disputes, highlighting the potential fragility and risks associated with such practices.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ethereum co-founder discusses the implications of extending Ethereum's consensus beyond its intended purpose. He points out that when a blockchain attempts to incorporate real-world information and becomes entangled in external conflicts, it risks compromising its core functionality. Buterin presents a cautionary tale set in 2034, where Ethereum's infrastructure supporting an ETH/BRL price oracle becomes a battleground for geopolitical disputes, leading to a chain split and division within the community.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">One of the key concerns raised by Buterin is the increased complexity and costs for validators if Ethereum's consensus is expanded to encompass additional responsibilities. Validators would need to manage and update multiple protocols, leading to potential inefficiencies and heightened risks. In this instance, externalizing dispute resolution to the Ethereum community could create an expectation for frequent chain splits, favoring larger projects over smaller ones and introducing too-big-to-fail dynamics.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin suggests case-by-case solutions to address these challenges. He proposes the development of decentralized oracles with emergency recovery strategies that do not rely on appealing to Ethereum's social consensus. Additionally, he advocates for the gradual integration of complex functionalities into the protocol itself, reducing the need for external decision-making.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ethereum and other generalized blockchains have continued to expand in economic and social significance, raising concerns about the misuse of social consensus which may arise from various factors. It is in this snense that blockchain industry must navigate these challenges to ensure the long-term stability and integrity of blockchain-based products.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sreeram Kannan, founder of Eigenlayer, opined on Buterin's measured approach and discouraged overdependence on Ethereum to resolve conflicts or errors in other applications. Kannan claimed that EigenLayer's restaking functionality forms a low-risk option to what Buterin has discussed, referring to a "third dimension" of restaking in terms of MEV (miner extractable value) and its relationship with restaking.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Buterin acknowledged the importance of addressing bugs and improving oracles, he also cautioned against relying (perhaps too much) on Ethereum's social consensus as the primary solution. Buterin argues for exploring alternate strategies and approaches to achieve security goals without overburdening Ethereum's consensus mechanism.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Preserving Ethereum's Balance</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The systemic risks of expanding Ethereum's social consensus beyond its core functionality were presented by Buterin through science fiction examples of external factors such as political events or price fluctuations, which may can divide the community and potentially lead to chain splits.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin emphasized the importance of maintaining Ethereum's purity as a mathematical construct and warns against incorporating real-world information into the blockchain's protocol. He suggests case-by-case solutions, including the development of decentralized oracles with alternative recovery strategies and careful consideration of the responsibilities imposed on validators. Buterin urged the community supporting Ethereum to find balance, preserve the blockchain's minimalism, and explore alternate approaches to address security challenges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin's recent blog post has raised concerns about the potential risks associated with expanding the scope of social consensus within the Ethereum network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In his post, Buterin highlights the importance of maintaining a clear distinction between reusing validators and overloading social consensus for ostensibly external purposes. Buterin nuances his arguments by emphasizing the need for caution and the preservation of Ethereum's core functionality.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Buterin expressed his reservations about certain proposals that aim to utilize Ethereum's consensus and social consensus for purposes beyond the network's core functionality. While acknowledging the well-intentioned nature of these ideas, Buterin emphasizes the need to carefully evaluate the potential risks such proposals may pose to the Ethereum ecosystem.</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Don't overload Ethereum's consensus:https://t.co/07tzyCrZcJ</p>
&mdash; vitalik.eth (@VitalikButerin) May 21, 2023

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Validator Reuse and Social Consensus</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The blog post focuses on distinguishing between two concepts: reusing validators, which Buterin considers to be low-risk, and overloading social consensus, which he identifies as high-risk. Reusing validators involves utilizing Ethereum validators in different contexts without jeopardizing the network's stability. On the other hand, overloading social consensus refers to attempts to enlist Ethereum's social consensus for applications that extend beyond the protocol's intended scope.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin provides various examples to illustrate this distinction. He mentions scenarios such as leveraging Ethereum validator status for social network verification, demonstrating the low-risk nature of reusing validators. However, he cautions against situations where Ethereum social consensus is recruited to resolve external disputes, highlighting the potential fragility and risks associated with such practices.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The Ethereum co-founder discusses the implications of extending Ethereum's consensus beyond its intended purpose. He points out that when a blockchain attempts to incorporate real-world information and becomes entangled in external conflicts, it risks compromising its core functionality. Buterin presents a cautionary tale set in 2034, where Ethereum's infrastructure supporting an ETH/BRL price oracle becomes a battleground for geopolitical disputes, leading to a chain split and division within the community.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">One of the key concerns raised by Buterin is the increased complexity and costs for validators if Ethereum's consensus is expanded to encompass additional responsibilities. Validators would need to manage and update multiple protocols, leading to potential inefficiencies and heightened risks. In this instance, externalizing dispute resolution to the Ethereum community could create an expectation for frequent chain splits, favoring larger projects over smaller ones and introducing too-big-to-fail dynamics.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin suggests case-by-case solutions to address these challenges. He proposes the development of decentralized oracles with emergency recovery strategies that do not rely on appealing to Ethereum's social consensus. Additionally, he advocates for the gradual integration of complex functionalities into the protocol itself, reducing the need for external decision-making.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ethereum and other generalized blockchains have continued to expand in economic and social significance, raising concerns about the misuse of social consensus which may arise from various factors. It is in this snense that blockchain industry must navigate these challenges to ensure the long-term stability and integrity of blockchain-based products.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sreeram Kannan, founder of Eigenlayer, opined on Buterin's measured approach and discouraged overdependence on Ethereum to resolve conflicts or errors in other applications. Kannan claimed that EigenLayer's restaking functionality forms a low-risk option to what Buterin has discussed, referring to a "third dimension" of restaking in terms of MEV (miner extractable value) and its relationship with restaking.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">While Buterin acknowledged the importance of addressing bugs and improving oracles, he also cautioned against relying (perhaps too much) on Ethereum's social consensus as the primary solution. Buterin argues for exploring alternate strategies and approaches to achieve security goals without overburdening Ethereum's consensus mechanism.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Preserving Ethereum's Balance</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The systemic risks of expanding Ethereum's social consensus beyond its core functionality were presented by Buterin through science fiction examples of external factors such as political events or price fluctuations, which may can divide the community and potentially lead to chain splits.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Buterin emphasized the importance of maintaining Ethereum's purity as a mathematical construct and warns against incorporating real-world information into the blockchain's protocol. He suggests case-by-case solutions, including the development of decentralized oracles with alternative recovery strategies and careful consideration of the responsibilities imposed on validators. Buterin urged the community supporting Ethereum to find balance, preserve the blockchain's minimalism, and explore alternate approaches to address security challenges.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
