<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 12:04:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>DeFi Under Attack: $1.5B Stolen in Top 5 Crypto Heists of 2022: Forbes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/defi-under-attack-1-5b-stolen-in-top-5-crypto-heists-of-2022-forbes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 05:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hacking]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230887</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/DeFi_Hacks.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/DeFi_Hacks.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[2022 turned out to be a great year for malicious actors.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Cryptocurrency firms struggled greatly in 2022, with multiple companies facing financial issues and bankruptcy. In addition to these challenges, over $3 billion was stolen from crypto projects this year, according to Forbes. These setbacks have caused turmoil in the industry and raised concerns about its stability.</p>
<p class="p2">According to the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninabambysheva/2022/12/28/over-3-billion-stolen-in-crypto-heists-here-are-the-eight-biggest/" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, crypto projects witnessed more than 125 hacks, and the top five heists (all involving decentralized finance (DeFi) protocols) accounted for $1.48 billion of the total amount stolen.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>DeFi Protocols Suffered the Most Losses in 2022</b></h2>
<p class="p2">Forbes highlighted that these top five biggest crypto heists range from cross-chain hacks, code exploits, and flash loan attacks.</p>
<p class="p2">The top five hacks are <span class="s1">Ronin Network’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/largest-crypto-hack-ever-ronin-bridge-exploited-for-600m-in-eth-and-usdc/" data-wpel-link="internal">$625 million exploit</a></span>, Wormhole’s $325 million theft, Nomad Bridge’s $190 million hack, Beanstalk Farms’ $182 million flash loan attack, and <span class="s1">Wintermute’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-market-maker-wintermute-hackers-drain-160m-profanity-bug-suspected/" data-wpel-link="internal">$160 million exploit</a></span>.</p>
<p class="p2">According to the report, DeFi hacks represent around 49% of the total amount stolen by hackers this year. This has led to reduced investment in the sector, as data from blockchain analytics firm Elliptic shows that DeFi protocols lost 75% of their total value locked (TVL) in 2022. However, that also accounts for the declining asset prices.</p>
<p class="p2">Data from DeFi Llama also shows that TVL from DeFi protocols dropped from 166.58 billion at the start of 2022 to $39 billion in December.</p>
<p class="p2">The Forbes report stated that cross-chain bridges, which enable the swap of tokens between blockchains, were the top target for hackers this year. Hackers stole nearly $2 billion from blockchain bridges, accounting for 70% of all crypto theft in 2022.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Hackers Love DeFi</b></h2>
<p class="p2">The reports also show that DeFi has become a favorite playground for hackers despite its uniqueness. But how is this happening?</p>
<p class="p2">Blockchain analytics platform Chainalysis reported that most thefts in the DeFi space are due to flawed codes, where smart contract errors have been used to steal money from protocols.</p>
<p class="p2">The report explained that because the DeFi ecosystem is open source, anyone, including hackers, can search for vulnerabilities or errors and plan exploits well in advance.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/defi-under-attack-1-5b-stolen-in-top-5-crypto-heists-of-2022-forbes/" rel="nofollow">DeFi Under Attack: $1.5B Stolen in Top 5 Crypto Heists of 2022: Forbes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bosses of Fraudulent South Korean Crypto Exchange V Global Jailed</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bosses-of-fraudulent-south-korean-crypto-exchange-v-global-jailed/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[South Korea]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231039</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/jail_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With the latest arrests, there are now seven V Global execs serving their sentences behind bars.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>South Korean authorities appear to have tightened their control over the digital asset space. As such, two high-ranking execs, named Mr.Yang and Mr. Oh of the fraudulent crypto exchange, V Global, were sentenced to eight years and three years, respectively, for their role in defrauding investors.</p>
<p>V Global reportedly lured investors by promising 300% returns. The exchange, which operated between July 2020 and April 2021, required new users to create accounts and deposit approximately 6 million Korean won initially with a supposedly guaranteed return of 18 million won.</p>
<h2>V Global&#8217;s Shenanigans</h2>
<p>During its one year of operation, V Global managed to rake in nearly 50,000 investors by promising users 12 million won in a commission similar to a pyramid scheme. Some executives were nabbed while most employees were under investigation for violating the Act on the Regulation of Similar Reception Act, fraud, and violation of the Door-to-Door Sales Act.</p>
<p>According to a local <a href="https://economist-co-kr.translate.goog/2022/12/26/stock/virtualCurrency/20221226173443373.html?_x_tr_sl=auto&amp;_x_tr_tl=en&amp;_x_tr_hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">report</a>, the judge from the 12th Criminal Division of the Suwon District Court was quoted saying.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;The defendants only trusted the V Global management team, evaded responsibility, and once the investigation began, they destroyed evidence and interfered with the investigation. The defendants acknowledged and reflected on the facts themselves, and many of the victims reinvested the proceeds from their existing investments, so the actual amount of damage was less than the legally defrauded amount&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Victims</h2>
<p>The estimated victim count stands somewhere near 52,000. Daegun law firm, which represents the V Global invest, rs earlier revealed that most of the victims were middle-aged or senior citizens who sought a &#8220;stable life after retirement.&#8221; At least one victim has died by suicide after being scammed.</p>
<p>The prosecutors had <a href="https://www.yna.co.kr/view/AKR20220112095900061?input=1195m" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">said</a>,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Most of the victims were middle-aged or senior citizens who dreamed of a stable life after retirement.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Seniors over 60 lost over $1.7 billion to fraud last year, according to the FBI&#8217;s 2021 Elder Fraud <a href="https://www.ic3.gov/Media/PDF/AnnualReport/2021_IC3ElderFraudReport.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">Report</a>. This marked a 74% increase from 2020. Meanwhile, this cohort of individuals lost $239 million in 2021 to investment schemes alone, comprising get-rich-quick scams involving digital assets or cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>Seniors are also targeted by crypto scammers because of their less knowledge of the matter.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bosses-of-fraudulent-south-korean-crypto-exchange-v-global-jailed/" rel="nofollow">Bosses of Fraudulent South Korean Crypto Exchange V Global Jailed</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here&#8217;s Why MicroStrategy Sold 704 Bitcoins on December 22</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-microstrategy-sold-704-bitcoins-on-december-22/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MicroStrategy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230880</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/microstrategy_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/04/microstrategy_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Here's why MicroStrategy sold some of its bitcoins for the first time since it started accumulating the crypto asset in 2020. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Publicly-traded business intelligence company MicroStrategy revealed that it sold part of its bitcoin stash on December 22 for tax purposes.</p>
<p class="p2">Although the firm later purchased more bitcoins, the sale defied its promise of never selling any portions of its BTC stash.</p>
<h2 class="p3"><b>MicroStrategy Sold BTC for Tax Benefits</b></h2>
<p class="p2">As reported earlier, MicroStrategy <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-adds-2500-btc-total-stack-now-132251-bitcoin/" data-wpel-link="internal">purchased</a> 2,395 bitcoins worth about $42.8 million between November 1, 2022, and December 21, 2022. The company then sold 704 BTC for about $11.8 million on December 22 before purchasing another 810 BTC two days later.</p>
<p class="p2">The firm&#8217;s filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) shows that the bitcoins were sold to generate tax benefits.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;MicroStrategy plans to carry back the capital losses resulting from this transaction against previous capital gains, to the extent such carrybacks are available under the federal income tax laws currently in effect, which may generate a tax benefit,&#8221; <a href="https://www.microstrategy.com/content/dam/website-assets/collateral/financial-documents/financial-document-archive/form-8-k-12-28-2022.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">the company said</span></a>.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>A Broken Promise</b></h2>
<p class="p2">In the summer of 2020, MicroStrategy began its culture of accumulating Bitcoin through its former CEO, Michael Saylor. Since then, the company has accumulated 132,251 BTC, valued at $2.2 billion at current market prices. This positions MicroStrategy as the largest holder of BTC among public companies, even though it sits on a massive unrealized loss of almost $2 billion.</p>
<p class="p2">After the 2021 bull run, the price of bitcoin and other crypto assets plummeted. The downtrend became more pronounced in 2022, but the bear market did not dampen MicroStrategy&#8217;s BTC buying spirit.</p>
<p class="p2">In <span class="s1">a January <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-20/studio-1-0-microstrategy-chairman-ceo-michael-saylor-video" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">interview</a></span> with Bloomberg, Saylor vowed that his company would not sell its bitcoin holdings.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;Never. No. We&#8217;re not sellers. [. . .] We&#8217;re only acquiring and holding bitcoin, right? That&#8217;s our strategy,&#8221; he said.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p2">That same month, Phong Le, who was MicroStrategy&#8217;s Chief Financial Officer at the time, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/microstrategy-cfo-confirms-buy-and-hold-bitcoin-strategy-amid-market-turbulence/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">declared</span></a> that the company would keep to a &#8220;buy and hold&#8221; policy.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/heres-why-microstrategy-sold-704-bitcoins-on-december-22/" rel="nofollow">Here&#8217;s Why MicroStrategy Sold 704 Bitcoins on December 22</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin Price to Consolidate or Retrace Even Further in 2023: Analysis</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-to-consolidate-or-retrace-even-further-in-2023-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231115</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/bears_cover-1.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales have become net sellers recently, which Santiment believes is an indicator of more price drops. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The price of bitcoin took a massive hit in 2022, dropping by more than 50% in 12 months. However, the crypto analytics platform Santiment believes there&#8217;s more bad news incoming in the new year.</p>
<p>The company based its rather bearish prediction on the BTC whales&#8217; activity.</p>
<h2>BTC Whales Are Net Sellers</h2>
<p>Santiment began its <a href="https://insights.santiment.net/read/examining-the-impact-of-btc-whale-behavior-on-price-trends-7156" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">2023 prediction analysis</a> by highlighting the significance of BTC whales&#8217; behavior for the asset&#8217;s price movements. This is somewhat expected since these types of investors &#8211; who own between 1,000 and 100,000 BTC in a single wallet &#8211; could have a bigger impact if they decide to sell or buy in bulk.</p>
<p>They were quite active on the buying front during the bull market in 2021, but most have changed their strategy in the totally different environment of 2022. The analytics resource confirmed this, asserting that bitcoin whales have become &#8220;net sellers&#8221; recently, &#8220;and the price has been following suit.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;It is with confidence that we can predict sideways or even lower prices for BTC in the next 6-12 months.&#8221; &#8211; Santiment said.</p></blockquote>
<figure id="attachment_231117" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231117" style="width: 1081px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231117" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales.jpg" alt="Bitcoin Whales' Ownings. Source: Santiment" width="1081" height="448" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales.jpg 1081w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales-300x124.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales-1024x424.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales-768x318.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Whales-50x21.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1081px) 100vw, 1081px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231117" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Whales&#8217; Holdings. Source: Santiment</figcaption></figure>
<p>The analysis added that BTC bottoms are typically found once the whales&#8217; activity has declined substantially. However, this is not the case now as there&#8217;re over 10,000 transactions from such investors daily at the moment, while the count was down to 1,200-2,500 during previous bottoms.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;This may mean that we need to wait for the average to drop further before we can conclude that even the big players are giving up.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>Santiment predicted that a price drop to as low as $12,200 is not out of the question since there&#8217;re two notable volume gaps between that level and $14,600 that whales might be paying attention to.</p>
<h2>Retail Investors Differ</h2>
<p>There&#8217;s a big difference between what retail and whales were doing during previous bear cycles and this one. Historically, the former used to get scared more easily and sell their bags, while the latter went on an accumulation spree.</p>
<p>However, the 2022 bear market has seen a wildly different landscape. Whales have been disposing of their assets, as mentioned above, while retail investors (holding between 0.1 and 10 BTC) refused to sell and actually kept buying.</p>
<p>As such, their cumulative holdings reached an all-time high of 15.9% of bitcoin&#8217;s total available supply in mid-October, as <em>CryptoPotato</em> <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-whales-at-3-year-low-retail-investors-at-ath/" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> at the time.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-price-to-consolidate-or-retrace-even-further-in-2023-analysis/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Price to Consolidate or Retrace Even Further in 2023: Analysis</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Customers Refuse to Share Account Info in Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-customers-refuse-to-share-account-info-in-lawsuit/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 15:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230997</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/coinbase_legal_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/coinbase_legal_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The plaintiffs are seeking at least $5 million in damages.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase customers, who had previously sued the crypto exchange over unauthorized crypto transfers, have continued to hold back their account information in a bid to block efforts to move their case to arbitration.</p>
<p>A renewed emergency motion filed in federal court revealed that the plaintiffs agreed to provide the necessary information encompassing emails, usernames, and Ethereum addresses, in exchange for a protective order.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.gand.306368/gov.uscourts.gand.306368.1.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">filing</a> with the US District Court for the Northern District of Georgia, the plaintiff alleged that $6,000 worth of cryptocurrency was drained from his wallet to an address he had never interacted with before with Coinbase facilitating the breach of his account. The filing also showed that the hackers managed to withdraw $1,000 from his bank account.</li>
<li>The San Francisco-based crypto exchange, however, maintained that the users did not agree on whether to include a provision in the protective order that says Coinbase hasn’t relinquished its right to arbitrate the dispute.</li>
<li>With the lack of users&#8217; account information, Coinbase claimed that it is not able to match plaintiffs to their respective arbitration agreements.</li>
<li>In its emergency motion last month, the company stated,</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Refusal to provide this basic information is an improper attempt to undermine Coinbase’s right to compel arbitration under the Federal Arbitration Act.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>In August, a group of crypto investors brought a lawsuit against Coinbase, alleging it for having lax security systems that exposed user accounts to hackers.</li>
<li>Led by Georgia resident George Kattula, over 100 Coinbase users sued the trading platform for arbitrarily locking them out from accessing their accounts and funds, thereby blocking them from offloading underperforming tokens. This allegedly led to financial losses, read to the filing.</li>
<li>From <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-facing-lawsuit-over-unlicensed-crypto-asset-sales/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">unlicensed</a> crypto asset sales to &#8220;materially <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-faces-another-lawsuit-what-is-the-exchange-accused-of-this-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">making</a> false and misleading statements&#8221; and more, Coinbase has faced several <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-slapped-with-another-lawsuit-for-crashing-during-market-volatility/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">lawsuits</a> this past year.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-customers-refuse-to-share-account-info-in-lawsuit/" rel="nofollow">Coinbase Customers Refuse to Share Account Info in Lawsuit</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Wash Trading Stats Depict Worrying Picture</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-wash-trading-stats-depict-worrying-picture/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 12:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231071</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/washing_machine_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/washing_machine_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Crypto platforms with 70% total reported volume of wash trading moved up by 46 positions in rankings.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s no secret that wash trading continues to plague the crypto market. A paper titled &#8220;Crypto Wash Trading,&#8221; published by the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), found that an overwhelming number of unregulated crypto exchanges account for a sizeable portion of wash trades.</p>
<p>The nonprofit research organization <a href="https://www.nber.org/system/files/working_papers/w30783/w30783.pdf" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">studied</a> 29 major exchanges, such as Binance, Coinbase, and Huobi, as well as lesser-known exchanges from a period of July 9th to November 3rd, 2019.</p>
<h2>Wash Trading in Crypto</h2>
<p>Based on the rank of third-party websites, representativeness, and API compatibility, the crypto exchanges were classified into Tier-1 (ranked in the top 700 in the finance/investment section of SimilarWeb and Tier-2 (all ranked outside the top 960). Trades of crypto-assets, such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and XRP, were studied.</p>
<p>The authors took multiple approaches to detect cases of wash trading that are not likely to be affected by &#8220;dispersed traders&#8217; strategies, exchange characteristics, or specificities of the asset class.&#8221;</p>
<p>It was found that wash trades accounted for as high as 77.5% of the total trading volume on unregulated exchanges, with a median of 79.1%. Meanwhile, wash trades on the twelve Tier-2 exchanges were observed to be more than 80% of the total trade volume, &#8220;which is still over 70% after accounting for observable exchange heterogeneity.&#8221;</p>
<p>The paper read:</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Our first key finding is that wash trading broadly exists on unregulated exchanges but is absent on regulated exchanges,” they wrote. “We consistently find anomalous trading patterns only on unregulated exchanges, with Tier-1 exchanges failing more than 20% of the tests and Tier-2 exchanges failing more than 60%.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<h2>Worrying Figures</h2>
<p>The study stated that wash trading in crypto exchanges is positively correlated with the prices of crypto-assets over the short term.</p>
<p>Moreover, wash trades occur less in platforms with &#8220;longer establishment histories and larger userbases&#8221; Contrarily, less popular exchanges have short-term incentives for wash trading without attracting scrutiny.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;While current business incentives and ranking systems fuel the rampant wash trading on unregulated exchanges, the regulated exchanges, having committed considerable resources towards compliance and license acquisition and facing severe punishments for market manipulation, do little wash trading&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>In the first quarter of 2020 alone, the NEBR study recorded a whopping $4.5 trillion in wash trading in spot markets, while the same for the derivatives market stood at $1.5 trillion.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-exchange-wash-trading-stats-depict-worrying-picture/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Exchange Wash Trading Stats Depict Worrying Picture</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin to End 2022 With a 65% Yearly Drop: Weekend Watch</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-to-end-2022-with-a-65-yearly-drop-weekend-watch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 09:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231121</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitcoin_Red_Candle.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/05/Bitcoin_Red_Candle.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[With only hours left in 2022, BTC is about to close its most painful year in terms of USD price action.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For better or worse, 2022 is about to end, and the bitcoin bulls are in a hurry to send this rather violent year packing. The asset&#8217;s price tumbled amid macroeconomic hurdles, industry collapses and scams, and everything in between.</p>
<p>The micro scale doesn&#8217;t give much hope either, as BTC slipped to a new 10-day low of way below $16,500 yesterday.</p>
<h2>Bitcoin&#8217;s Nightmare Year Comes to an End</h2>
<p>After the massive bull market of 2021, in which bitcoin skyrocketed to an all-time high of $69,000, all eyes were on the asset to double down and keep charting new peaks. Recall that many expected the $100,000 milestone to be next, hence the countless <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-laser-eyes-meme-not-a-coincidence-that-this-marked-a-local-top-for-bitcoin-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">laser-eye profile pictures</a> on Twitter.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency entered 2022 at just under $50,000, but only a few could have predicted what would happen next. The start of a &#8220;special military operation&#8221; (a.k.a. war) in the middle of Europe was just more fuel thrown into the massive fire that became the galloping inflation worldwide.</p>
<p>Crypto had numerous internal blows that started with the sudden <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/4-valuable-lessons-from-terras-collapse-opinion/" data-wpel-link="internal">collapse of the Terra ecosystem</a>. This exposed the highly intertwined nature of the industry. The domino effect took down other former giants such as 3AC, Celsius, Voyager, and others.</p>
<p>BTC&#8217;s price was falling amid all of this. As it finally seemed to have settled in November, then came the even more sudden <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/the-fall-of-sam-bankman-frieds-crypto-empire-a-timeline-of-ftxs-collapse/" data-wpel-link="internal">FTX debacle</a>. Another hit for bitcoin, which now dumped to consecutive two-year lows.</p>
<p>Despite trying to recover some ground, BTC has remained stuck well below the coveted $20,000 line. The past several weeks were quite uneventful in terms of price action as the asset keep struggling around $16,500. This means bitcoin will close the yearly candle with a 65% decline unless there&#8217;s some miracle about to happen in the next several hours.</p>
<p>As such, its market capitalization is still beneath $320 billion, while its dominance over the alts is calm at 40.1%.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231122" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231122" style="width: 1791px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231122" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13.png" alt="BTCUSD. Source: TradingView" width="1791" height="774" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13.png 1791w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13-300x130.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13-1024x443.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13-768x332.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13-1536x664.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/BTCUSD-13-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1791px) 100vw, 1791px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231122" class="wp-caption-text">BTCUSD. Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Solana Recovers 8%</h2>
<p>The alternative coins also suffered a lot in 2022, but we will focus on their most recent price moves now. Solana has been among the worst hit due to his exposure to Alameda and FTX. The past week brought a 25% <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-dips-below-16-5k-solana-down-23-weekly-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal">decline</a> in its price, but SOL has bounced off by 8% and trades closely to $10.</p>
<p>Most of the market is in green as well, with minor recovery attempts. ETH is still under $1,200, even with a 0.5% daily increase. Binance Coin, Ripple, Cardano, Dogecoin, Polygon, Polkadot, Tron, and Litecoin have jumped by up to 2%.</p>
<p>OKB is among the best performers, following a 4% daily increase. As a result, OKX&#8217;s native coin trades at $26. The overall crypto market cap is close to $800 billion.</p>
<figure id="attachment_231123" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-231123" style="width: 1849px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-231123" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11.jpg" alt="Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto" width="1849" height="742" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11.jpg 1849w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11-300x120.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11-1024x411.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11-768x308.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11-1536x616.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Allcoins-11-50x20.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1849px) 100vw, 1849px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-231123" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptocurrency Market Overview. Source: Quantify Crypto</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-to-end-2022-with-a-65-yearly-drop-weekend-watch/" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin to End 2022 With a 65% Yearly Drop: Weekend Watch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Huobi Reportedly Plans Mass Layoffs and Salary Cuts </title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-reportedly-plans-mass-layoffs-and-salary-cuts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 06:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Huobi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231072</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/HuobiStop.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/HuobiStop.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Huobi is reportedly about to join the crypto layoff trend, with plans to cut salaries. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Popular cryptocurrency exchange Huobi will lay off a significant portion of its workforce and cut the salaries of senior employees, according to Chinese reporter Colin Wu.</p>
<p class="p4">Last month, the exchange debunked speculation that it would slash its headcount because of the high number of employees at the company. But people familiar with the matter have confirmed that Huobi will move forward with the plan while also cutting the paychecks of its senior executives.</p>
<h2 class="p5"><b>Huobi to Cancel Yearly Bonuses </b></h2>
<p class="p4">According to the <a href="https://twitter.com/wublockchain/status/1608774459124781059" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a>, the company intends to reduce its team size from 1,200 people to 600 and 800 employees. In addition, the exchange will cancel its yearly bonuses.</p>
<p class="p4">Last month, the company <a href="https://www.huobi.com/support/en-us/detail/64925499541459" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">announced </span></a>that it would introduce a series of year-end campaigns, which started on December 18. These campaigns include events and competitions that allow users to win prizes in particular cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="p4">The yearly bonuses have abruptly ended as the firm intends to cancel the program. The move comes amid an intensified bear market, with many companies struggling to maintain profitability and stay afloat.</p>
<p class="p4">Huobi, founded in 2013, has not yet released an official statement on the matter. The news has caused speculation about the company&#8217;s health and the industry&#8217;s future at large.</p>
<p class="p4">The exchange is one of the oldest and key players in the crypto space after the fall of FTX. The company has offices in Singapore, Hong Kong, and South Korea and serves millions of customers worldwide.</p>
<h2 class="p5"><b>The Crypto Layoff Trends </b></h2>
<p class="p4">Huobi will not be the first crypto firm to slash its workforce since the start of the bear market. Several crypto exchanges, including <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/after-coinbase-and-cryptocom-bybit-lays-off-employees-amid-market-pullback/" data-wpel-link="internal">Coinbase</a> and CryptoCom, have laid off a significant percentage of their headcount to cut operational costs and stay afloat.</p>
<p class="p4">Earlier this month, digital asset platform Bybit <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bybit-to-lay-off-30-of-workforce-amid-colder-crypto-winter/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">said</span></a> it would slash 30% of its workforce due to &#8220;ongoing reorganization aimed at refocusing efforts, and reductions will be across the board.&#8221;</p>
<p class="p4">The company&#8217;s CEO Alex Harper noted that the firm is in good condition and will continue functioning as usual without disruptions.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/huobi-reportedly-plans-mass-layoffs-and-salary-cuts/" rel="nofollow">Huobi Reportedly Plans Mass Layoffs and Salary Cuts </a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfarms CEO Emiliano Grodzki Resigns Amid Industry Struggles</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/bitfarms-ceo-emiliano-grodzki-resigns-amid-industry-struggles/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=230876</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitfarms_Quit.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Bitfarms_Quit.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The mining firm has named president and COO Geoffrey Morphy as its new chief executive officer.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Emiliano Grodzki has stepped down as CEO of leading Bitcoin mining firm Bitfarms, joining a long list of crypto executives who resigned from their positions amid the bear market this year.</p>
<p class="p2">The mining company <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2022/12/29/2580596/0/en/Bitfarms-Promotes-Geoffrey-Morphy-to-Chief-Executive-Officer.html" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">named</a> Geoffrey Morphy as its new CEO, promoting him from his role as president and chief operating officer (COO).</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;Our foundational work over the last years built the strength and depth of skills we needed to navigate external factors. I&#8217;m even more optimistic today about Bitfarms&#8217; long-term prospects than when I joined the company back in 2020.&#8221; &#8211; Morphy said.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Grodzki to Remain as Board Director </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Grodzki and his partner Nicolas Bonta co-founded Bitfarms in Canada in 2017. Although Grodzki will no longer function as CEO, he will remain in the company as a Director on the Board.</p>
<p class="p2">Bonta will also function as the company&#8217;s new Chairman of the Board of Directors, moving from the position of Executive Chairman.</p>
<p class="p2">Commenting on Morphy&#8217;s new position, Bonta noted that the new CEO had played a significant role in developing the firm&#8217;s management team, corporate structure, governance and control, investor relations, and operations and strategy since he joined Bitfarm two years ago.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p2">&#8220;In a little over two years, Geoff helped transform Bitfarms from a purely Canadian company trading on the TSX Venture Exchange with five farms in Quebec to an international powerhouse traded on both the Nasdaq and TSX with ten operating farms in four countries driving over 4.4 exahash/second (EH/s) today. I am proud to announce Geoff as Bitfarms&#8217; new CEO and am confident his expanded leadership will continue to bring success to Bitfarms in the coming years,&#8221; he added.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 class="p3"><b>Crypto Mining Firms Struggle </b></h2>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, Bitfarms&#8217; leadership change comes as many executives are <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/these-crypto-executives-have-stepped-down-since-the-market-crash-in-may/" data-wpel-link="internal">stepping down</a> from their roles due to an intensifying bear market that has forced several top crypto firms, including miners, into financial issues and even bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">Last week, Bitcoin mining giant Core Scientific <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitcoin-miner-core-scientific-files-for-bankruptcy-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">became</a> the first publicly-traded crypto firm to declare insolvency despite receiving a $72 million loan offer from one of its creditors to avoid bankruptcy.</p>
<p class="p2">In September, crypto mining infrastructure Compute North filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in the United States, with the firm owning at least $500 million to at least 200 creditors.</p>
<p class="p1">Bitfarms has also had its fair share of financial struggles this year. In June, the miner <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-mining-giant-bitfarms-sells-3000-btc-and-adjusts-its-hodl-strategy/" data-wpel-link="internal">sold</a> almost half of its bitcoin stash to improve its liquidity. The company repaid $27 million of its debt last month to strengthen its balance sheet.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bitfarms-ceo-emiliano-grodzki-resigns-amid-industry-struggles/" rel="nofollow">Bitfarms CEO Emiliano Grodzki Resigns Amid Industry Struggles</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did SBF Just Cash Out $684K?</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/did-sbf-just-cash-out-684k/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Mandy Williams]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 22:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FTX Exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=231052</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/SamBankmanFried.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The FTX boss allegedly withdrew the funds via a non-KYC platform and Ren Protocol despite court restrictions.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p2">Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the disgraced founder and former CEO of bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX, has reportedly cashed out $684,000 worth of crypto assets despite court restrictions on spendings above $1,000.</p>
<p class="p2">On-chain DeFi analyst BowTiedIguana took to Twitter to <a href="https://twitter.com/BowTiedIguana/status/1608653434387050496" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1">unravel</span></a> the location where SBF transferred the funds.</p>
<h2>Following the Money Trail</h2>
<p class="p2">After Bankman-Fried’s <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sam-bankman-fried-released-on-a-250m-bail-can-stay-at-parents-house/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span class="s1">$250 million bail</span></a> last week, the FTX boss sent all the ether (ETH) in his public wallet to a<a href="https://etherscan.io/txs?a=0x7386df2Cf7e9776bCE0708072c27d6a7135D51CB&amp;p=1" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span class="s1"> new wallet address</span></a> – 0x7386df2Cf7e9776bCE0708072c27d6a7135D51CB.</p>
<p class="p2">Some hours later, $367,000 worth of cryptocurrencies were transferred from 32 addresses owned by SBF’s trading firm Alameda Research to the same wallet.</p>
<p class="p2">The address received another $322,000 from other wallets, bringing the total assets to roughly $689,000.</p>
<p class="p2">The wallet address, 0x7386, then sent $629,000 worth of tokens from its entire holding into<span class="s1"> another <a href="https://etherscan.io/txs?a=0x64e9B9cD74A46f71e7631CB033afA6E7849a8683" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">wallet address</a></span> – 0x64e9B9cD74A46f71e7631CB033afA6E7849a8683.</p>
<p class="p2">Eleven wallet addresses labeled as Alameda-owned accounts sent a total of $1 million into the same wallet address, 0x64e9. Five transactions of less than 51 ETH were then conducted, as they were sent to a freshly created wallet address.</p>
<h2>Funds Transferred to Seychelles Exchange</h2>
<p class="p2">The funds were then transferred to a Seychelles-based crypto exchange that does not conduct Know-Your-Customer (KYC) activity for users.</p>
<p class="p2">Parts of the funds were also moved through the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ren-protocol-users-face-potential-losses-during-post-alameda-wind-down/" data-wpel-link="internal">Ren protocol</a> and subsequently to the Bitcoin network. The Ren protocol is a gateway that allows anyone to send BTC, ZEC, and BCH across blockchains. Alameda acquired the platform in February 2021.</p>
<p class="p2">Three sets of 200,000 USDT were also transferred to FixedFloat, a self-custodian crypto exchange that facilitates transactions through its Lightning Network.</p>
<p class="p2">It is still unclear if SBF was truly behind the withdrawals, but it is only a matter of time before U.S. attorneys begin to probe the transactions.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Bahamian Regulators Seize $3.5B From FTX</h2>
<p class="p2">Meanwhile, the Bahamas authorities have <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/bahamas-seized-3-5-billion-from-ftx-to-keep-them-from-vanishing/" data-wpel-link="internal">confiscated</a> $3.5 billion worth of assets belonging to FTX Digital Markets, the Bahamian subdivision of the bankrupt crypto exchange, to prevent the funds from vanishing.</p>
<p class="p2">According to regulators, the funds will be returned to investors at the court’s discretion.<span class="Apple-converted-space"> </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-sbf-just-cash-out-684k/" rel="nofollow">Did SBF Just Cash Out $684K?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
