<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:31:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Revolutionary Crowdfunding Platform For AI Startups, InQubeta launches QUBE Presale]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/revolutionary-crowdfunding-platform-for-ai-startups-inqubeta-launches-qube-presale</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_8_9434598398_1685560349yEC6RXWtSj.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_8_9434598398_1685560349yEC6RXWtSj.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_8_9434598398_1685560349yEC6RXWtSj.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 21:18:27 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/revolutionary-crowdfunding-platform-for-ai-startups-inqubeta-launches-qube-presale</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Mahe Island, Beau Vallon, Seychelles, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta, a pioneering platform in the crypto crowdfunding space, is thrilled to announce the launch of its innovative ecosystem powered by the QUBE token. Designed to revolutionize the investment landscape for AI startups, InQubeta offers users the opportunity to participate in crowdfunding campaigns in it's NFT marketplace.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta stands out in the blockchain industry by providing a dynamic environment for users to back and invest in AI startups using QUBE tokens. Through the platform, each listed startup is transformed into an NFT and fractionalized, allowing investors of all sizes to participate. Upon successful funding, investors can share in the startup's profits through returns paid in QUBE tokens. The entire process is transparent, secure, and backed by the power of blockchain technology.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To ensure the utmost quality and value for investors, InQubeta employs rigorous vetting procedures for startups seeking listing on their NFT marketplace. Additionally, the platform equips investors with valuable resources, including insights from experienced stakeholders and AI technology experts, enabling informed decision-making through comprehensive research and analysis.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">At the core of InQubeta's ecosystem lies the QUBE token, an ERC-20 utility and governance token. QUBE grants holders access to invest in AI startup projects listed on the platform's NFT marketplace. With deflationary properties, QUBE tokens provide long-term potential benefits to investors through a 2% buy-and-sell tax allocated to a burn wallet and a 5% sell tax directed to a reward pool. Moreover, QUBE token holders actively participate in governance, shaping the future of InQubeta by contributing to key proposals.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Security is a paramount concern, and InQubeta takes it seriously. The QUBE token has undergone  an extensive security audits by leading firm Hacken and KYC verification by Block Audit, providing peace of mind to investors and ensuring users' funds are protected from potential breaches.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Currently, the QUBE token is available in its presale phase, offering investors the opportunity to purchase tokens at the current lowest possible price directly from the official InQubeta website. The presale is designed to be investor-friendly, with a minimum investment amount of $50, making QUBE tokens accessible to everyone. Supported payment options include but are not limited to ETH, USDT, BNB, BUSD, and BTC. Following the presale, QUBE token holders can stake their assets via InQubeta's staking dapp, to earn potential rewards from the buy and sell taxes allocated to the reward pool.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta's cutting-edge crowdfunding ecosystem, impressive tokenomics, and commitment to security position it for success in the evolving landscape of AI investments.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To join the InQubeta presale, please visit inqubeta.ai</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About InQubeta</p><p>InQubeta is a crypto crowdfunding NFT marketplace that enables users to invest in AI startup projects using the QUBE token. Through its innovative platform, InQubeta aims to revolutionize the investment landscape for AI startups, providing investors a transparent and rewarding experience.</p>ContactInQubeta TeamInQubetainfo@inqubeta.ai]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mahe Island, Beau Vallon, Seychelles, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta, a pioneering platform in the crypto crowdfunding space, is thrilled to announce the launch of its innovative ecosystem powered by the QUBE token. Designed to revolutionize the investment landscape for AI startups, InQubeta offers users the opportunity to participate in crowdfunding campaigns in it's NFT marketplace.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta stands out in the blockchain industry by providing a dynamic environment for users to back and invest in AI startups using QUBE tokens. Through the platform, each listed startup is transformed into an NFT and fractionalized, allowing investors of all sizes to participate. Upon successful funding, investors can share in the startup's profits through returns paid in QUBE tokens. The entire process is transparent, secure, and backed by the power of blockchain technology.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To ensure the utmost quality and value for investors, InQubeta employs rigorous vetting procedures for startups seeking listing on their NFT marketplace. Additionally, the platform equips investors with valuable resources, including insights from experienced stakeholders and AI technology experts, enabling informed decision-making through comprehensive research and analysis.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">At the core of InQubeta's ecosystem lies the QUBE token, an ERC-20 utility and governance token. QUBE grants holders access to invest in AI startup projects listed on the platform's NFT marketplace. With deflationary properties, QUBE tokens provide long-term potential benefits to investors through a 2% buy-and-sell tax allocated to a burn wallet and a 5% sell tax directed to a reward pool. Moreover, QUBE token holders actively participate in governance, shaping the future of InQubeta by contributing to key proposals.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Security is a paramount concern, and InQubeta takes it seriously. The QUBE token has undergone  an extensive security audits by leading firm Hacken and KYC verification by Block Audit, providing peace of mind to investors and ensuring users' funds are protected from potential breaches.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">Currently, the QUBE token is available in its presale phase, offering investors the opportunity to purchase tokens at the current lowest possible price directly from the official InQubeta website. The presale is designed to be investor-friendly, with a minimum investment amount of $50, making QUBE tokens accessible to everyone. Supported payment options include but are not limited to ETH, USDT, BNB, BUSD, and BTC. Following the presale, QUBE token holders can stake their assets via InQubeta's staking dapp, to earn potential rewards from the buy and sell taxes allocated to the reward pool.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">InQubeta's cutting-edge crowdfunding ecosystem, impressive tokenomics, and commitment to security position it for success in the evolving landscape of AI investments.</p><p class="ql-align-justify">To join the InQubeta presale, please visit inqubeta.ai</p><p class="ql-align-justify">About InQubeta</p><p>InQubeta is a crypto crowdfunding NFT marketplace that enables users to invest in AI startup projects using the QUBE token. Through its innovative platform, InQubeta aims to revolutionize the investment landscape for AI startups, providing investors a transparent and rewarding experience.</p>ContactInQubeta TeamInQubetainfo@inqubeta.ai]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[CryptoMatch: The Future Of Web3 Professional Networking Powered By AI]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/cryptomatch-the-future-of-web3-professional-networking-powered-by-ai</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-2.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-2.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1920x1080-2.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adrian Barkley]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/cryptomatch-the-future-of-web3-professional-networking-powered-by-ai</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The web3 industry is booming and changing fast, bringing in cool new ways to tackle modern problems with the help of AI. These AI-powered tools make things like communication, collaboration, and getting stuff done a breeze, opening up all sorts of amazing opportunities we never had before.</p>
<p>However, here's the thing: no industry can thrive without networking, and web3 is no different. So, if you want to stay ahead of the game, you&rsquo;ve got to build a strong network and connect with other pros in the field.</p>
<p>Stats show that networking is the secret sauce for 88% of successful professionals who've climbed the career ladder. And guess what? 61% of these pros believe that reaching out to their network creates awesome opportunities. Plus, networking conferences are like treasure troves for event planners, with 66% saying they're the best way to find new clients.</p>
<p>A solid network of contacts in the web3 industry can make a huge difference. It opens doors to exciting possibilities and gives you access to capital, resources, and expertise that would otherwise be tough to find. You can team up with awesome people, bridge gaps between different parts of the industry, and make your professional dreams come true.</p>
<p>Sure, LinkedIn and other networking platforms are helpful, but they lack that personal touch we all crave. They're not exactly built for the highly technical and specialized world of web3. And let's face it, not everyone has the guts to reach out to strangers or get warm introductions. Looking for the perfect fit isn't easy, and networking can be time-consuming and daunting.</p>
<p>It doesn't end there! Web3 experts struggle to find trustworthy projects and individuals through exclusive communities and private events. They rely on word of mouth to find reliable contacts, but sometimes it doesn't work. That's why there should be a web3-specific network grounded in trust and professionalism, making it easier to connect with blockchain professionals.</p>
<p>This is where web3-centric, AI-driven platforms like CryptoMatch come in handy. Using embedded OpenAI technology, CryptoMatch pairs C-level executives, developers, investors, and founders, while also taking on a warm introduction role. This is the ideal way to start a conversation with web3 people &ndash; finally no more awkward silences or embarrassing blunders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, it builds community and connection within a fragmented web3 ecosystem. CryptoMatch links users to a network of more than 8,000 blockchain pros from 20 countries. It has arranged upwards of 12,000 successful meetings since its launch, and continues to be the go-to platform for web3 professionals worldwide. It has partnered with leading industry names, such as xDAO, Everscale, AIBC Conf, EpicWeb3, Guild DAO, Pontem Network, etc. There are a bunch of web3 products, communities, and DAOs signing up as well. &nbsp;</p>
<p>To put it another way, CryptoMatch is a web3 crowd-puller where founders can collaborate, or top-level analysts, advisors or marketers can find rip-roaring projects to work on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>From an investor's perspective, CryptoMatch helps VCs find the highest-quality startups to invest in. They can talk directly to founders about the ventures of interest and learn more about them. This makes investment decisions a great deal more informed.</p>
<p>Even the most experienced pros can use CryptoMatch to expand their networks, boost their skills, and grow their client base. Even if you're a crypto noob, CryptoMatch can help you learn and grow by connecting you with peers and mentors.</p>
<p>The bottom line is, CryptoMatch is the real deal when it comes to making meaningful connections in the web3 space. Therefore, if you're looking to hit a home run in the crypto space or open up new vistas, CryptoMatch is the platform for you. Start making valuable connections with CryptoMatch today!</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The web3 industry is booming and changing fast, bringing in cool new ways to tackle modern problems with the help of AI. These AI-powered tools make things like communication, collaboration, and getting stuff done a breeze, opening up all sorts of amazing opportunities we never had before.</p>
<p>However, here's the thing: no industry can thrive without networking, and web3 is no different. So, if you want to stay ahead of the game, you&rsquo;ve got to build a strong network and connect with other pros in the field.</p>
<p>Stats show that networking is the secret sauce for 88% of successful professionals who've climbed the career ladder. And guess what? 61% of these pros believe that reaching out to their network creates awesome opportunities. Plus, networking conferences are like treasure troves for event planners, with 66% saying they're the best way to find new clients.</p>
<p>A solid network of contacts in the web3 industry can make a huge difference. It opens doors to exciting possibilities and gives you access to capital, resources, and expertise that would otherwise be tough to find. You can team up with awesome people, bridge gaps between different parts of the industry, and make your professional dreams come true.</p>
<p>Sure, LinkedIn and other networking platforms are helpful, but they lack that personal touch we all crave. They're not exactly built for the highly technical and specialized world of web3. And let's face it, not everyone has the guts to reach out to strangers or get warm introductions. Looking for the perfect fit isn't easy, and networking can be time-consuming and daunting.</p>
<p>It doesn't end there! Web3 experts struggle to find trustworthy projects and individuals through exclusive communities and private events. They rely on word of mouth to find reliable contacts, but sometimes it doesn't work. That's why there should be a web3-specific network grounded in trust and professionalism, making it easier to connect with blockchain professionals.</p>
<p>This is where web3-centric, AI-driven platforms like CryptoMatch come in handy. Using embedded OpenAI technology, CryptoMatch pairs C-level executives, developers, investors, and founders, while also taking on a warm introduction role. This is the ideal way to start a conversation with web3 people &ndash; finally no more awkward silences or embarrassing blunders.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additionally, it builds community and connection within a fragmented web3 ecosystem. CryptoMatch links users to a network of more than 8,000 blockchain pros from 20 countries. It has arranged upwards of 12,000 successful meetings since its launch, and continues to be the go-to platform for web3 professionals worldwide. It has partnered with leading industry names, such as xDAO, Everscale, AIBC Conf, EpicWeb3, Guild DAO, Pontem Network, etc. There are a bunch of web3 products, communities, and DAOs signing up as well. &nbsp;</p>
<p>To put it another way, CryptoMatch is a web3 crowd-puller where founders can collaborate, or top-level analysts, advisors or marketers can find rip-roaring projects to work on.&nbsp;</p>
<p>From an investor's perspective, CryptoMatch helps VCs find the highest-quality startups to invest in. They can talk directly to founders about the ventures of interest and learn more about them. This makes investment decisions a great deal more informed.</p>
<p>Even the most experienced pros can use CryptoMatch to expand their networks, boost their skills, and grow their client base. Even if you're a crypto noob, CryptoMatch can help you learn and grow by connecting you with peers and mentors.</p>
<p>The bottom line is, CryptoMatch is the real deal when it comes to making meaningful connections in the web3 space. Therefore, if you're looking to hit a home run in the crypto space or open up new vistas, CryptoMatch is the platform for you. Start making valuable connections with CryptoMatch today!</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ex-Coinbase Manager Agrees to Settle SEC Insider Trading Charges]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ex-coinbase-manager-agrees-to-settle-sec-insider-trading-charges</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-1920.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:41:18 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/ex-coinbase-manager-agrees-to-settle-sec-insider-trading-charges</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The SEC announced that former Coinbase product manager Ishan Wahi and his brother agreed to settle charges against them that they engaged in insider trading. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that Ishan Wahi, a former Coinbase Global product manager, and his brother, Nikhil Wahi, agreed to settle charges that they engaged in insider trading relating to at least nine crypto asset securities.</p>
Wahi Brothers Agree to Settle Civil Charges
<p>The securities watchdog said the Wahi brothers agreed to settle civil charges that they engaged in a scheme to trade ahead of multiple announcements relating to at least nine crypto asset securities, which would be made available on Coinbase&rsquo;s platform.</p>
<p>Ishan Wahi was arrested in 2022 and charged with insider trading after it emerged that he was feeding his brother Nikhil, and another individual, with information about crypto assets to be listed on Coinbase.</p>
<p>Authorities investigating the matter said Wahi&rsquo;s brother and a fellow conspirator, Sameer Ramani, made over $1 million between June 2021 and April 2022 with the information provided by Ishan Wahi.</p>
<p>Ishan Wahi was sentenced to two years in prison after pleading guilty to charges of conspiracy to commit wire fraud.</p>
<p>Nikhil Wahi was sentenced to 10 months in prison in January and was ordered to pay a fine of $892,500 after pleading guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit wire fraud.</p>
SEC Argues Digital Assets Should Fall Under Its Oversight
<p>The SEC has grown increasingly active in policy in the crypto industry, filing numerous lawsuits against several major crypto-related firms since the start of 2023. Reuters reports that in the lawsuits, the agency has argued that many digital assets are securities and fall under its oversight, including the case against the Wahi brothers.</p>
<p>During pleading to the criminal charges, Ishan Wahi stated that he did not believe any of the tokens in question were securities.</p>
<p>Coinbase is not a party to the SEC allegations against the Wahi brothers, but the firm filed an amicus brief supporting the Wahi brother&rsquo;s motion to dismiss the SEC&rsquo;s case.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The SEC announced that former Coinbase product manager Ishan Wahi and his brother agreed to settle charges against them that they engaged in insider trading. </p>
<p>On Tuesday, the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) announced that Ishan Wahi, a former Coinbase Global product manager, and his brother, Nikhil Wahi, agreed to settle charges that they engaged in insider trading relating to at least nine crypto asset securities.</p>
Wahi Brothers Agree to Settle Civil Charges
<p>The securities watchdog said the Wahi brothers agreed to settle civil charges that they engaged in a scheme to trade ahead of multiple announcements relating to at least nine crypto asset securities, which would be made available on Coinbase&rsquo;s platform.</p>
<p>Ishan Wahi was arrested in 2022 and charged with insider trading after it emerged that he was feeding his brother Nikhil, and another individual, with information about crypto assets to be listed on Coinbase.</p>
<p>Authorities investigating the matter said Wahi&rsquo;s brother and a fellow conspirator, Sameer Ramani, made over $1 million between June 2021 and April 2022 with the information provided by Ishan Wahi.</p>
<p>Ishan Wahi was sentenced to two years in prison after pleading guilty to charges of conspiracy to commit wire fraud.</p>
<p>Nikhil Wahi was sentenced to 10 months in prison in January and was ordered to pay a fine of $892,500 after pleading guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit wire fraud.</p>
SEC Argues Digital Assets Should Fall Under Its Oversight
<p>The SEC has grown increasingly active in policy in the crypto industry, filing numerous lawsuits against several major crypto-related firms since the start of 2023. Reuters reports that in the lawsuits, the agency has argued that many digital assets are securities and fall under its oversight, including the case against the Wahi brothers.</p>
<p>During pleading to the criminal charges, Ishan Wahi stated that he did not believe any of the tokens in question were securities.</p>
<p>Coinbase is not a party to the SEC allegations against the Wahi brothers, but the firm filed an amicus brief supporting the Wahi brother&rsquo;s motion to dismiss the SEC&rsquo;s case.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tether (USDT) bought some Bitcoin, is Tradecurve a better bet for investors]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-usdt-bought-some-bitcoin-is-tradecurve-a-better-bet-for-investors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-80.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-80.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-2-80.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-usdt-bought-some-bitcoin-is-tradecurve-a-better-bet-for-investors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Tether (USDT) announced a staggering $1.48 billion in profits in Q1 2023 and announced it would buy Bitcoin (BTC) regularly with 15% of net profits. Tether (USDT) has already added a whopping $1.5 billion of BTC to its reserves, and traders view this sustained buy pressure positively. With Tether (USDT) supporting Bitcoin (BTC), it allows the rest of the market to move upwards, and analysts have put the spotlight on Tradecruve (TCRV), a new AI-specialized trading platform they believe will surge 5,000% in the coming weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) Democtaziing Access to Financial MarketsTradecurve reimagines the trading experience and powers a futuristic experience, all while users maintain anonymity. No KYC is required to use the platform, and investors can begin trading with just an email account. The protocol blends the best of decentralized trading platforms (self-custody &amp; anonymity) with the best features of centralized trading platforms (institutional-level liquidity) to deliver the ultimate trading experience. Tradecurve goes beyond a regular derivatives service provider with an integrated Metaverse trading academy, social trading features such as copy trading, and its artificial intelligence trading algorithms. These features are unlockable through token ownership, causing analysts to forecast massive buy pressure for $TCRV. They further stated it could quickly 50X in the coming weeks before the presale closes.The platform will introduce Proof of Reserves to ensure legitimacy. And detailed in the whitepaper is a thorough plan for registering 100,000 traders within three months of operation. With 500:1 leverage, low latency trades, and access to multiple markets, including forex, commodities, stocks, and cryptos from a single interface, Tradecurve has democratized access to financial markets for millions of retail investors globally and will grow in line with this outstanding value proposition. A pioneering derivatives service provider and an investment opportunity investors would be foolish to miss.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tether (USDT) Adds Bitcoin to its ReservesTether (USDT) initially launched in 2014 and is the crypto market&rsquo;s largest stablecoin ranked via market cap. Tether (USDT) was a beneficiary of the USDC depeg event as traders, users, and even whales rotated from USDC to Tether (USDT). Tether (USDT) has been doing excellent business as the FED has raised interest rates. Tether (USDT) holds billions and billions of dollars in short-dated treasury bills to back the value of Tether (USDT), which can be sold when investors want to exchange Tether (USDT) at a 1:1 ratio for dollars.As short-dated yields hit decade highs, Tether (USDT) has been clipping coupons and pocketing interest payments from the United States. Tether (USDT) has now decided to use some of this funding to buy Bitcoin (BTC), and this steady buy pressure should help markets rise. Seasoned investors realize that this buy pressure will bolster markets in general. Hence, the best strategy for high returns is to ignore Bitcoin (BTC) and focus on altcoins, especially those with solid fundamentals such as Tradecurve.&nbsp; Find out more about the Tradecurve presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale:https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tether (USDT) announced a staggering $1.48 billion in profits in Q1 2023 and announced it would buy Bitcoin (BTC) regularly with 15% of net profits. Tether (USDT) has already added a whopping $1.5 billion of BTC to its reserves, and traders view this sustained buy pressure positively. With Tether (USDT) supporting Bitcoin (BTC), it allows the rest of the market to move upwards, and analysts have put the spotlight on Tradecruve (TCRV), a new AI-specialized trading platform they believe will surge 5,000% in the coming weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) Democtaziing Access to Financial MarketsTradecurve reimagines the trading experience and powers a futuristic experience, all while users maintain anonymity. No KYC is required to use the platform, and investors can begin trading with just an email account. The protocol blends the best of decentralized trading platforms (self-custody &amp; anonymity) with the best features of centralized trading platforms (institutional-level liquidity) to deliver the ultimate trading experience. Tradecurve goes beyond a regular derivatives service provider with an integrated Metaverse trading academy, social trading features such as copy trading, and its artificial intelligence trading algorithms. These features are unlockable through token ownership, causing analysts to forecast massive buy pressure for $TCRV. They further stated it could quickly 50X in the coming weeks before the presale closes.The platform will introduce Proof of Reserves to ensure legitimacy. And detailed in the whitepaper is a thorough plan for registering 100,000 traders within three months of operation. With 500:1 leverage, low latency trades, and access to multiple markets, including forex, commodities, stocks, and cryptos from a single interface, Tradecurve has democratized access to financial markets for millions of retail investors globally and will grow in line with this outstanding value proposition. A pioneering derivatives service provider and an investment opportunity investors would be foolish to miss.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Tether (USDT) Adds Bitcoin to its ReservesTether (USDT) initially launched in 2014 and is the crypto market&rsquo;s largest stablecoin ranked via market cap. Tether (USDT) was a beneficiary of the USDC depeg event as traders, users, and even whales rotated from USDC to Tether (USDT). Tether (USDT) has been doing excellent business as the FED has raised interest rates. Tether (USDT) holds billions and billions of dollars in short-dated treasury bills to back the value of Tether (USDT), which can be sold when investors want to exchange Tether (USDT) at a 1:1 ratio for dollars.As short-dated yields hit decade highs, Tether (USDT) has been clipping coupons and pocketing interest payments from the United States. Tether (USDT) has now decided to use some of this funding to buy Bitcoin (BTC), and this steady buy pressure should help markets rise. Seasoned investors realize that this buy pressure will bolster markets in general. Hence, the best strategy for high returns is to ignore Bitcoin (BTC) and focus on altcoins, especially those with solid fundamentals such as Tradecurve.&nbsp; Find out more about the Tradecurve presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale:https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Huobi Joins HKVAC as First Member to Fuel Hong Kong's Ambition to be a Global Web3 Hub]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/huobi-joins-hkvac-as-first-member-to-fuel-hong-kongs-ambition-to-be-a-global-web3-hub</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/eeee_1685546476ZMKhrgEN6E.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/eeee_1685546476ZMKhrgEN6E.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/eeee_1685546476ZMKhrgEN6E.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:25:25 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/huobi-joins-hkvac-as-first-member-to-fuel-hong-kongs-ambition-to-be-a-global-web3-hub</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi announced that it became the first member of Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC). By joining HKVAC, an organization dedicated to providing credit ratings for crypto asset exchanges and trading products. Huobi aims to develop a venture capital database that caters to the needs of the market, actively engage in educating the public about crypto investments, and offer Hong Kong traders a "one-stop" crypto asset trading service. Ultimately, with Huobi Hong Kong (Huobi HK) as the pivot, Huobi is committed to supporting Hong Kong in its efforts to become a global Web3 hub.</p><p>HKVAC is said to be a collaboration of many crypto industry players, including exchanges, institutional investors, and Hong Kong-licensed rating agencies. It was established primarily to enhance the industry's capabilities in security risk management and to assist the Central Government and Hong Kong's local authorities in building a world-leading hub for virtual asset and digital finance. At the same time, it commits itself to creating a safe, open and transparent environment for crypto asset investments under the guidance of "Hong Kong's new crypto regulations.&rdquo; It will also promote the acceptance and recognition of crypto assets by helping the public gain systematic, correct and secure knowledge about crypto investments.</p><p>As an exchange that always prioritizes "global security and compliance operations", Huobi has maintained the best industry record of 100% functionality and no security incidents for ten years since its inception. Huobi will bring its expertise in security technology and its compliant, standardized processes to HKVAC as a reference. Together they can provide risk management indicators to investors in the industry and set strict rating standards to evaluate existing exchanges, so that more crypto investors can have a clear understanding of the risk level of their investments. This will accelerate the creation of a safe and friendly crypto environment in Hong Kong.</p><p>In addition, as a pioneer in establishing itself as a Web3 gateway, Huobi will join hands with HKVAC to continuously pursue multi-dimensional collaborations and advancements in technology, data, and ecosystem development. Together, Huobi and HKVAC will facilitate the application of Web3 infrastructure and build a bridge between the real world and the realm of Web3 to encourage wider acceptance and participation in Web3. These endeavors will drive the development of Hong Kong's Web 3.0 industry and serve as the stepping stones on Hong Kong's way to becoming a global hub for Web 3.0 (the third-generation Internet).</p><p>As previously reported, Huobi will officially launch Huobi HK. Starting June 1, Huobi HK is expected to deliver unparalleled trading experiences to Web3 users through its wide range of products. Users can trade cryptocurrencies like BTC, ETH, TRX, LTC, BCH, DOGE, SHIB, BTT, SOL, ADA, and other major cryptocurrencies listed in the independent index on Huobi HK.</p><p>A Huobi representative said that joining HKVAC will boost Huobi's business in Hong Kong and lay the foundation for future operations that comply with laws and regulations. Meanwhile, Huobi intends to work with various parties in the industry to build the ecosystem of Web3 under the premise of policy compliance. It will start by establishing itself as a Web3 gateway to promote the development of Web3 in Hong Kong. Hopefully, Huobi will be granted a cryptocurrency trading license in Hong Kong in the near future, so that it can collaborate with the Hong Kong government, regulators, and other institutions to create a better crypto market in the region.</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Huobi announced that it became the first member of Hong Kong Virtual Asset Consortium (HKVAC). By joining HKVAC, an organization dedicated to providing credit ratings for crypto asset exchanges and trading products. Huobi aims to develop a venture capital database that caters to the needs of the market, actively engage in educating the public about crypto investments, and offer Hong Kong traders a "one-stop" crypto asset trading service. Ultimately, with Huobi Hong Kong (Huobi HK) as the pivot, Huobi is committed to supporting Hong Kong in its efforts to become a global Web3 hub.</p><p>HKVAC is said to be a collaboration of many crypto industry players, including exchanges, institutional investors, and Hong Kong-licensed rating agencies. It was established primarily to enhance the industry's capabilities in security risk management and to assist the Central Government and Hong Kong's local authorities in building a world-leading hub for virtual asset and digital finance. At the same time, it commits itself to creating a safe, open and transparent environment for crypto asset investments under the guidance of "Hong Kong's new crypto regulations.&rdquo; It will also promote the acceptance and recognition of crypto assets by helping the public gain systematic, correct and secure knowledge about crypto investments.</p><p>As an exchange that always prioritizes "global security and compliance operations", Huobi has maintained the best industry record of 100% functionality and no security incidents for ten years since its inception. Huobi will bring its expertise in security technology and its compliant, standardized processes to HKVAC as a reference. Together they can provide risk management indicators to investors in the industry and set strict rating standards to evaluate existing exchanges, so that more crypto investors can have a clear understanding of the risk level of their investments. This will accelerate the creation of a safe and friendly crypto environment in Hong Kong.</p><p>In addition, as a pioneer in establishing itself as a Web3 gateway, Huobi will join hands with HKVAC to continuously pursue multi-dimensional collaborations and advancements in technology, data, and ecosystem development. Together, Huobi and HKVAC will facilitate the application of Web3 infrastructure and build a bridge between the real world and the realm of Web3 to encourage wider acceptance and participation in Web3. These endeavors will drive the development of Hong Kong's Web 3.0 industry and serve as the stepping stones on Hong Kong's way to becoming a global hub for Web 3.0 (the third-generation Internet).</p><p>As previously reported, Huobi will officially launch Huobi HK. Starting June 1, Huobi HK is expected to deliver unparalleled trading experiences to Web3 users through its wide range of products. Users can trade cryptocurrencies like BTC, ETH, TRX, LTC, BCH, DOGE, SHIB, BTT, SOL, ADA, and other major cryptocurrencies listed in the independent index on Huobi HK.</p><p>A Huobi representative said that joining HKVAC will boost Huobi's business in Hong Kong and lay the foundation for future operations that comply with laws and regulations. Meanwhile, Huobi intends to work with various parties in the industry to build the ecosystem of Web3 under the premise of policy compliance. It will start by establishing itself as a Web3 gateway to promote the development of Web3 in Hong Kong. Hopefully, Huobi will be granted a cryptocurrency trading license in Hong Kong in the near future, so that it can collaborate with the Hong Kong government, regulators, and other institutions to create a better crypto market in the region.</p><p>About Huobi</p><p>Founded in 2013, Huobi has evolved from a crypto exchange into a comprehensive ecosystem of blockchain businesses that span digital asset trading, financial derivatives, wallets, research, investment, incubation and other areas. Huobi serves millions of users worldwide, with a business presence covering over 160 countries and regions across five continents. Its three development strategies - "global development, technology drives development, and technology for good" - underpin its commitment to providing comprehensive services and values to global cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p><p></p>ContactMichael Wangglo-media@huobi.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Stops Elected Below 27477 - 1 June 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-27477-1-june-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-31-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-31-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-31-may-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bitcoin-price-analysis-stops-elected-below-27477-1-june-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 27477:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 31 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 27169.14 level, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25864.35 to 28473.93.&nbsp; &nbsp;Large Stops were elected below the 27477.07 area during the depreciation, representing the 38.2% retracement of the same appreciating range, before BTC/USD bottomed out around the 26978.45 area.&nbsp; Technical trading became evident when this relative low was right around a downside price objective related to selling pressure that strengthened around the 28473.93 and 28057.23 areas.&nbsp; Downside price objectives linked to the 28057.23 and 27875 levels include the 26744, 26526, 26335, and 25675 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 26861 and 26422 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27011.61 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26988.19.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Stops Elected Below 27477:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 31 May 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) extended its recent bearish momentum early in the Asian session as the pair continued to trade below the 27169.14 level, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 25864.35 to 28473.93.&nbsp; &nbsp;Large Stops were elected below the 27477.07 area during the depreciation, representing the 38.2% retracement of the same appreciating range, before BTC/USD bottomed out around the 26978.45 area.&nbsp; Technical trading became evident when this relative low was right around a downside price objective related to selling pressure that strengthened around the 28473.93 and 28057.23 areas.&nbsp; Downside price objectives linked to the 28057.23 and 27875 levels include the 26744, 26526, 26335, and 25675 areas.&nbsp; Stops are cited below the 26861 and 26422 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Additional downside price objectives include the 25474, 25442, 24705, 24440, 23208, and 22769 levels.&nbsp; Following recent price activity, areas of technical resistance and potential selling pressure include the 29048, 29143, and 29813 levels.&nbsp; Upside retracement levels in recent depreciating ranges include the 28700, 28741, 28868, 29243, 29299, and 29284 levels.&nbsp; Above the market, upside price objectives include the 30420.74, 31237.11, 31477.37, 32501.23, 32556.73, 32989.19, 34583.96, 34658.69, 35222.66, 37765.28, and 38403.97 levels.&nbsp; &nbsp;Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 200-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;100-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bullishly indicating above the 100-bar MA (hourly) and above the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 27011.61 and the&nbsp;200-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 26988.19.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;25604.51/ 24440.41/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bearishly below MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bearishly below MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[New Huo Technology and LD Capital US Launch 100% Virtual Asset Fund]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/new-huo-technology-and-ld-capital-us-launch-100-virtual-asset-fund</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-05-31-151611.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-05-31-151611.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image-2023-05-31-151611.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/new-huo-technology-and-ld-capital-us-launch-100-virtual-asset-fund</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s8">Hong Kong - New Huo Technology Holdings Limited (stock code: 1611.HK, &ldquo;New Huo Tech&rdquo;) has announced a partnership with LD Capital US to launch a fund that will provide eligible professional investors with a unique opportunity to invest 100% in virtual assets. The fund will adopt an active investment strategy by New Huo Asset Management (Hong Kong) Limited (&ldquo;NH Asset&rdquo;), a subsidiary of New Huo Tech.</p>
<p class="s8">NH Asset will be the fund manager of this actively managed fund launched in partnership with LD CapitalUS. The fund will focus on virtual assets and will target professional investors who have undergone rigorous risk and virtual asset knowledge assessments.</p>
<p class="s8">Leveraging NH Asset&rsquo;s investment management experiences and LD Capital US&rsquo;s investment research team, this collaboration will offer investors greater access to the virtual asset market and generate returns with risk mitigated.</p>
<p class="s8">About NH Asset</p>
<p class="s8">NH Asset is a subsidiary of New Huo Tech. It is a leading provider of institutional-level virtual asset management services, which holds a Type 4 (Advising on Securities) and Type 9 (Asset Management) license issued by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (&ldquo;HKSFC&rdquo;) and was approved tomanage investment portfolios which invest 100% in virtual assets. It is the first HKSFC-licensed virtual asset fund manager to actively manage virtual asset funds and can accept subscriptions in both fiat and virtual assets. NH Asset currently manages seven funds, including a Bitcoin tracker fund, an Ethereum tracker fund, two multi-strategy virtual asset funds, a blockchain venture capital fund, and two private equity funds related to blockchain mining operations. NH Asset's services are only available to professional investors as defined by the Securities and Futures Ordinance and its subsidiary legislation.</p>
<p class="s8">About LD Capital US</p>
<p class="s8">LD Capital US (&ldquo;LD&rdquo;) is a virtual asset investment-themed fund that specializes in investing in virtual assets in the secondary market. Its sub-funds consist of beta-enhanced funds such as POS-enhanced, ETH-enhanced, and BITO-enhanced portfolios. LD aims to create a positive impact and sustainable value on a global scale by effectively capturing market investment opportunities, actively participating in ecological infrastructure, and adopting effective wealth management strategies to adhere to bull and bear market cycles.</p>
<p class="s8">Twitter:</p>
<p class="s8">LD Capital: https://twitter.com/ld_capital</p>
<p class="s8">New Huo Tech: https://twitter.com/New_Huo_Tech</p>
<p class="s8">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s8">Hong Kong - New Huo Technology Holdings Limited (stock code: 1611.HK, &ldquo;New Huo Tech&rdquo;) has announced a partnership with LD Capital US to launch a fund that will provide eligible professional investors with a unique opportunity to invest 100% in virtual assets. The fund will adopt an active investment strategy by New Huo Asset Management (Hong Kong) Limited (&ldquo;NH Asset&rdquo;), a subsidiary of New Huo Tech.</p>
<p class="s8">NH Asset will be the fund manager of this actively managed fund launched in partnership with LD CapitalUS. The fund will focus on virtual assets and will target professional investors who have undergone rigorous risk and virtual asset knowledge assessments.</p>
<p class="s8">Leveraging NH Asset&rsquo;s investment management experiences and LD Capital US&rsquo;s investment research team, this collaboration will offer investors greater access to the virtual asset market and generate returns with risk mitigated.</p>
<p class="s8">About NH Asset</p>
<p class="s8">NH Asset is a subsidiary of New Huo Tech. It is a leading provider of institutional-level virtual asset management services, which holds a Type 4 (Advising on Securities) and Type 9 (Asset Management) license issued by the Hong Kong Securities and Futures Commission (&ldquo;HKSFC&rdquo;) and was approved tomanage investment portfolios which invest 100% in virtual assets. It is the first HKSFC-licensed virtual asset fund manager to actively manage virtual asset funds and can accept subscriptions in both fiat and virtual assets. NH Asset currently manages seven funds, including a Bitcoin tracker fund, an Ethereum tracker fund, two multi-strategy virtual asset funds, a blockchain venture capital fund, and two private equity funds related to blockchain mining operations. NH Asset's services are only available to professional investors as defined by the Securities and Futures Ordinance and its subsidiary legislation.</p>
<p class="s8">About LD Capital US</p>
<p class="s8">LD Capital US (&ldquo;LD&rdquo;) is a virtual asset investment-themed fund that specializes in investing in virtual assets in the secondary market. Its sub-funds consist of beta-enhanced funds such as POS-enhanced, ETH-enhanced, and BITO-enhanced portfolios. LD aims to create a positive impact and sustainable value on a global scale by effectively capturing market investment opportunities, actively participating in ecological infrastructure, and adopting effective wealth management strategies to adhere to bull and bear market cycles.</p>
<p class="s8">Twitter:</p>
<p class="s8">LD Capital: https://twitter.com/ld_capital</p>
<p class="s8">New Huo Tech: https://twitter.com/New_Huo_Tech</p>
<p class="s8">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[This New AI Altcoin Is On Track To Have A Bigger Growth Than Ethereum (ETH) In 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/this-new-ai-altcoin-is-on-track-to-have-a-bigger-growth-than-ethereum-eth-in-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-151410.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-151410.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-151410.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/this-new-ai-altcoin-is-on-track-to-have-a-bigger-growth-than-ethereum-eth-in-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="s7">The crypto market constantly evolves, allowing for crypto projects with better utilities and features. Some new altcoins have properties that make them stand out amongst established cryptocurrencies. Consequently, those with unique profit-making capabilities enjoy more success in the crypto market.</p>
<p class="s7">For new cryptocurrencies hoping to gain investors' trust, it is important to be backed up by properties that contribute to the token's value. One of the ways of doing this is by creating systems that can keep up with the technological evolution of the 21st century. InQubeta (QUBE) is here to usher AI technology into the crypto market this season.</p>
<p class="s7">By ensuring that crypto investors can now invest in AI start-ups, InQubeta is one of the unique altcoins that has created a new playing field for itself, and analysts suspect that it may soar higher than crypto giants like Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p class="s10">InQubeta (QUBE) Merges AI Investment with the Crypto Market</p>
<p class="s7">InQubeta is certainly on the right path to becoming one of the biggest cryptocurrencies. With an impressive presale, InQubeta is already making the right moves to ensure that it remains relevant long after it has been launched. The presale is in its early stages and has already raised over $200,000, with more than 50% of the Beta Stage tokens sold.</p>
<p class="s7">The increased demand for QUBE tokens will only increase its value. The InQubeta platform will make significant contributions to the growth of AI technology. The way it works is that AI start-ups needing investors can create trending NFTs with inherent utilities and list them on the InQubeta platform, allowing investors to choose what kinds they want.</p>
<p class="s7">By leveraging the properties and popularity of trending NFTs, InQubeta has positioned itself as a crypto project worth long-term investment purposes. The QUBE token also offers an avenue for governance on the platform. This means that QUBE holders can use their ERC20 tokens to participate in important decisions on the platform.</p>
<p class="s7">InQubeta ensures that investors can keep in touch with innovations in the AI market. Its ERC20 tokens are an added advantage as the Ethereum blockchain successfully allows the platform to host its NFT marketplace. What makes it all the more impressive is that InQubeta is projected to grow more than Ethereum in 2023.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s10">Ethereum (ETH) Opens the Door to a New Generation of Crypto Tokens</p>
<p class="s7">Ethereum (ETH) was one of the cryptocurrencies created to serve as an alternative to Bitcoin. It is now one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the world. A large portion of Ethereum's popularity is because it allows other cryptocurrencies to grow.</p>
<p class="s7">Several projects rely on the Ethereum blockchain, and numerous tokens rely on the Ethereum standard, making it a valuable addition to the crypto market. Many of these tokens are in the top 100 list on the DeFi market.</p>
<p class="s7">ETH was the first project to introduce the idea of smart contracts, making it possible for different parties to carry out transactions with each other. Overall, Ethereum has reduced transaction costs and increased the number of operations on its blockchain. By introducing periodic updates, Ethereum can stay ahead of the demands of the crypto market. It also allows for a cryptocurrency, such as InQubeta, to potentially experience bigger growth.</p>
<p class="s7">Conclusion</p>
<p class="s7">What better way to make money from the DeFi market than to invest in new crypto projects like InQubeta? This AI cryptocurrency is already on the way to making a name for itself worldwide. Every indication indicates that InQubeta could grow bigger than Ethereum in 2023.</p>
<p class="s7">Buying QUBE tokens from the InQubeta presale presents an opportunity to make more profit. The token's value increases further as time passes, ensuring that early investors can make more money. Be a part of InQubeta now to benefit from the evolution of the AI market.</p>
<p>Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="s7">The crypto market constantly evolves, allowing for crypto projects with better utilities and features. Some new altcoins have properties that make them stand out amongst established cryptocurrencies. Consequently, those with unique profit-making capabilities enjoy more success in the crypto market.</p>
<p class="s7">For new cryptocurrencies hoping to gain investors' trust, it is important to be backed up by properties that contribute to the token's value. One of the ways of doing this is by creating systems that can keep up with the technological evolution of the 21st century. InQubeta (QUBE) is here to usher AI technology into the crypto market this season.</p>
<p class="s7">By ensuring that crypto investors can now invest in AI start-ups, InQubeta is one of the unique altcoins that has created a new playing field for itself, and analysts suspect that it may soar higher than crypto giants like Ethereum (ETH).</p>
<p class="s10">InQubeta (QUBE) Merges AI Investment with the Crypto Market</p>
<p class="s7">InQubeta is certainly on the right path to becoming one of the biggest cryptocurrencies. With an impressive presale, InQubeta is already making the right moves to ensure that it remains relevant long after it has been launched. The presale is in its early stages and has already raised over $200,000, with more than 50% of the Beta Stage tokens sold.</p>
<p class="s7">The increased demand for QUBE tokens will only increase its value. The InQubeta platform will make significant contributions to the growth of AI technology. The way it works is that AI start-ups needing investors can create trending NFTs with inherent utilities and list them on the InQubeta platform, allowing investors to choose what kinds they want.</p>
<p class="s7">By leveraging the properties and popularity of trending NFTs, InQubeta has positioned itself as a crypto project worth long-term investment purposes. The QUBE token also offers an avenue for governance on the platform. This means that QUBE holders can use their ERC20 tokens to participate in important decisions on the platform.</p>
<p class="s7">InQubeta ensures that investors can keep in touch with innovations in the AI market. Its ERC20 tokens are an added advantage as the Ethereum blockchain successfully allows the platform to host its NFT marketplace. What makes it all the more impressive is that InQubeta is projected to grow more than Ethereum in 2023.</p>
<p>Visit InQubeta Presale </p>
<p class="s10">Ethereum (ETH) Opens the Door to a New Generation of Crypto Tokens</p>
<p class="s7">Ethereum (ETH) was one of the cryptocurrencies created to serve as an alternative to Bitcoin. It is now one of the largest cryptocurrencies in the world. A large portion of Ethereum's popularity is because it allows other cryptocurrencies to grow.</p>
<p class="s7">Several projects rely on the Ethereum blockchain, and numerous tokens rely on the Ethereum standard, making it a valuable addition to the crypto market. Many of these tokens are in the top 100 list on the DeFi market.</p>
<p class="s7">ETH was the first project to introduce the idea of smart contracts, making it possible for different parties to carry out transactions with each other. Overall, Ethereum has reduced transaction costs and increased the number of operations on its blockchain. By introducing periodic updates, Ethereum can stay ahead of the demands of the crypto market. It also allows for a cryptocurrency, such as InQubeta, to potentially experience bigger growth.</p>
<p class="s7">Conclusion</p>
<p class="s7">What better way to make money from the DeFi market than to invest in new crypto projects like InQubeta? This AI cryptocurrency is already on the way to making a name for itself worldwide. Every indication indicates that InQubeta could grow bigger than Ethereum in 2023.</p>
<p class="s7">Buying QUBE tokens from the InQubeta presale presents an opportunity to make more profit. The token's value increases further as time passes, ensuring that early investors can make more money. Be a part of InQubeta now to benefit from the evolution of the AI market.</p>
<p>Join InQubeta Communities</p>
<p class="s13">Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Will Shiba inu coin price go up, experts are bullish on hybrid exchange Tradecurve.io]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/will-shiba-inu-coin-price-go-up-experts-are-bullish-on-hybrid-exchange-tradecurveio</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-152026.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-152026.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/screenshot-2023-05-31-at-152026.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/will-shiba-inu-coin-price-go-up-experts-are-bullish-on-hybrid-exchange-tradecurveio</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Germany has officially entered a recession after growth contracted in the first quarter. With Germany leading the European Union&rsquo;s economy, many expect that Germany could pressure the European Central Bank to cut rates to stimulate the economy. Low-interest rates act as rocket fuel for altcoins, and analysts predict it would cause Shiba Inu (SHIB) to rally and add more fuel to Tradecurve (TCRV), a hybrid exchange that has already posted impressive growth in the past weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) On-Track to Raise $20 Million in PresaleTradecurve (TCRV) remains on track to raise a staggering $20 million in its presale as demand spikes. It seems the market has begun to process the value proposition of this exciting new platform that has already announced its plans to onboard 100,000 traders within three months of launch. Tradecurve will provide high leverage, anonymity, and unfettered access to global markets, including forex, stocks, crypto, and commodities. This nascent challenger in the trading industry features transparent on-chain pricing, intuitional level liquidity powering excellent fills for traders, and, most excitingly, has integrated artificial intelligence trading algorithms accessible only to $TCRV holders. Tradecurve is a derivatives platform where users stay anonymous. It provides a haven for millions of retail clients worldwide who cannot access leveraged trading products due to shortsighted government regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts predict explosive growth for $TCRV expecting a 5,000% leap before the presale closes. They cited the protocol&rsquo;s AI speciality and its plans to introduce Proof of Reserves to validate these claims. Some analysts even compared it to the famous Binance Coin (BNB) ICO in 2017 that began at a price of $0.15.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price PredictionShiba Inu (SHIB) benefitted from the memecoin mania that descended on Crypto Twitter recently. Still, the real hype has come from the impressive metrics posted by Shibarium, a layer two scaling solution built by the developers of Shiba Inu (SHIB). Shibaroium has executed more than twelve million transactions, and it will allow Shiba Inu (SHIB) holders to swap between the native ecosystem tokens $BONE and $LEASH with lower fees. Additionally, the chain will utilize $BONE for gas fees, and rumor is gas fees will be swapped for Shiba Inu (SHIB) and burnt. Analysts have forecast a range between $0.00001473 and $0.00001762 for Shiba Inu (SHIB), which appears slightly conservative given the amount of development currently taking place on the network. The release of Shibarium perfectly encapsulates the Shiba Inu (SHIB) philosophy of being a memecoin but also delivering utility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find out more about the Tradecurve presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale:https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Germany has officially entered a recession after growth contracted in the first quarter. With Germany leading the European Union&rsquo;s economy, many expect that Germany could pressure the European Central Bank to cut rates to stimulate the economy. Low-interest rates act as rocket fuel for altcoins, and analysts predict it would cause Shiba Inu (SHIB) to rally and add more fuel to Tradecurve (TCRV), a hybrid exchange that has already posted impressive growth in the past weeks.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&gt;&gt;BUY TCRV TOKENS NOW&lt;&lt;</p>
<p>Tradecurve (TCRV) On-Track to Raise $20 Million in PresaleTradecurve (TCRV) remains on track to raise a staggering $20 million in its presale as demand spikes. It seems the market has begun to process the value proposition of this exciting new platform that has already announced its plans to onboard 100,000 traders within three months of launch. Tradecurve will provide high leverage, anonymity, and unfettered access to global markets, including forex, stocks, crypto, and commodities. This nascent challenger in the trading industry features transparent on-chain pricing, intuitional level liquidity powering excellent fills for traders, and, most excitingly, has integrated artificial intelligence trading algorithms accessible only to $TCRV holders. Tradecurve is a derivatives platform where users stay anonymous. It provides a haven for millions of retail clients worldwide who cannot access leveraged trading products due to shortsighted government regulations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts predict explosive growth for $TCRV expecting a 5,000% leap before the presale closes. They cited the protocol&rsquo;s AI speciality and its plans to introduce Proof of Reserves to validate these claims. Some analysts even compared it to the famous Binance Coin (BNB) ICO in 2017 that began at a price of $0.15.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
<p>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price PredictionShiba Inu (SHIB) benefitted from the memecoin mania that descended on Crypto Twitter recently. Still, the real hype has come from the impressive metrics posted by Shibarium, a layer two scaling solution built by the developers of Shiba Inu (SHIB). Shibaroium has executed more than twelve million transactions, and it will allow Shiba Inu (SHIB) holders to swap between the native ecosystem tokens $BONE and $LEASH with lower fees. Additionally, the chain will utilize $BONE for gas fees, and rumor is gas fees will be swapped for Shiba Inu (SHIB) and burnt. Analysts have forecast a range between $0.00001473 and $0.00001762 for Shiba Inu (SHIB), which appears slightly conservative given the amount of development currently taking place on the network. The release of Shibarium perfectly encapsulates the Shiba Inu (SHIB) philosophy of being a memecoin but also delivering utility.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Find out more about the Tradecurve presale here:</p>
<p>Website: https://tradecurve.io/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Presale:https://app.tradecurve.io/sign-up&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/tradecurve_official&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/Tradecurveapp&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bumpers Breakthrough DeFi Protocol Set to Reshape Options Pricing]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bumpers-breakthrough-defi-protocol-set-to-reshape-options-pricing</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_2_3411670161_1685531273hA1ICLC3D5.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_2_3411670161_1685531273hA1ICLC3D5.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/imageedit_2_3411670161_1685531273hA1ICLC3D5.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 15:09:39 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bumpers-breakthrough-defi-protocol-set-to-reshape-options-pricing</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Marking a seismic shift in the digital asset landscape, DeFi platform Bumper today unveiled the findings of their comprehensive simulation, exhibiting new pricing efficiencies over traditional options desks ahead of the protocol launch in August 2023.</p><p>This report delineates a milestone in financial technology, showcasing an altogether new financial instrument that consistently outperforms existing options desks in generating both competitive premia and sustainable yields, backtested against genuine, multi-year historical cryptocurrency market data and options prices.</p><p>The report is the culmination of a two-year exercise in Research and Development powered by a $20m investment and derived in collaboration with CADLabs and the Swiss Centre for Cryptoeconomics.</p><p>Key highlights from the simulation report:</p><ul><li>On average, Bumper Takers paid 9.3% cheaper premia than buyers of traditional put options.</li><li>During the 2022 bear market, Bumper&rsquo;s simulation showed a yield improvement of 46.2% for Makers compared to options pricing, without resorting to token incentives.</li><li>The protocol remained solvent throughout the simulated conditions.</li><li>Despite having different inputs and methodology, Bumper&rsquo;s results reveal a remarkable correlation with the Nobel Prize-winning Black-Scholes model.</li></ul><p>These results have been pivotal in understanding and honing the resilience of the Bumper protocol across diverse market conditions.</p>On the release of the report, Bumper CEO Jonathan DeCarteret expressed, "By challenging and potentially reshaping the accepted norms of options pricing, Bumper stands to revolutionise not just the crypto options market, but also has the potential to penetrate traditional finance and disrupt the colossal $13T derivatives market in the future."<p>The report underscores the anticipated outcomes of Bumper's dynamic pricing, based on forward volatility rather than the usual implied volatility.&nbsp;</p><p>The findings of the simulation report positions Bumper as an immensely appealing prospect for institutions and fund managers, in addition to retail crypto investors.</p><p>The economic simulation report released today marks the most significant validation of Bumper's innovative approach to date, and signals what could be one of the most substantial challenges to the Black-Scholes derived pricing in half a century.</p><p>Read Bumper&rsquo;s simulation report here and for more information on the protocol visit https://bumper.fi.</p><p>About Bumper</p><p>Bumper is a DeFi risk market that provides protection from downside volatility in the price of crypto assets. Users buying protection (Takers) set a price at which they wish to protect their crypto should the price fall, but they don&rsquo;t lose out if the market heads upwards. Conversely, other users (Makers) earn a yield by providing stablecoin liquidity to the protocol.</p><p>Learn more about Bumper</p><p>Website | Twitter | Discord | Youtube</p>ContactCMOJason SuttieBumpermarketing@bumper.fi]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>London, United Kingdom, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Marking a seismic shift in the digital asset landscape, DeFi platform Bumper today unveiled the findings of their comprehensive simulation, exhibiting new pricing efficiencies over traditional options desks ahead of the protocol launch in August 2023.</p><p>This report delineates a milestone in financial technology, showcasing an altogether new financial instrument that consistently outperforms existing options desks in generating both competitive premia and sustainable yields, backtested against genuine, multi-year historical cryptocurrency market data and options prices.</p><p>The report is the culmination of a two-year exercise in Research and Development powered by a $20m investment and derived in collaboration with CADLabs and the Swiss Centre for Cryptoeconomics.</p><p>Key highlights from the simulation report:</p><ul><li>On average, Bumper Takers paid 9.3% cheaper premia than buyers of traditional put options.</li><li>During the 2022 bear market, Bumper&rsquo;s simulation showed a yield improvement of 46.2% for Makers compared to options pricing, without resorting to token incentives.</li><li>The protocol remained solvent throughout the simulated conditions.</li><li>Despite having different inputs and methodology, Bumper&rsquo;s results reveal a remarkable correlation with the Nobel Prize-winning Black-Scholes model.</li></ul><p>These results have been pivotal in understanding and honing the resilience of the Bumper protocol across diverse market conditions.</p>On the release of the report, Bumper CEO Jonathan DeCarteret expressed, "By challenging and potentially reshaping the accepted norms of options pricing, Bumper stands to revolutionise not just the crypto options market, but also has the potential to penetrate traditional finance and disrupt the colossal $13T derivatives market in the future."<p>The report underscores the anticipated outcomes of Bumper's dynamic pricing, based on forward volatility rather than the usual implied volatility.&nbsp;</p><p>The findings of the simulation report positions Bumper as an immensely appealing prospect for institutions and fund managers, in addition to retail crypto investors.</p><p>The economic simulation report released today marks the most significant validation of Bumper's innovative approach to date, and signals what could be one of the most substantial challenges to the Black-Scholes derived pricing in half a century.</p><p>Read Bumper&rsquo;s simulation report here and for more information on the protocol visit https://bumper.fi.</p><p>About Bumper</p><p>Bumper is a DeFi risk market that provides protection from downside volatility in the price of crypto assets. Users buying protection (Takers) set a price at which they wish to protect their crypto should the price fall, but they don&rsquo;t lose out if the market heads upwards. Conversely, other users (Makers) earn a yield by providing stablecoin liquidity to the protocol.</p><p>Learn more about Bumper</p><p>Website | Twitter | Discord | Youtube</p>ContactCMOJason SuttieBumpermarketing@bumper.fi]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Anoma Foundation Successfully Completes $25 Million Funding Round]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/anoma-foundation-successfully-completes-dollar25-million-funding-round</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-247.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-247.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/unnamed-247.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 14:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoDaily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/anoma-foundation-successfully-completes-dollar25-million-funding-round</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image: Anoma</p>
<p>Blockchain architecture firm, Anoma Foundation announced it has successfully completed its third funding round securing $25 million with an aim to extend its intent-centric technology to blockchain platforms. Announced Wednesday, the fundraising event was led by one of the top Web 3 VC firms CMCC Global. The latest capital round aims to further Anoma&rsquo;s goal to bring the third generation of blockchains to market and decentralize the financial system, giving power back to the users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fundraising also welcomed pledges from other prominent industry players including Electric Capital, Delphi Digital, Dialectic, KR1, Spartan, NGC, MH Ventures, Bixin Ventures, No Limit, Plassa, Perridon Ventures, Anagram, and Factor. Additionally, over 30 angel investors across the blockchain space also participated in the round, embracing Anoma Foundation&rsquo;s vision.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Swiss non-profit firm is focused on funding the development of its blockchain architecture to bring fully decentralized systems to Web 2.5 apps including rollups, DEXs and other DApps. With significant backing from investors across the blockchain industry, Anoma will further the development of intent-centric blockchain architecture, bringing to life a &ldquo;new paradigm for building blockchain infrastructure layers&rdquo;, the press statement reads.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Compared to existing architectures such as Ethereum/EVM, it makes dApps an order of magnitude more composable and an order of magnitude easier to build,&rdquo; said Adrian Brink, Co-founder of Anoma.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Anoma&rsquo;s intent-centric blockchain architecture allows these &ldquo;partially decentralized apps&rdquo; to give power back to their users while promoting the development of novel apps that previously could not be built on existing architectures.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;The team is pushing the boundaries of protocol design and reimagining how base layer infrastructure should operate,&rdquo; said Charlie Morris, Co-founder and Managing Partner of CMCC Global. &ldquo;It is refreshing to see Anoma&rsquo;s designs and philosophy against the backdrop of a homogenous group of layer-1 smart contract platforms.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Apart from offering a platform to build fully decentralized apps, Anoma&rsquo;s latest capital raise will also enhance the platform&rsquo;s scalability, user experience, privacy and interoperability, Tommy Shaughnessy, Founding Partner of Delphi Digital shared in his statement.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Anoma's intent-centric architecture represents a significant advancement across all fronts of blockchain infrastructure[...],&rdquo; Shaughnessy added. &ldquo;We are excited to be part of their journey towards revolutionizing decentralized applications.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Notwithstanding, the funding will also be used to support ongoing research and development initiatives, and boost adoption rates via easy-to-integrate development tools that enable the development of novel DApps. In addition, the cash will be used to form strategic partnerships and enhance the overall ecosystem development.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are super excited to be investing in Anoma,&rdquo; added Dialectic founder Ryan Zurrer. &ldquo;Their intent-centricity and inherent focus on low-level privacy promises to unlock novel use-cases, particularly in areas such as next-generation DeFi, and represents a major step forward for the space.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Image: Anoma</p>
<p>Blockchain architecture firm, Anoma Foundation announced it has successfully completed its third funding round securing $25 million with an aim to extend its intent-centric technology to blockchain platforms. Announced Wednesday, the fundraising event was led by one of the top Web 3 VC firms CMCC Global. The latest capital round aims to further Anoma&rsquo;s goal to bring the third generation of blockchains to market and decentralize the financial system, giving power back to the users.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The fundraising also welcomed pledges from other prominent industry players including Electric Capital, Delphi Digital, Dialectic, KR1, Spartan, NGC, MH Ventures, Bixin Ventures, No Limit, Plassa, Perridon Ventures, Anagram, and Factor. Additionally, over 30 angel investors across the blockchain space also participated in the round, embracing Anoma Foundation&rsquo;s vision.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The Swiss non-profit firm is focused on funding the development of its blockchain architecture to bring fully decentralized systems to Web 2.5 apps including rollups, DEXs and other DApps. With significant backing from investors across the blockchain industry, Anoma will further the development of intent-centric blockchain architecture, bringing to life a &ldquo;new paradigm for building blockchain infrastructure layers&rdquo;, the press statement reads.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Compared to existing architectures such as Ethereum/EVM, it makes dApps an order of magnitude more composable and an order of magnitude easier to build,&rdquo; said Adrian Brink, Co-founder of Anoma.&nbsp;</p>

<p>Anoma&rsquo;s intent-centric blockchain architecture allows these &ldquo;partially decentralized apps&rdquo; to give power back to their users while promoting the development of novel apps that previously could not be built on existing architectures.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;The team is pushing the boundaries of protocol design and reimagining how base layer infrastructure should operate,&rdquo; said Charlie Morris, Co-founder and Managing Partner of CMCC Global. &ldquo;It is refreshing to see Anoma&rsquo;s designs and philosophy against the backdrop of a homogenous group of layer-1 smart contract platforms.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Apart from offering a platform to build fully decentralized apps, Anoma&rsquo;s latest capital raise will also enhance the platform&rsquo;s scalability, user experience, privacy and interoperability, Tommy Shaughnessy, Founding Partner of Delphi Digital shared in his statement.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Anoma's intent-centric architecture represents a significant advancement across all fronts of blockchain infrastructure[...],&rdquo; Shaughnessy added. &ldquo;We are excited to be part of their journey towards revolutionizing decentralized applications.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Notwithstanding, the funding will also be used to support ongoing research and development initiatives, and boost adoption rates via easy-to-integrate development tools that enable the development of novel DApps. In addition, the cash will be used to form strategic partnerships and enhance the overall ecosystem development.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We are super excited to be investing in Anoma,&rdquo; added Dialectic founder Ryan Zurrer. &ldquo;Their intent-centricity and inherent focus on low-level privacy promises to unlock novel use-cases, particularly in areas such as next-generation DeFi, and represents a major step forward for the space.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Web3 payments and infrastructure provider Transac raises $20 million]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/web3-payments-and-infrastructure-provider-transac-raises-20-million</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/pay-3.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/pay-3.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/pay-3.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 13:59:10 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/web3-payments-and-infrastructure-provider-transac-raises-20-million</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Transac raises $20 million for its traditional finance to crypto payments business.</p>
A highly popular Series A
<p>A highly popular Series A funding round was partaken in by prominent VC firms and angel investors from across the board. According to TechFundingNews, the round was led by Chinese venture capital firm CE Innovation Capital, and other investors were SBI Ven Capital, Sygnum, Azimut, Third Kind Venture Capital, UOB Venture Management, Signum Capital, Animoca Brands, Genting Ventures, Istari Ventures, No Limit Holdings, Woodstock Fund, IOSG Ventures, KX, Axelar, Tokentus, and The Lao.</p>
<p>Sandeep Naiwal of Polygon, Jan Hammer of Index Ventures, and Charles Delingpole of ComplyAdvantage were among the individual angel investors who also took part in the round.</p>
<p>Bingze Gu, Partner at CE Innovation Capital, the lead investor in Transak&rsquo;s Series A said of his company&rsquo;s investment into Transac:</p>

<p>At CEiC, we&rsquo;re strategically invested in propelling the Web3 ecosystem forward. Transak stands at the forefront of this revolution, wielding their On &amp; Off Ramp solution as a potent instrument to usher in the next billion Web3 users. Their recent initiatives, such as Transak One and the NFT checkout offerings, are not just lowering the barriers to entry into Web3 &ndash; they&rsquo;re redefining them,&rdquo;</p>

Bridging the gap between traditional and crypto finance
<p>Transak bridges the gap between traditional finance and the decentralised world of cryptocurrencies. By eliminating complex technical processes, it offers a simplified and intuitive solution for individuals and businesses to engage with digital assets. This breakthrough enables users to transact directly from their bank accounts, making the onboarding process remarkably convenient for newcomers to the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>One of the core features that sets Transak apart is its dedication to user experience. Recognizing the importance of simplicity and accessibility, the platform enables users to purchase cryptocurrencies using their preferred fiat currency. This ease of use empowers individuals to effortlessly enter the exciting realm of digital currencies without requiring any prior technical knowledge.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Transac raises $20 million for its traditional finance to crypto payments business.</p>
A highly popular Series A
<p>A highly popular Series A funding round was partaken in by prominent VC firms and angel investors from across the board. According to TechFundingNews, the round was led by Chinese venture capital firm CE Innovation Capital, and other investors were SBI Ven Capital, Sygnum, Azimut, Third Kind Venture Capital, UOB Venture Management, Signum Capital, Animoca Brands, Genting Ventures, Istari Ventures, No Limit Holdings, Woodstock Fund, IOSG Ventures, KX, Axelar, Tokentus, and The Lao.</p>
<p>Sandeep Naiwal of Polygon, Jan Hammer of Index Ventures, and Charles Delingpole of ComplyAdvantage were among the individual angel investors who also took part in the round.</p>
<p>Bingze Gu, Partner at CE Innovation Capital, the lead investor in Transak&rsquo;s Series A said of his company&rsquo;s investment into Transac:</p>

<p>At CEiC, we&rsquo;re strategically invested in propelling the Web3 ecosystem forward. Transak stands at the forefront of this revolution, wielding their On &amp; Off Ramp solution as a potent instrument to usher in the next billion Web3 users. Their recent initiatives, such as Transak One and the NFT checkout offerings, are not just lowering the barriers to entry into Web3 &ndash; they&rsquo;re redefining them,&rdquo;</p>

Bridging the gap between traditional and crypto finance
<p>Transak bridges the gap between traditional finance and the decentralised world of cryptocurrencies. By eliminating complex technical processes, it offers a simplified and intuitive solution for individuals and businesses to engage with digital assets. This breakthrough enables users to transact directly from their bank accounts, making the onboarding process remarkably convenient for newcomers to the world of cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>One of the core features that sets Transak apart is its dedication to user experience. Recognizing the importance of simplicity and accessibility, the platform enables users to purchase cryptocurrencies using their preferred fiat currency. This ease of use empowers individuals to effortlessly enter the exciting realm of digital currencies without requiring any prior technical knowledge.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Nansen Lays Off 30% Of Workforce]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nansen-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nansen-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nansen-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/nansen-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/nansen-lays-off-30-percent-of-workforce</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>In a move to streamline operations and reduce expenses, blockchain analytics firm Nansen has announced a significant reduction in its workforce.</p>
CEO Announces Layoffs
<p>Blockchain analytics platform Nansen has been the latest to lay off approximately 30% of its employees, seeking to navigate the challenging economic landscape and ensure long-term sustainability.</p>
<p>The decision, which the CEO confirmed in a public statement on Monday, comes as the firm aims to cut costs and optimize its operations, especially with the crypto markets running on a continuous slump.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nansen CEO, Alex Svanevik tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This week we announced the extremely difficult decision to reduce the size of the Nansen team. I&rsquo;m endlessly grateful to the incredible people we are parting ways with. They will go on to achieve great things, and we'll ensure they get a soft landing, with severance and support.&rdquo;</p>

Nansen To Focus On Core Strategy
<p>The announcement statement, penned by Svenavik, claimed that one of the reasons behind the decision was the avalanche effect of the company growing too fast, too soon. Svenavik took responsibility as CEO of the company taking on challenges that was not part of Nansen&rsquo;s core strategy and promised that the restructuring of the firm would focus on accomplishing less things but to a higher degree of quality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Secondly, the company also cited the less-than-ideal market conditions, claiming that their cost-base was too high relative to the company&rsquo;s status.&nbsp;</p>
Nansen Not Immune To Market Challenges
<p>According to LinkedIn data, before the reduction, the company used to employ a 50-100 strong workforce. Major crypto-focused media publications like The Block and Bloomberg have worked with Nansen across major blockchain networks like Polygon and Ethereum. In addition, the firm has been a prominent player in the blockchain analytics industry, specializing in providing insights and intelligence for decentralized finance (DeFi) and non-fungible token (NFT) ecosystems across over 100 million crypto wallets.</p>
<p>The layoffs, however, indicate that Nansen has been impacted by the challenges faced by the broader cryptocurrency market. Despite the rapid growth and innovation in the blockchain industry, the volatility and uncertainty inherent in the market can pose substantial risks to businesses. As such, cost-cutting measures have become necessary for many companies to maintain their financial stability.</p>
Mass Layoffs Plague Industry
<p>The restructuring efforts at Nansen align with the broader trend of companies in the cryptocurrency and blockchain industry taking steps to ensure sustainability. The market's maturity has necessitated a more strategic approach, resulting in mass layoffs and restructuring efforts across the industry. Crypto companies like Polygon, WazirX, and Genesis have been some of the big names that have let go of significant portions of their workforce due to the unfavorable conditions in the market right now. Even entertainment giant Disney had to let go of its entire metaverse team as a part of its efforts to streamline its operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a move to streamline operations and reduce expenses, blockchain analytics firm Nansen has announced a significant reduction in its workforce.</p>
CEO Announces Layoffs
<p>Blockchain analytics platform Nansen has been the latest to lay off approximately 30% of its employees, seeking to navigate the challenging economic landscape and ensure long-term sustainability.</p>
<p>The decision, which the CEO confirmed in a public statement on Monday, comes as the firm aims to cut costs and optimize its operations, especially with the crypto markets running on a continuous slump.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Nansen CEO, Alex Svanevik tweeted,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;This week we announced the extremely difficult decision to reduce the size of the Nansen team. I&rsquo;m endlessly grateful to the incredible people we are parting ways with. They will go on to achieve great things, and we'll ensure they get a soft landing, with severance and support.&rdquo;</p>

Nansen To Focus On Core Strategy
<p>The announcement statement, penned by Svenavik, claimed that one of the reasons behind the decision was the avalanche effect of the company growing too fast, too soon. Svenavik took responsibility as CEO of the company taking on challenges that was not part of Nansen&rsquo;s core strategy and promised that the restructuring of the firm would focus on accomplishing less things but to a higher degree of quality.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Secondly, the company also cited the less-than-ideal market conditions, claiming that their cost-base was too high relative to the company&rsquo;s status.&nbsp;</p>
Nansen Not Immune To Market Challenges
<p>According to LinkedIn data, before the reduction, the company used to employ a 50-100 strong workforce. Major crypto-focused media publications like The Block and Bloomberg have worked with Nansen across major blockchain networks like Polygon and Ethereum. In addition, the firm has been a prominent player in the blockchain analytics industry, specializing in providing insights and intelligence for decentralized finance (DeFi) and non-fungible token (NFT) ecosystems across over 100 million crypto wallets.</p>
<p>The layoffs, however, indicate that Nansen has been impacted by the challenges faced by the broader cryptocurrency market. Despite the rapid growth and innovation in the blockchain industry, the volatility and uncertainty inherent in the market can pose substantial risks to businesses. As such, cost-cutting measures have become necessary for many companies to maintain their financial stability.</p>
Mass Layoffs Plague Industry
<p>The restructuring efforts at Nansen align with the broader trend of companies in the cryptocurrency and blockchain industry taking steps to ensure sustainability. The market's maturity has necessitated a more strategic approach, resulting in mass layoffs and restructuring efforts across the industry. Crypto companies like Polygon, WazirX, and Genesis have been some of the big names that have let go of significant portions of their workforce due to the unfavorable conditions in the market right now. Even entertainment giant Disney had to let go of its entire metaverse team as a part of its efforts to streamline its operations.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Green Real Estate Project Qlindo Debuts on MEXC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/green-real-estate-project-qlindo-debuts-on-mexc</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-30_20-21-25_1685467296HclfkeFeH0.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-30_20-21-25_1685467296HclfkeFeH0.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/photo_2023-05-30_20-21-25_1685467296HclfkeFeH0.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:41:57 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/green-real-estate-project-qlindo-debuts-on-mexc</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In a defining moment for green real estate investment accessibility, Qlindo, the innovative project making waves in sustainable investing, announces its listing on the MEXC Exchange on May 31, 2023.</p><p>Prior to this exciting development, Qlindo carved a niche of reliability and impact in the green real estate and energy sector. From successfully completing an audit by CERTIK, one of the most respected auditing firms in the crypto industry, to forging a strong alliance with TechWoodHomes, Qlindo has consistently demonstrated commitment to its mission. As a result, the first green real estate projects have been funded, bolstering Qlindo&rsquo;s impact in the market.</p><p>Moreover, despite the prevailing bear market conditions, Qlindo has maintained an impressive uptrend, appreciating by over 100% over the past year. This remarkable performance is attributed to early investors' steadfast faith in Qlindo&rsquo;s long-term vision.</p><p>The listing on MEXC will broaden Qlindo's reach, enabling a wider audience to engage with the project and fostering potential growth and interest</p><p>In the spirit of celebration, MEXC Exchange will be hosting a grand Kickstarter Token Raffle. The event features an astounding prize pool of 10,000 USDT and 890,000 QLINDO tokens to be won. Users can participate in the raffle and stand a chance to win rewards. Users can find more details and join, by visiting the MEXC Kickstarter platform.</p>Michael Marczell, COO of Qlindo, expressed his enthusiasm about the development: "We are very pleased that the listing on MEXC makes it even easier to invest in QLINDO and, therefore, green real estate and green energy. QLINDO stands for accessible impact investing, and we are just getting started. Many thanks to MEXC."<p></p><p>But the exciting news doesn't end there. Qlindo is planning to announce another utility for its token in the upcoming weeks, adding even more value for its holders. While details remain under wraps, the update is set to further Qlindo's mission of making real estate investments more accessible for retail investors. #QLINDOX</p><p>Users can be part of Qlindo's groundbreaking moment by exploring the opportunities with QLINDO token. Embrace the future of green real estate and green energy investing, contributing to environmental sustainability and potential financial growth. To participate, users can create an account on the MEXC Exchange, where trading will begin on May 31, 2023.</p><p></p><p>About Qlindo</p><p>Qlindo is a project focused on bridging the gap between Blockchain Technology, and Green Real Estate and Renewable Energy Investment Opportunities. Through the QLINDO token, users are now able to invest in a diversified portfolio of green projects, led by an industry-leading expert team. The technology also allows investors to participate with their preferred amount, skipping the traditional interference of a middleman. Qlindo also collaborates with well-reputed and hand-picked real estate organizations such as TechWoodHomes to allow access to up-to-the-minute niche investments.</p><p>For more information: Official website | Twitter | Instagram | Telegram | LinkedIn</p>ContactMichael MarczellQlindom.marczell@qlindo.io]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, May 31st, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>In a defining moment for green real estate investment accessibility, Qlindo, the innovative project making waves in sustainable investing, announces its listing on the MEXC Exchange on May 31, 2023.</p><p>Prior to this exciting development, Qlindo carved a niche of reliability and impact in the green real estate and energy sector. From successfully completing an audit by CERTIK, one of the most respected auditing firms in the crypto industry, to forging a strong alliance with TechWoodHomes, Qlindo has consistently demonstrated commitment to its mission. As a result, the first green real estate projects have been funded, bolstering Qlindo&rsquo;s impact in the market.</p><p>Moreover, despite the prevailing bear market conditions, Qlindo has maintained an impressive uptrend, appreciating by over 100% over the past year. This remarkable performance is attributed to early investors' steadfast faith in Qlindo&rsquo;s long-term vision.</p><p>The listing on MEXC will broaden Qlindo's reach, enabling a wider audience to engage with the project and fostering potential growth and interest</p><p>In the spirit of celebration, MEXC Exchange will be hosting a grand Kickstarter Token Raffle. The event features an astounding prize pool of 10,000 USDT and 890,000 QLINDO tokens to be won. Users can participate in the raffle and stand a chance to win rewards. Users can find more details and join, by visiting the MEXC Kickstarter platform.</p>Michael Marczell, COO of Qlindo, expressed his enthusiasm about the development: "We are very pleased that the listing on MEXC makes it even easier to invest in QLINDO and, therefore, green real estate and green energy. QLINDO stands for accessible impact investing, and we are just getting started. Many thanks to MEXC."<p></p><p>But the exciting news doesn't end there. Qlindo is planning to announce another utility for its token in the upcoming weeks, adding even more value for its holders. While details remain under wraps, the update is set to further Qlindo's mission of making real estate investments more accessible for retail investors. #QLINDOX</p><p>Users can be part of Qlindo's groundbreaking moment by exploring the opportunities with QLINDO token. Embrace the future of green real estate and green energy investing, contributing to environmental sustainability and potential financial growth. To participate, users can create an account on the MEXC Exchange, where trading will begin on May 31, 2023.</p><p></p><p>About Qlindo</p><p>Qlindo is a project focused on bridging the gap between Blockchain Technology, and Green Real Estate and Renewable Energy Investment Opportunities. Through the QLINDO token, users are now able to invest in a diversified portfolio of green projects, led by an industry-leading expert team. The technology also allows investors to participate with their preferred amount, skipping the traditional interference of a middleman. Qlindo also collaborates with well-reputed and hand-picked real estate organizations such as TechWoodHomes to allow access to up-to-the-minute niche investments.</p><p>For more information: Official website | Twitter | Instagram | Telegram | LinkedIn</p>ContactMichael MarczellQlindom.marczell@qlindo.io]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Rental car owner arrested for taking payment in crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/rental-car-owner-arrested-for-taking-payment-in-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/indo-1.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/indo-1.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/indo-1.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:59:52 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/rental-car-owner-arrested-for-taking-payment-in-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>An Indonesian rental car owner was arrested by Bali police at his business premises after it was alleged he accepted crypto for payments.</p>
<p>It has always been so, that anyone who uses anything else other than a government-backed currency to make a transaction is considered to have broken the law, and is normally heavily sanctioned compared to other far more heinous crimes, depending on the country in which they reside.</p>
<p>In this particular case, police in Bali carried out an undercover operation in order to expose the illegal transactions that were being made, i.e., taking payments in crypto in exchange for car rentals.</p>
<p>The police set up the car rental owner by first infiltrating a Telegram group and then asked the suspect for a wallet address for crypto payment. In a subsequent meeting to finalise the deal the business owner was arrested and his mobile phone was seized as well as other possessions.</p>
<p>If proven guilty, the punishment meted out by Indonesian courts for such an offence is up to one year in prison, and a fine of IDR 200 million (US$13,337).&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Coconuts Bali, Nanang Prihasmoko, the Bali Crime Investigation Unit Chief, said of the incident:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We encourage the use of the Indonesian rupiah because it is the only currency in Indonesia, and we must conduct transactions with it,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Opinion
<p>On the face of it, requiring citizens to transact in the officially recognised currency of the land appears to be not only sensible but laudable, given that the use of other, non-official currencies, can take away from the official currency, and over time confidence in it can erode.</p>
<p>However, as the following chart demonstrates, the Indonesian rupiah is not maintaining its value. The chart is for the price of gold in kilograms against the Indonesian rupiah over the last 15 years. It can be seen that the rupiah has fallen around 400% to gold in this time.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Source: Goldprice.org</p>
<p>Every fiat currency in the world is also suffering a similar fate, leading to vastly reduced purchasing power for citizens of all countries. The question is whether citizens should agree to allow their governments to continue to prop up banks and save in rapidly devaluing currencies.</p>
<p>The fiat currency experiment has failed on the most spectacular level. This being said, governments and banks have locked their citizens into this system with very few escape routes out. Crypto, gold, and silver are those routes out, so stand by for them to become ever more difficult to purchase.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Indonesian rental car owner was arrested by Bali police at his business premises after it was alleged he accepted crypto for payments.</p>
<p>It has always been so, that anyone who uses anything else other than a government-backed currency to make a transaction is considered to have broken the law, and is normally heavily sanctioned compared to other far more heinous crimes, depending on the country in which they reside.</p>
<p>In this particular case, police in Bali carried out an undercover operation in order to expose the illegal transactions that were being made, i.e., taking payments in crypto in exchange for car rentals.</p>
<p>The police set up the car rental owner by first infiltrating a Telegram group and then asked the suspect for a wallet address for crypto payment. In a subsequent meeting to finalise the deal the business owner was arrested and his mobile phone was seized as well as other possessions.</p>
<p>If proven guilty, the punishment meted out by Indonesian courts for such an offence is up to one year in prison, and a fine of IDR 200 million (US$13,337).&nbsp;</p>
<p>According to Coconuts Bali, Nanang Prihasmoko, the Bali Crime Investigation Unit Chief, said of the incident:</p>

<p>&ldquo;We encourage the use of the Indonesian rupiah because it is the only currency in Indonesia, and we must conduct transactions with it,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Opinion
<p>On the face of it, requiring citizens to transact in the officially recognised currency of the land appears to be not only sensible but laudable, given that the use of other, non-official currencies, can take away from the official currency, and over time confidence in it can erode.</p>
<p>However, as the following chart demonstrates, the Indonesian rupiah is not maintaining its value. The chart is for the price of gold in kilograms against the Indonesian rupiah over the last 15 years. It can be seen that the rupiah has fallen around 400% to gold in this time.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Source: Goldprice.org</p>
<p>Every fiat currency in the world is also suffering a similar fate, leading to vastly reduced purchasing power for citizens of all countries. The question is whether citizens should agree to allow their governments to continue to prop up banks and save in rapidly devaluing currencies.</p>
<p>The fiat currency experiment has failed on the most spectacular level. This being said, governments and banks have locked their citizens into this system with very few escape routes out. Crypto, gold, and silver are those routes out, so stand by for them to become ever more difficult to purchase.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[BTC At 20% Off On Binance Australia, Crypto Daily TV 31/5/2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-at-20-off-on-binance-australia-crypto-daily-tv-31-5-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-20.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-20.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/1450-720-btc-20.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/btc-at-20-off-on-binance-australia-crypto-daily-tv-31-5-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin was trading 20% lower on Binance Australia</p>
<p>Bitcoin was trading at about 20% discount on Binance&rsquo;s Australia arm, compared with rival exchanges. This comes after Binance Australia halted Australian dollar bank transfers earlier this month, citing its third-party payment service provider as the issue and said that it's working to find an alternative</p>
<p>Bali plans to deport and punish tourists that pay with crypto</p>
<p>Bali's provincial government declared that any foreigners using&nbsp; cryptocurrency instead of the Indonesian rupiah would be met with harsh punishment. The Bank of Indonesia tolerates crypto but has explicitly prohibited it as a payment method since 2017.</p>
<p>Bybit will be exiting Canada</p>
<p>Bybit has announced that it will be exiting the Canadian market starting as soon as today due to recent regulatory developments in the country, adding to several other exchanges that pulled out from the country.</p>
The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained a moderate 0.1% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 0.1% in the last session after rising as much as 1.0% during the session. The RSI is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 270541 and resistance is at 288221.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.6% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained 0.6% in the last session after rising as much as 1.2% during the session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1851.5167 and resistance is at 1946.2167.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD exploded 5.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair skyrocketed 5.9% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an overbought market. Support is at 0.4695 and resistance is at 0.5074.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 1.2% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.2% in the last session. The ROC's negative signal contradicts our overall technical analysis. Support is at 89.1533 and resistance is at 93.0133.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>DE Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market. Germany's Unemployment Rate will be released at 07:55 GMT, Australia's Construction Work Done at 01:30 GMT, and the US Fed's Beige Book at 18:00 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Construction Work Done</p>
<p>The Construction Work Done measures the amount of construction work done in the last month. It is a key indicator of the Australian construction sector.</p>
<p>US Fed's Beige Book</p>
<p>The Beige Book reports on the current economic situation using interviews with key business contacts, economists, market experts, and other sources.</p>
<p>JP Annualized Housing Starts</p>
<p>The Annualized Housing Starts captures how many new single-family homes or buildings were constructed annually. It is a key indicator of the housing market. Japan's Annualized Housing Starts will be released at 05:00 GMT, the US Chicago Purchasing Managers' Index at 13:45 GMT, and Germany's Unemployment Change at 07:55 GMT.</p>
<p>US Chicago PMI</p>
<p>The Chicago Purchasing Managers Index released by ISM-Chicago captures the business conditions across Illinois, Indiana, and Michigan. </p>
<p>DE Unemployment Change</p>
<p>The Unemployment Change measures the absolute change in the number of unemployed people using seasonally adjusted data. A rise in this indicator has negative implications for consumer spending.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[In Todays Headline TV CryptoDaily News:
<p></p>
<p>Bitcoin was trading 20% lower on Binance Australia</p>
<p>Bitcoin was trading at about 20% discount on Binance&rsquo;s Australia arm, compared with rival exchanges. This comes after Binance Australia halted Australian dollar bank transfers earlier this month, citing its third-party payment service provider as the issue and said that it's working to find an alternative</p>
<p>Bali plans to deport and punish tourists that pay with crypto</p>
<p>Bali's provincial government declared that any foreigners using&nbsp; cryptocurrency instead of the Indonesian rupiah would be met with harsh punishment. The Bank of Indonesia tolerates crypto but has explicitly prohibited it as a payment method since 2017.</p>
<p>Bybit will be exiting Canada</p>
<p>Bybit has announced that it will be exiting the Canadian market starting as soon as today due to recent regulatory developments in the country, adding to several other exchanges that pulled out from the country.</p>
The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained a moderate 0.1% in the last session.
<p>The Bitcoin-Dollar pair gained 0.1% in the last session after rising as much as 1.0% during the session. The RSI is giving a positive signal, which matches our overall technical analysis. Support is at 270541 and resistance is at 288221.</p>
<p>The RSI is currently in positive territory.</p>
<p></p>
ETH/USD gained 0.6% in the last session.
<p>The Ethereum-Dollar pair gained 0.6% in the last session after rising as much as 1.2% during the session. The Ultimate Oscillator is giving a positive signal. Support is at 1851.5167 and resistance is at 1946.2167.</p>
<p>The Ultimate Oscillator is currently in the positive zone.</p>
<p></p>
XRP/USD exploded 5.9% in the last session.
<p>The Ripple-Dollar pair skyrocketed 5.9% in the last session. The Stochastic-RSI indicates an overbought market. Support is at 0.4695 and resistance is at 0.5074.</p>
<p>The Stochastic-RSI points to an overbought market.</p>
<p></p>
LTC/USD skyrocketed 1.2% in the last session.
<p>The Litecoin-Dollar pair exploded 1.2% in the last session. The ROC's negative signal contradicts our overall technical analysis. Support is at 89.1533 and resistance is at 93.0133.</p>
<p>The ROC is giving a negative signal.</p>
<p></p>
Daily Economic Calendar:
<p>DE Unemployment Rate</p>
<p>The Unemployment Rate measures the percentage of unemployed people in the country. A high percentage indicates weakness in the labor market. Germany's Unemployment Rate will be released at 07:55 GMT, Australia's Construction Work Done at 01:30 GMT, and the US Fed's Beige Book at 18:00 GMT.</p>
<p>AU Construction Work Done</p>
<p>The Construction Work Done measures the amount of construction work done in the last month. It is a key indicator of the Australian construction sector.</p>
<p>US Fed's Beige Book</p>
<p>The Beige Book reports on the current economic situation using interviews with key business contacts, economists, market experts, and other sources.</p>
<p>JP Annualized Housing Starts</p>
<p>The Annualized Housing Starts captures how many new single-family homes or buildings were constructed annually. It is a key indicator of the housing market. Japan's Annualized Housing Starts will be released at 05:00 GMT, the US Chicago Purchasing Managers' Index at 13:45 GMT, and Germany's Unemployment Change at 07:55 GMT.</p>
<p>US Chicago PMI</p>
<p>The Chicago Purchasing Managers Index released by ISM-Chicago captures the business conditions across Illinois, Indiana, and Michigan. </p>
<p>DE Unemployment Change</p>
<p>The Unemployment Change measures the absolute change in the number of unemployed people using seasonally adjusted data. A rise in this indicator has negative implications for consumer spending.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[ByBit Joins Long List Of Crypto Exchanges To Exit Canada]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bybit-joins-long-list-of-crypto-exchanges-to-exit-canada</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bybit-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bybit-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/bybit-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 09:41:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/bybit-joins-long-list-of-crypto-exchanges-to-exit-canada</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>ByBit has become the latest cryptocurrency exchange to exit Canada and plans to shutter all services and products offered in the country. The announcement was made on the 30th of May.</p>
<p>ByBit joins a growing list of cryptocurrency exchanges that are exiting Canada, citing an unfavorable regulatory environment.&nbsp;</p>
ByBit To Shutter Canadian Operations
<p>ByBit added that Canadian users would be unable to access any services and products offered by the exchange. Furthermore, Canadian users will also be unable to open new accounts on the exchange starting from the 31st of May. The exchange announced the news in a blog post, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It has always been Bybit&rsquo;s primary objective to operate our business in compliance with all relevant rules and regulations in Canada. In light of recent regulatory development, Bybit has made the difficult but necessary decision to pause the availability of our products and services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Additionally, existing users will not be able to trade or make deposits on the platform after the 31st of July, 2023. The exchange also asked its users in Canada to close out their positions by the 30th of September. Failure to wind down the positions would result in the automatic liquidation of any and all positions in both derivative contracts and margin products.</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;Canadian Customers who are implicated by these measures should take steps by the 30th of September, 2023, 8 AM UTC, to wind down and manage their positions. Failing which, open positions in any margin products and derivative contracts, including the following products listed below, will be liquidated, and the liquidated funds will be available for withdrawal.&rdquo;</p>

A Mass Exodus&nbsp;
<p>ByBit becomes the latest in a long line of cryptocurrency exchanges that have chosen to leave the Canadian markets, citing the unfavorable regulatory environment prevailing in the country. Canada had imposed several new regulations on the crypto industry in the country and given exchanges the option of complying with them or leaving the markets. The new rules bar crypto exchanges from offering any type of leverage, including margin and credit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, exchanges were also prevented from allowing the purchase or deposit of stablecoins without obtaining prior written consent from regulators, leading to a de-facto ban on stablecoins in the country. This de-facto ban on stablecoins is the primary driver of the mass exodus of cryptocurrency exchanges from the country. Some of the notable exits include Paxos, dYdX, Bittrex, OKX, and Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance had halted its services for Canadian users under similar circumstances back in May, stating that the current regulatory landscape made operations unfavorable. The exchange had stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Unfortunately, new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits provided to crypto exchanges makes the Canadian market no longer tenable for Binance at this time. We put off this decision as long as we could to explore other reasonable avenues to protect our Canadian users, but it has become apparent that there are none.&rdquo;</p>

<p>OKX had announced the suspension of services in Canada as early as March. This was followed by dYdX and Paxos in April, with both announcing they were withdrawing from the Canadian markets.</p>
Not All Exchanges Eying An Exit&nbsp;
<p>However, not all exchanges are looking to exit the Canadian markets and have decided to comply with the new regulations, despite the restrictions. Kraken and Coinbase are two of the major exchanges that have pledged to continue operations in Canada and have gone on record to state they would comply with the new rules. Coinbase Canada, the exchange&rsquo;s Canadian arm, has signed a pre-registration undertaking (PRU) with regulators and has pledged to help create a strong regulatory framework.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We applaud the Canadian securities regulators&rsquo; efforts to bring clarity to the industry and look forward to continuing our collaboration with them on regulation that protects consumers while embracing innovation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase vice-president of international and business development, Nana Murugesan, stated that the Canadian approach to crypto is better than America&rsquo;s because the rules are clearly defined.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;There&rsquo;s a couple of ways we see regulators acting: one is regulation by engagement; the other one is regulation by enforcement. The latter part is tough because you don&rsquo;t know what the rules are. But the Canadian regulator is definitely the former, which is regulation by engagement &ndash; which we love.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Kraken also made its intention of staying in the Canadian markets clear by announcing that it had filed a PRU with Canadian regulators. Kraken pointed out an OSC survey stating that 31% of Canadians planned to buy crypto next year as the main reason to stay in the market. Other exchanges that have filed a PRU with Canadian regulators include Gemini, Shakepay, and BitBuy. BitBuy is one of the top exchanges in Canada and was brought under the regulatory umbrella much before others, such as Kraken, Coinbase, and Gemini.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ByBit has become the latest cryptocurrency exchange to exit Canada and plans to shutter all services and products offered in the country. The announcement was made on the 30th of May.</p>
<p>ByBit joins a growing list of cryptocurrency exchanges that are exiting Canada, citing an unfavorable regulatory environment.&nbsp;</p>
ByBit To Shutter Canadian Operations
<p>ByBit added that Canadian users would be unable to access any services and products offered by the exchange. Furthermore, Canadian users will also be unable to open new accounts on the exchange starting from the 31st of May. The exchange announced the news in a blog post, stating,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;It has always been Bybit&rsquo;s primary objective to operate our business in compliance with all relevant rules and regulations in Canada. In light of recent regulatory development, Bybit has made the difficult but necessary decision to pause the availability of our products and services.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Additionally, existing users will not be able to trade or make deposits on the platform after the 31st of July, 2023. The exchange also asked its users in Canada to close out their positions by the 30th of September. Failure to wind down the positions would result in the automatic liquidation of any and all positions in both derivative contracts and margin products.</p>

<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;Canadian Customers who are implicated by these measures should take steps by the 30th of September, 2023, 8 AM UTC, to wind down and manage their positions. Failing which, open positions in any margin products and derivative contracts, including the following products listed below, will be liquidated, and the liquidated funds will be available for withdrawal.&rdquo;</p>

A Mass Exodus&nbsp;
<p>ByBit becomes the latest in a long line of cryptocurrency exchanges that have chosen to leave the Canadian markets, citing the unfavorable regulatory environment prevailing in the country. Canada had imposed several new regulations on the crypto industry in the country and given exchanges the option of complying with them or leaving the markets. The new rules bar crypto exchanges from offering any type of leverage, including margin and credit.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Furthermore, exchanges were also prevented from allowing the purchase or deposit of stablecoins without obtaining prior written consent from regulators, leading to a de-facto ban on stablecoins in the country. This de-facto ban on stablecoins is the primary driver of the mass exodus of cryptocurrency exchanges from the country. Some of the notable exits include Paxos, dYdX, Bittrex, OKX, and Binance.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Binance had halted its services for Canadian users under similar circumstances back in May, stating that the current regulatory landscape made operations unfavorable. The exchange had stated at the time,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Unfortunately, new guidance related to stablecoins and investor limits provided to crypto exchanges makes the Canadian market no longer tenable for Binance at this time. We put off this decision as long as we could to explore other reasonable avenues to protect our Canadian users, but it has become apparent that there are none.&rdquo;</p>

<p>OKX had announced the suspension of services in Canada as early as March. This was followed by dYdX and Paxos in April, with both announcing they were withdrawing from the Canadian markets.</p>
Not All Exchanges Eying An Exit&nbsp;
<p>However, not all exchanges are looking to exit the Canadian markets and have decided to comply with the new regulations, despite the restrictions. Kraken and Coinbase are two of the major exchanges that have pledged to continue operations in Canada and have gone on record to state they would comply with the new rules. Coinbase Canada, the exchange&rsquo;s Canadian arm, has signed a pre-registration undertaking (PRU) with regulators and has pledged to help create a strong regulatory framework.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;We applaud the Canadian securities regulators&rsquo; efforts to bring clarity to the industry and look forward to continuing our collaboration with them on regulation that protects consumers while embracing innovation.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Coinbase vice-president of international and business development, Nana Murugesan, stated that the Canadian approach to crypto is better than America&rsquo;s because the rules are clearly defined.&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;There&rsquo;s a couple of ways we see regulators acting: one is regulation by engagement; the other one is regulation by enforcement. The latter part is tough because you don&rsquo;t know what the rules are. But the Canadian regulator is definitely the former, which is regulation by engagement &ndash; which we love.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Kraken also made its intention of staying in the Canadian markets clear by announcing that it had filed a PRU with Canadian regulators. Kraken pointed out an OSC survey stating that 31% of Canadians planned to buy crypto next year as the main reason to stay in the market. Other exchanges that have filed a PRU with Canadian regulators include Gemini, Shakepay, and BitBuy. BitBuy is one of the top exchanges in Canada and was brought under the regulatory umbrella much before others, such as Kraken, Coinbase, and Gemini.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Tether To Begin Bitcoin Mining In Uruguay, Use Renewable Energy]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-to-begin-bitcoin-mining-in-uruguay-use-renewable-energy</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/tether-1450-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 08:44:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/tether-to-begin-bitcoin-mining-in-uruguay-use-renewable-energy</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>USDT stablecoin issuer Tether has announced its foray into Bitcoin mining and plans to set up Bitcoin mining operations in Uruguay using renewable energy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes on the heels of the stablecoin issuer stating that it would begin to purchase Bitcoin at regular intervals using its profits.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Foray Into Mining&nbsp;
<p>The company announced that it would soon begin mining operations in the country and has entered into a partnership with a local licensed company. However, Tether has not shared the name or any other details regarding the local entity. The news about the company&rsquo;s entry into the mining space comes soon after it announced that it would invest around 15% of its profits into purchasing Bitcoin in an effort to strengthen its reserves, similar to strategies adopted by Tesla and MicroStrategy. The announcement also indicates that Tether is bullish about the prospects of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency. CTO of Tether Paolo Ardonio stated in the announcement,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;By harnessing the power of Bitcoin and Uruguay&rsquo;s renewable energy capabilities, Tether is leading the way in sustainable and responsible Bitcoin mining. Our unwavering commitment to renewable energy ensures that every Bitcoin we mine leaves a minimal ecological footprint while upholding the security and integrity of the Bitcoin network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether also added that it is on the lookout for experts to help the company expand its footprint in the renewable energy space. Bitcoin mining is extremely energy intensive and relies on a distributed global network of computers to verify transactions and release new Bitcoin tokens into circulation.&nbsp;</p>
Is Uruguay The Ideal Location?&nbsp;
<p>Tether also shared its reasoning behind choosing Uruguay to set up its Bitcoin mining operations. In its announcement, Tether stated that the South American country had emerged as a major global leader in renewable energy. In fact, the country has generated 94% of its electricity from renewable sources such as solar power and wind energy. Tether stated in its announcement,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Blessed with abundant natural resources, Uruguay offers ideal conditions for the production of renewable energy, facilitating the establishment of wind farms, solar parks, and hydropower projects, guaranteeing a consistent supply of clean and environmentally friendly energy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether is also looking to hire people in various roles in its new Bitcoin mining and energy venture and plans to expand its Bitcoin mining operations to several other countries.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Controversial Past&nbsp;
<p>Tether is the entity that issues the USDT, which is the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, with a circulating supply of 83,184,323,408 USDT. It competes with other major stablecoins in the market, such as Binance&rsquo;s BUSD and Circle&rsquo;s USDC stablecoins. According to Tether, each of its USDT stablecoins is backed in a 1:1 ratio by US-denominated assets held in reserve. However, the company has gotten into trouble with regulators, with several questions raised about the integrity of the assets backing the stablecoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Previously, Tether held all its reserve assets in the form of reserve paper, which is a less liquid form of corporate debt. However, the company has since replaced all the commercial paper held by it with US Treasuries.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>USDT stablecoin issuer Tether has announced its foray into Bitcoin mining and plans to set up Bitcoin mining operations in Uruguay using renewable energy.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The announcement comes on the heels of the stablecoin issuer stating that it would begin to purchase Bitcoin at regular intervals using its profits.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Foray Into Mining&nbsp;
<p>The company announced that it would soon begin mining operations in the country and has entered into a partnership with a local licensed company. However, Tether has not shared the name or any other details regarding the local entity. The news about the company&rsquo;s entry into the mining space comes soon after it announced that it would invest around 15% of its profits into purchasing Bitcoin in an effort to strengthen its reserves, similar to strategies adopted by Tesla and MicroStrategy. The announcement also indicates that Tether is bullish about the prospects of the world&rsquo;s largest cryptocurrency. CTO of Tether Paolo Ardonio stated in the announcement,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;By harnessing the power of Bitcoin and Uruguay&rsquo;s renewable energy capabilities, Tether is leading the way in sustainable and responsible Bitcoin mining. Our unwavering commitment to renewable energy ensures that every Bitcoin we mine leaves a minimal ecological footprint while upholding the security and integrity of the Bitcoin network.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether also added that it is on the lookout for experts to help the company expand its footprint in the renewable energy space. Bitcoin mining is extremely energy intensive and relies on a distributed global network of computers to verify transactions and release new Bitcoin tokens into circulation.&nbsp;</p>
Is Uruguay The Ideal Location?&nbsp;
<p>Tether also shared its reasoning behind choosing Uruguay to set up its Bitcoin mining operations. In its announcement, Tether stated that the South American country had emerged as a major global leader in renewable energy. In fact, the country has generated 94% of its electricity from renewable sources such as solar power and wind energy. Tether stated in its announcement,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Blessed with abundant natural resources, Uruguay offers ideal conditions for the production of renewable energy, facilitating the establishment of wind farms, solar parks, and hydropower projects, guaranteeing a consistent supply of clean and environmentally friendly energy.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Tether is also looking to hire people in various roles in its new Bitcoin mining and energy venture and plans to expand its Bitcoin mining operations to several other countries.&nbsp;</p>
Tether&rsquo;s Controversial Past&nbsp;
<p>Tether is the entity that issues the USDT, which is the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, with a circulating supply of 83,184,323,408 USDT. It competes with other major stablecoins in the market, such as Binance&rsquo;s BUSD and Circle&rsquo;s USDC stablecoins. According to Tether, each of its USDT stablecoins is backed in a 1:1 ratio by US-denominated assets held in reserve. However, the company has gotten into trouble with regulators, with several questions raised about the integrity of the assets backing the stablecoin.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Previously, Tether held all its reserve assets in the form of reserve paper, which is a less liquid form of corporate debt. However, the company has since replaced all the commercial paper held by it with US Treasuries.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Whales Follow HedgeUp Presale Offer, Big Eyes Coin Set for Big Launch, Hope For Stellar]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/whales-follow-hedgeup-presale-offer-big-eyes-coin-set-for-big-launch-hope-for-stellar</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-626.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-626.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-626.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 01:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/whales-follow-hedgeup-presale-offer-big-eyes-coin-set-for-big-launch-hope-for-stellar</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, new projects and developments emerge, attracting attention and sparking excitement among investors. In this article, we will explore three notable developments: Big Eyes Coin (BIG) gearing up for its June 15 launch, HedgeUp (HDUP) presale attracts Bitcoin (BTC) and Monero (XMR) whales, and the potential bounce in Stellar (XLM) price despite its fragile outlook. These developments offer unique perspectives on the cryptocurrency landscape and highlight the opportunities and challenges that investors may encounter.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin Unpacks The Power Of Memes To Build An Ecosystem For Success</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin is set to launch on June 15, following a successful presale campaign that edges closer to raising $50 million. $BIG stands out as a meme token, featuring an adorable cat as its central theme. With impressive presale performance and strong community support, BIG is poised for growth and has attracted significant attention. The upcoming launch presents an opportunity for investors to participate in a project that has already generated substantial interest and funding. The token's integration of a casino and its approach to building a dedicated ecosystem add further appeal to the investment proposition. The presale for $BIG is coming to an end on June 3rd with the available token supply predicted to be sold out in the next 48 hours. The current presale valuation is locked in at $0.00017 with the valuation expected to increase by 250% or $0.0006.</p>
<p>HedgeUp Empowers Traders With Asset-Backed Trading</p>
<p>HedgeUp is an emerging trading platform that introduces the concept of asset-backed trading. Its recent presale has garnered attention from influential Bitcoin (BTC) and Monero (XMR) whales, renowned for their strategic investments and ability to influence market trends. The unique value proposition of HedgeUp, along with its potential for high returns, has attracted these whales, who see it as a groundbreaking project. Bitcoin whales, in particular, are interested in projects that can replicate or surpass the success of Bitcoin. HedgeUp's commitment to security and its innovative approach to trading make it an enticing option for investors seeking both risk mitigation and profitability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Stellar In Search For A Short-Term Rebound Amidst Long-Term Uncertainty</p>
<p>Despite a decline in the Stellar (XLM) price since April and a fragile outlook in the long term, there are indications of a potential bounce in the short term. Stellar lost a crucial horizontal area during its downward movement, but the short-term chart suggests the possibility of a rebound. While the long-term readings remain bearish, traders and investors are closely watching for any signs of a bounce. Stellar's underlying technology and partnerships continue to drive interest, and a short-term recovery could provide an opportunity for those looking to capitalize on market movements.</p>
<p>Crypto Market Relishes HedgeUp Presale Offer, BIG Launch, and Hopeful Stellar</p>
<p>These three developments reflect the dynamic nature of the cryptocurrency market, offering investors diverse opportunities and challenges. Big Eyes Coin's impending launch and successful presale demonstrate the potential for meme tokens to capture the market's attention and generate significant funding. HedgeUp's attracting of Bitcoin and Monero whales underscores the appeal of asset-backed trading platforms and the search for high returns among seasoned investors. Stellar's price dynamics highlight the volatility and potential for short-term rebounds, while also emphasizing the importance of long-term outlooks and technological advancements.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The world of cryptocurrencies continues to evolve, presenting exciting developments and opportunities for investors. Big Eyes Coin, HedgeUp, and Stellar exemplify the diverse projects and trends within the market. From meme tokens to asset-backed trading platforms and established cryptocurrencies, each presents its unique value proposition and challenges. As investors navigate this landscape, conducting thorough research and staying informed about market trends is crucial. The cryptocurrency market remains dynamic, and prudent decision-making is vital to success.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG)</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/BigEyesCoin/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, new projects and developments emerge, attracting attention and sparking excitement among investors. In this article, we will explore three notable developments: Big Eyes Coin (BIG) gearing up for its June 15 launch, HedgeUp (HDUP) presale attracts Bitcoin (BTC) and Monero (XMR) whales, and the potential bounce in Stellar (XLM) price despite its fragile outlook. These developments offer unique perspectives on the cryptocurrency landscape and highlight the opportunities and challenges that investors may encounter.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin Unpacks The Power Of Memes To Build An Ecosystem For Success</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin is set to launch on June 15, following a successful presale campaign that edges closer to raising $50 million. $BIG stands out as a meme token, featuring an adorable cat as its central theme. With impressive presale performance and strong community support, BIG is poised for growth and has attracted significant attention. The upcoming launch presents an opportunity for investors to participate in a project that has already generated substantial interest and funding. The token's integration of a casino and its approach to building a dedicated ecosystem add further appeal to the investment proposition. The presale for $BIG is coming to an end on June 3rd with the available token supply predicted to be sold out in the next 48 hours. The current presale valuation is locked in at $0.00017 with the valuation expected to increase by 250% or $0.0006.</p>
<p>HedgeUp Empowers Traders With Asset-Backed Trading</p>
<p>HedgeUp is an emerging trading platform that introduces the concept of asset-backed trading. Its recent presale has garnered attention from influential Bitcoin (BTC) and Monero (XMR) whales, renowned for their strategic investments and ability to influence market trends. The unique value proposition of HedgeUp, along with its potential for high returns, has attracted these whales, who see it as a groundbreaking project. Bitcoin whales, in particular, are interested in projects that can replicate or surpass the success of Bitcoin. HedgeUp's commitment to security and its innovative approach to trading make it an enticing option for investors seeking both risk mitigation and profitability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Stellar In Search For A Short-Term Rebound Amidst Long-Term Uncertainty</p>
<p>Despite a decline in the Stellar (XLM) price since April and a fragile outlook in the long term, there are indications of a potential bounce in the short term. Stellar lost a crucial horizontal area during its downward movement, but the short-term chart suggests the possibility of a rebound. While the long-term readings remain bearish, traders and investors are closely watching for any signs of a bounce. Stellar's underlying technology and partnerships continue to drive interest, and a short-term recovery could provide an opportunity for those looking to capitalize on market movements.</p>
<p>Crypto Market Relishes HedgeUp Presale Offer, BIG Launch, and Hopeful Stellar</p>
<p>These three developments reflect the dynamic nature of the cryptocurrency market, offering investors diverse opportunities and challenges. Big Eyes Coin's impending launch and successful presale demonstrate the potential for meme tokens to capture the market's attention and generate significant funding. HedgeUp's attracting of Bitcoin and Monero whales underscores the appeal of asset-backed trading platforms and the search for high returns among seasoned investors. Stellar's price dynamics highlight the volatility and potential for short-term rebounds, while also emphasizing the importance of long-term outlooks and technological advancements.</p>
<p>Conclusion</p>
<p>The world of cryptocurrencies continues to evolve, presenting exciting developments and opportunities for investors. Big Eyes Coin, HedgeUp, and Stellar exemplify the diverse projects and trends within the market. From meme tokens to asset-backed trading platforms and established cryptocurrencies, each presents its unique value proposition and challenges. As investors navigate this landscape, conducting thorough research and staying informed about market trends is crucial. The cryptocurrency market remains dynamic, and prudent decision-making is vital to success.</p>
<p>Big Eyes Coin (BIG)</p>
<p>Presale: https://buy.bigeyes.space/</p>
<p>Website: https://bigeyes.space/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Telegram: https://t.me/BIGEYESOFFICIAL</p>
<p>Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/BigEyesCoin/&nbsp;</p>
<p>Twitter: https://twitter.com/BigEyesCoin</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto AI spikes post debt ceiling agreement]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-ai-spikes-post-debt-ceiling-agreement</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aicrypto.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aicrypto.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/aicrypto.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:57:37 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/05/crypto-ai-spikes-post-debt-ceiling-agreement</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>A debt ceiling agreement appears to have been reached, but a vote is still needed. Crypto AI tokens are rising strongly.</p>
Still some way to go to agree debt ceiling
<p>Amid mutterings of discontent about the debt ceiling deal, especially on the Republican side, the issue is due to be put before the House. Republican lawmaker Chip Roy put it into perspective by remarking in a tweet on Sunday:</p>
<p>&ldquo;they haven&rsquo;t been educated yet on what a t*rd-sandwich this &ldquo;deal&rdquo; is.&nbsp; They will be.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Republicans and Democrats need to get the deal voted on and passed by June 6. Should they fail to do so, a most unlikely scenario, the US government would default on its debt for the first time in history.</p>
Crypto is a hedge out of the debt debacle
<p>Bitcoin and crypto are receiving an advantage of the uncertainty as investors dip their feet into the asset class in order to diversify and hedge their risk.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, it&rsquo;s not the entire crypto sector that is benefiting. Bitcoin and ethereum are looking strong, as are some of the more fundamentally sound tokens, although the sector as a whole is still flat after the crypto rally from the beginning of the year - that is with the exception of the artificial intelligence niche.</p>
AI tokens make strong moves to the upside
<p>Certain of these AI tokens have surged considerably today. Ocean (OCEAN) has been one of the most prominent of the AI crypto tokens to make some great gains in the last several hours. From a price of $0.34 OCEAN rose as high as $0.39 - a 14% increase. Now the token looks to be forming a flag at the upper limit of a trendline formed since early February. A further break to the upside is a possibility.</p>
<p>SingularityNET (AGIX) is another trendline breaker. It has managed 13% in all today, but the price is still to come back and retest the trendline before potentially going much higher.</p>
<p>Possibly the most successful of the AI tokens so far today is Matrix.ai (MAN). MAN surged more than 30% in just the last two hours, taking it to a price of just under $0.32. The price has since returned to $0.30, but there does appear to be more in the tank for a potential move higher.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A debt ceiling agreement appears to have been reached, but a vote is still needed. Crypto AI tokens are rising strongly.</p>
Still some way to go to agree debt ceiling
<p>Amid mutterings of discontent about the debt ceiling deal, especially on the Republican side, the issue is due to be put before the House. Republican lawmaker Chip Roy put it into perspective by remarking in a tweet on Sunday:</p>
<p>&ldquo;they haven&rsquo;t been educated yet on what a t*rd-sandwich this &ldquo;deal&rdquo; is.&nbsp; They will be.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Republicans and Democrats need to get the deal voted on and passed by June 6. Should they fail to do so, a most unlikely scenario, the US government would default on its debt for the first time in history.</p>
Crypto is a hedge out of the debt debacle
<p>Bitcoin and crypto are receiving an advantage of the uncertainty as investors dip their feet into the asset class in order to diversify and hedge their risk.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, it&rsquo;s not the entire crypto sector that is benefiting. Bitcoin and ethereum are looking strong, as are some of the more fundamentally sound tokens, although the sector as a whole is still flat after the crypto rally from the beginning of the year - that is with the exception of the artificial intelligence niche.</p>
AI tokens make strong moves to the upside
<p>Certain of these AI tokens have surged considerably today. Ocean (OCEAN) has been one of the most prominent of the AI crypto tokens to make some great gains in the last several hours. From a price of $0.34 OCEAN rose as high as $0.39 - a 14% increase. Now the token looks to be forming a flag at the upper limit of a trendline formed since early February. A further break to the upside is a possibility.</p>
<p>SingularityNET (AGIX) is another trendline breaker. It has managed 13% in all today, but the price is still to come back and retest the trendline before potentially going much higher.</p>
<p>Possibly the most successful of the AI tokens so far today is Matrix.ai (MAN). MAN surged more than 30% in just the last two hours, taking it to a price of just under $0.32. The price has since returned to $0.30, but there does appear to be more in the tank for a potential move higher.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
