<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:41:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>EV Charging Payments App on Blockchain Raises $310k in Presale – Invest Early in Future-Proof Project</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ev-charging-payments-solution-on-blockchain-raises-310k-in-presale-invest-early-in-future-proof-project.htm</link><description>C+Charge is an upcoming EV charging payment app that aims to streamline the charging process and provide rewards to users. The app will connect EV owners with charging networks, allowing for easy payment transactions and earning carbon credits and sustainable cryptocurrency rewards in the process.  &lt;br /&gt;
Utilizing decentralized blockchain technology, C+Charge's P2P payment system is making EV charging more efficient, cost-effective, and transparent....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ev-charging-payments-solution-on-blockchain-raises-310k-in-presale-invest-early-in-future-proof-project.htm"&gt;Read More: EV Charging Payments App on Blockchain Raises $310k in Presale – Invest Early in Future-Proof Project&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Ev Charging App</category><category>Ev Cryptocurrency</category><category>C+Charge</category><category>CCHG</category><category>Sustainable Cryptocurrency</category><category>Sustainable Crypto</category><category>Green Crypto</category><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ev-charging-payments-solution-on-blockchain-raises-310k-in-presale-invest-early-in-future-proof-project.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101752/251322/ev-charging-app-c-charge-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="2344694"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Whales Show Confidence in Latest Rally as They Refuse to Sell, On-Chain Data Reveals</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-whales-show-confidence-in-latest-rally-as-they-refuse-to-sell-on-chain-data-reveals.htm</link><description>Despite the rally in Bitcoin that has seen prices jump around 27% since the start of the year, on-chain data suggests that Bitcoin whales are not using the pump as an opportunity to sell their holdings. According to some analysts, this is a sign of confidence that the recent rally signals the start of a longer-lasting bull market....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-whales-show-confidence-in-latest-rally-as-they-refuse-to-sell-on-chain-data-reveals.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Whales Show Confidence in Latest Rally as They Refuse to Sell, On-Chain Data Reveals&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin whales</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-whales-show-confidence-in-latest-rally-as-they-refuse-to-sell-on-chain-data-reveals.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101746/251308/bitcoin-whale.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="4922850"/></item><item><title>Genesis to Declare Bankruptcy Soon While DoJ to Announce Major International Crypto Enforcement Action - Bitcoin Drops</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-to-declare-bankruptcy-soon-while-doj-to-announce-major-international-crypto-enforcement-action-bitcoin-drops.htm</link><description>Bloomberg reports that Genesis may be getting ready to declare bankruptcy. The troubled crypto lender has been under the shadow of insolvency for weeks, following the credit crisis that has hit the crypto industry. &lt;br /&gt;
Genesis was one of the largest lenders in the space, often acting as a third-party for other lending outfits promising yields way above anything available in the traditional financial markets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-to-declare-bankruptcy-soon-while-doj-to-announce-major-international-crypto-enforcement-action-bitcoin-drops.htm"&gt;Read More: Genesis to Declare Bankruptcy Soon While DoJ to Announce Major International Crypto Enforcement Action - Bitcoin Drops&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/genesis-to-declare-bankruptcy-soon-while-doj-to-announce-major-international-crypto-enforcement-action-bitcoin-drops.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101745/251302/adobestock-548367233-editorial-use-only.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="3819351"/></item><item><title>Has Bitcoin Entered Its Next Bull Market Cycle? This Analyst Thinks It Might Have</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-entered-its-next-bull-market-cycle-analyst-thinks-it-might.htm</link><description>Bitcoin may be at the start of a bull market that could last another nearly 1000 days, according to chart analysis from the pseudonymous crypto-focused Twitter account @CryptoHornHairs. According to a chart shared by CryptoHornHairs on the 11th of January, Bitcoin is at the beginning of a near four-year market cycle that it has followed closely since 2015....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-entered-its-next-bull-market-cycle-analyst-thinks-it-might.htm"&gt;Read More: Has Bitcoin Entered Its Next Bull Market Cycle? This Analyst Thinks It Might Have&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Bull Market Cycle</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-entered-its-next-bull-market-cycle-analyst-thinks-it-might.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101741/251264/bitcoin.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2906608"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Network Validators Have Surged to 500,000 as Shanghai Fever Grows</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-network-validators-surged-500000-as-shanghai-fever-grows.htm</link><description>Ethereum has reached a new milestone in adoption and security as the number of validators on its network now exceeds 500,000, according to data from BeaconScan. As to whether this milestone or the upcoming Shanghai upgrade will impact Ethereum's price, this depends on a number of factors that we'll explore below....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-network-validators-surged-500000-as-shanghai-fever-grows.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Network Validators Have Surged to 500,000 as Shanghai Fever Grows&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Shanghai Upgrade</category><category>Shanghai Update</category><category>Ethereum Shanghai Update</category><category>Shanghai Upgrade Ethereum Price</category><category>Ethereum Price</category><category>Ethereum Validators</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-network-validators-surged-500000-as-shanghai-fever-grows.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101736/251237/ethereum-price-shanhai-upgrade.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="698591"/></item><item><title>Would a US Debt Default Derail Crypto Price Rally or Embolden It?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/would-us-debt-default-derail-crypto-price-rally-or-embolden-it.htm</link><description>The rising interest rates in the US mean that the US government is now paying more in interest repayments on their debt than the entirety of their spending on their armed forces.  &lt;br /&gt;
The current debt repayments are going to be a difficult burden for the US taxpayer to bear, particularly when one considers that we are also now in a cost of living crisis. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/would-us-debt-default-derail-crypto-price-rally-or-embolden-it.htm"&gt;Read More: Would a US Debt Default Derail Crypto Price Rally or Embolden It?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/would-us-debt-default-derail-crypto-price-rally-or-embolden-it.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101670/251107/1200px-flag-of-the-united-states-svg.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="207167"/></item><item><title>Coinbase Exits Japan Citing "Market Conditions"</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-exits-japan-citing-market-conditions.htm</link><description>Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase is exiting Japan due to market conditions. The move comes days after the company announced its third round of layoffs in less than a year amid the ongoing bear market.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Wednesday blog post, the exchange said it has made the "difficult decision" to halt operations in Japan and conduct a complete review of its business in the country due to market conditions. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-exits-japan-citing-market-conditions.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase Exits Japan Citing "Market Conditions"&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Crypto Exchange</category><category>Japan</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-exits-japan-citing-market-conditions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101728/251193/adobestock-gguy-1-media-library-original-1350-901-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="188179"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Coinbase Halts Japan Operations, Digital Currency Group is Suspending Quarterly Dividends, Amber Group is Slashing Costs and Jobs</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-halts-japan-operations-digital-currency-group-is-suspending-quarterly-dividends-amber-group-is-slashing-costs-and-jobs.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-halts-japan-operations-digital-currency-group-is-suspending-quarterly-dividends-amber-group-is-slashing-costs-and-jobs.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Coinbase Halts Japan Operations, Digital Currency Group is Suspending Quarterly Dividends, Amber Group is Slashing Costs and Jobs&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Japan</category><category>Switzerland</category><category>ConsenSys</category><category>Legal</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Investment</category><category>Web3</category><category>Gaming</category><category>Dapp</category><category>Mining</category><category>Griid</category><category>Hong Kong</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-coinbase-halts-japan-operations-digital-currency-group-is-suspending-quarterly-dividends-amber-group-is-slashing-costs-and-jobs.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101681/251176/adobestock-ra2-studio-1.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="176714"/></item><item><title>Solana Price is Up 87% in a Month - Buy Before Recovery Takes the Price Past $30 Soon?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-is-up-87-in-a-month-buy-before-recovery-takes-the-price-past-30-soon.htm</link><description>The Solana price explosive move since late December has seen investors rush back to the project in the wake of the FTX implosion. Recovery began with a final dip to $8.05, riding on the momentum created by BONK, the first meme token on the Solana blockchain....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-is-up-87-in-a-month-buy-before-recovery-takes-the-price-past-30-soon.htm"&gt;Read More: Solana Price is Up 87% in a Month - Buy Before Recovery Takes the Price Past $30 Soon?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/solana-price-is-up-87-in-a-month-buy-before-recovery-takes-the-price-past-30-soon.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101711/251175/sol-1d-graph-coinmarketcap-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="173892"/></item><item><title>Why Casper Enterprise Friendly PoW Coin is 15% Higher Today at $0.039 - Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-casper-enterprise-friendly-pow-coin-is-15-higher-today-at-0038-time-to-buy.htm</link><description>CSPR's price has exploded in recent days and is currently up 8% in the past 24 hours to trade at $0.03924. What's driving this upward trend and will Casper's price continue to rise – or is this just a temporary surge? &lt;br /&gt;
The positive sentiment in the overall cryptocurrency market, along with bets on the Fed easing rate hikes in early 2023, are cited as potential factors driving the rally....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/why-casper-enterprise-friendly-pow-coin-is-15-higher-today-at-0038-time-to-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Why Casper Enterprise Friendly PoW Coin is 15% Higher Today at $0.039 - Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Casper Price</category><category>Casper Price Prediction</category><category>Cspr Price</category><category>Cspr Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/why-casper-enterprise-friendly-pow-coin-is-15-higher-today-at-0038-time-to-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101710/251163/casper.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="693186"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin and Other Crypto Prices Pump After US Retail Sales and PPI Inflation Falls More Than Expected</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-pump-as-us-retail-sales-producer-price-inflation-fall-more-than-expected.htm</link><description>Bitcoin and wider crypto prices are getting a strong tailwind today after the release of the latest US economic data shows softening inflation and slowing retail sales. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin at the time of writing is priced at $21,565, up 0.9% and Ethereum is currently 0.85% higher at $1,602. &lt;br /&gt;
The closely watched US retail sales figure fell -1.1%, greater than the -0.8% forecast by economists....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-pump-as-us-retail-sales-producer-price-inflation-fall-more-than-expected.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin and Other Crypto Prices Pump After US Retail Sales and PPI Inflation Falls More Than Expected&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-prices-pump-as-us-retail-sales-producer-price-inflation-fall-more-than-expected.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101703/251157/bitcoin-take-off.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="663159"/></item><item><title>Researchers Say These 7 Factors Will Determine Bitcoin Prices in 2023</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-say-these-7-factors-will-determine-bitcoin-prices-2023.htm</link><description>Researchers at the South Korean crypto exchange Bithumb have named seven factors they believe will affect bitcoin (BTC) and crypto prices in 2023 – and determine whether the bear market will give way to bullish forces for a sustained period. &lt;br /&gt;
The crypto exchange’s researchers claimed that bitcoin prices could rise to the $42,000 mark in the next 12 months – provided certain events come to pass....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-say-these-7-factors-will-determine-bitcoin-prices-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: Researchers Say These 7 Factors Will Determine Bitcoin Prices in 2023&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Bithumb</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/researchers-say-these-7-factors-will-determine-bitcoin-prices-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101658/251087/adobestock-557379083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="8533806"/></item><item><title>Would a Clear Out of Crypto Moguls and Their Centralized Companies Be Good for the Digital Asset Class?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/would-clear-out-of-crypto-moguls-their-centralized-companies-good-for-digital-asset-class.htm</link><description>As more and more crypto companies face scrutiny – and some throw in the towel after a rough bear market - questions are being raised whether that could be a good thing for crypto after all....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/would-clear-out-of-crypto-moguls-their-centralized-companies-good-for-digital-asset-class.htm"&gt;Read More: Would a Clear Out of Crypto Moguls and Their Centralized Companies Be Good for the Digital Asset Class?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Gemini</category><category>Digital Currency Group</category><category>Barry Silbert</category><category>Binance</category><category>FTX</category><category>Mike Novogratz</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/would-clear-out-of-crypto-moguls-their-centralized-companies-good-for-digital-asset-class.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101695/251142/clear-out-of-crypto-companies.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="67891"/></item><item><title>Can Dogecoin Price Kill a Zero as it Climbs 6% to $0.088 as Meme Coins Gain Traction</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-dogecoin-price-kill-zero-as-it-climbs-6-0088-as-meme-coins-gain-traction-ji.htm</link><description>Dogecoin price continues to outperform its peers as it inches closer to obliterating one zero. In just 14 days, DOGE’s value has grown by 22.2% to trade at $0.088 at the time of writing. The largest meme coin will probably close the week above $0.1 as the bulls eye a return to $0.1586....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/can-dogecoin-price-kill-zero-as-it-climbs-6-0088-as-meme-coins-gain-traction-ji.htm"&gt;Read More: Can Dogecoin Price Kill a Zero as it Climbs 6% to $0.088 as Meme Coins Gain Traction&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Dogecoin</category><category>Dogecoin price prediction</category><category>DOGE</category><category>DOGEUSD</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 12:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/can-dogecoin-price-kill-zero-as-it-climbs-6-0088-as-meme-coins-gain-traction-ji.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101686/251141/dogeusd-2023-01-18-14-29-34.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="297609"/></item><item><title>Bernstein Analyst - Institutions Need to Give Up on Zero Crypto Strategies and Start Allocating Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-analyst-institutions-need-to-give-up-on-zero-crypto-strategies-and-start-allocating-now.htm</link><description>Brokerage firm Bernstein has advised institutions to dabble into crypto and give up their "zero crypto allocation" strategy.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a research report on Monday, the asset manager said crypto is poised to pivot from a fat infrastructure thesis to a fat application thesis in 2023, laying the foundations for a decade-long “golden age” of innovation for cryptocurrency applications. The company also said 2023 will be the best year for institutions to create their crypto strategy....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-analyst-institutions-need-to-give-up-on-zero-crypto-strategies-and-start-allocating-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Bernstein Analyst - Institutions Need to Give Up on Zero Crypto Strategies and Start Allocating Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Bernstein</category><category>Adoption</category><category>CRYPTO</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 12:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bernstein-analyst-institutions-need-to-give-up-on-zero-crypto-strategies-and-start-allocating-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101685/251138/man-gfc364a8e0-1920.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="260411"/></item><item><title>Fantasy Battle Card Play to Earn Game Calvaria Nears $3m in Presale but Finishing Soon So Move Fast to Invest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantasy-battle-card-play-earn-game-calvaria-nears-3m-presale-but-finishing-soon-so-move-fast-invest-1.htm</link><description>Disclaimer: The Industry Talk section features insights by crypto industry players and is not a part of the editorial content of Cryptonews.com &lt;br /&gt;
Calvaria's native token, RIA, has raised over $2.83 million from its presale, with only 8% of the tokens left to be purchased. The presale is finishing soon, and interested investors can still purchase it before it ends....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/fantasy-battle-card-play-earn-game-calvaria-nears-3m-presale-but-finishing-soon-so-move-fast-invest-1.htm"&gt;Read More: Fantasy Battle Card Play to Earn Game Calvaria Nears $3m in Presale but Finishing Soon So Move Fast to Invest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/fantasy-battle-card-play-earn-game-calvaria-nears-3m-presale-but-finishing-soon-so-move-fast-invest-1.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/101677/251131/1eb55533-5d0b-40a6-9e72-917bffc97e35.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="201012"/></item></channel></rss>
