<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://v2.cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Breaks Above $27,000 Resistance – Here's Where BTC is Heading Now</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-breaks-above-27000-resistance-heres-where-btc-heading-now.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has made a significant move by breaking above the crucial resistance level of $27,000.  &lt;br /&gt;
This breakout has generated anticipation among investors and traders, who are now eagerly observing where Bitcoin's price might head next.  &lt;br /&gt;
With this breakout, BTC has entered a new territory, and the focus has shifted to identifying the next target levels and potential price movements....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-breaks-above-27000-resistance-heres-where-btc-heading-now.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Breaks Above $27,000 Resistance – Here's Where BTC is Heading Now&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-breaks-above-27000-resistance-heres-where-btc-heading-now.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115852/311359/4-4.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="481419"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction Following Huge $2 Billion Capital Surge - Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-following-huge-2-billion-capital-surge-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm</link><description>XRP, the digital asset associated with Ripple, has experienced a significant surge in the capital, with an influx of $2 billion.  &lt;br /&gt;
This notable increase in investment has sparked speculation about the potential price trajectory of XRP in the coming year.  &lt;br /&gt;
Investors and enthusiasts are now wondering if XRP has the potential to reach the $10 mark in 2023. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-following-huge-2-billion-capital-surge-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction Following Huge $2 Billion Capital Surge - Can XRP Reach $10 in 2023?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 15:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-following-huge-2-billion-capital-surge-can-xrp-reach-10-in-2023.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115850/311355/xrp.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="96866"/></item><item><title>US Senators Express Concerns over El Salvador's Bitcoin Adoption – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senators-express-concerns-over-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>El Salvador’s adoption of Bitcoin as a legal tender has caused concern among American lawmakers, who are calling for a risk report on the potential impact on bilateral economic relations and law enforcement cooperation.  &lt;br /&gt;
Last month, US Senators Jim Risch and Bob Menendez reintroduced a bipartisan bill requesting a State Department report on El Salvador’s Bitcoin adoption. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senators-express-concerns-over-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: US Senators Express Concerns over El Salvador's Bitcoin Adoption – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><category>El Salvador</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>Regulation</category><category>US Regulations</category><category>Nayib Bukele</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/us-senators-express-concerns-over-el-salvadors-bitcoin-adoption-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115846/311345/adobestock-525250918-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="406764"/></item><item><title>Trending Crypto Coins - CatGPT, Injustice Samurai, Jim, Planet Trend on DEXTools</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/trending-crypto-coins-catgpt-jim-injustice-samurai-planet-price-dextools.htm</link><description>Among the most trending crypto coins on DEXTools today are $CATGPT, $IS, $JIM, and $PLANET, topping the hot pairs list with explosive price action. &lt;br /&gt;
They're joined on the DEXTboard by Viral, Pick Or Rick (RICK), PSYOP, RefundCoin (RFD), LBR, and PEPE. Bart, BEN, and Fish have also been trending today. &lt;br /&gt;
A brand-new coin listed on Uniswap this weekend, CatGPT coin has no token description or CoinMarketCap page yet....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/trending-crypto-coins-catgpt-jim-injustice-samurai-planet-price-dextools.htm"&gt;Read More: Trending Crypto Coins - CatGPT, Injustice Samurai, Jim, Planet Trend on DEXTools&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/trending-crypto-coins-catgpt-jim-injustice-samurai-planet-price-dextools.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115847/311347/jim-token-trending-crypto-coin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="315348"/></item><item><title>Marinade (MNDE) Price Pumps 160%, LBR Trends On Liquid Staking Derivatives Influx</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/marinade-mnde-price-pumps-160-lbr-trends-liquid-staking-derivatives-influx.htm</link><description>Solana-based liquidity staking derivative (LSD) coin Marinade ($MNDE) is up 160% in a continuing weekend pump as general interest in the LSD complex grows.  &lt;br /&gt;
MNDE has risen from $0.03 at the end of Friday trading to $0.08 today, for a 166% gain.  &lt;br /&gt;
Meanwhile Lybra Finance (LBR), which motored to an all time high above $0.05 last week, has also been garnering interest. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/marinade-mnde-price-pumps-160-lbr-trends-liquid-staking-derivatives-influx.htm"&gt;Read More: Marinade (MNDE) Price Pumps 160%, LBR Trends On Liquid Staking Derivatives Influx&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Staking</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/marinade-mnde-price-pumps-160-lbr-trends-liquid-staking-derivatives-influx.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115843/311344/mnde-7d-graph-coinmarketcap.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="310530"/></item><item><title>Celsius Network's $800 Million Ether Staking Strategy Change Stretches Ethereum Validator Queue – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-800-million-ether-staking-strategy-change-stretches-ethereum-validator-queue-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>Now-defunct crypto lender Celsius Network has caused a stir with changes in its ETH staking strategy, exacerbating the already elongated queue to activate new validators on the Ethereum network.  &lt;br /&gt;
Over a period of two days, Celsius transferred ETH into staking contracts after redeeming nearly $813 million of staked ETH from Lido Finance. The company has deposited $745 million of ETH since early June, according to data provided by Arkham Intelligence. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-800-million-ether-staking-strategy-change-stretches-ethereum-validator-queue-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Celsius Network's $800 Million Ether Staking Strategy Change Stretches Ethereum Validator Queue – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Celsius Network</category><category>Celsius</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>Staking</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/celsius-networks-800-million-ether-staking-strategy-change-stretches-ethereum-validator-queue-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115842/311332/celsius-logo-media-librar.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="126532"/></item><item><title>Terra Classic Price Up 6% - Crypto Whales Buying LUNC For v2.1.0 Parity Upgrade?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-spikes-6-are-crypto-whales-accumulating-lunc.htm</link><description>The LUNC price has spiked over 6% on news of the v2.1.0 upgrade proposal being up for discussion, tweeted out by the @LUNCBurnArmy account. &lt;br /&gt;
The Terra Classic 24 hour trading volume is up approximately 300%, however the LUNC price has a long way to go to recover its September 2022 high of $0.00059. &lt;br /&gt;
The latest release from LUNC Burn Army is the third major upgrade to the Terra Classic blockchain, set to take place June 14th at approximately 17:20 UTC....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-spikes-6-are-crypto-whales-accumulating-lunc.htm"&gt;Read More: Terra Classic Price Up 6% - Crypto Whales Buying LUNC For v2.1.0 Parity Upgrade?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/terra-classic-price-spikes-6-are-crypto-whales-accumulating-lunc.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115840/311320/terra-classic-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="239316"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rebounds from Recent Bottom – Where is the Next BTC Target?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rebounds-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm</link><description>Bitcoin has made a significant recovery from its recent low point of $26,600, now trading slightly above $27,000.  &lt;br /&gt;
This upward movement has sparked speculation regarding its next potential target. &lt;br /&gt;
The cryptocurrency's price has experienced an upward movement, prompting speculation about its future trajectory....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rebounds-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Rebounds from Recent Bottom – Where is the Next BTC Target?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-btc-rebounds-from-recent-bottom-where-next-btc-target.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115835/311318/4-3.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="524437"/></item><item><title>Breaking - Atomic Wallet Hacked, Crypto Analyst ZachXBT Investigates</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/atomic-wallet-hacked-crypto-analyst-zachxbt-investigates.htm</link><description>Reports are emerging that Atomic Wallet has been hacked and user funds compromised, with some victims having their entire balance drained. &lt;br /&gt;
Earlier today, June 3rd, @AtomicWallet tweeted: &lt;br /&gt;
On-chain sleuth ZachXBT, who has in the past managed to trace where stolen funds were sent to and helped authorities make arrests, is seen below requesting the transaction hash from an affected Atomic Wallet user....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/atomic-wallet-hacked-crypto-analyst-zachxbt-investigates.htm"&gt;Read More: Breaking - Atomic Wallet Hacked, Crypto Analyst ZachXBT Investigates&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/atomic-wallet-hacked-crypto-analyst-zachxbt-investigates.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115821/311296/atomic-wallet-hacked.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="77338"/></item><item><title>Coinbase: AI and Crypto Merging Represents a Major Opportunity</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ai-crypto-merging-represents-major-opportunity.htm</link><description>Coinbase has released a research report stating that the intersection of artificial intelligence and blockchain represents a major opportunity for entrepreneurs.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a Thursday report, the largest US-based cryptocurrency exchange highlighted the benefits of combining both techs to create new solutions for societal challenges presented by AI....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ai-crypto-merging-represents-major-opportunity.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase: AI and Crypto Merging Represents a Major Opportunity&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-ai-crypto-merging-represents-major-opportunity.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115813/311277/ai-chip-media-library-ori.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="141543"/></item><item><title>Dogecoin Price Prediction as Elon Musk Hit With DOGE Insider Trading Lawsuit - Is He Pumping Meme Coins?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-hit-with-doge-insider-trading-lawsuit-is-he-pumping-meme-coins.htm</link><description>As Dogecoin continues to capture the attention of the cryptocurrency market, a recent development has raised eyebrows among investors and enthusiasts.  &lt;br /&gt;
Elon Musk, the influential billionaire and Tesla CEO, is now facing an insider trading lawsuit specifically related to his tweets and statements about Dogecoin....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-hit-with-doge-insider-trading-lawsuit-is-he-pumping-meme-coins.htm"&gt;Read More: Dogecoin Price Prediction as Elon Musk Hit With DOGE Insider Trading Lawsuit - Is He Pumping Meme Coins?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/dogecoin-price-prediction-as-elon-musk-hit-with-doge-insider-trading-lawsuit-is-he-pumping-meme-coins.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115810/311274/dogecoin-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="113615"/></item><item><title>Pick Or Rick ($RICK) Token Trends Above $PEPE On DEXTools With Elon Musk Tweet - Meme Coin Insider Trading?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/pick-or-rick-crypto-trending-above-pepe-on-dextools-after-elon-musk-tweet-meme-coin-insider-trading.htm</link><description>An episode of Adult Swim's cartoon Rick and Morty has inspired the latest meme coin on Uniswap, with the apparent help of an Elon Musk tweet - Pick Or Rick (RICK) token. &lt;br /&gt;
The RICK/WETH pair made the top ten list of hot pairs on DEXTools today, at points being the #1 trending token, higher than Pepe (PEPE)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/pick-or-rick-crypto-trending-above-pepe-on-dextools-after-elon-musk-tweet-meme-coin-insider-trading.htm"&gt;Read More: Pick Or Rick ($RICK) Token Trends Above $PEPE On DEXTools With Elon Musk Tweet - Meme Coin Insider Trading?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/pick-or-rick-crypto-trending-above-pepe-on-dextools-after-elon-musk-tweet-meme-coin-insider-trading.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115808/311263/pick-or-rick-crypto-coin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="404658"/></item><item><title>Rivaling Visa, Skyrocketing Trezor, Binancing All and 20 Crypto Jokes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/rivaling-visa-skyrocketing-trezor-binancing-all-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</link><description>This week in crypto: Ethereum transaction volume rivaled Visa as blockchain transactions soared, Tether saw its market capitalization hit a new record high, a long-forgotten Ethereum ICO wallet resurfaced with $15 million worth of funds after eight years of dormancy, and Saifedean Ammous was appointed as an economic advisor to El Salvador's National Bitcoin Office,...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/rivaling-visa-skyrocketing-trezor-binancing-all-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm"&gt;Read More: Rivaling Visa, Skyrocketing Trezor, Binancing All and 20 Crypto Jokes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Features</category><category>Community</category><category>Humor</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/exclusives/rivaling-visa-skyrocketing-trezor-binancing-all-and-20-crypto-jokes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115598/278880/8-web3-0-memes-instagram.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="363935"/></item><item><title>FTX Exchange Objects to Prolonged Mediation Talks with Bankrupt Genesis – Here's the Latest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-exchange-objects-prolonged-mediation-talks-with-bankrupt-genesis-heres-latest.htm</link><description>FTX and its affiliates have objected to extending court-mediated settlement talks for bankrupt crypto lender Genesis.  &lt;br /&gt;
In a recent court filing, FTX said it had not been invited to a court-appointed mediation in May that involved Genesis, its parent company Digital Currency Group, and creditor Gemini Trust Co, despite being a major Genesis creditor....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-exchange-objects-prolonged-mediation-talks-with-bankrupt-genesis-heres-latest.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Exchange Objects to Prolonged Mediation Talks with Bankrupt Genesis – Here's the Latest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Bankruptcy</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-exchange-objects-prolonged-mediation-talks-with-bankrupt-genesis-heres-latest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115805/311258/adobestock-343719449-medi.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="482981"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Surges Above $27,000; Key Level to Monitor Today</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-surges-above-27000-key-level-monitor-today.htm</link><description>In a significant bullish move, the price of Bitcoin (BTC) has surged above the $27,000 level, capturing the attention of cryptocurrency investors and traders. &lt;br /&gt;
This upward movement has sparked optimism and speculation about the potential direction of BTC in the near term.  &lt;br /&gt;
As Bitcoin reclaims this crucial level, market participants will closely monitor its price action and key levels to gauge the strength of the current bullish momentum. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-surges-above-27000-key-level-monitor-today.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction: BTC Surges Above $27,000; Key Level to Monitor Today&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 06:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-btc-surges-above-27000-key-level-monitor-today.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115800/311251/3-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="524640"/></item><item><title>Draft Legislation From House Republicans Drums Up Support From Crypto Advocates</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm</link><description>New draft legislation is drumming up support among cryptocurrency advocates who cheered its focus on defining what constitutes a security versus a commodity. &lt;br /&gt;
Republican lawmakers teamed up on Friday in the US House Financial Services Committee and the House Agriculture Committee on a discussion draft to regulate digital assets....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm"&gt;Read More: Draft Legislation From House Republicans Drums Up Support From Crypto Advocates&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>CFTC</category><category>SEC</category><category>House Agriculture</category><category>House Financial Services</category><category>Coinbase</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/draft-legislation-from-house-republicans-drums-up-support-from-crypto-advocates.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115789/311241/adobestock-230599906.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="533273"/></item><item><title>More China CBDC Public Transport Options Unveiled – Digital Yuan Readies Asian Games Debut</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm</link><description>Digital yuan payment adoption is stepping up in China ahead of the Asian Games, with venue cities rolling out a range of central bank digital currency (CBDC) transport options. &lt;br /&gt;
Per Shanghai Securities News, preparations are in advanced stages in the host city of Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province. &lt;br /&gt;
The city was slated to host the event in September last year, but the games were eventually delayed by a year due to the coronavirus pandemic....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm"&gt;Read More: More China CBDC Public Transport Options Unveiled – Digital Yuan Readies Asian Games Debut&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Digital Yuan</category><category>China</category><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/more-china-cbdc-public-transport-options-unveiled-digital-yuan-readies-asian-games-debut.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115696/278882/zhejiang.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="490095"/></item><item><title>Blockchain Association Files Amicus Brief To Support Coin Center’s Lawsuit Over Tornado Cash Sanctions</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm</link><description>Washington DC-based Blockchain Association filed an amicus brief in support of crypto think tank Coin Center’s lawsuit against the US Treasury Department over its sanctions against Tornado Cash. &lt;br /&gt;
Treasury sanctioned the crypto mixer in August, claiming that it laundered more than $7 billion worth of virtual currency and effectively banning Americans from using it.  &lt;br /&gt;
Coin Center sued Treasury in October over that sanction and said the service has legitimate use cases. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm"&gt;Read More: Blockchain Association Files Amicus Brief To Support Coin Center’s Lawsuit Over Tornado Cash Sanctions&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Blockchain Association</category><category>DeFi</category><category>Coin Center</category><category>Tornado Cash</category><category>Treasury</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/blockchain-association-files-amicus-brief-support-coin-centers-lawsuit-over-tornado-cash-sanctions.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115785/311240/adobestock-19789947.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="433501"/></item><item><title>Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Becomes One of the Best Performing Coins of the Week – Time to Buy?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm</link><description>Litecoin (LTC), the cryptocurrency that powers the payments-focused Litecoin blockchain, has been on a great run recently. &lt;br /&gt;
LTC was last changing hands just below $95 per token, having pumped over 3% this week despite a 1.5% fall in the broader cryptocurrency’s market capitalization. &lt;br /&gt;
That means Litecoin is one of the best-performing coins of the week and price predictions thus remains bullish....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm"&gt;Read More: Litecoin Price Prediction as LTC Becomes One of the Best Performing Coins of the Week – Time to Buy?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Litecoin</category><category>LTC</category><category>Price Prediction</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/litecoin-price-prediction-as-ltc-becomes-one-of-best-performing-coins-of-week-time-buy.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115780/311238/ltc-2.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="531951"/></item><item><title>Crypto Assets Should Be Classified as Securities, Says European Parliament Study</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm</link><description>A study commissioned by the European Parliament has proposed that all crypto assets should be treated as transferable securities by default. &lt;br /&gt;
To avoid being classified as a security, the study’s authors proposed that the intermediary behind a crypto asset can get an exemption from a national competent authority (NCA), meaning the relevant regulatory authority in an EU member state....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm"&gt;Read More: Crypto Assets Should Be Classified as Securities, Says European Parliament Study&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>EU</category><category>Regulation</category><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/crypto-assets-should-classified-as-securities-says-european-parliament-study.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://v2.cimg.co/news/115758/311205/eu-parliament.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="160377"/></item></channel></rss>
