<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link><description>A cryptocurrency is a type of digital or virtual currency which does not need to exist in a physical form to have value. These days cryptocurrencies have become extremely popular due to their decentralized exchange system between peers, making it essential for everyone to stay up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news today. Our original top cryptocurrency news will help you stay up to date about everything that's happening in the crypto world. Whether you are simply curious about the industry, are just starting out with cryptocurrencies or are a seasoned trader, we will make sure that staying up to date with the latest cryptocurrency news will be worth your time. The interesting thing about cryptocurrency news is that the industry is still very young and that the space is always evolving. New cryptocurrencies are popping up every day with certain projects clearly using blockchain technology better than others. Staying up to date with cryptocurrency news today will ensure you hear all about the interesting coins that are out there - particularly the disruptive ones that could be mass adopted and are pushing the boundaries of the cryptocurrency industry forward. The aim of cryptocurrency news today is not only to keep you up to date on all the cryptocurrency news, but to educate you on all the technological developments in the space, to portray an interesting vision of where the industry is headed, and to keep you informed on security measures to be aware of in order to protect your cryptocurrencies.</description><image><url>https://cimg.co/p/assets/android-chrome-512x512.png</url><title>Cryptonews</title><link>https://cryptonews.com</link></image><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>Russian Regions Say CBDC Will Help Them Fight Corruption</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-regions-say-cbdc-will-help-them-fight-corruption.htm</link><description>Russian regions say that the nation’s CBDC, the digital ruble, will help them fight corruption by “eliminating the shadow economy.” &lt;br /&gt;
Per Dela, an economy-focused newspaper that covers the Krasnoyarsk Krai region, officials in Siberia are keen to use the coin to conduct their business....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-regions-say-cbdc-will-help-them-fight-corruption.htm"&gt;Read More: Russian Regions Say CBDC Will Help Them Fight Corruption&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Russia</category><category>CBDC</category><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/russian-regions-say-cbdc-will-help-them-fight-corruption.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122660/324389/adobestock-190032884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="529943"/></item><item><title>Rumors SEC Poised To Approve Ethereum Futures ETF - ETH/BTC Bounces After Crypto Crash</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-sec-poised-to-approve-ethereum-futures-etf-after-crypto-prices-crash-ethbtc-bounces.htm</link><description>After a market-wide crash that saw Bitcoin hit as low as the $24,000 region on derivatives exchanges - in the largest liquidation event since the FTX collapse - surprise news hit. &lt;br /&gt;
A Bloomberg exclusive, syndicated by Yahoo Finance, states that the SEC is 'set to greenlight Ether-Futures ETFs'. &lt;br /&gt;
That headline alone caused the Ethereum price to sharply bounce from its low of $1,550 on Binance - even hitting $1,465 on Bybit - back to just under the $1,700 level at the time of writing....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-sec-poised-to-approve-ethereum-futures-etf-after-crypto-prices-crash-ethbtc-bounces.htm"&gt;Read More: Rumors SEC Poised To Approve Ethereum Futures ETF - ETH/BTC Bounces After Crypto Crash&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/rumors-sec-poised-to-approve-ethereum-futures-etf-after-crypto-prices-crash-ethbtc-bounces.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122743/324602/eth-btc-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="84863"/></item><item><title>FTX Seeks $176 Million Settlement with Genesis Entities Amid Legal Dispute</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-seeks-176-million-settlement-with-genesis-entities-amid-legal-dispute.htm</link><description>According to a legal filing on August 16, FTX, the bankrupted cryptocurrency exchange, and its CEO, John J. Ray III, have submitted a motion to settle with Genesis entities for $176 million. &lt;br /&gt;
With motion hearing scheduled for September 9, FTX Trading and related debtors have formally requested court intervention to settle a $176 million dispute with Genesis, who is seeking to address customer claims amounting to the same sum against FTX Trading and its affiliates....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-seeks-176-million-settlement-with-genesis-entities-amid-legal-dispute.htm"&gt;Read More: FTX Seeks $176 Million Settlement with Genesis Entities Amid Legal Dispute&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>FTX</category><category>Genesis</category><category>Legal</category><category>Alameda Research</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ftx-seeks-176-million-settlement-with-genesis-entities-amid-legal-dispute.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122741/324591/ftx-media-library-origina.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="121432"/></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price Prediction as Fundstrat's Tom Lee Says BTC Could Reach $180,000 Next Year – Time to Buy the Dip?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fundstrats-tom-lee-says-btc-could-reach-180000-next-year-time-buy-dip.htm</link><description>Amidst the fluctuating cryptocurrency markets, Bitcoin's future value remains a topic of fervent discussion.  &lt;br /&gt;
Recently, Fundstrat's Tom Lee has projected that BTC could soar to a staggering $180,000 by next year.  &lt;br /&gt;
This prediction has left many wondering if now is the opportune moment to invest and "buy the dip." ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fundstrats-tom-lee-says-btc-could-reach-180000-next-year-time-buy-dip.htm"&gt;Read More: Bitcoin Price Prediction as Fundstrat's Tom Lee Says BTC Could Reach $180,000 Next Year – Time to Buy the Dip?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Bitcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitcoin-price-prediction-as-fundstrats-tom-lee-says-btc-could-reach-180000-next-year-time-buy-dip.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122736/324577/17-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="489503"/></item><item><title>Philippine National Police Warns Citizens On Axie Infinity’s Play-to-Earn Model, Cites Security Concerns</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-citizens-on-axie-infinitys-play-earn-model-cites-security-concerns.htm</link><description>The Philippine police has raised alarms on blockchain gaming saying it may be riskier than investing in cryptocurrencies if capitalized by bad actors. &lt;br /&gt;
In a new statement, the Philippine National Police Anti-Cybercrime Group (PNP ACG) says citizens should be wary of the risk of being extorted by gaming models that require them to buy non-fungible tokens (NFTs). ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-citizens-on-axie-infinitys-play-earn-model-cites-security-concerns.htm"&gt;Read More: Philippine National Police Warns Citizens On Axie Infinity’s Play-to-Earn Model, Cites Security Concerns&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Axie Infinity</category><category>Scam</category><category>Philippine</category><category>NFT</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-citizens-on-axie-infinitys-play-earn-model-cites-security-concerns.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122730/324554/axie-infinity-media-libra.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="2043415"/></item><item><title>Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – METAL, XBULL, XDOGE</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-metal-xbull-xdoge.htm</link><description>Blue chip crypto markets are under broad selling pressure on Thursday amid a combination of macro and technical selling pressures. &lt;br /&gt;
Bitcoin (BTC) was last down around 3%, having recently slipped below its 2023 uptrend to new multi-month lows under $28,000. &lt;br /&gt;
Ether (ETH) fell around 3.7% on Thursday, trading under $1,750 after it fell below key support in the form of its 200DMA....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-metal-xbull-xdoge.htm"&gt;Read More: Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on DEXTools – METAL, XBULL, XDOGE&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>DEXTools</category><category>Bitcoin</category><category>btc</category><category>Ether</category><category>ETH</category><category>Shit Coins</category><category>Meme Coins</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/biggest-crypto-gainers-today-dextools-metal-xbull-xdoge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122728/324550/dext-media-library-origin.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="41433"/></item><item><title>Microsoft and LeverFi Launch AI-Backed Solution to Overcome DeFi Challenges</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/microsoft-and-leverfi-launch-ai-backed-solution-to-overcome-defi-challenges.htm</link><description>Microsoft and LeverFi have joined forces to launch an AI-backed solution that aims to tackle the challenges facing the decentralized finance (DeFi) industry. &lt;br /&gt;
The DeFi ecosystem is grappling with some significant challenges, including security hacks, poor risk management policies, and manual execution processes.  &lt;br /&gt;
These challenges have led to a lack of confidence among users and remain a major barrier for new users entering the DeFi space....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/microsoft-and-leverfi-launch-ai-backed-solution-to-overcome-defi-challenges.htm"&gt;Read More: Microsoft and LeverFi Launch AI-Backed Solution to Overcome DeFi Challenges&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Microsoft</category><category>LeverFi</category><category>Artificial Intelligence</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/microsoft-and-leverfi-launch-ai-backed-solution-to-overcome-defi-challenges.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122701/324480/d0dc871d28-media-library-.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="82192"/></item><item><title>The Philippine National Police Warns Against the Risks of Crypto Gaming Schemes</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-against-risks-of-crypto-gaming-schemes.htm</link><description>The anti-cybercrime group of the Philippine National Police released a warning note to citizens on possible risks involved in cryptocurrency gaming schemes such as the play-to-earn model used by Axie Infinity. &lt;br /&gt;
The cautionary report said that the decentralized nature of crypto gaming leaves higher risks than investing directly in cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin (BTC) and Ether (ETH)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-against-risks-of-crypto-gaming-schemes.htm"&gt;Read More: The Philippine National Police Warns Against the Risks of Crypto Gaming Schemes&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/philippine-national-police-warns-against-risks-of-crypto-gaming-schemes.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122679/324431/axie.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="391904"/></item><item><title>Critics Raise Concerns Over Gitcoin's Shell Partnership: Is It Truly 'Greenwashing'?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/critics-raise-concerns-over-gitcoins-shell-partnership-it-truly-greenwashing.htm</link><description>Open-source crowdfunding platform Gitcoin has announced a green-focused partnership with oil and gas giant Shell – and crypto pundits are no fans of the move....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/critics-raise-concerns-over-gitcoins-shell-partnership-it-truly-greenwashing.htm"&gt;Read More: Critics Raise Concerns Over Gitcoin's Shell Partnership: Is It Truly 'Greenwashing'?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/critics-raise-concerns-over-gitcoins-shell-partnership-it-truly-greenwashing.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122719/324534/adobestock-429938972-edit.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="64807"/></item><item><title>Ethereum Price Prediction as Vitalik Compares X's Social Media Algorithm to Crypto – Here's What You Need to Know</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-vitalik-compares-xs-social-media-algorithm-crypto-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</link><description>The price of Ethereum (ETH) has declined by 2% in the past 24 hours, dropping to $1,782 amid a similar fall for the wider cryptocurrency community today. &lt;br /&gt;
ETH is now down by 4% in the past week and by 6% in the last 30 days, with the market's biggest altcoin having risen by 49% since the start of 2023....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-vitalik-compares-xs-social-media-algorithm-crypto-heres-what-you-need-know.htm"&gt;Read More: Ethereum Price Prediction as Vitalik Compares X's Social Media Algorithm to Crypto – Here's What You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/ethereum-price-prediction-as-vitalik-compares-xs-social-media-algorithm-crypto-heres-what-you-need-know.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122709/324515/ethereum-price-prediction.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1223120"/></item><item><title>Today in Crypto: Polygon Labs and Mobile Giant SK Telecom Sign a Web3 Deal, Coinbase Partners With Trustly for Payments in Canada, Singaporean Police Arrest Ten Foreigners and Seize Crypto</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-polygon-labs-and-mobile-giant-sk-telecom-sign-a-web3-deal-coinbase-partners-with-trustly-for-payments-in-canada-singaporean-police-arrest-ten-foreigners-and-seize-crypto.htm</link><description>Get your daily, bite-sized digest of cryptoasset and blockchain-related news – investigating the stories flying under the radar of today’s crypto news.__________...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-polygon-labs-and-mobile-giant-sk-telecom-sign-a-web3-deal-coinbase-partners-with-trustly-for-payments-in-canada-singaporean-police-arrest-ten-foreigners-and-seize-crypto.htm"&gt;Read More: Today in Crypto: Polygon Labs and Mobile Giant SK Telecom Sign a Web3 Deal, Coinbase Partners With Trustly for Payments in Canada, Singaporean Police Arrest Ten Foreigners and Seize Crypto&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><category>Certik</category><category>Polygon</category><category>SK Telecom</category><category>Web3</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Canada</category><category>Security</category><category>Singapore</category><category>Crime</category><category>Police</category><category>Sotheby's</category><category>Legal</category><category>BAYC</category><category>Yuga Labs</category><category>NFT</category><category>North Korea</category><category>Hack</category><category>Gaming</category><category>chatGPT</category><category>OpenAI</category><category>AI</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/today-in-crypto-polygon-labs-and-mobile-giant-sk-telecom-sign-a-web3-deal-coinbase-partners-with-trustly-for-payments-in-canada-singaporean-police-arrest-ten-foreigners-and-seize-crypto.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122677/324500/adobestock-sundry-photogr.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="1154779"/></item><item><title>“Opportunistic and Baseless” - Yuga Labs and Sotheby’s Respond To Amended Lawsuit From Bored Ape Investors</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/opportunistic-and-baseless-yuga-labs-and-sothebys-respond-to-amended-lawsuit-from-bored-ape-investors.htm</link><description>Auction House Sotheby’s has responded to the new allegations leveled against it by Bored Ape investors describing it as opportunistic and simply without merit. &lt;br /&gt;
The statement comes as the auction house was named in the class action suit against YugaLabs the creators of Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC)....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/opportunistic-and-baseless-yuga-labs-and-sothebys-respond-to-amended-lawsuit-from-bored-ape-investors.htm"&gt;Read More: “Opportunistic and Baseless” - Yuga Labs and Sotheby’s Respond To Amended Lawsuit From Bored Ape Investors&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>NFT News</category><category>Bored Apes</category><category>Yuga Labs</category><category>Sotheby's</category><category>Lawsuit</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/opportunistic-and-baseless-yuga-labs-and-sothebys-respond-to-amended-lawsuit-from-bored-ape-investors.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122707/324509/adobestock-ascannio-1-1-m.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="109196"/></item><item><title>Inside Shibarium's Launch Hiccups: How the SHIBarmy Battled Unprecedented Traffic Surge</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/inside-shibariums-launch-hiccups-how-shibarmy-battled-unprecedented-traffic-surge.htm</link><description>The highly anticipated Shibarium launch proved that no amount of preparation can truly brace a project for the unanticipated strength and fervor of its community. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes after huge traction caused a storm amid the Shibarium launch, fuelling wild speculation on crypto twitter and triggering significant downside action on the markets.  &lt;br /&gt;
But before we dive into the nitty-gritty of the recent event, let's take a step back....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/inside-shibariums-launch-hiccups-how-shibarmy-battled-unprecedented-traffic-surge.htm"&gt;Read More: Inside Shibarium's Launch Hiccups: How the SHIBarmy Battled Unprecedented Traffic Surge&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Altcoin News</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/inside-shibariums-launch-hiccups-how-shibarmy-battled-unprecedented-traffic-surge.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122708/324505/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="530466"/></item><item><title>Is It Too Late to Buy HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu? Viral Meme Coin Rockets Up 200% and This Platform Uses AI to Find the Next Crypto to Explode</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-harrypotterobamasonic10inu-viral-meme-coin-rockets-up-200-platform-uses-ai-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</link><description>HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu (BITCOIN) appears to be making a come back in DEX markets, following a +30% bounce out of retracement. &lt;br /&gt;
This comes following rockstar performance by the unusually-named meme coin, which enjoyed a sensational +9,500% pump back in July on the back of a short-lived trend for Bitcoin spin-off coins....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-harrypotterobamasonic10inu-viral-meme-coin-rockets-up-200-platform-uses-ai-find-next-crypto-explode.htm"&gt;Read More: Is It Too Late to Buy HarryPotterObamaSonic10Inu? Viral Meme Coin Rockets Up 200% and This Platform Uses AI to Find the Next Crypto to Explode&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Industry Talk</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/it-too-late-buy-harrypotterobamasonic10inu-viral-meme-coin-rockets-up-200-platform-uses-ai-find-next-crypto-explode.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122680/324448/image.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1474767"/></item><item><title>Coinbase-Backed Securitize Set to Acquire Crypto Investment Platform Onramp Invest</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-backed-securitize-set-to-acquire-crypto-investment-platform-onramp-invest.htm</link><description>Securitize, a firm that specializes in tokenizing private investments, is all set to acquire the crypto investment platform Onramp Invest. &lt;br /&gt;
The Informant reported Onramp's team of 18 is all set to integrate into Securitize's existing workforce of 150.  &lt;br /&gt;
Securitize, backed by companies like Coinbase Ventures, Morgan Stanley, Blockchain Capital, Ava Labs, Borderless Capital, IDC Ventures, has raised over $120 million in funding so far. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-backed-securitize-set-to-acquire-crypto-investment-platform-onramp-invest.htm"&gt;Read More: Coinbase-Backed Securitize Set to Acquire Crypto Investment Platform Onramp Invest&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Securitize</category><category>Onramp</category><category>Coinbase</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/coinbase-backed-securitize-set-to-acquire-crypto-investment-platform-onramp-invest.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122695/324481/secuiritize-1.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="123691"/></item><item><title>BitGo Crypto Custodian Secures $100 Million in Funding, Valuation Reaches $1.75 Billion</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm</link><description>Crypto custody provider BitGo has raised $100 million in a Series C funding round to reach a valuation of $1.75 billion, the firm announced on Wednesday. &lt;br /&gt;
Participating in the funding round were several “new, outside strategic investors,” BitGo said in the announcement. &lt;br /&gt;
The firm did not name any of the investors....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm"&gt;Read More: BitGo Crypto Custodian Secures $100 Million in Funding, Valuation Reaches $1.75 Billion&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>BitGo</category><category>Investment</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/bitgo-crypto-custodian-secures-100-million-funding-valuation-reaches-175-billion.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122694/324471/bitgo-ceo.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="74618"/></item><item><title>XRP Price Prediction as $1.4 Billion Sends XRP Down 1.5% – Are Whales Selling?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm</link><description>The XRP price has dropped by 1.5% in the past 24 hours, slipping to $0.585019 as the cryptocurrency market as a whole falls by 2% within the same timeframe. &lt;br /&gt;
The market has been pulled down by a number of factors today, from ongoing weakness in stock markets to disappointment over delayed Bitcoin ETF decisions, with XRP sharing in the general negativity....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm"&gt;Read More: XRP Price Prediction as $1.4 Billion Sends XRP Down 1.5% – Are Whales Selling?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/xrp-price-prediction-as-14-billion-sends-xrp-down-15-are-whales-selling.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122689/324460/xrp-price-chart.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1694720"/></item><item><title>Valkyrie Funds Looks to Launch Ethereum Strategy ETF</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm</link><description>Asset management firm Valkyrie Funds has filed for an Ethereum Strategy exchange-traded fund (ETF) that will invest in Ether futures. &lt;br /&gt;
According to a Wednesday filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission, the new fund, called the Valkyrie Ethereum Strategy ETF, aims to capitalize on the growing interest in Ethereum (ETH) futures....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm"&gt;Read More: Valkyrie Funds Looks to Launch Ethereum Strategy ETF&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Ethereum News</category><category>Valkyrie Funds</category><category>Ethereum</category><category>ETF</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/valkyrie-funds-looks-launch-ethereum-strategy-etf.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122685/324445/ethereum-coin-media-libra.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" length="106104"/></item><item><title>Sichuan Province of China Targets Metaverse Industry Expansion to Reach $34.4 Billion by 2025</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm</link><description>Sichuan, a southwestern Chinese province, once recognized as a thriving crypto mining hub prior to the national ban on mining, is now looking to expand the metaverse industry.  &lt;br /&gt;
Sichuan’s government unveiled an ambitious draft action plan with an aim to cultivate the nascent metaverse industry into a colossal market worth 250 billion yuan ($34.4 billion) by the year 2025. ...&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm"&gt;Read More: Sichuan Province of China Targets Metaverse Industry Expansion to Reach $34.4 Billion by 2025&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Blockchain News</category><category>Metaverse</category><category>China</category><category>Blockchain</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/sichuan-province-of-china-targets-metaverse-industry-expansion-reach-344-billion-by-2025.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122690/324464/china-metaverse.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="183738"/></item><item><title>Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Drops 7.5% After Shibarium Launch – What's Going On?</title><link>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm</link><description>The Shiba Inu price has dropped by more than 7.5% today, with its slide to $0.00000888 coming after the full public launch of the much-anticipated Shibarium layer-two network. &lt;br /&gt;
This means SHIB is down by 9% in the past week, with Shibarium's arrival being plagued by technical issues that have dragged down the meme token's price....&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href="https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm"&gt;Read More: Shiba Inu Price Prediction as SHIB Drops 7.5% After Shibarium Launch – What's Going On?&lt;/a&gt;</description><category>Price Predictions</category><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cryptonews.com/news/shiba-inu-price-prediction-as-shib-drops-75-after-shibarium-launch-whats-going-on.htm</guid><enclosure url="https://cimg.co/news/122676/324458/shiba-inu-price-predictio.jpg" type="image/jpeg" length="1303493"/></item></channel></rss>
