<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom/"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
>

	<channel>
    <title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
		<atom:link href="https://cryptodaily.co.uk/tw-feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:56:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-GB</language>
		<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
		<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
		<description>Let us guide you through the crypto world and find such things as the Best Crypto wallets, monitor what the crypto market are doing and get the crypto news.</description>
		<generator>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</generator>

		<image>
			<url>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/assets/cryptodaily/img/cryptodaily-favicon-32x32.jpg</url>
			<title>Crypto Daily&#8482;</title>
			<link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk</link>
			<width>32</width>
			<height>32</height>
		</image>

											<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Starknet Introduces Appchains Framework $STRK]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/starknet-introduces-appchains-framework-strk</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/starknet-appchains-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/starknet-introduces-appchains-framework-strk</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet, an Ethereum Layer 2, has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The innovative project is in alignment with the growing trend of modular networks in the Layer 2 ecosystem, spearheaded by projects like Optimism, Polygon, zkSync, and Arbitrum. </p>
A New Era For Application-Specific Chains
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Developers can harness Starknet Stack, the native developer toolkit of Starknet's ecosystem, to create these appchains, using STARK proofs to boost security. Central to this toolkit is Cairo, a programming language developed by the StarkWare team, bearing similarities to Rust.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent blog post, Starknet revealed that the use of appchains could offer developers an enhanced performance, a claim further supported by Starknet's recent v0.12.0 upgrade on the mainnet, which reportedly amplified network performance. </p>
Advancing Customization For Devs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A unique aspect of appchains lies in their capability to support features currently not present on Starknet's main network. This includes features like custom fee market logic and consernsus mechanisms, among others. This flexibility can potentially grant developers the ability to customize their application's configurations and functionalities, thus offering a greater degree of control over their projects.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Starknet Appchains are the bespoke environment where applications can tailor an instance of Starknet to achieve better control over the specs, lower cost, greater scale, and opt-in privacy," the firm shared.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The team underscored the escalating interest in application-specific blockchains, tailored to meet customized requirements. They stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The need for appchains has been apparent for several years and is now getting renewed attention."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet's introduction of appchains represents a significant milestone in the blockchain landscape, enhancing developers' capacity for customization, and making the ecosystem more versatile and adaptable to specific application requirements. Such a move signals a key step towards a more decerntralized, diversified, and performance-oriented blockchain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet, an Ethereum Layer 2, has disclosed the initiation of "appchains," a framework designed to enable developers to construct several application-specific blockchains within the Starknet ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The innovative project is in alignment with the growing trend of modular networks in the Layer 2 ecosystem, spearheaded by projects like Optimism, Polygon, zkSync, and Arbitrum. </p>
A New Era For Application-Specific Chains
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Developers can harness Starknet Stack, the native developer toolkit of Starknet's ecosystem, to create these appchains, using STARK proofs to boost security. Central to this toolkit is Cairo, a programming language developed by the StarkWare team, bearing similarities to Rust.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">In a recent blog post, Starknet revealed that the use of appchains could offer developers an enhanced performance, a claim further supported by Starknet's recent v0.12.0 upgrade on the mainnet, which reportedly amplified network performance. </p>
Advancing Customization For Devs
<p class="md-end-block md-p">A unique aspect of appchains lies in their capability to support features currently not present on Starknet's main network. This includes features like custom fee market logic and consernsus mechanisms, among others. This flexibility can potentially grant developers the ability to customize their application's configurations and functionalities, thus offering a greater degree of control over their projects.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Starknet Appchains are the bespoke environment where applications can tailor an instance of Starknet to achieve better control over the specs, lower cost, greater scale, and opt-in privacy," the firm shared.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The team underscored the escalating interest in application-specific blockchains, tailored to meet customized requirements. They stated:</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"The need for appchains has been apparent for several years and is now getting renewed attention."</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Starknet's introduction of appchains represents a significant milestone in the blockchain landscape, enhancing developers' capacity for customization, and making the ecosystem more versatile and adaptable to specific application requirements. Such a move signals a key step towards a more decerntralized, diversified, and performance-oriented blockchain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Spectrum Finance To Integrate With Cardano $SPF $ADA]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/spectrum-finance-to-integrate-with-cardano-spf-ada</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/spectrum-finance-x-cardano-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/spectrum-finance-to-integrate-with-cardano-spf-ada</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance, a distinguished name in the decentralized exchange (DEX) landscape, renowned for fostering trustless, cross-chain programmable messaging, has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is intended to extend Spectrum's capabilities into the Cardano ecosystem, enabling new opportunities for seamless blockchain interoperability.</p>
Amplified Capacities
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance has garnered recognition in the crypto industry by offering various functionalities tailored to user-specific needs, providing access to the Spectrum Network, a cross-chain smart contract platform for facilitating the creation of dApps that operate natively in a cross-chain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Its standout feature is its ability to interact seamlessly with native currencies and tokens across different blockchains simultaneously. This negates the need for wrapped or synthetic assets when conducting transactions between blockchains, allowing actions such as swapping native ETH from the Ethereum mainnet to native ADA on the Cardano mainnet with ease.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For Cardano, a platform built on peer-reviewed research and high-assurance development, the partnership with Spectrum Finance signals a significant enhancement. It will enable Cardano to offer its users a broader range of cross-chain functionality, capitalizing on Spectrum's interoperability capabilities. The integration with Spectrum sets the stage for the creation of innovative dApps leveraging the combined potential of Cardano's sophisticated smart contract capabilities and Spectrum's cross-chain abilities. This synergy is expected to yield dApps with unprecedented reach and functionality, harnessing the best features from both platforms.</p>
Challenges For Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Blockchain interoperability has been a central challenge inhibiting wider adoption of the technology. It ensures seamless transactions across various blockchain networks without the need for intermediaries, reducing the fragmentation of the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, interoperability protocol implementation is complex, as different blockchains have distinct security solutions, consensus algorithms, and programming languages.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solutions such as the Spectrum Protocol, which offers a truly decentralized, secure, and scalable cross-chain interoperability solution, are vital to overcoming this hurdle. The integration of Spectrum and Cardano represents a critical step towards both transforming and effectively pushing forward blockchain interoperability, with the promise and potential of unlocking new possibilities for the crypto industry, bringing users closer to an interconnected and seamless blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance, a distinguished name in the decentralized exchange (DEX) landscape, renowned for fostering trustless, cross-chain programmable messaging, has revealed its strategic collaboration with Cardano, the innovative smart contract platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is intended to extend Spectrum's capabilities into the Cardano ecosystem, enabling new opportunities for seamless blockchain interoperability.</p>
Amplified Capacities
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Spectrum Finance has garnered recognition in the crypto industry by offering various functionalities tailored to user-specific needs, providing access to the Spectrum Network, a cross-chain smart contract platform for facilitating the creation of dApps that operate natively in a cross-chain environment.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Its standout feature is its ability to interact seamlessly with native currencies and tokens across different blockchains simultaneously. This negates the need for wrapped or synthetic assets when conducting transactions between blockchains, allowing actions such as swapping native ETH from the Ethereum mainnet to native ADA on the Cardano mainnet with ease.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">For Cardano, a platform built on peer-reviewed research and high-assurance development, the partnership with Spectrum Finance signals a significant enhancement. It will enable Cardano to offer its users a broader range of cross-chain functionality, capitalizing on Spectrum's interoperability capabilities. The integration with Spectrum sets the stage for the creation of innovative dApps leveraging the combined potential of Cardano's sophisticated smart contract capabilities and Spectrum's cross-chain abilities. This synergy is expected to yield dApps with unprecedented reach and functionality, harnessing the best features from both platforms.</p>
Challenges For Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Blockchain interoperability has been a central challenge inhibiting wider adoption of the technology. It ensures seamless transactions across various blockchain networks without the need for intermediaries, reducing the fragmentation of the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">However, interoperability protocol implementation is complex, as different blockchains have distinct security solutions, consensus algorithms, and programming languages.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Solutions such as the Spectrum Protocol, which offers a truly decentralized, secure, and scalable cross-chain interoperability solution, are vital to overcoming this hurdle. The integration of Spectrum and Cardano represents a critical step towards both transforming and effectively pushing forward blockchain interoperability, with the promise and potential of unlocking new possibilities for the crypto industry, bringing users closer to an interconnected and seamless blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Crypto Market Analysis for H1 According to CoinMarketCap]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-market-analysis-for-h1-according-to-coinmarketcap</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cmc-1.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cmc-1.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/cmc-1.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 21:00:13 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/crypto-market-analysis-for-h1-according-to-coinmarketcap</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>CoinMarketCap has released a report on the global crypto market after H1. The report delves into a general market overview, recent key events, and what it expects H2&rsquo;s key themes will be. </p>
<p>Today, CoinMarketCap, the world&rsquo;s leading price-tracking website for crypto assets, released its 2023 H1 Crypto Market Analysis Report.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto Market Kicks 2023 Off Strong
<p>The crypto market started this year with a bang witnessing the bitcoin price doubling, the rise of L2s such as Arbitrum and ZK, and the NFT market showing signs of improvement. By the end of Q2, the global crypto market capitalization reached an impressive $1.17 trillion, marking a 48% YTD increase. Q1 and Q2, however, concluded with similar total market caps, meaning Q2 showed much less growth.</p>
<p>Q2 was instead characterized by trends such as the &ldquo;memecoin&rdquo; frenzy and the rise of BRC20 tokens, which, despite being noteworthy, did not garner the same excitement as the previous quarter&rsquo;s developments.</p>
<p>Market sentiment improved significantly by the end of Q1, with the CMC Crypto Fear and Greed Index registering at a neutral 52 &ndash; a vast improvement over the start of the year, which registered a fearful 30.</p>
<p>According to CMC&rsquo;s report, the Total Spot Trade Volume of the Top 20 Crypto Exchanges peaked in March but declined by around 36% quarter-on-quarter.</p>
Top Growing Sectors
<p>Despite what can only be called challenging market conditions, certain industry sectors witnessed remarkable growth in market cap year-to-date. VR/AR (704%0 and AI &amp; Big Data (323%) exceeded expectations, while blue-chip decentralized finance (DeFi) projects appear to be making a strong comeback.</p>
<p>The &ldquo;memecoin&rdquo; frenzy saw the sector add over 260 new coins YTD, with AI &amp; Big Data taking second place, adding 61 coins. DeFi ranked third, adding 47 new listings YTD.</p>
<p></p>
Bitcoin and Ethereum Developments
<p>The market&rsquo;s top tokens, Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) experienced several events, resulting in noteworthy price fluctuations.</p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
CMC&rsquo;s Top Views
<p>CoinMarketCap saw a surge in views from the memecoin sector as $PEPE took the industry by storm. PEPE&rsquo;s explosive rally of over 3700x from April to May sparked particular interest in the sector, and it joined CMC&rsquo;s &ldquo;Most Added to Watchlist.&rdquo; Memes also registered the most engagement in CMC Community.</p>
<p>The DeFi sector registered sustained interest throughout the year&rsquo;s first half to become the second most viewed. Sector interest largely focused on Terra Classic (LUNC) as Binance burned 2.65 billion LUNC tokens, worth approximately $236,000. &nbsp;</p>
<p>AI and Big Data have undoubtedly marked 2023 following the launch of OpenAI&rsquo;s revolutionary ChatGPT, and it is reflected in views.</p>
Best Performing Coins
<p>Arbitrum ecosystem tokens such as Pendle (PENDLE) and Radiant Capital (RDNT) appeared to be H1&rsquo;s top gainers, along with Optimist ecosystem tokens such as Velodrome Finance (VELO).</p>
<p></p>
<p>Other top gainers include layer-one blockchains, including Dione Protocol (DIONE), Conflux (CFX), and Injective (INJ). AI-related tokens such as SingularityNET (AGIX) and Render (RNDR) also performed well.</p>
Key Themes for H2
<p>CoinMarketCap identified the key themes for the second half of 2023.</p>
Bitcoin ETFs
<p>The crypto news cycle has recently been dominated by talks of Bitcoin ETFs after BlackRock, the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, filed for a Bitcoin spot ETF with the SEC. News of BlackRock&rsquo;s application spurred a host of other firms, such as Valkyrie, Fidelity and 21 Shares, to announce they are also seeking ETF approval.</p>
<p>The SEC has yet to approve any of the applications. Should the regulator grant these ETFs, they could unlock substantial investor demand by offering regulated products for asset allocation.</p>
Decentralized Public Infrastructure Networks
<p>One of H2&rsquo;s key themes will be Decentralized Physical Infrastructure (DePIN). DePIN is still in its early stages of expansion and aims to provide solutions for access sharing of physical assets or services like warehousing and data networks.</p>
Real World Assets (RWAs)
<p>The tokenization of assets has become an increasing focus for the crypto asset industry. Projects focused on making RWAs tradeable on-chain largely consist of credit market protocols such as Maple Finance and Goldfinch allow businesses to use DeFi to secure financing and loans.</p>
Liquid Staking Derivative (LSDs)
<p>Liquid Staking Derivative witnessed a dramatic surge in activity in H1 owing largely to Ethereum&rsquo;s Shapella upgrade. Market leaders such as Lido and Rocket Pool saw their TVLs rise 138% and 220%, respectively.</p>
<p>By the end of June, LSD platforms secured over a third of Ethereum&rsquo;s Total Value Staked.</p>
<p></p>
Restaking
<p>The introduction of EigenLayer &ndash; a middleware platform which allows staked ETH or liquid staked ETH tokens to be reused on the consensus layer, prompted restaking as an emerging theme in H1.</p>
<p>Restaking was in demand after EigenLayer&rsquo;s Restaking Smart Contracts were deployed and reached their maximum limits within a day of the mainnet launch.</p>
zkSync
<p>zkSync, a zero-knowledge roll-up solution, emerged as a popular Ethereum-based layer-2 solution and strong competitor against Ethereum optimistic roll-ups, including Optimism and Arbitrum.</p>
<p>zkSync utilizes zero-knowledge technology to offload traffic from Ethereum to an efficient second layer, helping to increase Ethereum&rsquo;s throughput while enabling an array of new applications.</p>
Modular Blockchains (Celestia)
<p>Most layer-1 blockchains are monolithic chains that result in issues surrounding efficiency, stemming from the blockchain trilemma of decentralization, security and scalability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Modular blockchains like Celestia address these issues by separating blockchains into three layers: execution, settlement, consensus and data availability. In doing so, modular blockchains provide developers with modular data availability and consensus layers which dApps and sidechains can leverage to bootstrap development.</p>
FTX Bankruptcy Developments
<p>After FTX collapsed, its depositors could not determine how much of the almost $9 billion shortfall could be collected during the liquidation process.</p>
<p>In January, it emerged that more than $5 billion in liquid assets were collected, and this number subsequently increased to $7 billion. The firm overseeing FTX&rsquo;s restructuring recently contacted creditors, giving them a &ldquo;Customer Bar Date&rdquo; of September 29, 2023.</p>
<p>Debtors are, however, unlikely to receive a payout until at least H2 2024.</p>
Bitcoin Remains Most-Viewed Crypto Across All Regions
<p>Regional differences in interest in various crypto sectors were insignificant. Bitcoin continues as the most-viewed crypto across all regions in H1 2023, similar to data from Q4 2022. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance over altcoins increased by 25% from 40.09% at the beginning of the year to 50.39% at the end of H1.</p>
<p></p>
<p>As expected, the US continues to dominate the distribution of crypto users worldwide.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CoinMarketCap has released a report on the global crypto market after H1. The report delves into a general market overview, recent key events, and what it expects H2&rsquo;s key themes will be. </p>
<p>Today, CoinMarketCap, the world&rsquo;s leading price-tracking website for crypto assets, released its 2023 H1 Crypto Market Analysis Report.&nbsp;</p>
Crypto Market Kicks 2023 Off Strong
<p>The crypto market started this year with a bang witnessing the bitcoin price doubling, the rise of L2s such as Arbitrum and ZK, and the NFT market showing signs of improvement. By the end of Q2, the global crypto market capitalization reached an impressive $1.17 trillion, marking a 48% YTD increase. Q1 and Q2, however, concluded with similar total market caps, meaning Q2 showed much less growth.</p>
<p>Q2 was instead characterized by trends such as the &ldquo;memecoin&rdquo; frenzy and the rise of BRC20 tokens, which, despite being noteworthy, did not garner the same excitement as the previous quarter&rsquo;s developments.</p>
<p>Market sentiment improved significantly by the end of Q1, with the CMC Crypto Fear and Greed Index registering at a neutral 52 &ndash; a vast improvement over the start of the year, which registered a fearful 30.</p>
<p>According to CMC&rsquo;s report, the Total Spot Trade Volume of the Top 20 Crypto Exchanges peaked in March but declined by around 36% quarter-on-quarter.</p>
Top Growing Sectors
<p>Despite what can only be called challenging market conditions, certain industry sectors witnessed remarkable growth in market cap year-to-date. VR/AR (704%0 and AI &amp; Big Data (323%) exceeded expectations, while blue-chip decentralized finance (DeFi) projects appear to be making a strong comeback.</p>
<p>The &ldquo;memecoin&rdquo; frenzy saw the sector add over 260 new coins YTD, with AI &amp; Big Data taking second place, adding 61 coins. DeFi ranked third, adding 47 new listings YTD.</p>
<p></p>
Bitcoin and Ethereum Developments
<p>The market&rsquo;s top tokens, Bitcoin (BTC) and Ethereum (ETH) experienced several events, resulting in noteworthy price fluctuations.</p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
CMC&rsquo;s Top Views
<p>CoinMarketCap saw a surge in views from the memecoin sector as $PEPE took the industry by storm. PEPE&rsquo;s explosive rally of over 3700x from April to May sparked particular interest in the sector, and it joined CMC&rsquo;s &ldquo;Most Added to Watchlist.&rdquo; Memes also registered the most engagement in CMC Community.</p>
<p>The DeFi sector registered sustained interest throughout the year&rsquo;s first half to become the second most viewed. Sector interest largely focused on Terra Classic (LUNC) as Binance burned 2.65 billion LUNC tokens, worth approximately $236,000. &nbsp;</p>
<p>AI and Big Data have undoubtedly marked 2023 following the launch of OpenAI&rsquo;s revolutionary ChatGPT, and it is reflected in views.</p>
Best Performing Coins
<p>Arbitrum ecosystem tokens such as Pendle (PENDLE) and Radiant Capital (RDNT) appeared to be H1&rsquo;s top gainers, along with Optimist ecosystem tokens such as Velodrome Finance (VELO).</p>
<p></p>
<p>Other top gainers include layer-one blockchains, including Dione Protocol (DIONE), Conflux (CFX), and Injective (INJ). AI-related tokens such as SingularityNET (AGIX) and Render (RNDR) also performed well.</p>
Key Themes for H2
<p>CoinMarketCap identified the key themes for the second half of 2023.</p>
Bitcoin ETFs
<p>The crypto news cycle has recently been dominated by talks of Bitcoin ETFs after BlackRock, the world&rsquo;s largest asset manager, filed for a Bitcoin spot ETF with the SEC. News of BlackRock&rsquo;s application spurred a host of other firms, such as Valkyrie, Fidelity and 21 Shares, to announce they are also seeking ETF approval.</p>
<p>The SEC has yet to approve any of the applications. Should the regulator grant these ETFs, they could unlock substantial investor demand by offering regulated products for asset allocation.</p>
Decentralized Public Infrastructure Networks
<p>One of H2&rsquo;s key themes will be Decentralized Physical Infrastructure (DePIN). DePIN is still in its early stages of expansion and aims to provide solutions for access sharing of physical assets or services like warehousing and data networks.</p>
Real World Assets (RWAs)
<p>The tokenization of assets has become an increasing focus for the crypto asset industry. Projects focused on making RWAs tradeable on-chain largely consist of credit market protocols such as Maple Finance and Goldfinch allow businesses to use DeFi to secure financing and loans.</p>
Liquid Staking Derivative (LSDs)
<p>Liquid Staking Derivative witnessed a dramatic surge in activity in H1 owing largely to Ethereum&rsquo;s Shapella upgrade. Market leaders such as Lido and Rocket Pool saw their TVLs rise 138% and 220%, respectively.</p>
<p>By the end of June, LSD platforms secured over a third of Ethereum&rsquo;s Total Value Staked.</p>
<p></p>
Restaking
<p>The introduction of EigenLayer &ndash; a middleware platform which allows staked ETH or liquid staked ETH tokens to be reused on the consensus layer, prompted restaking as an emerging theme in H1.</p>
<p>Restaking was in demand after EigenLayer&rsquo;s Restaking Smart Contracts were deployed and reached their maximum limits within a day of the mainnet launch.</p>
zkSync
<p>zkSync, a zero-knowledge roll-up solution, emerged as a popular Ethereum-based layer-2 solution and strong competitor against Ethereum optimistic roll-ups, including Optimism and Arbitrum.</p>
<p>zkSync utilizes zero-knowledge technology to offload traffic from Ethereum to an efficient second layer, helping to increase Ethereum&rsquo;s throughput while enabling an array of new applications.</p>
Modular Blockchains (Celestia)
<p>Most layer-1 blockchains are monolithic chains that result in issues surrounding efficiency, stemming from the blockchain trilemma of decentralization, security and scalability.</p>
<p></p>
<p>Modular blockchains like Celestia address these issues by separating blockchains into three layers: execution, settlement, consensus and data availability. In doing so, modular blockchains provide developers with modular data availability and consensus layers which dApps and sidechains can leverage to bootstrap development.</p>
FTX Bankruptcy Developments
<p>After FTX collapsed, its depositors could not determine how much of the almost $9 billion shortfall could be collected during the liquidation process.</p>
<p>In January, it emerged that more than $5 billion in liquid assets were collected, and this number subsequently increased to $7 billion. The firm overseeing FTX&rsquo;s restructuring recently contacted creditors, giving them a &ldquo;Customer Bar Date&rdquo; of September 29, 2023.</p>
<p>Debtors are, however, unlikely to receive a payout until at least H2 2024.</p>
Bitcoin Remains Most-Viewed Crypto Across All Regions
<p>Regional differences in interest in various crypto sectors were insignificant. Bitcoin continues as the most-viewed crypto across all regions in H1 2023, similar to data from Q4 2022. Bitcoin&rsquo;s dominance over altcoins increased by 25% from 40.09% at the beginning of the year to 50.39% at the end of H1.</p>
<p></p>
<p>As expected, the US continues to dominate the distribution of crypto users worldwide.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Polygon Eyes Governance Restructure For 2.0 Roadmap $POL $MATIC]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/polygon-eyes-governance-restructure-for-2-0-roadmap-pol-matic</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-restructure-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-restructure-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/polygon-restructure-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/polygon-eyes-governance-restructure-for-2-0-roadmap-pol-matic</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">The developers behind Polygon Labs have proposed changes to their governance system, with proposed changes that are integral to their forthcoming Polygon 2.0 roadmap, which aims to establish multiple layer-2 networks on the Polygon platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The new proposed governance structure will be comprised of "three main pillars", each catering to a distinct function. </p>
A New Approach to Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The first pillar involves the expansion of the Polygon Improvement Proposal (PIP) framework, currently limited to the Polygon PoS chain, to all applications and blockchains that run on the Polygon network. This adjustment will allow community members to propose and research upgrades that could potentially become part of the protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The second pillar, termed "System Smart Contracts Governance," is designed to facilitate upgrades for software implemented as smart contracts. The developers propose the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a body elected by the community, to oversee these changes. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The third pillar, the "Community Treasury", aims to support the growth of the Polygon ecosystem and fund projects. Initially, the Treasury will be managed by an independent Community Treasury Board before transitioning to community governance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Community input will play a crucial role in determining the final shape of the governance plans. Therefore, Polygon Labs has encouraged developers, network validators, and other stakeholders to engage in discussions regarding the proposals.</p>
Community Deliberation and the Three Governance Pillars
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon 2.0 is a reimagination of the current Polygon ecosystem. The proposal for the new governance structure seeks to address the complexities of blockchain governance and proposes a decentralized framework for decision-making over all Polygon protocols and the ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposal borrows elements from existing successful blockchain governance models, including Ethereum's open, inclusive governance ethos. The "Three Governance Pillars" are designed to provide governance over the entire Polygon ecosystem and define suitable decision makers for each pillar.</p>
Protocol Governance and System Smart Contracts Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The first pillar, Protocol Governance, involves the expansion of the PIP framework to cover all of Polygon's permissionless stack. The goal is to give the community a formal way to propose upgrades that could potentially become part of the protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The second pillar, System Smart Contracts Governance, proposes the creation of an Ecosystem Council to upgrade system smart contracts. The Council will ensure the ongoing upgradeability of the protocol components implemented as smart contracts.</p>
Community Treasury Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The third pillar, Community Treasury Governance, proposes the creation of a self-sustainable ecosystem fund, the Community Treasury. The fund will support the growth of the Polygon ecosystem and fund projects and initiatives.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The potential transformation outlined in the Polygon 2.0 governance proposal reflects the platform's commitment to decentralization and community empowerment. In this sense, ommunity-driven governance models are increasingly becoming as critical components of key platforms such as Polygon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">This governance restructure, if adopted, may effectively position Polygon as a forerunner in this new phase of blockchain development. However, it is the community's acceptance and participation that will ultimately determine the realization of this vision. With this plan, Polygon could potentially pave the way for a future where the community holds the reins of blockchain protocols, fostering a truly decentralized ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">The developers behind Polygon Labs have proposed changes to their governance system, with proposed changes that are integral to their forthcoming Polygon 2.0 roadmap, which aims to establish multiple layer-2 networks on the Polygon platform.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The new proposed governance structure will be comprised of "three main pillars", each catering to a distinct function. </p>
A New Approach to Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The first pillar involves the expansion of the Polygon Improvement Proposal (PIP) framework, currently limited to the Polygon PoS chain, to all applications and blockchains that run on the Polygon network. This adjustment will allow community members to propose and research upgrades that could potentially become part of the protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The second pillar, termed "System Smart Contracts Governance," is designed to facilitate upgrades for software implemented as smart contracts. The developers propose the creation of an Ecosystem Council, a body elected by the community, to oversee these changes. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The third pillar, the "Community Treasury", aims to support the growth of the Polygon ecosystem and fund projects. Initially, the Treasury will be managed by an independent Community Treasury Board before transitioning to community governance.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Community input will play a crucial role in determining the final shape of the governance plans. Therefore, Polygon Labs has encouraged developers, network validators, and other stakeholders to engage in discussions regarding the proposals.</p>
Community Deliberation and the Three Governance Pillars
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Polygon 2.0 is a reimagination of the current Polygon ecosystem. The proposal for the new governance structure seeks to address the complexities of blockchain governance and proposes a decentralized framework for decision-making over all Polygon protocols and the ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The proposal borrows elements from existing successful blockchain governance models, including Ethereum's open, inclusive governance ethos. The "Three Governance Pillars" are designed to provide governance over the entire Polygon ecosystem and define suitable decision makers for each pillar.</p>
Protocol Governance and System Smart Contracts Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The first pillar, Protocol Governance, involves the expansion of the PIP framework to cover all of Polygon's permissionless stack. The goal is to give the community a formal way to propose upgrades that could potentially become part of the protocols.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The second pillar, System Smart Contracts Governance, proposes the creation of an Ecosystem Council to upgrade system smart contracts. The Council will ensure the ongoing upgradeability of the protocol components implemented as smart contracts.</p>
Community Treasury Governance
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The third pillar, Community Treasury Governance, proposes the creation of a self-sustainable ecosystem fund, the Community Treasury. The fund will support the growth of the Polygon ecosystem and fund projects and initiatives.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The potential transformation outlined in the Polygon 2.0 governance proposal reflects the platform's commitment to decentralization and community empowerment. In this sense, ommunity-driven governance models are increasingly becoming as critical components of key platforms such as Polygon.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">This governance restructure, if adopted, may effectively position Polygon as a forerunner in this new phase of blockchain development. However, it is the community's acceptance and participation that will ultimately determine the realization of this vision. With this plan, Polygon could potentially pave the way for a future where the community holds the reins of blockchain protocols, fostering a truly decentralized ecosystem.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Anounces Google Cloud Partnership, Tradecurve To List on CoinMarketCap and Coingecko]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/pancakeswap-anounces-google-cloud-partnership-tradecurve-to-list-on-coinmarketcap-and-coingecko</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-649.png" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-649.png" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/image1-649.png" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 19:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/pancakeswap-anounces-google-cloud-partnership-tradecurve-to-list-on-coinmarketcap-and-coingecko</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market is exciting as prominent projects make significant strides toward mainstream adoption. Today, we explore two notable developments: PancakeSwap price rise following its partnership with Google Cloud and Tradecurve's anticipation of a listing on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko.&nbsp;</p>
&nbsp;
PancakeSwap (CAKE): A Boost From Google Cloud Partnership
<p>PancakeSwap has witnessed a surge in price following its recent partnership with Google Cloud. Collaborating with Google Cloud, a leading cloud computing service provider, brings enhanced security, scalability, and reliability to the PancakeSwap ecosystem.</p>
<p>This partnership enables Google Cloud to provide users with access to BNB endpoints. Additionally, it offers platform scalability, which can handle high traffic. This partnership has instilled confidence among investors and traders, leading to increased demand and a subsequent rise in the PancakeSwap coin price.</p>
<p>Currently, the PancakeSwap coin value sits at $1.51 with a market cap of $315M, a rise of 1.05% in the last 24 hours. Not only that, the PancakeSwap trading volume increased by 37.56% in that same period, reaching $30,248,679. All signs for the PancakeSwap coin are bullish, so experts predict a rise to $1.66 soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve (TCRV): Awaiting Listing on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko
<p>Tradecurve, the unique trading platform that brings forth the best features of CEX and DEX, has set its sights on securing listings on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko. Tradecurve's visibility and trustworthiness would be significantly increased by being listed on these platforms, bringing in more users and perhaps increasing trading volume.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Supporting Worldwide Traders&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve will be a borderless trading platform that any trader can sign up for with a working email only. As it requires no sign-up KYC checks, traders will remain completely anonymous as they access all derivatives on one account. Not only that, Tradecurve also offers high leverage, starting at 500:1, and the ability to subscribe to AI-driven trading bots.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve could become a fan-favorite for millions of worldwide traders. This is with regulation often limiting access to such advanced trading tools and highly leveraged products based on geographical location. This is now slowly becoming a reality as over 12,500 users have registered for Tradecurve, and the number is rising daily.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Providing an Excellent Return on Investment (ROI)
<p>The platform's native token, TCRV, is now worth $0.018 in Stage 4 of its presale. Those who purchased it during Stage 1 now enjoy an 80% ROI. It has significant long-term potential, and as it moves through the presale phases, the price of each token will rise. The price increase is expected when Stage 5 begins by the end of July, pushing the value up by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is well-positioned to experience a surge in value. It is expanding its reach into multiple financial markets. This includes the forex market, which saw a $7.5T daily turnaround in April 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts now predict this emerging presale star will soar by 50x before its presale finishes. So sign up for it below and capitalize off of this projected growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency market is exciting as prominent projects make significant strides toward mainstream adoption. Today, we explore two notable developments: PancakeSwap price rise following its partnership with Google Cloud and Tradecurve's anticipation of a listing on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko.&nbsp;</p>
&nbsp;
PancakeSwap (CAKE): A Boost From Google Cloud Partnership
<p>PancakeSwap has witnessed a surge in price following its recent partnership with Google Cloud. Collaborating with Google Cloud, a leading cloud computing service provider, brings enhanced security, scalability, and reliability to the PancakeSwap ecosystem.</p>
<p>This partnership enables Google Cloud to provide users with access to BNB endpoints. Additionally, it offers platform scalability, which can handle high traffic. This partnership has instilled confidence among investors and traders, leading to increased demand and a subsequent rise in the PancakeSwap coin price.</p>
<p>Currently, the PancakeSwap coin value sits at $1.51 with a market cap of $315M, a rise of 1.05% in the last 24 hours. Not only that, the PancakeSwap trading volume increased by 37.56% in that same period, reaching $30,248,679. All signs for the PancakeSwap coin are bullish, so experts predict a rise to $1.66 soon.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Tradecurve (TCRV): Awaiting Listing on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko
<p>Tradecurve, the unique trading platform that brings forth the best features of CEX and DEX, has set its sights on securing listings on CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko. Tradecurve's visibility and trustworthiness would be significantly increased by being listed on these platforms, bringing in more users and perhaps increasing trading volume.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Supporting Worldwide Traders&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve will be a borderless trading platform that any trader can sign up for with a working email only. As it requires no sign-up KYC checks, traders will remain completely anonymous as they access all derivatives on one account. Not only that, Tradecurve also offers high leverage, starting at 500:1, and the ability to subscribe to AI-driven trading bots.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Tradecurve could become a fan-favorite for millions of worldwide traders. This is with regulation often limiting access to such advanced trading tools and highly leveraged products based on geographical location. This is now slowly becoming a reality as over 12,500 users have registered for Tradecurve, and the number is rising daily.&nbsp;</p>
<p></p>
Providing an Excellent Return on Investment (ROI)
<p>The platform's native token, TCRV, is now worth $0.018 in Stage 4 of its presale. Those who purchased it during Stage 1 now enjoy an 80% ROI. It has significant long-term potential, and as it moves through the presale phases, the price of each token will rise. The price increase is expected when Stage 5 begins by the end of July, pushing the value up by 40%.&nbsp;</p>
<p>TCRV is well-positioned to experience a surge in value. It is expanding its reach into multiple financial markets. This includes the forex market, which saw a $7.5T daily turnaround in April 2022.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Analysts now predict this emerging presale star will soar by 50x before its presale finishes. So sign up for it below and capitalize off of this projected growth.&nbsp;</p>
<p>For more information about the Tradecurve presale:</p>
<p>Click Here For Website</p>
<p>Click Here To Buy TCRV Presale Tokens</p>
<p>Follow Us Twitter</p>
<p>Join Our Community on Telegram</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[French bank first to obtain licence to trade and custody crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/french-bank-first-to-obtain-licence-to-trade-and-custody-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/soc-2.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/soc-2.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/soc-2.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/french-bank-first-to-obtain-licence-to-trade-and-custody-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Societe Generale, the third biggest French bank, has become the first bank to procure a licence to provide trading and custody of cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p>Societe Generale has its own cryptocurrency division, SG Forge, which is now licenced to offer the buying, selling, and custody of digital assets. According to the press release on the SG Forge website, being in possession of a DASP (Digital Asset Service Provider) licence means that Societe Generale has demonstrated:</p>

<p>&ldquo;a comprehensive level of security and reliability of compliance, internal control and cybersecurity processes and systems, as well as the maintenance of sufficient regulatory capital&rdquo;</p>

<p>Jean-Marc Stenger, CEO of Societe Generale Forge said of the licence acquisition:</p>

<p>&ldquo;With the DASP license approval, Societe Generale &ndash; FORGE confirms its pioneering role in the crypto assets ecosystem. This step will allow us to continue supporting our institutional clients wishing to benefit from services on digital assets that meet the highest standards of compliance and banking security.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Opinion
<p>With such an important French bank entering into the race to offer crypto services, this is an important feather in the cap of France&rsquo;s ambitions to become the premier crypto hub in Europe.</p>
<p>The UK will no doubt be following this move carefully. Being outside of the European Union, but still in Europe as it were, it has some advantages over its European competitors in being free to set its own agenda and plans for crypto supremacy in this part of the world.</p>
<p>Other parts of the world that are hoping to take advantage of crypto technology, such as Singapore, Dubai, Hong Kong etc., will also be watching these events closely.</p>
<p>However, the US, the biggest economy in the world, is forced to sit on the sidelines, impotently watching as the rest of the world starts to divide up the technological spoils. As this happens, its watchdog financial agencies, the SEC, and the CFTC, are engaged in trying to erase the crypto industry from its shores, possibly under the assumption that crypto might be a threat to the dollar.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s not just the US financial agencies either. So-called global financial agencies such as the IMF, the FATF, and others, with the addition of all central banks, are aligned in the same endeavour.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, no technology in history has ever been successfully repressed for any length of time. For the US to be on the wrong side of this says much for the new direction that this world power is now following.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Societe Generale, the third biggest French bank, has become the first bank to procure a licence to provide trading and custody of cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p>Societe Generale has its own cryptocurrency division, SG Forge, which is now licenced to offer the buying, selling, and custody of digital assets. According to the press release on the SG Forge website, being in possession of a DASP (Digital Asset Service Provider) licence means that Societe Generale has demonstrated:</p>

<p>&ldquo;a comprehensive level of security and reliability of compliance, internal control and cybersecurity processes and systems, as well as the maintenance of sufficient regulatory capital&rdquo;</p>

<p>Jean-Marc Stenger, CEO of Societe Generale Forge said of the licence acquisition:</p>

<p>&ldquo;With the DASP license approval, Societe Generale &ndash; FORGE confirms its pioneering role in the crypto assets ecosystem. This step will allow us to continue supporting our institutional clients wishing to benefit from services on digital assets that meet the highest standards of compliance and banking security.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Opinion
<p>With such an important French bank entering into the race to offer crypto services, this is an important feather in the cap of France&rsquo;s ambitions to become the premier crypto hub in Europe.</p>
<p>The UK will no doubt be following this move carefully. Being outside of the European Union, but still in Europe as it were, it has some advantages over its European competitors in being free to set its own agenda and plans for crypto supremacy in this part of the world.</p>
<p>Other parts of the world that are hoping to take advantage of crypto technology, such as Singapore, Dubai, Hong Kong etc., will also be watching these events closely.</p>
<p>However, the US, the biggest economy in the world, is forced to sit on the sidelines, impotently watching as the rest of the world starts to divide up the technological spoils. As this happens, its watchdog financial agencies, the SEC, and the CFTC, are engaged in trying to erase the crypto industry from its shores, possibly under the assumption that crypto might be a threat to the dollar.</p>
<p>It&rsquo;s not just the US financial agencies either. So-called global financial agencies such as the IMF, the FATF, and others, with the addition of all central banks, are aligned in the same endeavour.</p>
<p>Be that as it may, no technology in history has ever been successfully repressed for any length of time. For the US to be on the wrong side of this says much for the new direction that this world power is now following.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Pomerium expands Ecosystem with Focus on BNB Chain]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/pomerium-expands-ecosystem-with-focus-on-bnb-chain</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance-NFT_1_16897457598OTScxMZ6o.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance-NFT_1_16897457598OTScxMZ6o.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/Binance-NFT_1_16897457598OTScxMZ6o.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:18:03 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/pomerium-expands-ecosystem-with-focus-on-bnb-chain</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 19th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Pomerium recently announced the listing of Pome Survival NFT on Binance NFT. Pomerium is a Web3 gaming studio that is expanding its project ecosystem centered around the BNB Chain.</p><p>One of the key features of Pomerium, which has released two Web3 games on the BNB Chain since 2022, is its expansion of the ecosystem on the BNB Chain as a single chain, setting it apart from other Gamefi projects that are expanding their projects through multi-chain approaches.</p><p>In June, Pomerium was selected as one of the twelve projects for the Zero2Hero incubator program hosted on the BNB Chain. Following this activity, the sale of Pome Survival NFT: BNB Edition is scheduled on Binance NFT.</p>SY KIM, the representative of Pomerium, stated, "It is an honor to have joined the esteemed Zero2Hero program hosted on the BNB Chain. The listing on Binance NFT, coupled with our collaboration with Ret Games, the developer of Pome Survival, has opened up a great opportunity for us.&rdquo;<p>Pome Survival is being developed by Ret Games, a prominent blockchain company in South Korea that recently signed a partnership agreement for blockchain industry cultivation with the city of Incheon. Pomerium, on the other hand, is responsible for publishing the Web3 Gamefi project.</p><p>The sale of Pome Survival NFT: BNB Edition will commence on July 26th on the Binance NFT homepage.</p><p>About Pomerium</p><p>Pomerium is a Web3 multi-game platform that focuses on mobile games. Its unique token economy is designed to create a sustainable mobile gaming ecosystem, and its platform enables gamers to play games on mobile devices instead of being limited to PC or web browsers. Pomerium plans to expand its services and influence in the GameFi market in the coming years.</p><p>For more information: Official website | Twitter | Telegram | Discord | Docs</p>ContactAllen ParkPomeriumallen@pomerium.space]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Singapore, Singapore, July 19th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Pomerium recently announced the listing of Pome Survival NFT on Binance NFT. Pomerium is a Web3 gaming studio that is expanding its project ecosystem centered around the BNB Chain.</p><p>One of the key features of Pomerium, which has released two Web3 games on the BNB Chain since 2022, is its expansion of the ecosystem on the BNB Chain as a single chain, setting it apart from other Gamefi projects that are expanding their projects through multi-chain approaches.</p><p>In June, Pomerium was selected as one of the twelve projects for the Zero2Hero incubator program hosted on the BNB Chain. Following this activity, the sale of Pome Survival NFT: BNB Edition is scheduled on Binance NFT.</p>SY KIM, the representative of Pomerium, stated, "It is an honor to have joined the esteemed Zero2Hero program hosted on the BNB Chain. The listing on Binance NFT, coupled with our collaboration with Ret Games, the developer of Pome Survival, has opened up a great opportunity for us.&rdquo;<p>Pome Survival is being developed by Ret Games, a prominent blockchain company in South Korea that recently signed a partnership agreement for blockchain industry cultivation with the city of Incheon. Pomerium, on the other hand, is responsible for publishing the Web3 Gamefi project.</p><p>The sale of Pome Survival NFT: BNB Edition will commence on July 26th on the Binance NFT homepage.</p><p>About Pomerium</p><p>Pomerium is a Web3 multi-game platform that focuses on mobile games. Its unique token economy is designed to create a sustainable mobile gaming ecosystem, and its platform enables gamers to play games on mobile devices instead of being limited to PC or web browsers. Pomerium plans to expand its services and influence in the GameFi market in the coming years.</p><p>For more information: Official website | Twitter | Telegram | Discord | Docs</p>ContactAllen ParkPomeriumallen@pomerium.space]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Saitama Receives Donation from LBank Labs Meme Fund]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/saitama-receives-donation-from-lbank-labs-meme-fund</link>
			  <media:content url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/img_v2_56692c67-0be7-48b1-84bf-a89d22bf7deh_1689780117eKO9D5VA4d.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/img_v2_56692c67-0be7-48b1-84bf-a89d22bf7deh_1689780117eKO9D5VA4d.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://app.chainwire.org/storage/uploads/users/img_v2_56692c67-0be7-48b1-84bf-a89d22bf7deh_1689780117eKO9D5VA4d.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:34:12 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/saitama-receives-donation-from-lbank-labs-meme-fund</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 19th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Saitama, a project that started as a meme token and has since developed into a comprehensive DeFi platform, has received a donation from the LBank Labs Meme Fund. The Meme Fund, a public benefit initiative launched by LBank Labs with a $10 million fund, is proposed to drive the progression of high-quality and innovative meme projects, catalyze industry growth, and provide benefit to the larger community.</p><p>Saitama, which started as a meme token, has undergone a considerable transformation, focusing on initiatives to streamline and bolster the security of decentralized finance (DeFi) for its users. The project places a strong emphasis on transparency and education and strives to develop practical use cases that integrate smoothly into a daily routine which includes SaitaPro (an all-in-one trading app)., SaitaCard (Master card), and SaitaLogistics that people can ship packages across the world Which includes news on Yahoo Finance.</p><p>The LBank Labs Meme Fund, a $10 million fund, exists to provide donations to a variety of meme-based projects. Those projects which fulfill certain criteria can apply and receive donations from the Meme Fund without any conditions, promoting growth and innovation within the meme ecosystem. The LBank Labs Meme Fund, along with these innovative Meme projects, are part of an ecosystem working towards the expansion and evolution of the meme token sector, highlighting the potential of these tokens to become fully functional DeFi platforms.</p><p>The progression of the partnership between LBank Labs Meme Fund and Saitama is set to continue, with pertinent updates anticipated in due course.</p><p>LBank Labs Meme Fund continues its global search for innovative and quality-driven meme projects, a move that reflects its engagement with the global meme project landscape.&nbsp;</p><p>Apply for the Meme Fund Grand: https://www.lbanklabs.com/contact-8</p><p>LBank Labs official website: https://www.lbanklabs.com/</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, "The Other Angle," through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Labsjunjie.niu@lbanklabs.com]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Road Town, BVI, July 19th, 2023, Chainwire</p><p>Saitama, a project that started as a meme token and has since developed into a comprehensive DeFi platform, has received a donation from the LBank Labs Meme Fund. The Meme Fund, a public benefit initiative launched by LBank Labs with a $10 million fund, is proposed to drive the progression of high-quality and innovative meme projects, catalyze industry growth, and provide benefit to the larger community.</p><p>Saitama, which started as a meme token, has undergone a considerable transformation, focusing on initiatives to streamline and bolster the security of decentralized finance (DeFi) for its users. The project places a strong emphasis on transparency and education and strives to develop practical use cases that integrate smoothly into a daily routine which includes SaitaPro (an all-in-one trading app)., SaitaCard (Master card), and SaitaLogistics that people can ship packages across the world Which includes news on Yahoo Finance.</p><p>The LBank Labs Meme Fund, a $10 million fund, exists to provide donations to a variety of meme-based projects. Those projects which fulfill certain criteria can apply and receive donations from the Meme Fund without any conditions, promoting growth and innovation within the meme ecosystem. The LBank Labs Meme Fund, along with these innovative Meme projects, are part of an ecosystem working towards the expansion and evolution of the meme token sector, highlighting the potential of these tokens to become fully functional DeFi platforms.</p><p>The progression of the partnership between LBank Labs Meme Fund and Saitama is set to continue, with pertinent updates anticipated in due course.</p><p>LBank Labs Meme Fund continues its global search for innovative and quality-driven meme projects, a move that reflects its engagement with the global meme project landscape.&nbsp;</p><p>Apply for the Meme Fund Grand: https://www.lbanklabs.com/contact-8</p><p>LBank Labs official website: https://www.lbanklabs.com/</p><p>About LBank Labs</p><p>LBank Labs, a prominent player in the web3 space, manages a versatile $100 Million fund that extends beyond specific protocols and exchanges. With a team of experienced web3 veterans from prestigious entities, they have built an extensive network of expertise and connections. Their investment strategy includes fund-of-fund investments, direct investments in early-stage projects, and liquid projects, enabling them to explore diverse opportunities. LBank Labs actively promotes their investment thesis, "The Other Angle," through engaging discussions and focuses on the PSE principles to foster sustainable growth and innovation in the web3 landscape. With a Fund of Fund network comprising 12 funds and over $1 billion in AUM, and offices in seven global regions, LBank Labs is well-positioned to expand their network and drive innovation in the web3 ecosystem, together with their partners and collaborators.</p>ContactLBank Labsjunjie.niu@lbanklabs.com]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Global Gaming Giant PlayWay partners with GameSwift to release OuterLife utilising a zk-powered Polygon Supernet]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/global-gaming-giant-playway-partners-with-gameswift-to-release-outerlife-utilising-a-zk-powered-polygon-supernet</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/photo-2023-07-18-12-18-14.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/photo-2023-07-18-12-18-14.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/uploads/youtube/photo-2023-07-18-12-18-14.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Crypto Daily]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/global-gaming-giant-playway-partners-with-gameswift-to-release-outerlife-utilising-a-zk-powered-polygon-supernet</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The frequent name on Steam&rsquo;s Global bestseller list is now entering web3, porting the first batch of its world famous simulator games into OuterLife.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PlayWay, the global gaming giant, has teamed up with GameSwift to introduce and launch OuterLife as their entry into the web3 gaming world on Polygon network</p>
<p>OuterLife is an innovative Web3 gaming accelerator and incubator, and it will allow PlayWay to integrate blockchain technology and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) into its famous simulator titles such as Animal Shelter, Farming Life, Cafe Owner Simulator and more.. PlayWay commented that it will port some of its existing catalogue of games, providing new, engaging and fresh experiences for its gamers with constantly evolving storylines and added productions. OuterLife also gives opportunity to other gaming studios producing simulators to join the incubator and using a zk-powered Polygon Supernet, to also build their own blockchains.</p>
<p>Pawe askarzewski, COO at OuterLife expressed that the gaming industry is &ldquo;ripe for disruption,&rdquo; in this case led by blockchain and NFT based initiatives. He said,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Blockchain technology has the ability to provide new and engaging enhancements to tried and tested gaming models that have worked over the years, allowing players to get close to the game more than ever.&rdquo;</p>

<p> Marek Parzyski, PlayWay, conveyed his delight in being part of the OuterLife launch and looks forward to a promising future in collaboration with both Polygon Labs and GameSwift.</p>
What does this mean for players and developers?&nbsp;
<p>Through the collaboration, existing and new developers within PlayWay&rsquo;s ecosystem and beyond will be able to connect their games to a world of interconnected digital reality, simply by an SDK, creating a truly open world. For players, OuterLife will offer an all new gaming experience where players can enhance statistics, acquire in-game items as non-fungible tokens and establish interconnected gaming simulations.</p>
<p>CEO of GameSwift Wojciech Gruszka known also under his Twitter handle as Pan Paragraf comments, </p>

<p>&ldquo;With OuterLife, character developments and upgrades in one game simulator will also have an impact in another - creating a truly interconnected digital reality with the power of blockchain.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Healthy Supply and Demand
<p>Major strides are being made to bring blockchain technology to mainstream gaming, with over $739M invested in Q1 2023 alone, according to a DappRadar report. Driving forces for mass adoption are games that are fun, and not complicated for user onboarding, regardless of its usage of blockchain technology. In addition to fun, trends suggest healthy supply and demand for ownership, privacy, creator empowerment and ecosystem growth.</p>
<p>OuterLife will use a zk-powered Polygon Supernet integration, which will address those to create a winning economic formula, while ensuring a seamless, scalable, easy to onboard and privacy-focused ecosystem for players, developers and gaming studios alike.&nbsp;</p>
Not Far Off
<p>PlayWay, the leading company behind gaming boom, was listed as the third-largest games company&mdash;trailing only CD Projekt Red, developers of The Witcher series and Cyberpunk 2077, and Techland with Dying Light. It is worth to highlight that PlayWay has around 4 times bigger capitalization than Ten Square Games, the mobile giant behind Let&rsquo;s Fish and Fishing Clash. The Global Giant has been home to some of the most successful gaming titles on Steam marketplace, with more than 100 titles in development, having partnered with more than 120 studios worldwide. While it's unclear on when the watershed mass-adoption moment will arrive, it's clear to see it having a major push with one of the biggest game studios in the world making heaps with the technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Gaming continues to be one of the major vectors of mainstream adoption for Web3,&rdquo; said Urvit Goel, Vice President, Head of Global Business Development at Polygon Labs. &ldquo;When leading game companies like PlayWay and GameSwift join forces to establish the groundwork for Web3 gaming infrastructure, and with the market leading advancements in zero knowledge technology being developed at Polygon Labs, the future of gaming holds tremendous potential.</p>
<p>PlayWay&rsquo;s simulator games have frequently been on Steam&rsquo;s global bestseller list, and the partnership with GameSwift only means it is not a question of if, but when blockchain technology will enhance games in a way that drives mass adoption.&nbsp;</p>
About PlayWay:
<p>PlayWay is one of the biggest group of gaming simulator studios in the world. Created in 2011, it has produced and released over 100 games that are sold and downloaded worldwide. With over 200 more still to come, PlayWay is listed at the Stock Exchange, with over 10 companies from PlayWay Group now on the stock exchange.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
About GameSwift:
<p>GameSwift is a Modular Gaming Ecosystem based on Modular Blockchain with Steam-like platform in its heart, which enables gamers to play web3 games with just one click (using Google/Facebook account) and without any blockchain know-how. GameSwift collaborated with Polygon Labs in August 2022 and will be building a Polygon Supernet. GameSwift will be backing PlayWay on the way to build their side chain using ZK rollups.</p>
About Polygon Labs:
<p>Polygon Labs develops Ethereum scaling solutions for Polygon protocols. Polygon Labs engages with other ecosystem developers to help make available scalable, affordable, secure and sustainable blockchain infrastructure for Web3.</p>
<p>Polygon Labs has initially developed a growing suite of protocols for developers to gain easy access to major scaling solutions, including layer 2s (zero-knowledge rollups), sidechains, app-specific chains and data availability protocols. Scaling solutions that Polygon Labs initially developed have seen widespread adoption with tens of thousands of decentralised apps, unique addresses exceeding 287 million, over 1.4 million smart contracts created and 2.7 billion total transactions processed since inception. The existing Polygon network is home for some of the biggest Web3 projects, such as Aave, Uniswap, and OpenSea, and well-known enterprises, including Robinhood, Stripe and Adobe. Polygon Labs is carbon neutral with the goal of leading Web3 in becoming carbon negative.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The frequent name on Steam&rsquo;s Global bestseller list is now entering web3, porting the first batch of its world famous simulator games into OuterLife.&nbsp;</p>
<p>PlayWay, the global gaming giant, has teamed up with GameSwift to introduce and launch OuterLife as their entry into the web3 gaming world on Polygon network</p>
<p>OuterLife is an innovative Web3 gaming accelerator and incubator, and it will allow PlayWay to integrate blockchain technology and non-fungible tokens (NFTs) into its famous simulator titles such as Animal Shelter, Farming Life, Cafe Owner Simulator and more.. PlayWay commented that it will port some of its existing catalogue of games, providing new, engaging and fresh experiences for its gamers with constantly evolving storylines and added productions. OuterLife also gives opportunity to other gaming studios producing simulators to join the incubator and using a zk-powered Polygon Supernet, to also build their own blockchains.</p>
<p>Pawe askarzewski, COO at OuterLife expressed that the gaming industry is &ldquo;ripe for disruption,&rdquo; in this case led by blockchain and NFT based initiatives. He said,</p>

<p>&ldquo;Blockchain technology has the ability to provide new and engaging enhancements to tried and tested gaming models that have worked over the years, allowing players to get close to the game more than ever.&rdquo;</p>

<p> Marek Parzyski, PlayWay, conveyed his delight in being part of the OuterLife launch and looks forward to a promising future in collaboration with both Polygon Labs and GameSwift.</p>
What does this mean for players and developers?&nbsp;
<p>Through the collaboration, existing and new developers within PlayWay&rsquo;s ecosystem and beyond will be able to connect their games to a world of interconnected digital reality, simply by an SDK, creating a truly open world. For players, OuterLife will offer an all new gaming experience where players can enhance statistics, acquire in-game items as non-fungible tokens and establish interconnected gaming simulations.</p>
<p>CEO of GameSwift Wojciech Gruszka known also under his Twitter handle as Pan Paragraf comments, </p>

<p>&ldquo;With OuterLife, character developments and upgrades in one game simulator will also have an impact in another - creating a truly interconnected digital reality with the power of blockchain.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

Healthy Supply and Demand
<p>Major strides are being made to bring blockchain technology to mainstream gaming, with over $739M invested in Q1 2023 alone, according to a DappRadar report. Driving forces for mass adoption are games that are fun, and not complicated for user onboarding, regardless of its usage of blockchain technology. In addition to fun, trends suggest healthy supply and demand for ownership, privacy, creator empowerment and ecosystem growth.</p>
<p>OuterLife will use a zk-powered Polygon Supernet integration, which will address those to create a winning economic formula, while ensuring a seamless, scalable, easy to onboard and privacy-focused ecosystem for players, developers and gaming studios alike.&nbsp;</p>
Not Far Off
<p>PlayWay, the leading company behind gaming boom, was listed as the third-largest games company&mdash;trailing only CD Projekt Red, developers of The Witcher series and Cyberpunk 2077, and Techland with Dying Light. It is worth to highlight that PlayWay has around 4 times bigger capitalization than Ten Square Games, the mobile giant behind Let&rsquo;s Fish and Fishing Clash. The Global Giant has been home to some of the most successful gaming titles on Steam marketplace, with more than 100 titles in development, having partnered with more than 120 studios worldwide. While it's unclear on when the watershed mass-adoption moment will arrive, it's clear to see it having a major push with one of the biggest game studios in the world making heaps with the technology.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Gaming continues to be one of the major vectors of mainstream adoption for Web3,&rdquo; said Urvit Goel, Vice President, Head of Global Business Development at Polygon Labs. &ldquo;When leading game companies like PlayWay and GameSwift join forces to establish the groundwork for Web3 gaming infrastructure, and with the market leading advancements in zero knowledge technology being developed at Polygon Labs, the future of gaming holds tremendous potential.</p>
<p>PlayWay&rsquo;s simulator games have frequently been on Steam&rsquo;s global bestseller list, and the partnership with GameSwift only means it is not a question of if, but when blockchain technology will enhance games in a way that drives mass adoption.&nbsp;</p>
About PlayWay:
<p>PlayWay is one of the biggest group of gaming simulator studios in the world. Created in 2011, it has produced and released over 100 games that are sold and downloaded worldwide. With over 200 more still to come, PlayWay is listed at the Stock Exchange, with over 10 companies from PlayWay Group now on the stock exchange.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
About GameSwift:
<p>GameSwift is a Modular Gaming Ecosystem based on Modular Blockchain with Steam-like platform in its heart, which enables gamers to play web3 games with just one click (using Google/Facebook account) and without any blockchain know-how. GameSwift collaborated with Polygon Labs in August 2022 and will be building a Polygon Supernet. GameSwift will be backing PlayWay on the way to build their side chain using ZK rollups.</p>
About Polygon Labs:
<p>Polygon Labs develops Ethereum scaling solutions for Polygon protocols. Polygon Labs engages with other ecosystem developers to help make available scalable, affordable, secure and sustainable blockchain infrastructure for Web3.</p>
<p>Polygon Labs has initially developed a growing suite of protocols for developers to gain easy access to major scaling solutions, including layer 2s (zero-knowledge rollups), sidechains, app-specific chains and data availability protocols. Scaling solutions that Polygon Labs initially developed have seen widespread adoption with tens of thousands of decentralised apps, unique addresses exceeding 287 million, over 1.4 million smart contracts created and 2.7 billion total transactions processed since inception. The existing Polygon network is home for some of the biggest Web3 projects, such as Aave, Uniswap, and OpenSea, and well-known enterprises, including Robinhood, Stripe and Adobe. Polygon Labs is carbon neutral with the goal of leading Web3 in becoming carbon negative.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This is a sponsored press release and is for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Analysis:  Better After 29525 Print - 20 July 2023]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-better-after-29525-print-20-july-2023</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-19-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-19-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/btcusd-19-july-2023-240-1920-1080.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Sally Ho]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/bitcoin-price-analysis-better-after-29525-print-20-july-2023</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Reclaiming Losses After 29525 Print:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 20 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to reclaim recent losses early in the Asian session as the pair hovered around the 30000 figure after trading as high as the 30196.24 area.&nbsp; Significant Stops were elected below the 29592.63 area during the pair&rsquo;s recent depreciation, a downside price objective that is related to recent selling pressure that strengthened around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; After BTC/USD escalated appreciated to interday highs and came off, Stops were elected below the 29860.62 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29525 to 30196.24.&nbsp; Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30420.27 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30001.33.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BTC/USD Reclaiming Losses After 29525 Print:&nbsp; Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis &ndash; 20 July 2023</p>
<p>Bitcoin (BTC/USD) worked to reclaim recent losses early in the Asian session as the pair hovered around the 30000 figure after trading as high as the 30196.24 area.&nbsp; Significant Stops were elected below the 29592.63 area during the pair&rsquo;s recent depreciation, a downside price objective that is related to recent selling pressure that strengthened around the 31862.21 and 31376.52 areas.&nbsp;&nbsp; After BTC/USD escalated appreciated to interday highs and came off, Stops were elected below the 29860.62 area, representing the 50% retracement of the recent appreciating range from 29525 to 30196.24.&nbsp; Following recent trading activity, areas of technical support and potential buying pressure include the 29108, 28275, 27443, 26413, and 26257 levels.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Below current price activity, the 28095.44 area represents the 23.6% retracement of the historical depreciating range from 69000 to 15460.&nbsp; Upside price objectives include the 32125 and 33569 areas, and Stops are cited above additional upside price objectives around the 32043, 34531, 34658, and 35912 areas.&nbsp; Traders are&nbsp;observing&nbsp;that the&nbsp;50-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;is&nbsp;bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (4-hourly)&nbsp;and&nbsp;above the&nbsp;200-bar MA (4-hourly).&nbsp; Also, the 50-bar MA (hourly) is bearishly indicating below the 100-bar MA (hourly) and below the 200-bar MA (hourly).</p>
<p>Price activity is nearest the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(4-hourly) at 30420.27 and the&nbsp;50-bar MA&nbsp;(Hourly) at 30001.33.</p>
<p>Technical Support&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;24440.41/ 23270.10/ 22769.39 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected below.</p>
<p>Technical Resistance&nbsp;is expected around&nbsp;31986.16/ 32989.19/ 34658.69 with&nbsp;Stops&nbsp;expected above.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>On&nbsp;4-Hourly&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bullishly above SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is Bullishly above MACDAverage.</p>
<p>On&nbsp;60-minute&nbsp;chart,&nbsp;SlowK&nbsp;is Bearishly below SlowD&nbsp;while&nbsp;MACD&nbsp;is&nbsp;Bullishly above MACDAverage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Disclaimer: Sally Ho&rsquo;s Technical Analysis is provided by a third party, and for informational purposes only. It does not reflect the views of Crypto Daily, nor is it intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, or financial advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[IMF: Extensive Policies Needed to Protect Economies and Investors]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/imf-extensive-policies-needed-to-protect-economies-and-investors</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/imf-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/imf-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/imf-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 15:00:46 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/imf-extensive-policies-needed-to-protect-economies-and-investors</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) underscored its views that crypto requires &ldquo;comprehensive policies to safeguard economies and investors.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) published a blog recently in which it clarifies that investors and economies will only be adequately protected by comprehensive crypto policies.</p>
<p>The IMFs policy suggestion comes amid a global push for clear guidelines for crypto assets under the Indian G20 Presidency.</p>
Global Crypto Regulation on G20&rsquo;s Agenda
<p>The collapse of some of the biggest crypto platforms in 2022 highlighted the dire need for establishing clear guidelines and policies for the industry to protect investors against the implications of a mostly unregulated industry.</p>
<p>The sheer loss and impact of the implosion of the crypto trading platform FTX and the Terra Luna stablecoin made it clear that the risk of fraud and misconduct could be disastrous for investors without comprehensive safeguards.</p>
<p>As such, the Group of 20 Nations (G20) directed its efforts to ensure that appropriate safeguards are put in place.</p>
<p>Regulatory bodies such as the Financial Stability Board (FSB) have issued recommendations to develop a global framework for crypto-assets, with further guidance expected from the Bank for International Settlements (BIS).</p>
<p>The IMF subsequently made its contribution to establishing such a regulatory framework.</p>
Three-Pillared Approach
<p>The reality of an evolving financial system is that digitization of currencies and assets is inevitable, and the likelihood of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and stablecoins replacing official currencies is increasing. To address the impact of such financial changes on countries&rsquo; monetary and fiscal policies, a comprehensive, consistent, and coordinated policy approach to crypto is needed.</p>
<p>The IMF assessed the potential macro-financial implications of the widespread adoption of CBDCs and relies on three aspects in its approach to a global regulatory framework.</p>
<p>The IMF developed its approach on three key aspects: &ldquo;a sound macro-policy foundation, clear legal treatment and granular rules, and effective implementation.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The bank developed a few key policy recommendations based on these three pillars.</p>
<p>First, protecting against substituting sovereign currencies will depend on maintaining robust, trusted, credible domestic institutions. To address crypto assets&rsquo; challenges effectively, &ldquo;transparent, consistent, and coherent monetary policy frameworks&rdquo; are imperative.</p>
<p>The IMF suggests to protect national sovereignty; crypto assets should not be granted the status of official currency or legal tender.</p>
<p>The IMF&rsquo;s third recommendation addresses the volatility of capital flows associated with crypto. The bank believes policymakers should integrate crypto within their existing regimes and rules for managing capital flows. Doing so will help ensure stability and minimize potential disruptions.</p>
<p>The IMF&rsquo;s final recommendation is tax policies &ldquo;should ensure unambiguous treatment of crypto assets, and administrators should strengthen compliance efforts.&rdquo; The IMF argues specific regulations to clarify the tax treatment of crypto are necessary.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) underscored its views that crypto requires &ldquo;comprehensive policies to safeguard economies and investors.&rdquo; </p>
<p>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) published a blog recently in which it clarifies that investors and economies will only be adequately protected by comprehensive crypto policies.</p>
<p>The IMFs policy suggestion comes amid a global push for clear guidelines for crypto assets under the Indian G20 Presidency.</p>
Global Crypto Regulation on G20&rsquo;s Agenda
<p>The collapse of some of the biggest crypto platforms in 2022 highlighted the dire need for establishing clear guidelines and policies for the industry to protect investors against the implications of a mostly unregulated industry.</p>
<p>The sheer loss and impact of the implosion of the crypto trading platform FTX and the Terra Luna stablecoin made it clear that the risk of fraud and misconduct could be disastrous for investors without comprehensive safeguards.</p>
<p>As such, the Group of 20 Nations (G20) directed its efforts to ensure that appropriate safeguards are put in place.</p>
<p>Regulatory bodies such as the Financial Stability Board (FSB) have issued recommendations to develop a global framework for crypto-assets, with further guidance expected from the Bank for International Settlements (BIS).</p>
<p>The IMF subsequently made its contribution to establishing such a regulatory framework.</p>
Three-Pillared Approach
<p>The reality of an evolving financial system is that digitization of currencies and assets is inevitable, and the likelihood of central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) and stablecoins replacing official currencies is increasing. To address the impact of such financial changes on countries&rsquo; monetary and fiscal policies, a comprehensive, consistent, and coordinated policy approach to crypto is needed.</p>
<p>The IMF assessed the potential macro-financial implications of the widespread adoption of CBDCs and relies on three aspects in its approach to a global regulatory framework.</p>
<p>The IMF developed its approach on three key aspects: &ldquo;a sound macro-policy foundation, clear legal treatment and granular rules, and effective implementation.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The bank developed a few key policy recommendations based on these three pillars.</p>
<p>First, protecting against substituting sovereign currencies will depend on maintaining robust, trusted, credible domestic institutions. To address crypto assets&rsquo; challenges effectively, &ldquo;transparent, consistent, and coherent monetary policy frameworks&rdquo; are imperative.</p>
<p>The IMF suggests to protect national sovereignty; crypto assets should not be granted the status of official currency or legal tender.</p>
<p>The IMF&rsquo;s third recommendation addresses the volatility of capital flows associated with crypto. The bank believes policymakers should integrate crypto within their existing regimes and rules for managing capital flows. Doing so will help ensure stability and minimize potential disruptions.</p>
<p>The IMF&rsquo;s final recommendation is tax policies &ldquo;should ensure unambiguous treatment of crypto assets, and administrators should strengthen compliance efforts.&rdquo; The IMF argues specific regulations to clarify the tax treatment of crypto are necessary.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinfund, Polychain Raise Over $350M]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinfund-polychain-raise-over-350-m-usd</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/pdax-funding.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/pdax-funding.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/pdax-funding.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:10:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinfund-polychain-raise-over-350-m-usd</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Venture capital firms Coinfund and Polychain Capital have successfully raised a total of $350 million in their latest fundraising rounds, showcasing returning confidence in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
Coinfund Raises $152M&nbsp;
<p>New York-based venture capital firm, Coinfund, has successfully raised $152 million in its latest funding round, showcasing confidence in the crypto space despite the recent pullback by many investors. The firm, known for its portfolio of 105 companies, prioritizes projects that contribute to the development of crypto infrastructure, with a specific focus on enabling greater decentralization.</p>
Polychain Raises $200M Of $400M Goal
<p>In a similar chain of events, another blockchain-based venture capital firm, Polychain Capital, has also completed its initial close, amassing approximately $200 million for its fourth crypto venture capital fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The total goal for the fund is set at $400 million, in line with the amount specified in an April filing with the SEC for the Polychain Ventures IV (Parallel) LP fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With just under $2.6 billion of assets under management, the VC firm struggled during the crypto winter, having to lay off staff, much like many other crypto-focused organizations. Crypto investments took a major hit last year, with funding for crypto projects shrinking from $9.1 billion a year earlier to only $1.7 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the recent crypto-positive ruling in the SEC vs. Ripple case has renewed interest in crypto, with Coinbase shares hitting their yearly high.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinfund Continues Crypto Bet</p>
<p>Coinfund has already made significant investments in companies such as Giza, an AI-focused venture that raised about $3 million in seed funding, and infrastructure projects like Cosmos, where it helped raise $10 million to advance the development of its Neutron smart contract platform in collaboration with Binance Labs and others.</p>
<p>This latest move by Coinfund comes amidst a broader retreat from crypto investments after a challenging year marked by multiple failures, including the collapse of the TerraLuna stablecoin and FTX exchange. Additionally, higher interest rates have made borrowing more expensive, complicating the fundraising landscape.</p>
Focusing On Scalability, Interoperability
<p>Coinfund's co-founder and chief investment officer, Alex Felix, explained that the implosion of cryptocurrency exchange FTX last year had led developers to double down on completing the roadmap to a decentralized application developer stack. As a result, scalability, interoperability, and user experience have become renewed areas of focus.</p>
<p>While previous rounds of fundraising centered on established categories like NFT gaming and DeFi, this latest round will shift the spotlight towards emerging sectors, particularly early-stage crypto start-ups, especially those involving artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Venture capital firms Coinfund and Polychain Capital have successfully raised a total of $350 million in their latest fundraising rounds, showcasing returning confidence in the crypto space.&nbsp;</p>
Coinfund Raises $152M&nbsp;
<p>New York-based venture capital firm, Coinfund, has successfully raised $152 million in its latest funding round, showcasing confidence in the crypto space despite the recent pullback by many investors. The firm, known for its portfolio of 105 companies, prioritizes projects that contribute to the development of crypto infrastructure, with a specific focus on enabling greater decentralization.</p>
Polychain Raises $200M Of $400M Goal
<p>In a similar chain of events, another blockchain-based venture capital firm, Polychain Capital, has also completed its initial close, amassing approximately $200 million for its fourth crypto venture capital fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>The total goal for the fund is set at $400 million, in line with the amount specified in an April filing with the SEC for the Polychain Ventures IV (Parallel) LP fund.&nbsp;</p>
<p>With just under $2.6 billion of assets under management, the VC firm struggled during the crypto winter, having to lay off staff, much like many other crypto-focused organizations. Crypto investments took a major hit last year, with funding for crypto projects shrinking from $9.1 billion a year earlier to only $1.7 billion.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, the recent crypto-positive ruling in the SEC vs. Ripple case has renewed interest in crypto, with Coinbase shares hitting their yearly high.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Coinfund Continues Crypto Bet</p>
<p>Coinfund has already made significant investments in companies such as Giza, an AI-focused venture that raised about $3 million in seed funding, and infrastructure projects like Cosmos, where it helped raise $10 million to advance the development of its Neutron smart contract platform in collaboration with Binance Labs and others.</p>
<p>This latest move by Coinfund comes amidst a broader retreat from crypto investments after a challenging year marked by multiple failures, including the collapse of the TerraLuna stablecoin and FTX exchange. Additionally, higher interest rates have made borrowing more expensive, complicating the fundraising landscape.</p>
Focusing On Scalability, Interoperability
<p>Coinfund's co-founder and chief investment officer, Alex Felix, explained that the implosion of cryptocurrency exchange FTX last year had led developers to double down on completing the roadmap to a decentralized application developer stack. As a result, scalability, interoperability, and user experience have become renewed areas of focus.</p>
<p>While previous rounds of fundraising centered on established categories like NFT gaming and DeFi, this latest round will shift the spotlight towards emerging sectors, particularly early-stage crypto start-ups, especially those involving artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice. </p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[EtherFi CEO Condemns OpenSeas Suspension Of Its NFTs]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/etherfi-ceo-condemns-opensea-suspension-of-its-nfts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etherfi-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etherfi-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etherfi-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/etherfi-ceo-condemns-opensea-suspension-of-its-nfts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Staking protocol EtherFi has called out the OpenSea marketplace for its decision to suspend the trading of the former&rsquo;s EtherFan NFT collection last week.&nbsp;</p>
EtherFi Open Letter Slams OpenSea&nbsp;
<p>Founder and CEO at EtherFi, Mike Silagadze, penned a reproachful letter addressing the OpenSea marketplace and its decision to halt the trading of the EtherFan NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Silagadze wrote that even though the collection launch was a success, it was short-lived. He wrote that even though the collection&rsquo;s all 3000 NFTs were minted within a day, the listings were removed from the OpenSea platform without any warning. The creators attempted to contact OpenSea through multiple channels but received no response for several days.</p>
&ldquo;OpenSea - An Unlicensed Casino&rdquo;
<p>Silagadze wrote that after days of attempted contact, the NFT marketplace finally responded in the form of a letter from its generic support email. The communication claimed that NFT collections involved in financial activities subject to registration or licensing are not allowed on the OpenSea platform. Since EtherFan NFTs are wrapped staked ETH with a PFP (Profile Picture), they fall under the category devised by the platform&rsquo;s conservative interpretation.</p>
<p>Saligadze also claimed that the NFT creators had previously communicated with the marketplace team prior to the launch to ensure compatibility and had received the green signal from them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;OpenSea has been running a de facto unlicensed casino where people engage in ruinous gambling and spend millions on pictures of monkeys and such. This is all great and ok apparently, but listing a collection that actually has utility is disallowed because it has utility.&rdquo;</p>

OpenSea Too Big To Take Risks
<p>He did state that he did not believe there were any malicious intentions behind the actions, but just that the scope of the platform has become too big for operational clarity. He believes OpenSea's growth into a large organization might have led to increased caution and risk aversion.</p>
<p>He wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Having the EtherFan NFT listed on a marketplace was a fairly important part of our marketing strategy because we expected there would be a resale market&hellip;Unequivocally, we did not get any indication whatsoever from OpenSea that any of what we were doing was potentially in violation of their Terms of Service,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The incident has sparked discussions within the crypto community about the importance of companies taking principled stands, with some pointing to Coinbase as an example. For now, EtherFan NFTs remain unavailable on OpenSea, leaving its creators and users seeking alternative solutions for trading and engagement.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Staking protocol EtherFi has called out the OpenSea marketplace for its decision to suspend the trading of the former&rsquo;s EtherFan NFT collection last week.&nbsp;</p>
EtherFi Open Letter Slams OpenSea&nbsp;
<p>Founder and CEO at EtherFi, Mike Silagadze, penned a reproachful letter addressing the OpenSea marketplace and its decision to halt the trading of the EtherFan NFT collection.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Silagadze wrote that even though the collection launch was a success, it was short-lived. He wrote that even though the collection&rsquo;s all 3000 NFTs were minted within a day, the listings were removed from the OpenSea platform without any warning. The creators attempted to contact OpenSea through multiple channels but received no response for several days.</p>
&ldquo;OpenSea - An Unlicensed Casino&rdquo;
<p>Silagadze wrote that after days of attempted contact, the NFT marketplace finally responded in the form of a letter from its generic support email. The communication claimed that NFT collections involved in financial activities subject to registration or licensing are not allowed on the OpenSea platform. Since EtherFan NFTs are wrapped staked ETH with a PFP (Profile Picture), they fall under the category devised by the platform&rsquo;s conservative interpretation.</p>
<p>Saligadze also claimed that the NFT creators had previously communicated with the marketplace team prior to the launch to ensure compatibility and had received the green signal from them.&nbsp;</p>
<p>He wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;OpenSea has been running a de facto unlicensed casino where people engage in ruinous gambling and spend millions on pictures of monkeys and such. This is all great and ok apparently, but listing a collection that actually has utility is disallowed because it has utility.&rdquo;</p>

OpenSea Too Big To Take Risks
<p>He did state that he did not believe there were any malicious intentions behind the actions, but just that the scope of the platform has become too big for operational clarity. He believes OpenSea's growth into a large organization might have led to increased caution and risk aversion.</p>
<p>He wrote,&nbsp;</p>

<p>&ldquo;Having the EtherFan NFT listed on a marketplace was a fairly important part of our marketing strategy because we expected there would be a resale market&hellip;Unequivocally, we did not get any indication whatsoever from OpenSea that any of what we were doing was potentially in violation of their Terms of Service,&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>

<p>The incident has sparked discussions within the crypto community about the importance of companies taking principled stands, with some pointing to Coinbase as an example. For now, EtherFan NFTs remain unavailable on OpenSea, leaving its creators and users seeking alternative solutions for trading and engagement.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Thodex CEO Gets 7-Month Prison Sentence On Charges Of Tax Evasion]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/thodex-ceo-gets-7-month-prison-sentence-on-charges-of-tax-evasion</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/thodex-1450.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/thodex-1450.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/thodex-1450.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/thodex-ceo-gets-7-month-prison-sentence-on-charges-of-tax-evasion</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and former CEO of the now-defunct Thodex cryptocurrency exchange has received a seven-month prison sentence after he failed to submit relevant documents requested during the trial.</p>
<p>Turkish prosecutors had initially sought a jail sentence of up to five years on smuggling charges under the country&rsquo;s Tax Procedure Law.</p>
A Protracted Court Case
<p>Thodex was one of the most prominent cryptocurrency exchanges operating in Turkey. However, the exchange abruptly shut down, with Faruk Fatih Ozer, the CEO of the exchange, fleeing to Albania. After Interpol issued a Red Notice, Ozer was deported back to Turkey and faced fraud charges for pocketing over $2 billion in client funds when Thodex shut down. The CEO and 21 other defendants face charges that include alleged fraud, money laundering, and operating a complex criminal network using Thodex. Ozer could face a significantly longer and more severe punishment if found guilty.</p>
Ozer Maintains Innocence
<p>The case was heard at the Anatolian 17th Criminal Court of First Instance, with magistrates initially sentencing Ozer to one and a half years in prison. However, this sentence was reduced after the court considered his social relations, behavior, and potential impact on his future. Ozer has maintained his innocence throughout the duration of the trial, which began in October 2021. Turkish authorities had asked the former CEO to submit documents related to his activities at Thodex to the Tax Inspection Board.</p>
<p>However, Ozer was unable to present the required documents within the stipulated time frame. Instead, he denied the charges, claiming that he had been framed and stating that the company was hacked. He also denied being a Thodex official at the time, claiming that a trustee had been appointed to oversee the exchange and business in his absence, preventing him from sharing the requested records. Ozer has also maintained that former employees, including his brother and sister, who were arrested in 2021, were unlawfully imprisoned.</p>
Problems Continue To Mount
<p>Ozer faces a number of other accusations, which could see the former CEO spend the rest of his life in prison. Prosecutors and investors have insisted that he had a key role in the collapse of the Thodex exchange. Thodex collapsed in 2021 when the platform abruptly stopped all services. As a result, over 400,000 customers were unable to withdraw their funds, with prosecutors alleging that Ozer made off with over $2 billion in customer funds. However, after being on the run for over a year, he was detained in Albania, with Albanian and Turkish officials negotiating his deportation.</p>
<p>Officials had initially sought a five year prison sentence for Ozer under the country&rsquo;s stringent Tax Procedure Law.</p>
Tax Evasion A Major Issue
<p>According to a study by Swedish crypto tax firm Divly, 99.5% of crypto investors did not end up paying taxes in 2022. The report states that Finland had the highest number of investors that paid the requisite taxes on their crypto investments, with the number just over 4%. Australia and Austria followed close behind with 3.65% and 2.75%, respectively, followed by Germany, the United Kingdom, Norway, Japan, Sweden, Canada, and the United States. Countries at the lower end of the table, such as India, Indonesia, and the Philippines, have only 0.07%, 0.04%, and 0.03% of crypto investors that paid taxes in 2022.</p>
<p>However, the report has also received considerable criticism, with many questioning the methodology used to arrive at the estimates mentioned in the report. The report itself notes that search volume data may not accurately reflect the actual number of taxpayers from the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and former CEO of the now-defunct Thodex cryptocurrency exchange has received a seven-month prison sentence after he failed to submit relevant documents requested during the trial.</p>
<p>Turkish prosecutors had initially sought a jail sentence of up to five years on smuggling charges under the country&rsquo;s Tax Procedure Law.</p>
A Protracted Court Case
<p>Thodex was one of the most prominent cryptocurrency exchanges operating in Turkey. However, the exchange abruptly shut down, with Faruk Fatih Ozer, the CEO of the exchange, fleeing to Albania. After Interpol issued a Red Notice, Ozer was deported back to Turkey and faced fraud charges for pocketing over $2 billion in client funds when Thodex shut down. The CEO and 21 other defendants face charges that include alleged fraud, money laundering, and operating a complex criminal network using Thodex. Ozer could face a significantly longer and more severe punishment if found guilty.</p>
Ozer Maintains Innocence
<p>The case was heard at the Anatolian 17th Criminal Court of First Instance, with magistrates initially sentencing Ozer to one and a half years in prison. However, this sentence was reduced after the court considered his social relations, behavior, and potential impact on his future. Ozer has maintained his innocence throughout the duration of the trial, which began in October 2021. Turkish authorities had asked the former CEO to submit documents related to his activities at Thodex to the Tax Inspection Board.</p>
<p>However, Ozer was unable to present the required documents within the stipulated time frame. Instead, he denied the charges, claiming that he had been framed and stating that the company was hacked. He also denied being a Thodex official at the time, claiming that a trustee had been appointed to oversee the exchange and business in his absence, preventing him from sharing the requested records. Ozer has also maintained that former employees, including his brother and sister, who were arrested in 2021, were unlawfully imprisoned.</p>
Problems Continue To Mount
<p>Ozer faces a number of other accusations, which could see the former CEO spend the rest of his life in prison. Prosecutors and investors have insisted that he had a key role in the collapse of the Thodex exchange. Thodex collapsed in 2021 when the platform abruptly stopped all services. As a result, over 400,000 customers were unable to withdraw their funds, with prosecutors alleging that Ozer made off with over $2 billion in customer funds. However, after being on the run for over a year, he was detained in Albania, with Albanian and Turkish officials negotiating his deportation.</p>
<p>Officials had initially sought a five year prison sentence for Ozer under the country&rsquo;s stringent Tax Procedure Law.</p>
Tax Evasion A Major Issue
<p>According to a study by Swedish crypto tax firm Divly, 99.5% of crypto investors did not end up paying taxes in 2022. The report states that Finland had the highest number of investors that paid the requisite taxes on their crypto investments, with the number just over 4%. Australia and Austria followed close behind with 3.65% and 2.75%, respectively, followed by Germany, the United Kingdom, Norway, Japan, Sweden, Canada, and the United States. Countries at the lower end of the table, such as India, Indonesia, and the Philippines, have only 0.07%, 0.04%, and 0.03% of crypto investors that paid taxes in 2022.</p>
<p>However, the report has also received considerable criticism, with many questioning the methodology used to arrive at the estimates mentioned in the report. The report itself notes that search volume data may not accurately reflect the actual number of taxpayers from the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Its only a matter of time for bitcoin]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/its-only-a-matter-of-time-for-bitcoin</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etf-7.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etf-7.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/etf-7.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:58:20 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Laurie Dunn]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/its-only-a-matter-of-time-for-bitcoin</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The writing is on the wall. Bitcoin ETFs are queued at the SEC and it is now just a matter of time before bitcoin explodes higher.</p>
SEC Gensler in a tough place
<p>The anti-crypto chairman of the SEC, Gary Gensler, is in between a rock and a hard place. He has the biggest asset management company in the world (Blackrock) as well as several other financial giants, awaiting his decision.</p>
<p>To buy himself time Gensler could put his decision back as much as 240 days, but the chances of the environment changing as far as granting a Spot Bitcoin ETF would likely be very small.</p>
<p>The SEC chair could continue to back himself and just turn the ETF applications down en masse. However, he is really running out of grounds for doing so, and the political pressure he must already be facing would ratchet up to insufferable levels.</p>
Poor SEC decisions
<p>Gensler would need to be a man of iron in order to continue steering his anti-crypto course, but his performances so far do not indicate that he has the backbone to do this.</p>
<p>Under his leadership the SEC has changed from its role as cop on the beat, that makes sure markets run smoothly, and that investors have proper protections, into a vehicle that is carrying out a hostile crusade against the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Gensler&rsquo;s decision to attack Coinbase now seems to have been a very poorly judged move, especially in the light of the recent SEC/Ripple case court decision that ruled that secondary sales of XRP on exchanges did not constitute the transaction of a security.</p>
<p>Therefore, continuing to spend millions of taxpayer dollars on trying to bring Coinbase down, a company that is seen to have made every effort to be compliant, looks to be folly, and might be regarded as the SEC making a perverse effort to destroy all the crypto exchanges in order to prevent retail investors from using them.</p>
A power that transcends government
<p>It might very well be argued that it&rsquo;s not just Gensler using the SEC as an armament against crypto. The decision to bring crypto down may well have come from much higher up, and possibly from the very highest echelon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there is still one power in the US that continues to transcend politics and government, and that is the power of money, and this comes in the form of institutional companies that own a piece of just about everything. Blackrock is the company at the pinnacle of all of them, and it will have the inside contacts and the resources to get what it wants, and that is a Spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>Whether it&rsquo;s good that such a company should have its fingers inside the Bitcoin pie is another thing, but given that Bitcoin is for everyone, those who are able to fully understand it and invest in it first will be those who profit the most.</p>
Just a matter of time
<p>Therefore, it is just a matter of time now before an ETF is granted and bitcoin is shot skywards on a wave of institutional buying. And if the SEC wins the day and somehow comes up with a reason for not approving an ETF, the institutions will still find a way to eventually get the job done.</p>
<p>That Bitcoin has begun its bull market there can be little doubt. Institutions or no institutions, if 75% of BTC holders are not selling, and with the halving approaching next year, bitcoin will still do its thing.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The writing is on the wall. Bitcoin ETFs are queued at the SEC and it is now just a matter of time before bitcoin explodes higher.</p>
SEC Gensler in a tough place
<p>The anti-crypto chairman of the SEC, Gary Gensler, is in between a rock and a hard place. He has the biggest asset management company in the world (Blackrock) as well as several other financial giants, awaiting his decision.</p>
<p>To buy himself time Gensler could put his decision back as much as 240 days, but the chances of the environment changing as far as granting a Spot Bitcoin ETF would likely be very small.</p>
<p>The SEC chair could continue to back himself and just turn the ETF applications down en masse. However, he is really running out of grounds for doing so, and the political pressure he must already be facing would ratchet up to insufferable levels.</p>
Poor SEC decisions
<p>Gensler would need to be a man of iron in order to continue steering his anti-crypto course, but his performances so far do not indicate that he has the backbone to do this.</p>
<p>Under his leadership the SEC has changed from its role as cop on the beat, that makes sure markets run smoothly, and that investors have proper protections, into a vehicle that is carrying out a hostile crusade against the crypto industry.</p>
<p>Gensler&rsquo;s decision to attack Coinbase now seems to have been a very poorly judged move, especially in the light of the recent SEC/Ripple case court decision that ruled that secondary sales of XRP on exchanges did not constitute the transaction of a security.</p>
<p>Therefore, continuing to spend millions of taxpayer dollars on trying to bring Coinbase down, a company that is seen to have made every effort to be compliant, looks to be folly, and might be regarded as the SEC making a perverse effort to destroy all the crypto exchanges in order to prevent retail investors from using them.</p>
A power that transcends government
<p>It might very well be argued that it&rsquo;s not just Gensler using the SEC as an armament against crypto. The decision to bring crypto down may well have come from much higher up, and possibly from the very highest echelon.&nbsp;</p>
<p>However, there is still one power in the US that continues to transcend politics and government, and that is the power of money, and this comes in the form of institutional companies that own a piece of just about everything. Blackrock is the company at the pinnacle of all of them, and it will have the inside contacts and the resources to get what it wants, and that is a Spot Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p>Whether it&rsquo;s good that such a company should have its fingers inside the Bitcoin pie is another thing, but given that Bitcoin is for everyone, those who are able to fully understand it and invest in it first will be those who profit the most.</p>
Just a matter of time
<p>Therefore, it is just a matter of time now before an ETF is granted and bitcoin is shot skywards on a wave of institutional buying. And if the SEC wins the day and somehow comes up with a reason for not approving an ETF, the institutions will still find a way to eventually get the job done.</p>
<p>That Bitcoin has begun its bull market there can be little doubt. Institutions or no institutions, if 75% of BTC holders are not selling, and with the halving approaching next year, bitcoin will still do its thing.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Torres Criticizes SECs Reckless Regulatory Assault on Crypto]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/torres-criticizes-secs-reckless-regulatory-assault-on-crypto</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/gensler.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:00:01 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Jana Serfontein]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/torres-criticizes-secs-reckless-regulatory-assault-on-crypto</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>Representative Ritchie Torres becomes the latest US lawmaker to level criticism against the SEC and its Chairman Gary Gensler&rsquo;s position on crypto. </p>
<p>New York Representative Ritchie Torres urged the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its Chairman Gary Gensler after &ldquo;crypto regulation by enforcement had a dreadful day in court.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Crypto regulation by enforcement had a dreadful day in court. In light of the SDNY&rsquo;s landmark decision in the Ripple case, @SECGov must reassess its reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry. My letter to Chair Gensler: pic.twitter.com/Mrk63N4KhH</p>
&mdash; Rep. Ritchie Torres (@RepRitchie) July 18, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Rep. Torres is a member of the Congressional Blockchain Caucus.</p>
SEC Should Limit Enforcement Cases to &ldquo;Bonafide Bad Actors&rdquo;
<p>In a letter to Chairman Gensler on July 18, Torres asked the agency to limit its enforcement cases to &ldquo;bonafide bad actors&rdquo; rather than &ldquo;indiscriminately&rdquo; dealing with most crypto assets as securities under its supervision.</p>
<p>Torres&rsquo;s criticism and motivation to call the SEC out on its &ldquo;reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry&rdquo; followed the landmark court ruling in the SEC&rsquo;s case against Ripple Labs. The regulator suggested Ripple&rsquo;s sale of its $XRP token on public exchanges was an offer of securities, leading numerous exchanges to delist the token and its value to plummet. &nbsp;</p>
<p>However, a ruling by Judge Analise Torres stated the $XRP token is &ldquo;not necessarily a security on its face.&rdquo; &nbsp;</p>
<p>In his letter, Rep. Torres said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m writing to inquire if the SEC intends to come to terms with the folly of the Commission&rsquo;s crusade against crypto assets in light of the latest decision by Judge Analisa Torres of the Southern District of New York.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;In a landmark legal opinion, Judge Torres resoundingly rejected the regulatory overreach of the SEC, which has been indiscriminately declaring all crypto assets, except bitcoin, to be securities.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The congressman concluded by saying:</p>

<p>I hope that the SEC will find itself so chastened by the court&rsquo;s decision that it will concentrate the Commission&rsquo;s enforcement energies where it belongs: on the bonafide bad actors who perpetrate serious transgressions like fraud, market manipulation, and the misappropriation of customer funds.</p>

SEC Has Failed to Provide Clear Guidance for the Crypto Industry
<p>Rep. Torres, who coincidently shares a last name with the judge presiding over the SEC&rsquo;s case against Ripple, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Under Chair Gensler, the SEC has not issued a single rule on crypto assets, nor has it given any clear guidance.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Adding, &ldquo;All it has done is sent mixed messages, one after the [other], not only contradicting the CFTC but often contradicting itself.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Torres and other industry experts believe that an immediate appeal by the SEC seems unlikely. The precedent set by the $XRP ruling would jeopardize the agency&rsquo;s case against Coinbase in particular.</p>
<p>Rep. Torres suggested:</p>

<p>[The SEC] must reassess its reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Representative Ritchie Torres becomes the latest US lawmaker to level criticism against the SEC and its Chairman Gary Gensler&rsquo;s position on crypto. </p>
<p>New York Representative Ritchie Torres urged the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and its Chairman Gary Gensler after &ldquo;crypto regulation by enforcement had a dreadful day in court.&rdquo;</p>

<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Crypto regulation by enforcement had a dreadful day in court. In light of the SDNY&rsquo;s landmark decision in the Ripple case, @SECGov must reassess its reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry. My letter to Chair Gensler: pic.twitter.com/Mrk63N4KhH</p>
&mdash; Rep. Ritchie Torres (@RepRitchie) July 18, 2023
<p>

</p>
<p>Rep. Torres is a member of the Congressional Blockchain Caucus.</p>
SEC Should Limit Enforcement Cases to &ldquo;Bonafide Bad Actors&rdquo;
<p>In a letter to Chairman Gensler on July 18, Torres asked the agency to limit its enforcement cases to &ldquo;bonafide bad actors&rdquo; rather than &ldquo;indiscriminately&rdquo; dealing with most crypto assets as securities under its supervision.</p>
<p>Torres&rsquo;s criticism and motivation to call the SEC out on its &ldquo;reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry&rdquo; followed the landmark court ruling in the SEC&rsquo;s case against Ripple Labs. The regulator suggested Ripple&rsquo;s sale of its $XRP token on public exchanges was an offer of securities, leading numerous exchanges to delist the token and its value to plummet. &nbsp;</p>
<p>However, a ruling by Judge Analise Torres stated the $XRP token is &ldquo;not necessarily a security on its face.&rdquo; &nbsp;</p>
<p>In his letter, Rep. Torres said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;I&rsquo;m writing to inquire if the SEC intends to come to terms with the folly of the Commission&rsquo;s crusade against crypto assets in light of the latest decision by Judge Analisa Torres of the Southern District of New York.&rdquo;</p>

<p>He added:</p>

<p>&ldquo;In a landmark legal opinion, Judge Torres resoundingly rejected the regulatory overreach of the SEC, which has been indiscriminately declaring all crypto assets, except bitcoin, to be securities.&rdquo;</p>

<p>The congressman concluded by saying:</p>

<p>I hope that the SEC will find itself so chastened by the court&rsquo;s decision that it will concentrate the Commission&rsquo;s enforcement energies where it belongs: on the bonafide bad actors who perpetrate serious transgressions like fraud, market manipulation, and the misappropriation of customer funds.</p>

SEC Has Failed to Provide Clear Guidance for the Crypto Industry
<p>Rep. Torres, who coincidently shares a last name with the judge presiding over the SEC&rsquo;s case against Ripple, said:</p>

<p>&ldquo;Under Chair Gensler, the SEC has not issued a single rule on crypto assets, nor has it given any clear guidance.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Adding, &ldquo;All it has done is sent mixed messages, one after the [other], not only contradicting the CFTC but often contradicting itself.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Torres and other industry experts believe that an immediate appeal by the SEC seems unlikely. The precedent set by the $XRP ruling would jeopardize the agency&rsquo;s case against Coinbase in particular.</p>
<p>Rep. Torres suggested:</p>

<p>[The SEC] must reassess its reckless regulatory assault on the crypto industry.</p>

<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[SEC Faces Deadlines For Spot ETF Applications As Pressure Mounts]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-faces-deadlines-for-spot-etf-applications-as-pressure-mounts</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/sec-15.jpeg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 07:51:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Amara Khatri]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/sec-faces-deadlines-for-spot-etf-applications-as-pressure-mounts</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission is under pressure to accept spot Bitcoin ETF applications as deadline looms.</p>
<p>They have already accepted BlackRock&rsquo;s refiled application sparking speculation that approval could be granted.</p>
Deadline For Approvals On The Horizon
<p>The clock has started ticking for the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to approve or reject BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund. According to the SEC&rsquo;s official calendar, BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF will be published in the Federal Register and kickstart a 21-day comment period. The application has been added to the SEC docket as part of the rule change process.</p>
<p>The development is a significant milestone for the application being considered by the Securities and Exchange Commission. The world&rsquo;s largest asset manager had submitted its original application in June. However, the Securities and Exchange Commission knocked back the application, prompting BlackRock to amend it. The updated application included a &ldquo;surveillance sharing&rdquo; provision with Coinbase, addressing one of the SEC&rsquo;s primary concerns with the initial application.</p>
More Bitcoin ETFs In The Pipeline
<p>BlackRock has over $9.4 trillion in assets under management and is known for obtaining ETF approvals. As a result, the asset manager&rsquo;s initial application for a spot Bitcoin ETF sparked a rush of applications from other firms looking to do the same. If the ETF is approved, BlackRock customers will be able to invest in Bitcoin without having to hold the token. Instead, these assets can be traded on traditional stock markets. The Securities and Exchange Commission has already approved the first Bitcoin Futures ETF.</p>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission also has to decide on other applications apart from BlackRock&rsquo;s for a spot Bitcoin ETF. These include Bitwise&rsquo;s Bitcoin ETP Trust&rsquo;s application which was included in the Federal Register on Tuesday. The other applications under consideration are WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust, VanEck Bitcoin Strategy ETF, Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, and Fidelity&rsquo;s Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust.</p>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission had published documents for public consultation on Bitcoin ETFs last week. However, the review process officially starts when the filings are included in the Federal Register. The initial deadline for approval or rejection is 45 days but can be extended to 240 days. Additionally, there is no guarantee that the SEC would approve any of the applications filed. However, BlackRock&rsquo;s application has led to considerable optimism surrounding approval. Other applications have already hit the Federal Register, with the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF included in the register on the 15th of May. However, the SEC extended the approval deadline in June. Meanwhile, Valkyrie&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund has not yet been listed on the Federal Register.</p>
Europe&rsquo;s Spot Bitcoin ETF
<p>While American regulators are still considering approval, Europe has moved ahead, with its highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund set to debut later this year. The ETF was filed by London-based multi-asset investment platform Jacobi Asset Management and was originally set to debut on the Euronext Amsterdam Exchange in July 2022. However, the launch was delayed indefinitely thanks to unfavorable market conditions caused by the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and the FTX exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The United States Securities and Exchange Commission is under pressure to accept spot Bitcoin ETF applications as deadline looms.</p>
<p>They have already accepted BlackRock&rsquo;s refiled application sparking speculation that approval could be granted.</p>
Deadline For Approvals On The Horizon
<p>The clock has started ticking for the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to approve or reject BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund. According to the SEC&rsquo;s official calendar, BlackRock&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin ETF will be published in the Federal Register and kickstart a 21-day comment period. The application has been added to the SEC docket as part of the rule change process.</p>
<p>The development is a significant milestone for the application being considered by the Securities and Exchange Commission. The world&rsquo;s largest asset manager had submitted its original application in June. However, the Securities and Exchange Commission knocked back the application, prompting BlackRock to amend it. The updated application included a &ldquo;surveillance sharing&rdquo; provision with Coinbase, addressing one of the SEC&rsquo;s primary concerns with the initial application.</p>
More Bitcoin ETFs In The Pipeline
<p>BlackRock has over $9.4 trillion in assets under management and is known for obtaining ETF approvals. As a result, the asset manager&rsquo;s initial application for a spot Bitcoin ETF sparked a rush of applications from other firms looking to do the same. If the ETF is approved, BlackRock customers will be able to invest in Bitcoin without having to hold the token. Instead, these assets can be traded on traditional stock markets. The Securities and Exchange Commission has already approved the first Bitcoin Futures ETF.</p>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission also has to decide on other applications apart from BlackRock&rsquo;s for a spot Bitcoin ETF. These include Bitwise&rsquo;s Bitcoin ETP Trust&rsquo;s application which was included in the Federal Register on Tuesday. The other applications under consideration are WisdomTree Bitcoin Trust, VanEck Bitcoin Strategy ETF, Invesco Galaxy Bitcoin ETF, and Fidelity&rsquo;s Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust.</p>
<p>The Securities and Exchange Commission had published documents for public consultation on Bitcoin ETFs last week. However, the review process officially starts when the filings are included in the Federal Register. The initial deadline for approval or rejection is 45 days but can be extended to 240 days. Additionally, there is no guarantee that the SEC would approve any of the applications filed. However, BlackRock&rsquo;s application has led to considerable optimism surrounding approval. Other applications have already hit the Federal Register, with the ARK 21Shares Bitcoin ETF included in the register on the 15th of May. However, the SEC extended the approval deadline in June. Meanwhile, Valkyrie&rsquo;s application for a spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund has not yet been listed on the Federal Register.</p>
Europe&rsquo;s Spot Bitcoin ETF
<p>While American regulators are still considering approval, Europe has moved ahead, with its highly anticipated and long-delayed spot Bitcoin exchange traded fund set to debut later this year. The ETF was filed by London-based multi-asset investment platform Jacobi Asset Management and was originally set to debut on the Euronext Amsterdam Exchange in July 2022. However, the launch was delayed indefinitely thanks to unfavorable market conditions caused by the collapse of the Terra ecosystem and the FTX exchange.</p>
<p>Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Ubisoft Joins Cronos Blockchain Ecosystem as Node Validator $CRO]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ubisoft-joins-cronos-blockchain-ecosystem-as-node-validator-cro</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ubisoft-x-cronos-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ubisoft-x-cronos-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/ubisoft-x-cronos-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 07:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/ubisoft-joins-cronos-blockchain-ecosystem-as-node-validator-cro</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft, a leading video game creator and publisher, is expanding its exploration of blockchain technology with a new partnership.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Joining the Cronos blockchain ecosystem as a node validator, Ubisoft adds its experience and expertise to this expanding digital network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft is set to join 27 other node operators contributing to the Cronos open-source blockchain. These node validators play a vital role in ensuring the stability and security of the network. As a validator, Ubisoft will participate in blockchain governance and network update approvals.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The decision to join the Cronos ecosystem aligns with Ubisoft's ongoing exploration of blockchain technology, spearheaded by its Strategic Innovation Lab. The inclusion of Ubisoft in the ecosystem aligns with Cronos' strategy of collaboration with technical contributors, which include Crypto.com, Blockdaemon, Dora Factory, and Allnodes, among others.</p>
An Extension of Ubisoft-Cronos Relationship
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is a progression of the existing relationship between Ubisoft and Cronos. Ubisoft previously participated as a start-up mentor in the Cronos Accelerator program, marking their initial collaborative efforts.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ken Timsit, Managing Director of Cronos Labs, a blockchain startup accelerator, commented on the partnership as well, expressing optimism about Ubisoft's contributions, given their understanding of blockchain's potential and limitations in creating deeper engagement between game creators and gamers. Timsit also mentioned the open-source Cronos project, where Ubisoft is expected to participate as a validator.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"They have unparalleled understanding of the potential and the limitations of blockchain technology when it comes to creating deeper engagement between game creators and gamers," Timsit said.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cronos' ecosystem stands to benefit from Ubisoft's expertise, particularly in providing feedback on technology upgrades to support gaming use cases. Ubisoft's Strategic Innovation Lab, tasked with anticipating the future and integrating innovative technologies, will play a pivotal role in this endeavor.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cronos has been active in the gaming industry with Cronos Play, a suite of developer tools and integrations for blockchain-based games. The developer tools are now available as a plugin in the Unreal Engine Marketplace, with more than 15 Web3 games launched or in the pipeline for launch on the Cronos blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Cronos (cronos.org) is an EVM-compatible layer 1 blockchain network built on the Cosmos SDK. It's supported by Crypto.com, Crypto.org, and more than 500 app developers and partners. The platform is adopted by over 1 million users and supports an ecosystem of more than 80 million users worldwide with the Cronos ($CRO) cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft's venture into the Cronos ecosystem reinforces the growing interest of leading technology firms in blockchain technology and its myriad applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft, a leading video game creator and publisher, is expanding its exploration of blockchain technology with a new partnership.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Joining the Cronos blockchain ecosystem as a node validator, Ubisoft adds its experience and expertise to this expanding digital network.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft is set to join 27 other node operators contributing to the Cronos open-source blockchain. These node validators play a vital role in ensuring the stability and security of the network. As a validator, Ubisoft will participate in blockchain governance and network update approvals.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The decision to join the Cronos ecosystem aligns with Ubisoft's ongoing exploration of blockchain technology, spearheaded by its Strategic Innovation Lab. The inclusion of Ubisoft in the ecosystem aligns with Cronos' strategy of collaboration with technical contributors, which include Crypto.com, Blockdaemon, Dora Factory, and Allnodes, among others.</p>
An Extension of Ubisoft-Cronos Relationship
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The partnership is a progression of the existing relationship between Ubisoft and Cronos. Ubisoft previously participated as a start-up mentor in the Cronos Accelerator program, marking their initial collaborative efforts.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ken Timsit, Managing Director of Cronos Labs, a blockchain startup accelerator, commented on the partnership as well, expressing optimism about Ubisoft's contributions, given their understanding of blockchain's potential and limitations in creating deeper engagement between game creators and gamers. Timsit also mentioned the open-source Cronos project, where Ubisoft is expected to participate as a validator.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"They have unparalleled understanding of the potential and the limitations of blockchain technology when it comes to creating deeper engagement between game creators and gamers," Timsit said.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cronos' ecosystem stands to benefit from Ubisoft's expertise, particularly in providing feedback on technology upgrades to support gaming use cases. Ubisoft's Strategic Innovation Lab, tasked with anticipating the future and integrating innovative technologies, will play a pivotal role in this endeavor.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Cronos has been active in the gaming industry with Cronos Play, a suite of developer tools and integrations for blockchain-based games. The developer tools are now available as a plugin in the Unreal Engine Marketplace, with more than 15 Web3 games launched or in the pipeline for launch on the Cronos blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Cronos (cronos.org) is an EVM-compatible layer 1 blockchain network built on the Cosmos SDK. It's supported by Crypto.com, Crypto.org, and more than 500 app developers and partners. The platform is adopted by over 1 million users and supports an ecosystem of more than 80 million users worldwide with the Cronos ($CRO) cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Ubisoft's venture into the Cronos ecosystem reinforces the growing interest of leading technology firms in blockchain technology and its myriad applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO to Discuss Crypto Legislation with House Democrats]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinbase-ceo-to-discuss-crypto-legislation-with-house-democrats</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/coinbase-regulation-update-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 05:40:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/coinbase-ceo-to-discuss-crypto-legislation-with-house-democrats</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Inc.'s Chief Executive Officer, Brian Armstrong, is set to hold a private meeting with House Democrats on Wednesday, according to Democratic aides familiar with the agenda.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The closed-door session will mainly revolve around digital-asset legislation, covering critical aspects like taxation, national security, privacy, and climate.</p>
A Step Toward Regulatory Clarity
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The upcoming meeting comes as Coinbase, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges globally, contends with a lawsuit from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Armstrong has bbeen spearheading a campaign in Washington aimed at establishing clearer regulations around digital assets. The U.S. firm has been urging lawmakers to consider two circulating bills that promise more definitive guidance on crypto exchange registration with regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The New Democrat Coalition, comprising of some 100 center-left members, is the group scheduled for the meeting with Armstrong. The coalition aims to collaborate across party lines to foster innovative, inclusive, and forward-thinking policies, as stated on their website.</p>
Navigating a Regulatory Maze
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC accuses Coinbase of violating rules that necessitate it to register as a securities exchange. Coinbase rejects these allegations and has motioned for the lawsuit's dismissal. The SEC, under Chair Gary Gensler's leadership, has amplified its focus on the cryptocurrency industry, launching several enforcement actions in recent months.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Armstrong has highlighted inconsistencies in statements by the SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), two separate US regulators, over which body has jurisdiction over segments of the crypto industry. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"This is why the US Congress is introducing new legislation to fix the situation," Armstrong stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The meeting's outcome could potentially inform legislative direction for the US crypto industry, significantly affecting businesses and investors in the sector.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Last week, Coinbase shares surged by 24% following a federal court ruling perceived as potentially restricting SEC oversight on what can be listed on cryptocurrency trading platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This gathering signals a significant development for the cryrptocurrency industry, providing a platform for open dialogue and potential consensus on the sector's regulatory landscape. In the face of an increasingly regulated and scrutinized industry, the meeting offers a chance for Armstrong and other crypto industry leaders to influence future legislation and seek clarity on existing regulatory expectations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Coinbase Inc.'s Chief Executive Officer, Brian Armstrong, is set to hold a private meeting with House Democrats on Wednesday, according to Democratic aides familiar with the agenda.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The closed-door session will mainly revolve around digital-asset legislation, covering critical aspects like taxation, national security, privacy, and climate.</p>
A Step Toward Regulatory Clarity
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">The upcoming meeting comes as Coinbase, one of the largest cryptocurrency exchanges globally, contends with a lawsuit from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Armstrong has bbeen spearheading a campaign in Washington aimed at establishing clearer regulations around digital assets. The U.S. firm has been urging lawmakers to consider two circulating bills that promise more definitive guidance on crypto exchange registration with regulators.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The New Democrat Coalition, comprising of some 100 center-left members, is the group scheduled for the meeting with Armstrong. The coalition aims to collaborate across party lines to foster innovative, inclusive, and forward-thinking policies, as stated on their website.</p>
Navigating a Regulatory Maze
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The SEC accuses Coinbase of violating rules that necessitate it to register as a securities exchange. Coinbase rejects these allegations and has motioned for the lawsuit's dismissal. The SEC, under Chair Gary Gensler's leadership, has amplified its focus on the cryptocurrency industry, launching several enforcement actions in recent months.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Armstrong has highlighted inconsistencies in statements by the SEC and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), two separate US regulators, over which body has jurisdiction over segments of the crypto industry. </p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"This is why the US Congress is introducing new legislation to fix the situation," Armstrong stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">The meeting's outcome could potentially inform legislative direction for the US crypto industry, significantly affecting businesses and investors in the sector.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Last week, Coinbase shares surged by 24% following a federal court ruling perceived as potentially restricting SEC oversight on what can be listed on cryptocurrency trading platforms.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">This gathering signals a significant development for the cryrptocurrency industry, providing a platform for open dialogue and potential consensus on the sector's regulatory landscape. In the face of an increasingly regulated and scrutinized industry, the meeting offers a chance for Armstrong and other crypto industry leaders to influence future legislation and seek clarity on existing regulatory expectations.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
														<item>
			  <title><![CDATA[Oasis Network Launches Sapphire Privacy Blockchain $ROSE]]></title>
			  <link>https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/oasis-network-launches-sapphire-privacy-blockchain-rose</link>
			  <media:content url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/oasis-network-h.jpg" medium="image" />
			  <media:thumbnail url="https://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/oasis-network-h.jpg" />
			  <enclosure url="http://cryptodailycdn.ams3.digitaloceanspaces.com/oasis-network-h.jpg" length="528" type="image/jpg" />
			  <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 20:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
			  <dc:creator><![CDATA[Vince Dioquino]]></dc:creator>
			  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptodaily.co.uk/2023/07/oasis-network-launches-sapphire-privacy-blockchain-rose</guid>
			  <description><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Oasis Network, developers of privacy-centric blockchain products, has announced the launch of Sapphire, a privacy-focused Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The chain makes use of Oasis's privacy layer, and aims to offer a more secure platform for existing decentralized apps across EVM networks, eliminating the need for cross-chain swaps.</p>
Sapphire: A New Dawn for Web3 Development
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire represents an exciting development for privacy-focused Web3 development. With its unique privacy-first features, it is set to significantly enhance the security of dApps on any EVM network. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Oasis Foundation Director Jernej Kos explained how the Oasis Privacy Layer (OPL) and Sapphire work in harmony to bolster the functionality of DApps. Specifically, he outlined how DApps can incorporate various features of Sapphire without migrating to the Oasis blockchain.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Being fully EVM-compatible means that developers can build private smart contracts in an environment that they are already familiar with," Kos stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire's full compatibility with EVM environments also bolsters cross-chain Web3 development, providing a confidential voting mechanism for decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) smart contracts, for instance. The outcome of such confidential voting can then be conveyed to the core DAO contract on a different chain.</p>
Unlocking the Power of Privacy
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The majority of DApps built on the Oasis blockchain are privacy-centric, and this trend is reflected in the tools and platforms developed within the Oasis ecosystem. Sapphire's release is expected to drive the development of privacy-enabled blockchain games, confidential decentralized exchanges, private voting systems, sealed-bid auctions, and key management tools, among other applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire employs Oasis' proprietary privacy technology that relies on a secure computing technology known as a Trusted Execution Environment (TEE), which serves as a secure enclave for smart contract execution. During execution, encrypted data is fed into the Secure Enclave alongside the smart contract, where it's decrypted and processed. The data is then re-encrypted before it leaves the Secure Enclave, ensuring that user data remains confidential and isn't disclosed to node operators or application developers.</p>
A Gateway to Familiarity and Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire offers a familiar environment for blockchain developers due to its EVM compatibility. User-facing tools like the Web3 gateway, wallets, and block explorers are already familiar to many, and developers will recognize tools such as Solidity/Vyper, Hardhat/Truffle, and Web3.js/Ethers. Developers can port their DApps to Sapphire within minutes and start using its privacy technology and built-in functions such as Random Number Generation (RNG), signing, and encryption.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Sapphire on testnet marks an important milestone in Oasis's roadmap. Oasis has already planned a mainnet deployment for later this year and is encouraging developers to utilize the testnet to familiarize themselves with Sapphire's capabilities. In an effort to cultivate a vibrant developer community around Sapphire, Oasis plans to host its first Sapphire Hackathon in September.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire&rsquo;s inception offers a more privacy-focused era for Web3 development, enabling developers to incorporate enhanced security features into their DApps without compromising the familiarity of their build environment. The privacy capabilities offered by Sapphire represent an essential step in the pursuit of a more secure and private Web3 environment, advancing the blockchain industry's progress towards widespread Web3 adoption.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></description>
			  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="md-end-block md-p">Oasis Network, developers of privacy-centric blockchain products, has announced the launch of Sapphire, a privacy-focused Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible blockchain.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The chain makes use of Oasis's privacy layer, and aims to offer a more secure platform for existing decentralized apps across EVM networks, eliminating the need for cross-chain swaps.</p>
Sapphire: A New Dawn for Web3 Development
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire represents an exciting development for privacy-focused Web3 development. With its unique privacy-first features, it is set to significantly enhance the security of dApps on any EVM network. </p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Oasis Foundation Director Jernej Kos explained how the Oasis Privacy Layer (OPL) and Sapphire work in harmony to bolster the functionality of DApps. Specifically, he outlined how DApps can incorporate various features of Sapphire without migrating to the Oasis blockchain.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">"Being fully EVM-compatible means that developers can build private smart contracts in an environment that they are already familiar with," Kos stated.</p>

<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire's full compatibility with EVM environments also bolsters cross-chain Web3 development, providing a confidential voting mechanism for decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) smart contracts, for instance. The outcome of such confidential voting can then be conveyed to the core DAO contract on a different chain.</p>
Unlocking the Power of Privacy
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The majority of DApps built on the Oasis blockchain are privacy-centric, and this trend is reflected in the tools and platforms developed within the Oasis ecosystem. Sapphire's release is expected to drive the development of privacy-enabled blockchain games, confidential decentralized exchanges, private voting systems, sealed-bid auctions, and key management tools, among other applications.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire employs Oasis' proprietary privacy technology that relies on a secure computing technology known as a Trusted Execution Environment (TEE), which serves as a secure enclave for smart contract execution. During execution, encrypted data is fed into the Secure Enclave alongside the smart contract, where it's decrypted and processed. The data is then re-encrypted before it leaves the Secure Enclave, ensuring that user data remains confidential and isn't disclosed to node operators or application developers.</p>
A Gateway to Familiarity and Interoperability
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire offers a familiar environment for blockchain developers due to its EVM compatibility. User-facing tools like the Web3 gateway, wallets, and block explorers are already familiar to many, and developers will recognize tools such as Solidity/Vyper, Hardhat/Truffle, and Web3.js/Ethers. Developers can port their DApps to Sapphire within minutes and start using its privacy technology and built-in functions such as Random Number Generation (RNG), signing, and encryption.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">The launch of Sapphire on testnet marks an important milestone in Oasis's roadmap. Oasis has already planned a mainnet deployment for later this year and is encouraging developers to utilize the testnet to familiarize themselves with Sapphire's capabilities. In an effort to cultivate a vibrant developer community around Sapphire, Oasis plans to host its first Sapphire Hackathon in September.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p">Sapphire&rsquo;s inception offers a more privacy-focused era for Web3 development, enabling developers to incorporate enhanced security features into their DApps without compromising the familiarity of their build environment. The privacy capabilities offered by Sapphire represent an essential step in the pursuit of a more secure and private Web3 environment, advancing the blockchain industry's progress towards widespread Web3 adoption.</p>
<p class="md-end-block md-p md-focus">Disclaimer: This article is provided for informational purposes only. It is not offered or intended to be used as legal, tax, investment, financial, or other advice.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
					
	</channel>
</rss>
