<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
	>

<channel>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cryptopotato.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<description>Crypto Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 06:16:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/cropped-potato-fav2-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>CryptoPotato</title>
	<link>https://cryptopotato.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Binance to Close Canadian Shop Citing Recent Regulatory Changes</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-close-canadian-shop-citing-recent-regulatory-changes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jordan Lyanchev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 06:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Binance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250468</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Canada_Binance.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Canada_Binance.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The crypto exchange said it tried to delay the departure for as long as possible.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world&#8217;s largest crypto trading platform said it will be winding down its Canadian arm two years after being greenlighted to operate in the country.</p>
<p>Binance mentioned a recent amendment in the local legislation that affected stablecoin deposits and purchases on exchanges.</p>
<ul>
<li>Binance <a href="https://twitter.com/binance/status/1657099651210969088?s=20" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> its intentions on Twitter, saying it will &#8220;be joining other prominent crypto businesses in proactively withdrawing from the Canadian marketplace.&#8221;</li>
<li>The exchange admitted that it was a small but &#8220;sentimental&#8221; market, which it intended to keep working in. However, a recent decision by the Canadian Securities Administrators stands in its way.</li>
<li>The CSA <a href="https://www.osc.ca/en/news-events/news/canadian-securities-regulators-strengthen-oversight-enhance-expectations-crypto-asset-trading" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">announced</a> new guidelines in February that make it mandatory for local exchanges to seek its permission before accepting stablecoin deposits or allowing users to buy such assets. The watchdog has multiple due diligence tests in place making the process lengthy.</li>
</ul>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We put off this decision as long as we could to explore other reasonable avenues to protect our Canadian users, but it has become apparent that there are none.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<ul>
<li>Canada&#8217;s overall approach to crypto has been relatively positive, with a few traditional financial institutions investing in the industry. The country also approved one of the first spot Bitcoin ETFs a few years back, but its recent policy change harmed several exchanges, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/cryptocom-to-delist-usdt-in-canada-due-to-regulatory-pressures/" data-wpel-link="internal">including</a> Crypto.com.</li>
<li>Binance has been on an expansion roll for the past several months, receiving multiple licenses to operate in <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-another-crypto-license-in-dubai/" data-wpel-link="internal">Dubai</a>, a few European countries, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-secures-license-to-offer-crypto-services-in-kazakhstan/" data-wpel-link="internal">Kazakhstan</a>, as well as <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/this-is-when-binance-japan-will-officially-launch/" data-wpel-link="internal">Japan</a>.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/binance-to-close-canadian-shop-citing-recent-regulatory-changes/" rel="nofollow">Binance to Close Canadian Shop Citing Recent Regulatory Changes</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnamese Residents Accused of $1.5 Million Crypto Theft and Kidnapping to Face Justice (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/vietnamese-residents-accused-of-1-5-million-crypto-theft-and-kidnapping-to-face-justice-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto Scams]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250221</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Vietnam.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Vietnam.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Two former police officers and 14 other Vietnamese supposedly kidnapped an individual and stole $1.5 worth of bitcoin. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The People&#8217;s Court of Ho Chi Minh City reportedly brought to court 16 Vietnamese who might stand behind a $1.5 million crypto robbery and kidnapping. Interestingly, two of the defendants are former police officers.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Vietnam is one of the global leaders in terms of cryptocurrency adoption. Despite its rising popularity, the government has not imposed a legal framework on the asset class. </span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Movielike Story</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">According to a local media outlet, the whole drama </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://tuoitre.vn/lam-quan-su-cho-nhom-cuop-tien-ao-cuu-canh-sat-hinh-su-cung-dong-pham-hau-toa-20230510070447545.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">started</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in 2018 when Le Duc Nguyen advised Ho Ngoc Tai to sell around 1,000 BTC (valued at approximately $4.2 million at the time) to purchase other digital currencies.</span></p>
<p>Nonetheless, the investment did not go as planned, making Tai believe he had become a victim of a crypto scam. He could not accept the loss and assembled a team in May 2020 whose goal was to steal the assets back.</p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The entity, consisting of 16 people (including two former police officers), tracked Nguyen&#8217;s whereabouts using GPS devices installed on his vehicle. The individuals hired a van, bought realistic weapons, and kidnapped the target at gunpoint.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">While in their custody, the team insisted Nguyen&#8217;s bother transfers the original amount of 1,000 BTC to Tai&#8217;s wallet. However, the gang realized that his relative did not have the requested amount and restored &#8220;only&#8221; $1.5 million worth of crypto. The victim was later abandoned in the city of Thu Duc: about 15 kilometers north of Ho Chi Minh City&#8217;s center. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The law enforcement agencies of the Vietnamese city recently brought to trial Tai and his 15 alleged accomplices. It is worth noting that the mastermind of the operation initially admitted to standing behind the crime. However, he reversed his confession during the process of investigation. For their part, the remaining defendants said they thought Tai would collect the debt from Nguyen normally and not via kidnapping.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Vietnamese are Fond of Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The Asian country often tops studies that are focused on cryptocurrency adoption. The blockchain service provider &#8211; Chainalysis &#8211; </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/vietnam-reaffirms-global-leadership-in-crypto-adoption-chainalysis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">estimated</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> in September 2022 that Vietnam is the world&#8217;s leader in that field with a score of 1.000. The company further suggested that 21% of the locals have used or owned digital currencies at some point during their lives.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The &#8220;Vietnam Crypto Market Report 2022,&#8221; released in March this year, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-flourishes-in-vietnam-with-16-6-million-holders-report/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">showed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> that the asset class continues to be highly popular inside the country&#8217;s borders. According to the research, 17% of Vietnamese (around 16.6 million people) are HODLers. Nearly a third of those have invested in bitcoin.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The report claimed that Vietnam ranks second to Thailand in the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) in terms of crypto adoption. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/vietnamese-residents-accused-of-1-5-million-crypto-theft-and-kidnapping-to-face-justice-report/" rel="nofollow">Vietnamese Residents Accused of $1.5 Million Crypto Theft and Kidnapping to Face Justice (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Customers Can Pay With Ethereum Through PayPal via MetaMask Integration</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/metamask-launches-ethereum-purchases-via-paypal-for-us-users/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin Young]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MetaMask]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PayPal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250280</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/MetaMask.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/MetaMask.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Popular Ethereum wallet MetaMask has teamed up with payment giant PayPal to increase offerings for American users.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On May 11, MetaMask revealed that it had added PayPal as a payment option for Ethereum purchases. However, the new payment channel is only available to U.S. users.</p>
<blockquote><p>“MetaMask is the first web3 wallet to enable users to buy ETH using PayPal, a leader in the digital payment space,” it said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The integration also supports ETH transfers from PayPal to MetaMask, creating more self-custody adoption.</p>
<p>However, many of those responding to the tweet were more interested in when MetaMask would be launching its own token. The firm has urged users to <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/there-wont-be-a-metamask-airdrop-snapshot-on-march-31st-team-member-warns-of-scams/" data-wpel-link="internal">avoid scams</a> for MASK tokens, adding that there are no immediate airdrop plans.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DYK?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">#DYK</a></p>
<p>MetaMask<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f98a.png" alt="🦊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is the first web3 wallet to enable users to buy ETH using PayPal!</p>
<p>Get started here<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f447.png" alt="👇" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><a href="https://t.co/RGcamJQoQ2" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">https://t.co/RGcamJQoQ2</a></p>
<p>— MetaMask <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f98a.png" alt="🦊" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/1f499.png" alt="💙" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@MetaMask) <a href="https://twitter.com/MetaMask/status/1656672836990435333?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">May 11, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<h2>MetaMask PayPal Collaboration</h2>
<p>The collaboration was initially announced in December, but payments have only just been <a href="https://metamask.io/news/latest/metamask-and-paypal-all-you-need-to-know-about-buying-eth/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">launched</a>.</p>
<blockquote><p>“With this new integration, users will be able to use their PayPal balance, linked bank account, or debit card to add ETH to their MetaMask wallet directly.”</p></blockquote>
<p>Ethereum purchases can be made easily through the MetaMask browser extension, mobile app, or portfolio feature. The “Buy Crypto” feature also supports debit and credit cards and bank transfers.</p>
<p>In addition to PayPal, MetaMask already supports several payment channels, including Coinbase Pay, MoonPay, Sardine, Transak, and Wyre.</p>
<h2>Recent Moves by PayPal and MetaMask</h2>
<p>In a quarterly report filed this week, PayPal <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/paypal-holds-1-billion-in-crypto-on-balance-sheet-records-show/" data-wpel-link="internal">revealed</a> it had $943 million in crypto assets under management as of March 31. Furthermore, the figure is a 56% increase over the previous quarter when the company disclosed $604 million.</p>
<p>In late March, MetaMask <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/metamask-taps-moonpay-to-enable-nigerians-buy-crypto-via-instant-bank-transfers/" data-wpel-link="internal">integrated</a> crypto fintech platform MoonPay to expand its offerings in Nigeria.</p>
<p>In February, the popular Web3 wallet <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/metamask-unveils-new-privacy-features-for-crypto-wallets/" data-wpel-link="internal">unveiled</a> a raft of privacy features following online criticism of how it handled transaction data.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/metamask-launches-ethereum-purchases-via-paypal-for-us-users/" rel="nofollow">US Customers Can Pay With Ethereum Through PayPal via MetaMask Integration</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ukraine Seeks to Trace Illicit Crypto Transactions With American Help (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/ukraine-seeks-to-trace-illicit-crypto-transactions-with-american-help-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Dimitar Dzhondzhorov]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ukraine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250319</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Ukraine_Russia.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Ukraine_Russia.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The US IRS supposedly partnered with Ukrainian agencies to provide assistance in the economic battle against Russia. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The US IRS has reportedly provided advanced training to Ukrainian law enforcement agencies in an attempt to detect illegal cryptocurrency transactions carried out by Russian oligarchs and companies. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Numerous entities and experts have argued that Russia could employ digital assets to evade restrictions (imposed by the Western World after the start of the military conflict in Ukraine) or finance war-related efforts. The US Treasury Department sanctioned five crypto addresses tied to Task Force Rusich last year. The latter is a Russian paramilitary group that has committed atrocities against soldiers.</span></p>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Battling on the Economic Front </span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">As </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-trains-ukrainian-law-enforcement-to-pursue-russian-crypto-assets-e005ba5" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">reported</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> by the Wall Street Journal, the US Internal Revenue Service (IRS) provided Ukraine with licenses to use Chinalysis Reactor (an investigation software that connects cryptocurrency transactions to real-world entities) to trace illicit proceedings conducted by Russians. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Ukrainian investigators have also received in-person training from the American department that could give the war-torn country an upper hand in its economic clash with Russia. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;We resist the aggressor state not only on the battlefield but also on the economic front,&#8221; said Eduard Fedorov &#8211; Acting Director of Ukraine&#8217;s Economic Security Bureau.</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Another goal for the Ukrainian agencies is to halt Russian fundraising campaigns related to cryptocurrencies. Yurii Vykhodets, who leads the cyber department of Ukraine&#8217;s National Police, said:</span></p>
<blockquote><p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">&#8220;One key area is the identification and elimination of centers of support for occupation forces that raise funds for the purchase of things necessary for the war. We often see fundraising campaigns conducted with the use of cryptocurrency, as Russia believes in the possibility of circumventing sanctions by using virtual assets.&#8221; </span></p></blockquote>
<h2><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Russia Should Stay Away From Crypto</span></h2>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine in February last year (described as a &#8220;special military operation&#8221; by President Vladimir Putin) has resulted in severe sanctions against the world&#8217;s largest country by landmass.</span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The USA, the European Union, Australia, and many others have </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us-imposes-sanctions-over-100-targets-action-over-russias-invasion-ukraine-2023-04-12/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">imposed</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> crippling financial restrictions in a bid to cease the aggression and dwindle Russia&#8217;s military strength. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">In addition, many agencies and prominent figures have warned crypto companies to cut all ties with the invader, arguing that sanctioned oligarchs and organizations could use digital currencies to bypass penalties or fund war-related operations. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">One example was the President of the European Central Bank &#8211; Christine Lagarde &#8211; who </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/ecb-president-warns-crypto-companies-against-helping-russians-avoid-sanctions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">said</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> entities interacting with Russia could be the subject of enhanced scrutiny. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The International Money Fund (IMF) has also given its two cents on the matter, </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/russia-could-mine-bitcoin-and-other-cryptocurrencies-to-evade-sanctions-imf-warns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">suggesting</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> the nation could mine bitcoin and altcoins to dodge restrictions. </span></p>
<p><span data-preserver-spaces="true">The United States Treasury Department </span><a class="editor-rtfLink" href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-treasury-sanctions-crypto-addresses-tied-with-neo-nazi-russian-group/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal"><span data-preserver-spaces="true">added</span></a><span data-preserver-spaces="true"> five cryptocurrency addresses to its sanctions blacklist in September last year. Interestingly, all of them were connected to Task Force Rusich: a &#8220;neo-Nazi paramilitary group&#8221; that has been in combat and has committed brutal crimes on Ukrainian territory. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ukraine-seeks-to-trace-illicit-crypto-transactions-with-american-help-report/" rel="nofollow">Ukraine Seeks to Trace Illicit Crypto Transactions With American Help (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>SEC Disclosure Reveals High Security Bill for Coinbase&#8217;s CEO Brian Armstrong</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/sec-disclosure-reveals-high-security-bill-for-coinbases-ceo-brian-armstrong/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Chayanika Deka]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 19:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brian Armstrong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SEC]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250399</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Brian-Armstrong-min.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Brian-Armstrong-min.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[The exec's stock mostly comprises of stock. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Amidst regulatory tussle, an SEC disclosure revealed an expensive bill for Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong&#8217;s security benefits.</p>
<p>The exec was granted security benefits of $6.3 million last year, representing more than triple the amount his security cost Coinbase the previous year.</p>
<ul>
<li>According to the public <a href="https://www.sec.gov/ix?doc=/Archives/edgar/data/0001679788/000167978823000065/coin-20230428.htm#i3cb39573656744c194f48e26318d6b44_40" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="external">document</a>, Armstrong&#8217;s total compensation for the whole of 2022 was $7.5 million, and received a flat salary of $1 million, while the remaining can be characterized as security and legal costs. The base salary was the same for the previous two years as well.</li>
<li>Moreover, a huge chunk of the Coinbase CEO&#8217;s wealth comes from his holdings and sales of the company stock.</li>
<li>Armstrong received nearly $57 million in option awards as well, besides making a profit after Coinbase went public. He still holds 39 million shares in the company, which is currently worth around $2.4 billion if sold.</li>
<li>The CEO&#8217;s compensation for 2022 was up by almost 134% since the previous year. His subordinates, including COO Emilie Choi, CFO Alesia Haas, CPO Surojit Chatterjee, and CLO Paul Grewal, also witnessed a considerable appreciation in their total compensation for the year.</li>
<li>In fact, all the five top executives of the San Francisco-based exchange giant receive nearly $1 million in cash salary.</li>
<li>The development emerges just a week after Coinbase <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-posts-79m-net-loss-but-beats-expectations/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">reported</a> a fifth consecutive quarter of losses. The company posted $79 million in losses while its total revenue plunged to $772.5 million, representing a decline of 37% from the $1.1 billion in revenue for Q1 2022.</li>
<li>Coinbase&#8217;s stock also took a <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/coinbase-stock-slides-as-exchanges-regulatory-woes-deepen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-wpel-link="internal">beating</a> as a result of tremendous regulatory pressure in the United States.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/sec-disclosure-reveals-high-security-bill-for-coinbases-ceo-brian-armstrong/" rel="nofollow">SEC Disclosure Reveals High Security Bill for Coinbase&#8217;s CEO Brian Armstrong</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Did Fake News Lead to Bitcoin&#8217;s Recent Crash? CryptoQuant Chips In</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/did-fake-news-lead-to-bitcoins-recent-crash-cryptoquant-chips-in/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Andrew Throuvalas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AA News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250440</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/fud.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/fud.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the US government is not selling its Bitcoin – despite what some Twitter accounts may claim. ]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitcoin crashed on Friday down to $26,166 and continues struggling to break back above the $26,500 level. What gives?</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Crypto market analytics platform CryptoQuant said the latest fall may be due to a coordinated FUD campaign against the primary cryptocurrency, which triggered a wave of liquidations this week. </span></p>
<h2>The US Government Did Not Sell Its BTC</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a </span><a href="https://cryptoquant.com/insights/quicktake/645cc10e19fb876efeb4ca18-Coordinated-FAKE-NEWS-about-US-government-selling-Bitcoins-leads-to-second-large?utm_source=twitter&amp;utm_medium=sns&amp;utm_campaign=Quicktake&amp;utm_content=ITTech" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">post</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Friday, CryptoQuant analyst IT Tech called attention to a wave of online, “coordinated fake news” related to the US government selling its Bitcoin earlier this week. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">He specifically called out a Twitter account called </span><a href="https://twitter.com/WhaleChart" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Whale Chart</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, which he deemed “one of the worst accounts to follow” due to publishing “fake news without sources.” </span></p>
<p>https://twitter.com/WhaleChart/status/1656350642426740740?s=20</p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Many accounts retweeted this news without any fact-checking, and as a result, we saw the second-largest long liquidations in 2023, with over $36M being liquidated within one hour,” wrote IT Tech. </span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The US government is currently one of the world’s largest holders of Bitcoin, having seized billions of dollars in coins related to illicit financial activity over many years. Some of those funds are related to the online darknet marketplace </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-doj-seized-over-50000-btc-related-to-silk-road/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Silk Road</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, while others were connected to the 2016 </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/justice-department-recovers-bitfinex-hack-funds-in-largest-ever-financial-seizure/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">Bitfinex hack</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> – the latter of which remains the largest-ever financial seizure.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">According to the on-chain data platform </span><a href="https://studio.glassnode.com/metrics?a=BTC&amp;category=&amp;m=distribution.BalanceUsGovernment&amp;s=1604361600&amp;u=1683763200&amp;zoom=" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">Glassnode</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, the US Government’s on-chain balance is 205,514 Bitcoin. This balance has not changed in recent days, last moving in early March when the government sold 9861 BTC seized from Silk Road, which was </span><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/brandonkochkodin/2023/03/31/us-government-sells-bitcoin-seized-from-silk-road-case-netting-over-215-million/#:~:text=According%20to%20a%20memo%20filed,%24215.5%20million%20after%20transaction%20fees." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank"><span style="font-weight: 400">publicly disclosed</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> weeks later.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">CryptoQuant possesses a similar dashboard, which reports a slightly different figure for the government’s Bitcoin balance at 204, 013 BTC. However, its timing for when the government last moved its coins seems to match Glassnode’s. </span></p>
<figure id="attachment_250441" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250441" style="width: 1024px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img class="size-large wp-image-250441" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-1024x645.png" alt="" width="1024" height="645" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-1024x645.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-300x189.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-768x484.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-1536x967.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-2048x1290.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/usg_btc_address_balance_calculation-50x31.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250441" class="wp-caption-text">US Government&#8217;s Bitcoin Balance. Source: CryptoQuant</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Nevertheless, fears </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/150m-in-liquidations-as-bitcoin-dumped-to-2-month-low-market-watch/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">swept the market</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> on Thursday, resulting in $150 million in liquidations within one day, and $40 billion cleared from the total crypto market cap. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">“Fortunately, we can verify this type of news using on-chain data,” added the analyst. </span></p>
<h2>CryptoQuant is Bullish on Bitcoin</h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In an </span><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-intend-to-buy-bitcoin-in-late-2023-interview-with-cryptoquant/" data-wpel-link="internal"><span style="font-weight: 400">interview</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> with CryptoQuant in April, representatives for the firm told CryptoPotato that institutional investors are eyeing Q3 and Q4 2023 as a time to invest, waiting for confirmation that Bitcoin has left the bear market behind. </span></p>
<blockquote><p><span style="font-weight: 400">“These are from conversations that I’ve been having mainly with institutional allocators and also people who are fundraising core funds as well,” said CryptoQuant’s Head of BD &amp; Strategy Benjamin Brannan.  “They’ve been speaking with various institutions or high net worth individuals.”</span></p></blockquote>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Brannan added that he doesn’t expect Bitcoin to retest its post-FTX $16,000 lows going forwards – bar  a “black swan” event like “Russia blowing a nuclear weapon into Ukraine, or Binance blowing up.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, Head of Marketing Ho Chan Chung claimed that Bitcoin could return to its previous all-time highs by Q2 2024. </span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/did-fake-news-lead-to-bitcoins-recent-crash-cryptoquant-chips-in/" rel="nofollow">Did Fake News Lead to Bitcoin&#8217;s Recent Crash? CryptoQuant Chips In</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP Tumbles 8% Weekly but is a Crash Below $0.4 Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-tumbles-8-weekly-but-is-a-crash-below-0-4-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoVizArt]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250386</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Ripple&#8217;s price is currently hovering near a crucial support region which consists of both the 200-day moving average and the $0.41 price zone. A breach below this critical level could potentially trigger a significant downturn toward the descending trendline. Technical Analysis By Shayan The Daily Chart On the daily chart, it’s apparent that after the [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ripple&#8217;s price is currently hovering near a crucial support region which consists of both the 200-day moving average and the $0.41 price zone. A breach below this critical level could potentially trigger a significant downturn toward the descending trendline.</p>
<h2>Technical Analysis</h2>
<p>By <a href="https://twitter.com/greatest_trader" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">Shayan</a></p>
<h3>The Daily Chart</h3>
<p>On the daily chart, it’s apparent that after the recent weeks of rejection, the price has arrived at a strong support area at the 200-day moving average of $0.41. Considering the power of this moving average, XRP may enter a consolidation phase.</p>
<p>However, if the price fails to hold above this crucial support zone, it could trigger a cascade leading to bearish sentiment over the market. Conversely, if the cryptocurrency finds support at the 200-day moving average, buyers can hope for a mid-term uptrend toward the $0.56 resistance level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250389" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250389" style="width: 2708px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250389 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly.png" alt="xrp_price_chart_1205231" width="2708" height="1466" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly.png 2708w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-300x162.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-1024x554.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-768x416.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-1536x832.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-2048x1109.png 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-Dailly-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2708px) 100vw, 2708px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250389" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h3>The 4-Hour Chart</h3>
<p>On the 4-Hour Chart, Ripple&#8217;s price has formed an ascending channel. The recent rejection has caused it to drop below the minor support level of $0.48 and the channel&#8217;s mid-trend line. Currently, the price faces a crucial support level at $0.41.</p>
<p>In summary, this PA is supportive of a potential consolidation stage around the mentioned support area until a breakout occurs. However, it&#8217;s important to see how the price will actually react, as this would probably give us a clue about the short-term trend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250388" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250388" style="width: 2560px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-scaled.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="wp-image-250388 size-full" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-scaled.jpg" alt="xrp_price_chart_1205232" width="2560" height="1386" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-300x162.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-1024x554.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-768x416.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-1536x832.jpg 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-2048x1109.jpg 2048w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRP-4H-5-50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250388" class="wp-caption-text">Source: TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/xrp-tumbles-8-weekly-but-is-a-crash-below-0-4-imminent-ripple-price-analysis/" rel="nofollow">XRP Tumbles 8% Weekly but is a Crash Below $0.4 Imminent? (Ripple Price Analysis)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE&#8217;s Crash and Burn, Bitcoin Tumbles to $26K, Crypto Markets in Freefall: This Week&#8217;s Recap</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/pepes-crash-and-burn-bitcoin-tumbles-to-26k-crypto-markets-in-freefall-this-weeks-recap/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[George Georgiev]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 15:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BTCEUR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCGBP]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[BTCUSDT]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250422</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[Easy come - easy go. This week saw PEPE crash and burn, losing over 70% since its all-time high. The rest of the market is also bleeding out.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past seven days saw the cryptocurrency market lose close to $100 billion off its total capitalization, which currently sits at $1.150B. It&#8217;s not been very fun for market participants as the majority of coins are trading well in the red. Once again, the hottest story of the week might as well be PEPE, but not for the same reasons as last week. Let&#8217;s dive in.</p>
<p>First things first, Bitcoin&#8217;s price crashed by roughly 9% through the past week and is currently trading at around $26,500. There&#8217;s no sugarcoating it &#8211; it&#8217;s been down-only, and buyers failed to catch a break. The bears were relentless and rejected the price at the single attempt at $30K this time last week, and it&#8217;s been an avalanche afterward.</p>
<p>The price dipped below $29K last Saturday and was unable to recover above that level. By Monday evening, it was already trading at close to $27K. The CPI announcement on Wednesday provided some hope, as BTC pumped above $28K, but it was shortlived as the correction was almost immediate. Since then, the cryptocurrency continued spiraling downward and is found where it currently trades at around $26,500.</p>
<p>Looking at the altcoins, it doesn&#8217;t get much better, as most of them are trading well in the red. ETH, BNB, XRP, ADA, DOGE, SOL, MATIC, DOT &#8211; all of them are charting considerable losses.</p>
<p>But all of the above fade in comparison to PEPE. The memecoin that reigned over the market in the past few weeks seems to have finally found some sort of a top and has crashed by 60% on the weekly and by more than 70% since its ATH.</p>
<p>And while it&#8217;s interesting to see whether PEPE will stage a recovery, the odds aren&#8217;t looking very good at the moment.</p>
<p>All in all, the market sentiment has definitely shifted throughout the past few weeks, and the optimism is fading. It&#8217;s interesting to see if this is just a temporary correction or if a deeper winter is once again in the making, albeit in the summer. Sell in May and go away? Will the popular saying keep true?</p>
<h2 style="text-align: left;">Market Data</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;">Market Cap: $1,150B | 24H Vol: $49B | BTC Dominance: 44.5%</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">BTC: $26,455 (-9.1%) | ETH: $1,771 (-7.7%) | BNB: $306 (-5.6%)</p>
<p><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover.jpg" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-250424" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover.jpg" alt="bburn_cover" width="1201" height="720" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover.jpg 1201w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover-300x180.jpg 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover-1024x614.jpg 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover-768x460.jpg 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/bburn_cover-50x30.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1201px) 100vw, 1201px" /></a></p>
<h2>This Week&#8217;s Crypto Headlines You Can&#8217;t Miss</h2>
<p><strong>Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon to Be Released on $440K Bail (Report). </strong>Do Kwon &#8211; the founder of Terraform Labs, <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terraform-labs-founder-do-kwon-to-be-released-on-440k-bail-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">has pleaded</a> not guilty to allegations of traveling to Montenegro on a forged Passport. He might be released on a $400K bail.</p>
<p><strong>Twitter Chief Elon Musk to Pass on Mantle to New CEO, Takes CTO Role. </strong>The owner of Twitter &#8211; Elon Musk &#8211; will <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/twitter-chief-elon-musk-to-pass-on-mantle-to-new-ceo-takes-ceo-role/" data-wpel-link="internal">step down</a> as the company&#8217;s Chief Executive Office. Instead, he will take up the role of a CTO, while a potential CEO candidate is reportedly Linda Yaccarino from NBC Universal.</p>
<p><strong>Ethereum Crashes to 6-Week Lows Despite ETH on Exchanges Declining. </strong>ETH has <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/ethereum-crashes-to-6-week-lows-despite-eth-on-exchanges-declining/" data-wpel-link="internal">crashed</a> to six-week lows despite the fact that the Ethereum stored on exchanges continues declining. In fact, the ETH on exchanges has declined to only 10.3%.</p>
<p><strong>USDC Issuer Circle Rebalances Treasury Holdings Amid US Debt Ceiling Crisis. </strong>The issuer of the second-largest stablecoin by means of total market capitalization &#8211; USDC &#8211; will <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/usdc-issuer-circle-rebalances-treasury-holdings-amid-us-debt-ceiling-crisis/" data-wpel-link="internal">rebalance</a> treasury holdings amid the US debt ceiling crisis. Circle is preparing to avoid potential lapses.</p>
<p><strong>New York to Embrace Stablecoins as Payment Method for Bail Bonds. </strong>Assembly bill number 7024 is <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/new-york-to-embrace-stablecoins-as-payment-method-for-bail-bonds/" data-wpel-link="internal">aimed</a> at providing stablecoins a status of official means of payment for bail bonds inside the state of New York. This would be a considerable step forward if made a reality.</p>
<p><strong>Institutions Intend to Buy Bitcoin in Late 2023: Interview With CryptoQuant. </strong>During an <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/institutions-intend-to-buy-bitcoin-in-late-2023-interview-with-cryptoquant/" data-wpel-link="internal">interview</a> for CryptoPotato at Consensus this year, CryptoQuant analysts shared that institutions seem to be intending to buy BTC in late 2023. This would also align with other projections that the bull market could start later in the year or in the next one.</p>
<h2>Charts</h2>
<p>This week we have a chart analysis of Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, PEPE, and DOGE – <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-12-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-and-doge/" data-wpel-link="internal">click here for the complete price analysis</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/pepes-crash-and-burn-bitcoin-tumbles-to-26k-crypto-markets-in-freefall-this-weeks-recap/" rel="nofollow">PEPE&#8217;s Crash and Burn, Bitcoin Tumbles to $26K, Crypto Markets in Freefall: This Week&#8217;s Recap</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Price Analysis May-12: ETH, XRP, ADA, PEPE, and DOGE</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-12-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-and-doge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Duo Nine]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[ADABTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ADAUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DOGEUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETH Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ETHUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Price Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRP Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPBTC]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[XRPUSD]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dogecoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PEPE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ripple (XRP) Price]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250303</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/friday_post_1205231.jpg" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/friday_post_1205231.jpg" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Pepe, and Dogecoin. Ethereum (ETH) With the market in the red, Ethereum has fallen by 7.4% this week. In the process, the key level at $1,800 has turned into a resistance. This highlights a major change in the structure and puts bears in control [&#8230;]]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week, we take a closer look at Ethereum, Ripple, Cardano, Pepe, and Dogecoin.</p>
<h2>Ethereum (ETH)</h2>
<p>With the market in the red, Ethereum has fallen by 7.4% this week. In the process, the key level at $1,800 has turned into a resistance. This highlights a major change in the structure and puts bears in control of the price action.</p>
<p>The momentum has turned bearish, and a test of the key support at $1,660 appears likely in the coming week. This becomes increasingly so if Bitcoin continues with its correction.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, if the key support at $1,660 holds, Ethereum might maintain its macro uptrend (higher lows). If not, then bulls will be put in a very difficult position, as that would open the path for this cryptocurrency to revisit levels not seen since March 2023 (under $1,500).</p>
<figure id="attachment_250313" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250313" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250313" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00.png" alt="ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00" width="1814" height="861" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00-1024x486.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00-768x365.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00-1536x729.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ETHUSD_2023-05-12_14-20-00-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250313" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Ripple (XRP)</h2>
<p>Ripple&#8217;s downtrend accelerated this week and resulted in an 8% loss in valuation. With the support at 44 cents lost and turned into resistance, buyers have retreated to the 40 cents level.</p>
<p>Historically, it has been a critical point where the price pivoted and reversed. If buyers return, then XRP could put a stop to its correction.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, sellers are in charge, and the seemingly more likely scenario is for XRP&#8217;s price to fall until the 40 cents support. Once there, its reaction to this level would likely determine the short-term trend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250311" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250311" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250311" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08.png" alt="XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08" width="1814" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08-1024x453.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/XRPUSDT_2023-05-12_14-22-08-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250311" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<h2>Cardano (ADA)</h2>
<p>With the head and shoulders reversal pattern confirmed ADA fell by 7.7% this week. It seems less likely that the price will stop until it hits the support at 34 cents. This price action is somewhat similar to XRP, and buyers will likely be absent until the key support is hit.</p>
<p>The momentum indicators, like the MACD and RSI, are bearish and falling to lower lows. The daily RSI is under 40 and still has room until it hits the oversold area (under 30). Together with a bearish MACD, this indicates sellers may likely continue to dominate for some time.</p>
<p><span style="color: #2b2b2b;"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Looking ahead</span></span>, this cryptocurrency remains bearish. If buyers don&#8217;t return at the 34 cents support, then the next likely candidate will be found at 30 cents, which is also a key psychological level.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250312" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250312" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250312" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43.png" alt="ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43" width="1814" height="860" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43-300x142.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43-1024x485.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43-768x364.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43-1536x728.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/ADAUSDT_2023-05-12_14-20-43-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250312" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Pepe (PEPE) </span></p>
<p>The spectacular performance from PEPE ended up with an equally spectacular crash. This meme coin crashed by 37% in the past week and by over 75% from its all-time high. Worst yet, the selling pressure has intensified in the past few days. This highlights that some holders have capitulated and taken the loss.</p>
<p>The Binance listing turned out as a top event, and the price has not stopped falling since. PEPE is also the worst performer on our list this week. In a way, this is not surprising, considering that the level of FOMO and hype achieved peak irrationality around that period.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, PEPE has support at $0.0000010. However, any support for this meme coin is fragile, and considering its supply, it would not be surprising to see it crash by over 90%. This is even more likely if the overall market remains bearish.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250309" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250309" style="width: 1813px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250309" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32.png" alt="PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32" width="1813" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32.png 1813w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32-1024x454.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/PEPEWETH_A43FE1_ETHUSDT_2023-05-12_14-24-32-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1813px) 100vw, 1813px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250309" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p><span style="font-size: 24px; font-weight: bold;">Dogecoin (DOGE)</span></p>
<p>With Dogecoin being completely overshadowed by PEPE, this meme coin did not find any buyers, and its price has fallen by 10.5% in the past seven days.</p>
<p>Since the momentum favors sellers, the daily RSI is approaching fast the oversold area at 30 points. This could provide buyers with an opportunity to stop the downtrend at the key support level. The current resistance is at 7.5 cents.</p>
<p>Looking ahead, a test of the key support appears imminent. On the weekly timeframe, the price action in 2023 shows a flat trend, and DOGE has failed to gather enough strength to enter into an uptrend.</p>
<figure id="attachment_250308" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-250308" style="width: 1814px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><a href="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08.png" data-wpel-link="internal"><img class="size-full wp-image-250308" src="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08.png" alt="DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08" width="1814" height="803" srcset="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08.png 1814w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08-300x133.png 300w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08-1024x453.png 1024w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08-768x340.png 768w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08-1536x680.png 1536w, https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/05/DOGEUSDT_2023-05-12_14-26-08-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1814px) 100vw, 1814px" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-250308" class="wp-caption-text">Chart by TradingView</figcaption></figure>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/crypto-price-analysis-may-12-eth-xrp-ada-pepe-and-doge/" rel="nofollow">Crypto Price Analysis May-12: ETH, XRP, ADA, PEPE, and DOGE</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon to Be Released on $440K Bail (Report)</title>
		<link>https://cryptopotato.com/terraform-labs-founder-do-kwon-to-be-released-on-440k-bail-report/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Arun Srivastav]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Crypto News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[featured1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Do Kwon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terra (LUNA)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cryptopotato.com/?p=250296</guid>
		<media:content url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon.png" medium="image"/>
		<enclosure url="https://cryptopotato.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/10/Do_Kwon.png" length="840" type="image/jpg"/>
					
			            <description><![CDATA[After his arrest in March in Montenegro, Kwon is facing trial for traveling on forged documents to the Southeastern European country.]]></description>
            																<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do Kwon, founder of Terraform Labs, which operated Terra stablecoin and Luna cryptocurrency, has pleaded not guilty to traveling to Montenegro on a forged passport.</p>
<p>In the Basic Court of Montenegro’s capital Podgorica, Kwon and Terraform’s chief financial officer Han Chang-Joon denied document forgery charges.</p>
<p>Shortly after, another local <a href="https://www.pobjeda.me/clanak/prihvaceno-jemstvo-od-800000-eura-korejskim-drzavljanima" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">report</a> informed that the Court approved the bail worth €400,000 that was proposed by Kwon. As such, he is set to be released ahead of the trial.</p>
<p>The prosecutors objected to the decision, arguing that Kwon and Chang-Joon had no interest in remaining in Montenegro until the court date.</p>
<h2>Kwon Proposes €400K for Bail</h2>
<p>Kwon and Han were <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terras-do-kwon-reportedly-arrested-in-montenegro/" data-wpel-link="internal">arrested</a> at the Podgorica airport on March 23, and the prosecutors filed the charges against them on April 2. On the May 11 hearing, their lawyers sought the defendants&#8217; bail and proposed a combined amount of €400,000. They also asked the court to define the measures for the defendants to “leave the apartment” during the prohibition and its supervision.</p>
<blockquote><p>“A trial was held before the Basic Court in Podgorica in the case against the defendants C.J.H. and K.D.H., who are accused of having committed the criminal offense of document forgery. At the main hearing, the defendants denied the commission of the criminal offense they were charged with and presented their defense,” Podgorica’s Basic Court, in a <a href="https://sudovi.me/ospg/sadrzaj/aL9R" data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">statement</a>, said.</p></blockquote>
<p>The defense lawyers further asked the court to allow Kwon and Han to “report to the state authority periodically.” However, the state prosecutors opposed these proposals. The court has not decided on the matter and set June 16 as the next hearing date.</p>
<h2>No Immediate Extradition</h2>
<p>After his arrest, the US and South Korea officially asked Montenegro for Kwon’s <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/skorea-us-seeking-extradition-crypto-entrepreneur-do-kwon-montenegro-2023-03-29/#:~:text=PODGORICA%2C%20March%2029%20(Reuters),Marko%20Kovac%20said%20on%20Wednesday." data-wpel-link="external" target="_blank">extradition</a>, the country’s Justice Minister Marko Kovac told a press conference in Podgorica on March 23. He further said Kwon and Han had been charged with traveling to the country on forged documents, and they would be deported only after the trial was completed and they had served the sentence that the courts might give against them.</p>
<p>Both countries also requested the Montenegro authorities to hand over the <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/us-sec-gains-access-to-do-kwons-singaporean-records-report/" data-wpel-link="internal">computers</a> of the two arrested Terraform executives.</p>
<p>Terraform Lab’s Terra and Luna coins, which were pegged to each other in an algorithmic arrangement, collapsed in early May 2022 and left the crypto market with a loss of nearly $40 billion.</p>
<p>The South Korean courts clubbed the complaints from investors in these coins who lost their money in two cases and pursued to bring Kwon and his associates to justice. Kwon has denied any wrongdoing, except that his business strategies failed, leading to the collapse of the Terra-Luna ecosystem. However, he refused to answer the summons and has been evading arrest by the South Korean authorities.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/terraform-labs-founder-do-kwon-to-be-released-on-440k-bail-report/" rel="nofollow">Terraform Labs Founder Do Kwon to Be Released on $440K Bail (Report)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://cryptopotato.com/" rel="nofollow">CryptoPotato</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
																</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
